I wrote better from Mars Women are from
Venus
25 years ago I've been teaching the
ideas for over 35 years and the number
one question I get now as I'm doing
interviews and talking about that book
is how have relationships changed those
ideas still apply and ironically all
those ideas still apply and that
understanding men and women are
different and we need new communication
skills however the challenge is couples
face today is not just about
communication it's about managing stress
within their own bodies it's a man it's
managing their own levels of happiness
because what's happened is the terrain
of relationships has changed and this is
different from 25 years ago so I've
written a new book which is called
Beyond Mars and Venus and basically and
Beyond Mars and Venus we're looking at
the new challenges the new problems and
the solutions so that we can experience
a higher level of love I call that
soulmate love and what is a soulmate
love a soulmate relationship is a
relationship where you have the
emotional support the freedom to
authentically express all of who you are
that's what people want today and the
more traditional relationship men had
the freedom to express their masculinity
women had the freedom to express their
feminine qualities but we were
restricted and today we want more we
want full expression of who we are and
that creates new challenges equality
between men and women has never happened
in the past and you suddenly have an
equal relationship this is all new
challenges this is women wanting to be
on their masculine side will simply call
that independence and the seminar in the
book we talk about the 12 qualities of
masculinity we talk about the 12
qualities of femininity and we talk
about the importance of balancing those
according to our own unique self every
man and woman has a unique balance of
masculine and feminine qualities and to
the extent that you have to suppress
either your female side or your male
side if you have to suppress a part of
who you authentically are your own
internal stress levels will increase
your
ability to feel love and happiness and
fulfillment in your life and your
relationships will be diminished and
that's why in traditional relationships
passion would go away people would
become comfortable they would become at
ease but the aliveness the passion the
vitality the sexual attraction that was
all gone because people had to suppress
parts of who they are today people want
to express all of who they are and when
they can't they feel even greater
dissatisfaction so the dissatisfaction
level in marriage today has gone way up
it's gone up in singles because we want
more what we want is the full expression
of who we are but we don't yet know how
to coexist in a relationship where a
woman can be both her masculine side and
her feminine side and a man can be both
his feminine side and his masculine side
it creates all new challenges now how do
those challenges look the bottom line of
how they look is as women have come
forth into their masculine side it
releases a huge amount of energy no
longer than having to suppress a part of
who they are so it feels really good as
she's expressing more for independence
more of her detachment more of her
problem-solving more of her analytical
abilities organizing abilities
leadership qualities these are our
masculine side a woman has a masculine
side a man has a masculine side but our
feminine side is the feeling side of us
the loving side of us the cooperative
side of us the interdependent side of us
and identifying these different
qualities which we do in my new book
Beyond Mars and Venus and we realize
that when you're expressing a female
quality it actually stimulates female
hormones in your body and when you're
expressing a masculine quality it
stimulates masculine hormones so much of
this book is understanding the biology
of men and women because for a man if
he's not expressing his masculine
qualities because he's expressing more
of his feminine qualities his estrogen
levels goes too high his testosterone
levels go down and that imbalance of
hormones actually causes dissatisfaction
in his relationships it creates a sense
of irritation moodiness irritable lack
of libido for his partner lack of motive
station in life it can be depression
there's so many qualities of hormonal
and balance and men when their
testosterone levels are going down their
estrogen levels are going higher so we
learn about that we learn about for
women as their testosterone male
hormones are increasing their female
hormones are going down and when a
woman's female hormones go down her
stress levels go up and for women it's a
lot more complicated so there's several
chapters in the book explaining that
when women are pre menopausal when
they're still cycling their hormonal
needs first particular stimulation
changes every day of the month what are
the days when she needs a man's love the
most what can she do to get that love
and support what can men do to provide
the support she needs I call that the
five-day love window that's when he can
have the biggest impact there's other
times of the month when she needs more
progesterone where he has less impact on
her but he needs to create a safe space
for her to find her inner fulfillment
there's other times when her work can be
more fulfilling for her as her estrogen
levels are rising and her testosterone
levels are steady so we learn about
these different hormonal shifts and
women men learn okay what time of the
month is it what kind of support does
she need because men often experience
one day she feels this way next day it's
changes what did I do wrong
what we have to understand is the
signals of how to give a woman to
support she needs and also men what
support they need so what we need in a
basic simple format is if a man doesn't
have at least 10 times more testosterone
than the average woman his stress levels
will be much higher and if a woman
doesn't have 10 times more estrogen than
the average male young healthy male then
what's going to happen is she is going
to be unhappy overwhelmed and stress and
explain all these symptoms of hormonal
imbalance you don't have to go and get
tests you don't have to take hormones
you just have to learn how to behave at
certain times of the month in certain
ways with the opposite sex in order to
stimulate the right hormones in your
body to find balance within you so this
is all new information it takes us
beyond the Mars Venus information which
is also there in the book understanding
our differences brings it to a
biological level where we recognize if
we
want to sustain passion in a
relationship the bottom line on a
biological level there's chemical
messages going on there's pheromones
that get produced there's touch there's
saliva all these give messages to the
body that awaken passion did awaken
attraction and its foundation is based
upon the hormonal balance and a man and
a woman if a man's testosterone levels
are not ten times higher than a woman's
she will not be attracted to him this is
a bottom line couples lose their
attraction his testosterone levels start
to drop research is showing that a man
gets married has children his
testosterone levels start to drop
naturally her attraction becomes less
but what can she say do and what can he
say and do to rebuild those testosterone
levels to keep them high to keep the
passion alive it needs to be 10 times
more than her and for her he will not be
turned on to her he will not be
attracted her in a biological level if
her pheromones are not communicating
that her estrogen levels this female
hormone is 10 times greater than his ten
times greater this is female hormones
male hormones this is biology and once
we start understanding the biological
differences between men and women and we
certainly had no idea about this back 25
years ago when I wrote minute from Mars
every single difference I talked about
in the minute from Mars books is based
upon these biological differences and
our new challenges today in our
relationships is as women go too far the
male side their male hormones get
produced which inhibit the ability for
her to make her female hormones so what
can men say do and interact with a woman
to help her come back to her feminine
what can she do say in order to bring
her back to her feminine to produce the
estrogen or the progesterone are the
right balance of testosterone and
estrogen these are all changing hormones
at different times for her and for
postmenopausal women at different times
of the month for her as well which I
explore in the book because her hormones
are still they produce less hormones but
they still have to be in balance
everything about everything about
happiness and fulfillment and lasting
passion and attraction has to do with
the authentic balance of hormones
according to your authentic self your
unique self and today
we want more in our relationships we can
have more but we have to learn how to be
able to express all of who we are
communicate all that who we are in a way
that doesn't cause our partner to shut
down in a way that keeps keeps us from
feeling like I'm not safe to express Who
I am because self-expression to show up
who we are is what allows love to come
in to us and only for growing in love
expressing more and more feeling more
and more safe we're more authentic can
we grow in love and that is a
possibility that we have today and it
never existed before
we don't have guidelines we don't have
rules we have instructions we'd have a
roadmap never before have human beings
attempted to have equal relationship
between men and women sharing equally in
a relationship we all want it but we
don't know how to get it we have higher
expectations we can't achieve it we get
a glimpse of it when we fall in love but
we lose it because we don't know how to
sustain the hormonal balance of being in
love and yes this is 31 years I've been
married to my wife it's not like I'm
always in love with my wife I always
loved her but falling in love again and
again is a journey of finding that
balance within ourselves to experience
the ecstasy of balancing your hormones
inside reflecting on expressions of both
your male qualities and your female
qualities identifying what those are so
you know what to do when you're out of
balance without having to change your
partner this is amazing new information
I'm excited for you to understand it
invite you to read my new book beyond
Mars and Venus so that you can fulfill
your dreams of having lasting passion
romance growing in love experiencing
greater fulfillment in your life and
that's the gift that's the promise of
this book