should be coming back shortly we back
hello testing it looks like it's working
now just no way until someone actually
hears me
original recipe sweet okay we're back in
business so given that I have no idea
what you heard and didn't hear
unfortunately I'm gonna reintroduce this
briefly and start over ish what what I'm
hoping to accomplish on this dream today
is some sort of basic DevOps integration
that will get us from get us into a
workflow where when I submit code to a
pull request against the repo it will
run a series of tests on circle CI that
will test to make sure that the software
is still working before accepting the
pull request so I won't be able to merge
the pull requests unless the tests pass
after the pull request is merged if it's
merged to the branch that I'm using for
development or staging it will deploy to
a Heroku web dyno which will be our
staging environment so that my team can
test it on our staging servers and at
that point that's sort of a reasonable
DevOps CI workflow we'll also include in
the testing making sure that the lint is
running successfully so that the code is
oh boy someone's gonna get mad at me but
formatted correctly and and I don't even
well it's not really a format checker
it's lint it will just use that verb
because that's easier beyond that I will
make sure that I can't just commit code
directly to master say for example so
that I'm not accidentally committing
code to production there's a lot of
setup and nitpick enos that goes on here
this is my personal workflow for doing
it there are a trillion ways to skin
account when it comes to this these are
the services I've used in the past and
the ones that I find convenient and easy
and smart to set up I would love to hear
feedback if you've got a better way or a
different way or something that I can
tweak to make this
with that all said let's now look at how
we want to accomplish this
so in package.json which is the sort of
metadata descriptor file for our project
for the jobs module or the micro service
here we this this lists out like I said
a bunch of metadata the dependencies for
the project as well as the scripts that
it executes my hope here is to write a
test script that when executed it runs a
series of jest tests which is just as a
node testing library developed by
Facebook it'll run these tests against
the repo locally on my machine here if I
if I run just sort of NPM test or yarn
test and those would be the same tests
that certain CI runs for the sake of
making sure that I'm writing good code
and functional code so a gigantic
disclaimer before I do this I have very
little experience writing test cases
with jest so this is gonna be a lot of
learning for me it's it's a good thing
to do we'll probably start with an
extremely basic test case something that
just runs the app and make sure it
doesn't fail or something like that
to get the entire DevOps sort of
workflow going and then when when when
I'm confident that that's working at
least in a way that I expect then we can
go into building tests that are more
thorough and and hopefully test against
a pretty big surface area of the code
that's in this repo this is as much
learning experience for me as it is for
you so you know caveat emptor whatever
you want to say I'm learning as I go
it may be a frustrating thing to watch
but hopefully that's also entertaining
because of the whole schadenfreude a
thing in human psychology alright let's
get started so just is the testing
library we're going to use its
delightful JavaScript testing
incidentally there are some docs for
just on their repo we've already done
this step sort of adding it as a
dependency let me see if I can put these
side-by-side quickly and also before I
forget I'm going to zoom in on this
great so in my dev dependencies there
should be just that is
true I might quickly check to make sure
that it is on the most recent version in
my terminal here yeah okay so there's
this command you can run yard upgrade
interactive latest which will check all
of my dependencies in the app against
what's currently published 10:00 p.m. we
can see that there's a minor update to
just twenty two four zero two twenty
four two four two that's lovely
we're also going to update node Mon and
Express while we're at it
these all have fairly larger bumps that
probably won't be a big deal but I like
to do the revision package updates first
so we're gonna do that it'll take a
second install the new dependencies and
then we'll commit our changes after
running this to make sure that
everything works still
so all this this is kind of a
thoroughness of DevOps sort of it this
is a DevOps chore that you should
probably get used to to if you're
building node projects just to make sure
that dependencies are up-to-date if you
have something that's deployed it keeps
everything secure or as secure as it can
be when you're using someone else's code
there are a lot of hypothetical issues
that can still come up if you do that
but for the sake of simplicity we'll use
this okay so it looks like this is still
working you can see the page is still
loading and in the background the
terminals doing whatever magic it's
doing to display stuff to me so I'm
going to commit some code here it looks
like there's a change but I didn't
commit from last time I working on this
that is a-okay we're gonna get rid of
that console East
don't save my changes there so let's
make this big and the job listing
there's a console print here that I
don't need to print any longer this is
purely a debug tool just make sure that
I've only made some changes here that
looks like a okay yeah that's all from
last time so I'm going to create a
commit first for this source components
job listing get commit - um update
function call sure
that's a terrible commit then we're
gonna add
with new revisions on NPM great okay so
we'll leave it at that for now this
should still run once again nothing
should be broken here yeah it looks like
that's still running we can double
triple check that but this is gonna come
up still okay so now that we've updated
Justin we've confirmed that it's in the
project we're going to write a very
simple test there are several different
ways you can write tests and just or
what's better ready to say it there are
several different ways you can name your
tests ingest that it will look for you
can go with something that says dot SaaS
and just we'll know to look for that you
can also create I believe a directory at
the root of your project or I think
actually in any directory of your
project called
this tests with surrounded by two
hundred scores on either side I don't
really have a preference but for the
time being because this is such a small
project I'm just gonna put them next to
each other so we're gonna create a new
file here and it's gonna be job listing
dot test J s there we go and we'll look
at how we can write a simple test case
here so first thing we have to do is go
into the package file and add this test
script that we were talking about before
all it does is run just just being the
test library here and we may have to do
some magic to make sure that just is
included by our transpiler here but a
very simple test is exactly this or
something like this we could we could
write a stub function like that but here
let me maximize this so you can actually
read so oh yeah here we go so we do need
to add some
transpiling you don't need to install
anything extra freezing babel if using
babel version seven then you need pen I
don't think I am Babel yeah okay so
don't forget to add a Babel our Senior
Projects root folder if using es6 and
react let's see I believe that's done
already - no okay well what do you know
so we're gonna create this is all
transpiling goodness and we need to add
these guys a shoot that's not I wanted
yawn ad D Babel preset and
sure dummies about the same time yarn
and D Babel preset react
bingo-bango we are all set with that so
if I run just now in this directory
it'll look for test cases it'll probably
complain that there's no actual tests in
that one test file if it finds it your
test suite must contain at least one
test that's a good start though and so I
found the test file and so now we have
to write a test so let's go to the
actual docs for this
create a file named some dye test IJ yes
did you do and the syntax takes a little
bit to get used to but it's actually not
too bad
so in our file where we're gonna write
the test case against this job listing
and to be honest this might not be a
great place to start because this is
rendering a component let's do you know
what we can write against util first
that's a nice easy one so in my source
folder where this util is I'm gonna make
a u tilde test yes we'll come back to
this job listing test in a bit and we're
going to the first test we're going to
write is against this distance between
two points function it shouldn't be too
hard so
this is what tests look like for jest
we're gonna say expect right import
right
Const utils equals require you to
till dot who I don't actually export it
we're gonna export it so we can test it
okay
so we'll test the distance between two
points function and this is kind of what
the syntax looks like so we have this
expect and then there's this to be
syntax that can go after it
and this is where we expect the result
to happen so mmm my winter is
complaining about test is not defined
because this needs a just added run ad D
is lint tests plugin no I think it's
plugin just
okay now this is hopefully not
complaining about that any longer
it still is hmm I'll have to figure that
out a bit later on so let's go back to
that actual test script and we're gonna
create two points now we're gonna say so
I need to figure out what the inputs for
this function should be which is a sign
that I have done a poor job of
documenting this because that should be
obvious they should have a dot latitude
and longitude so let's write a little
comment here position one let's see the
position object we're in the form
latitude longitude there's probably a
better way to write this taking
advantage of all the nice things that J
stock has to offer but I'm not really an
expert on that either
there's always room or now returns the
distance between two points given to two
geographic points and this is a
Cartesian
okay so now there's a whole notion of
something called test-driven development
where you write the test cases first and
then make your code function against
those test cases which is a smart thing
to do in part because a lot of the times
if you go and rate the tests after the
fact it's really easy to write tests
that pass no matter what so for example
I might write distance between two
points for where I live in Charlotte in
New York City run the calculation myself
and write one test case for that which
would look something like this
Const Charlotte position equals latitude
figure out what that should be
longitude figure out what that should be
and we'll get the actual distance
between these two points
okay so
in this case it's really easy to write
this test to be zero because I haven't
actually defined any latitude and
longitude points for either of them we
can run this test and it will probably
pass yeah look at that
it passed even though those aren't
really valid points it will work right
this is technically a functioning test
case we do have in here this constants
file which has all these markets in it
which is lovely so we're actually going
to import and poor sorry coasts markets
equals require and we'll grab our
constants and hopefully that has markets
define that it hasn't defined this site
and instead of this we're gonna say
markets will get the ID for Charlotte
61 Ward's and we'll do the same thing
for New York City and we're gonna kind
of back our way into this
eleven
there we go
so now this test will fail because I
have actual distances in there so what
this is saying is the distance is
expected to be zero but it got eight
point seven six which is a funny value
still but that is a distance in latitude
and longitude right that's not actually
miles or anything like that this hasn't
been converted but basically what I'm
gonna do is work my test case backwards
so I'm gonna say cons distance between
Charlotte and NYC equals that look at
that suddenly I've got a working test
case again I'm sure actually it might
not work in depending on rounding error
oh yeah look it worked so I guess the
whole point of that exercise is that I
wrote this test and the test works and
it would be possible to submit this to
as a test case against this whole
function to say that okay now the the
the distance between two points function
is tested and it's good to go but there
are a number of ways in which this is
lacking so all right we'll show you
we're gonna write a couple more test
cases and I'll explain why this is not
sufficient okay so
one of the things I'm not currently
happy with is I know there's a way to
write a whole suite of tests against one
thing that fall under the same name I
don't know what mattress is we're gonna
find out
I'm just looking for a very specific
syntax I guess I could do it like this
I'm yeah actually that's fine because
it'll be grouped by the file so here I'm
going to write another test case based
on this we're gonna move these
definitions up because we'll probably
use them again it all is great so now
I'm going to write another test based on
this and we'll call we'll give this test
a better name should return should be
calculated accurately this one is going
to be should return 0 if points are the
same so this is another test case you
might reasonably be expected to write
make sure that if you're testing against
to the same points they should be 0 they
shouldn't be null it shouldn't be false
or anything like that but what about
should return an exception if only one
point is provided so we're gonna write a
test against that because you can't do
the distance between only one point so
expect you till distance between points
of Charlotte position null dot to throw
two two
so there's specific function for
exceptions here that function syntax is
what I'm looking for so Row two throwing
it okay to throw and this is also a
valid test case but the way the code is
written right now
boom distance between Charlotte and NYC
is calculated accurately should return
zero of points are the same is correct
but it failed the test against should
return an exception if only one point is
provided because currently I'm not
checking for that right we're getting
right into it and looking at latitude
one latitude two without checking to see
if those positions actually exist so I'm
going to actually write a test case
against both of those which would be
this it's the row thoreau and so now in
the spirit of sort of test-driven
development these would have been
written first and then I would have gone
and written a function that would work
against them because we're kind of
backing our way into this which is maybe
not the right way to do it if you're
being really traditional about it or
whatever you want to call it now I need
to go and fix my code so this works and
we'll do that presently so we're going
to say if position 1
or not position to we're gonna say throw
new error to positions need to be
provided to calculate a distance that's
a helpful message that will show up in
the console when that error happens so
let's see now it's already error to
position their command failed oh oh yeah
okay well so I would sort of have
expected that to pass the test case
because it through an error maybe I need
to write that a little more specifically
let's take a look at this
when test the drink flavor octopus
throws exact yeah so I actually would
expect that to have worked
let's see what's going on here maybe my
syntax was incorrect I'm losing my voice
again
excuse me okay
well tell you what rather than running
this in the test environment let's test
it from the actual app itself and we're
just going to run here we're gonna say
and this is gonna be an object with a
zero in it and then null here and this
should get me to the same place right so
if I run yarn start this should
definitely fail unexpected token I don't
disagree with you oh I say
okay
well it's definitely throwing an error
that's great I'm not sure why just isn't
picking it up
hmm no you must wrap the code in a
function otherwise the error will be not
be calling the assertion will fail
well what does that mean I would guess
that means this function
oh oh maybe I didn't do that
I see so it has to go inside of the
expect look at that
okay so now this should work
yeah look at that okay so that was
that's just a nuance of just so like I
said I'm learning that still but that's
the only way to catch an exception is if
it's within a function returning sort of
the output of that function which would
be the exception that's cool right this
is a little aggravating and I'd like to
get rid of it but maybe we'll work on
that so my point here is you can see how
this is testing this function more more
thoroughly one thing I might also test
for in this guy so when I'm writing this
function to the best possible capacity
is a type check to make sure that
positions both have a latitude and a
longitude so
so this is saying basically if either of
these are missing a lot of tuturro
longitude we're gonna throw new error
both input coordinates must have a
latitude and longitude provided
specified who specified well it's a v'
in now formats that in a way that I
probably wouldn't have ever done we're
still dealing with prettier if you
recall and so now we can test against
that too so we would do tests both input
coordinates must have lat
we're going to define a new point here
constant malformed formatted point
equals latitude zero and no longitude
this point is intentionally missing
longitude so here we're going to test
for Charlotte position to malformed
added point and that should throw
and we're gonna do a bunch of these so
we're gonna do
Swiss wampum a Knopf formatted point on
one side Charlotte position on the other
side the point here is to be as thorough
as as is reasonably expected yeah
reasonably thorough maybe is there any
way to put it without killing yourself
there are organizations that can afford
to have you know Suites of test
engineers who do nothing but write test
cases all day and the point of that is
to make sure that your code never starts
to break right like code gets updated
all the time
and you want to make sure that a minor
patch to something doesn't bring down a
whole network which if you follow text
tech news like hacker news and stuff
like that this sort of stuff does really
happen all the time because it's a
complicated thing to manage and there's
a balance to be struck between the right
amount of tests for function versus how
often it's used and how impactful it is
and what not so let's run the test again
I'm not going to do this the whole
stream but I just want to give some good
examples of tests here like I said it
would and then we'll move on to the next
step
something else I might test for I'll
leave some comments for other tests
other tests I might write for distance
between points and we're gonna do like
this make sure and valid yeah sure
launch are valid latitudes and
longitudes make sure distance is
calculated correctly across
negative and positive lat/longs
so because we're working with a sphere
the globe is is defined in two sort of
180 degree hemispheres and the
interesting points along the that
hemisphere for this calculation or when
it goes from zero it goes from zero to
180 in both directions so negative and
positive so at one point it meets a sort
of one at negative one and then at the
other point it meets at would I guess
it'd 179 and negative hundred
seventy-nine and we need to make sure
that calculations across those two
surfaces both on latitude and longitude
work correctly so that's that's probably
a particularly important test for
something like this and and the kind of
thing that could definitely come to bite
you if you hadn't thought of it
beforehand I was talking to actually a
friend the other day who works for a
start-up here in town and they launched
a service that manages a pretty complex
schedule of people running tasks
throughout the city here that they have
to drive around the city which was
working phenomenally and they did some
really cool algorithm work to make sure
that the people in that city were
scheduled to do these driving tasks
around town in the most efficient path
possible but what they didn't take into
account which happened recently it was
daylight savings time
so when daylight savings happened their
customers some of their customers
appointments were an hour off in one
direction some had already adjusted for
it and it was kind of a nightmare so
that's the kind of thing that a test
like this might prevent against the
catch is of course that you have to
think of that test in order to write it
to test against it to make sure that
you're compliant with the logic that you
need to put in place so for the sake of
demonstration on stream here I'm gonna
let these four tests be my entire test
suite for the time being while we set up
circle CI integration and then I might
come back and write some more tests
against the other parts of this software
for now this will do so let's look at
what we have to do to get circled going
so I'm gonna close all these files and
we'll go to Circle C eyes Doc's here so
I'm adding this this is the repo I'm
adding it to circle CI this is sort of
inside of their app already what they do
actually is they go and integrate with
github so I have authenticated circle CI
with github it's looking at my repo
already and what it's done is it's
determined that it can run either on
Linux or Mac OS or probably runs on
either Linux or Mac OS in fact I'm not
sure circle tests against Windows
it may well so it asks which OS you're
on and asks which language you're using
which is already inferred based on the
repo and what's in there and it gives
you some instructions for how to
configure circle for it so it's actually
pretty easy and there's some
interpretation and different approaches
to this but we'll start with a fairly
simple one so step one create a focal
for the folder named circle CI and add a
file excuse me had a file called config
dot yml within it file path lily circle
CI config dot yml so we're gonna create
a dot circle CI and I believe V s code
will detect it that is nope maybe not
config yml yeah okay
there's some formatting I thought there
was a special circle CI integration here
populate the config with the contents of
the sample why am L shown below we're
just going to copy that to clipboard and
paste it in here there we go
use the sample yml to reflect your
project's configuration push this change
to github start building this will
launch your project on circle CI and
make our web hooks listen for updates to
your work
so we're gonna do all these changes
first we'll write this to work against
our repo oh and actually before I do
this I'm gonna take one step backwards
so this this function here yarn test
it's important to me or at least I think
it's a good practice to have a CI
command so we're gonna do tests Oh
actually you know we can do this a
different way so my whole point is in CI
I'm going to run this test script and
this lint
script and make sure they both pass just
for the sake of being thorough so let's
go into that config file and we will do
them in here so this is a yellow file
which has a specific format it's a lot
like Jason it's just a little more
compact a lot of this stuff comes from
circles specifications for what what
there am a file looks like for the
config this creates a doctor image of
circle CI slash node 710 we can specify
the version we desire based on that we
could go see what docker images are
available here but that one will
probably work it creates a working
directory which we can which will use
its its home directory slash repo I
think it's best practice to put the repo
name in here and actually this repo is
not called jobs module it's called jobs
micro service so we're gonna hang on to
that it checks out the code so it pulls
it down from github it pulls down the
cache and dependencies which is fine
it runs yarn install it then runs yarn
tests we're also going to run yarn lint
and that should be it that that is all
it takes to send this thing up to circle
CI so I'm going to commit the the
various codes we've just written so
we're gonna do get add babel RC git add
source util test j s we're gonna do get
add circle CI
okay
you know what I'm gonna do this in the
UI because it's just gonna make my life
easier so here we go so first I'm going
to do the test stuff which is here so
update dependencies config for just
that's gonna be this guy as well and
this guy we should get rid of that code
which is no longer necessary so let's do
that we're going to add these test cases
in
we'll commit that and then we're also
going to configure circle CI so we're
gonna push these five commits up to
github in a moment actually now I'm just
gonna do that now so these will be
pushed up to github on the master branch
we're gonna have to do some magic in a
bit with this config file but for now
this is a good place to start so I hit
start building this is going to go then
look at github and start building from
the repo so it's doing all the things we
it just told me or we just told it to do
checking out our code restoring a cache
and installing the dependencies from
yarn
this will take a minute of course save
the cash for possibly use the next time
around so it doesn't the yarn step
doesn't take so long it's now running
our tests tests fast it's running lint
which may not pass Hey look at that
all those Lin errors that's great
actually so there's our very first build
on this jobs micro service repo and
there are a bunch of problems because I
haven't been paying particular attention
to lint lately so let's go and fix those
things and then we'll submit another
build and hopefully they'll pass the
tests so job listing dot Jas has a
problem that this campaign let's see
where are my problems here campaign prop
type is defined but prop is never used
so what we should do here is just put a
campaign in here which is fine and
that's probably actually meant to go
inside of this guy okay well we should
look at that
in a second here my voice is killing me
I'm going to do a up on water I'll be
back in just a moment
okay sorry about that I'm back let's do
this thing all right so this is actually
one case where lint is probably saving
me um I've provided this campaign prompt
to the job listing and it's not being
used anywhere inside of this component
which is probably indicative of a
logical error in this case so we're
gonna leave this generate URL for job
function and actually we can see thanks
to vs code inside of this function it
looks for a campaign prop I'll just
click on it and show you looks for a
campaign prop and passes that in as a
part of the slug so oh actually it's
just up here conveniently enough
[Music]
and we're just gonna sort of reformat
this this is not my favorite syntax sort
of change in the world but it should at
least make that a little more clear here
not jobs job okay great so now that's
used that clears up that issue so we're
going to commit that use campaign if
provided to job listing will commit that
but not push it yet and let's look at
the other problems we've got here from
the build minor segments is assigned a
value but never used in job API job API
okay we're gonna comment that out
because I'm just not using it unused
syntax and in theory my test should
still pass
we can see what's wrong with link if I
run this locally here to great Oh
actually I'm okay I'm distracting myself
too much we're gonna look for this error
here test is not defined I should be
looking on the gist just Lynch yes and
just my cat just jumped onto my arm dude
you're killing me please all right
that's how you know we're doing it live
all right now where was I
son of a okay so in my insolent
definition here I need an end of jest
I'll put that oh yeah no in double
quotes like prettier likes and maybe
that I'll have addressed it
alright needs a comma
ha ha just true I did that wrong
okay
boom and that fixes that so I actually
don't know if I even needed this plug-in
to be honest we'll let that be for now
so this will be configure yes lint to
expect just syntax okay now if I commit
this code and I hit push and send it up
to the branch on github it will kick off
another build on circle CI in a second
when we saw it just popped up as queued
and then we'll run through the test
again okay and see if I'm bleeding over
here no blood just some good scrapes
what's going on here check out code
so we can see this test running it's now
past everything look at that this build
is now fixed how cool is that very cool
I hope so excuse me sorry
very slowly losing my voice here okay so
now we want to now is when I need to
start being more strict with how I'm
doing this development work so a pattern
I like to follow when I'm working on
small personal projects here without a
bigger team
is a modification of what's called the
git flow workflow which is sort of just
a pattern to follow with which branches
you're using for development how you run
releases and this and that it's not
super hard but we can basically define
some branches that we use specifically
in one case versus the next so when I'm
building something we can define well
here I'll just show you easier to show
than to explain so what I'm gonna do is
I'm gonna create a branch called develop
which will be sort of our working branch
in my settings for this project I'm
going to go to branches and I'm going to
protect both my master branch in my
develop branch so I'm gonna hit protect
require pull request reviews before
merging not gonna do in this case
because there's no one really to review
my pull requests you that you can't
review your own pull requests on github
I will require status checks to pass
it's already seen that Circle CI has run
on this repo so we're gonna require that
to pass require signed commits basically
means that you have to have a verified
Shaw signature against your the get
account the or when you're pushing to
get I believe I'm set up correctly for
that we might not include that then I'm
gonna include administrators because
that's me
we will restrict to can push to this
branch specify team's allowed to push to
this branch required status checks over
any people from ridging if
fail yeah okay we're gonna set all of
those things up I'm gonna add my
password real quick grab it from my
password manager
lots of to factor this going on there
never please okay now that's all well
and done so we're gonna go back up to
here and we're gonna protect the develop
branch as well with the same setups
status checks circle see I signed
commits include administrators restrict
you can push all of the above so now
that means that I cannot commit code
directly to either of these branches
which means that to I'm going to run a
fetch here so I get the new branch from
github develop should show up here which
basically means that from here on in
this master branch will be treated as
production the developed branch will be
treated as the staging environment and
then anything I do will be done in a
branch that opens a pull request against
first develop and then master its it
sounds a little abstract at first
perhaps but once you get used to it it's
not too bad there are definitely
different things you should do on bigger
teams this is what I do for projects
with small teams like my work booster
Museum where the development team is the
guy you're looking at right now so we're
gonna create a new branch from the
develop branch we're gonna call it
feature and we will call it feature roku
no we're not gonna do Heroku yet we're
gonna do circle CI config so now I have
this branch because I can't open I can't
commit code directly to develop and
master that's true my team is not just
me but the only one writing code
currently is me the people testing the
code and working with me to do designs
and whatnot are also on the line I don't
mean to diminish anyone's egos certainly
thank you Andrew all right so here's
what I'm hoping to do here is write some
code here that in this in this not in
here and my circle config which will do
some specific functionality depending on
the branch that we're in so because of
this new pull request magic we're adding
in we want to make sure that they're
there certain behaviors in place for the
develop branch and the master branch
which are now special cases so let's do
that it's going to require some
modification to this file and that's
totally okay so we're looking for some
syntax on the circle CI config that's
specific to branches so I'll show you
how I would find that well these are
sample config files which is lovely
we're gonna do configuration reference
and basically what I'm looking for is
branches hey look at that
so defines rules for whitelisting
blacklisting execution of some branches
if workflows are not configured if
you're using workflows job level
branches will be ignored and must be
configured in the work flow section of
your config dot yml file which is
probably what we need to do instead so
see workflow section for details
excuse me I'm sorry okay so the
workflows setup basically runs certain
certain tasks as a workflow within
circle CI so basically what it'll do is
it'll break your config tasks into
separate oh it's hard to describe but
basically you'll have we'll have one
here that says test one that says deploy
the test obviously we're on all the
tests if the tests all pass it will then
go into the deploy task which we can use
to push things up to Heroku actually I
may be overthinking it this may not be
necessary
okay let's hold off on that for now
maybe now is when I should be setting up
Heroku
so let's do that
so on a tab you can't see because I've
forgotten I am creating a new Heroku
Dino
Heroku is runs basically small virtual
machines small virtualized environments
to run bits of code there are a number
of service tiers they provide from free
up to super enterprise distributed stuff
we're gonna start with the free one here
because this is a small project in
testing but in in the future when we go
to sort of a production environment we
may choose to up that so well let me
connect it to github on another screen
just so I don't reveal any of my git
passwords accidentally no password there
[Music]
great I've now connected that let me
bring this back to you
lovely so connected to gymnasium jobs
micro service that's good
enable automatic deploys from github
we're gonna wait for CI to pass before
deployment we're going to use develop
for this one because this is going to be
my staging environment and we're going
to enable automatic deploys now there's
some work we need to do to actually
configure this for circle CI and we'll
talk about that in a second here we're
not going to use a pipeline because we
don't need to Walter promote well well
we might end up doing that okay so now
we go into settings config are
essentially environment variables for
this for this instance which we will end
up using in the future for today we
probably won't we're gonna add a build
pack which is basically how Heroku knows
how to run your app much like just used
these docker images so just uses docker
images Heroku uses build packs which are
different but similar in functionality
this is a node.js project so we will add
the node.js build pack and I believe
that might be all I need to do here to
make this work I believe I believe oh no
I'm sorry there's one more step so we're
gonna I mean that config should be saved
that's great so I am actually since I
didn't do anything I'm gonna rename this
branch to feature Heroku config
and to run on Heroku there's a special
file that Heroku looks for wrong screen
wrong screen wrong screen Heroku proc
file so this thing called a proc file
that Heroku uses which determines what
job to run it all looks like this and
there's some specific syntax for it
basically what you need to know is that
the proc file runs a command that runs
your app it should go in the root of the
project and be called proc file with a
capital C capital P and that one see
it's already recognizing it as a Heroku
thing in BS code there's some specific
syntax ascesis is here but I believe
actually NPM is one of the special ones
that works naming and location it should
be named proc file exactly and not
anything else yes yes yes a number of
process type declarations these are in
the new line each process type is a
declaration of a command that is
executed when a dyno of that process
type is started for example if a web
process type is declared then when a
dyno of that type is started the command
associated with the web process type
will be executed that comma probably
doesn't need to be there this could mean
starting a web server for example so
basically this is defining the type of
process and then this is the command to
run so this is a ruby on rails app
that's a closure app apparently Java all
kinds of good stuff in our case this
actually might be pretty simple I think
we can get away with yarn start and
that's it so now we need to push this to
this pull request add Heroku proc file
we will commit that and then push this
and now a couple things should happen so
we should see a build start here we can
watch this run it'll take a minute
inside of this repo there's now this new
branch feature Heroku config which we
can create a pull request against will
make a nice nice pull request here I'm
gonna add myself as a well Andrew here
your Revere and Justin
Jeremy's off today I believe I'm gonna
assign all of us we will create this as
an enhancement there are no projects on
this no milestones whatever this should
allow this project to be deployed on
Heroku after this PR closes bombs up
create this pull request you'll see that
this pull request waited for the check
to pass we can show which check it was
looking for so the so the I need to shut
that off I don't have signed commits
coming from my machine right now so my
test is passed on circle CI that's
lovely so if we clicked on this it would
bring me back to this page everything
worked as we would expect
we can now I'm just gonna go shut off
those signed commits that's a failing to
set up my machine correctly here really
but since I know me I'm just gonna shut
this off that's a terrible thing to say
don't do this if you're not me okay so
now we can go back to that poll request
it is here now everything's hunky-dory I
can merge this pull request before I do
I'm going to go to the logs for this
Heroku app and hopefully we can watch it
deploy it should deploy let me show that
again because we have this setup to
automatically come from under deploy
here it automatically deploys from the
develop branch after CI passes
automatically when when that branch is
updated so this is gonna happen quickly
and I mean I hope I can kind of make it
make it through to watch all these
things all at once but when I close this
pull request when I merge this pull
request is going to kick off a new build
on here for that develop branch when
that build passes it's going to kick off
a deployment to this Heroku Dino if that
works then we can view this from the web
I think maybe alright take a deep breath
let's see what happens
merge pull request
so I'm gonna delete that branch well
we'll delete it if it works so we can
see this test is now running
tests should pass shortly Aaron test ran
yarn lint ran this build is now passing
if we come into here in theory I should
see a build get kicked off here I
believe maybe maybe not
it might take a second I might also not
have configured this correctly
and how do I view these logs
hmm
yes No oh we're gonna River at that pull
request you silly fool
I open it against the wrong branch yeah
actually I guess I don't really need to
revert it in this case straight away
damn okay we're just gonna do a new poll
requests and demonstrate the same thing
this should have been developed and
actually because I made that mistake I'm
going to do this which I set up for most
of my repos to set the default branch to
develop rather than master so that I
have to yes update that please basically
what that says is that now in this jobs
micro service branch develop will show
up here first rather than master so that
when I create a new pull request from
this guy here that's not what I wanted
when I create a pull request from this
branch here it will go to develop
automatically so I'm gonna make this
pull request staging a Toro proc file
we'll do the same thing we just did
assign these guys so they get an email
from github because who doesn't love
emails
this should deploy set up deployments to
Heroku staging from PRS on the develop
branch okay
I'm gonna create this pull request it'll
run tests if it no it's already run the
tests here that's good we're gonna come
back here we're gonna watch all this
stuff happen again hopefully it'll work
like I expect so this is now against
develop will merge this pull requests
will see the new tests fire off here
these are by the way are all sort of
growing pains that happen when you set
up this DevOps stuff typically
traditionally when I've set up circle CI
is taken like on more complicated
projects sometimes dozens of tries to
get the circle tests even run so
consider this a pretty good pretty good
setup this is now running that's setting
up the docker image that this test will
be running on
doing all the things installing all of
the packages
running my test cases
that build past maybe our release will
run now
whoo there we go build started
I'm not sure how long this will take to
be honest I'd expect maybe a minute or
two
oh no daman not found
okay so that's a good point for my
development environment I have this
running node monitor which does the
Babel conversions and then runs yeah so
it runs a couple commands at once or
sorry runs this node monban which looks
for changes so we're actually gonna have
to update this this is gonna now be my
start dev command and we'll have a start
server command which will just run the
transpiled code and I'm gonna actually I
have to actually test which command that
is so let's come into here and we're
gonna run node and all of that that
didn't work okay oh I see so we're gonna
have to have a build step
[Music]
hmm
okay so there's gonna be a few things
that get added here build which will
compile my your transpiling my code so
this will be the babel node bit and then
we're gonna have start server which runs
on babel yarn build and node index j a
spore that index IJ s is going to be in
a built directory somewhere here so
let's see how that has to work all of
this is jumping through some hoops to
make everything work because we have to
transpile our code because we chose to
use es6 syntax in the app here right
maybe
yeah it's not the es6 syntax it's the
JSX syntax that's the problem here so
we okay
hmm okay this is what I'm looking to
execute but I think I need some help
here now French only ignore extensions
plugins presets
hmm you know what it's possible that
this might be what I need to run so I'm
just trying to figure out which come in
needs to run to do the transpiling and
then run the web service which i think
is and then this list of presets after
sweet I think that did it so
let's make sure this is running and
doing what we expect yeah okay that
worked so it's actually simpler than I
thought it was we don't need a build
step because that's kind of happening on
the fly here I'm going to run that
command as my start server command so
that's going to be node it's gonna be
just what I dumped into the console here
a second ago
and actually we might not even need node
there I might even just be able to say
this if I run it with yarn yarn start
server need a comma totally that works
okay so now we have this start server
command which runs the transpiled
service without running this node
monitor which is what I'm using in my
dev environment to monitor for changes
so we're going to commit that so and
actually I need to change the proc file
to to run start server which will run
this command instead of just start so
edie start server script to package
jason we will do the same thing we did
before that'll kick off a test will
create a pull request we'll do all that
excuse me test running right now we're
gonna create another pull request
probably on that same branch even
caught her who take to say what this PR
does we don't need to run ooh actually
this might not work I will explain that
in a second to reviewers I'm gonna
dispatch with all that stuff for now we
will label it as an enhancement and
assign myself why not okay make a pull
request now once again we should see how
this magic happen that build pasts we're
good to go we're gonna merge this pull
request in to develop it will run tests
tests will run and pass Heroku will
detect a deployment trigger there it is
build started
and we'll see what happens
ah crap it didn't work okay I had a
feeling this would be the case that is
because Babel node runs from Babel CLI
which I put in as a dev dependency which
means that on Heroku it doesn't get
installed because Heroku is running this
is a production environment and it's not
installing these to have dependencies so
I'm gonna move all of these Babel
dependencies over to dependencies and
we'll try that move Babel steps to
dependencies since Heroku needs commits
that push that it'll run a test will
make another pull request a circle of
life carries on
beside myself label it as an enhancement
because that's what I do create a pull
request these tests might already be
done they're not done yet we can wait
for the tests to complete it should
still show up here good good
large the pull request watch this all
happen again here is another test state
changed from starting to crashed lovely
remember when I said sometimes it takes
dozens of commits to make this all work
par for the course for me at least
nobody's perfect
build started
sometimes I don't even need help
breaking all the stuff
state changed from crashing the starting
uh-huh that might be a problem okay
we're gonna open the app we probably
won't see anything here funny enough I
need to pass in a port I believe well
yeah okay that's partially a problem so
the spirit server is only running on
port 3000 but Heroku decides which port
to run on for you and so there's some
magic we need to use inside of my inside
of the script that runs this whole thing
there we go
that looks familiar so that should do it
now so what this did is if the process
that's spinning up this specifies a port
the Apple listen on that port we need to
do or three thousand ago at a default
one will do Const port equals or three
thousand and we're gonna do
listen porch and we're gonna change this
to display me which port which is not
super important but yeah and we're gonna
say running and give it one of those and
maybe an emoji for good measure how
about the old head explode great we'll
see if that breaks anything okay
to allow for a port to be specified by
the running process this is required for
Heroku to work correctly like I said
because Heroku does not expose port 3000
by default on everything that they do on
all their Dinah's
the port is in fact passed into the
build environment sort of dynamically so
we're gonna make yet another pull
request yet another deployment
assign myself an appointment create a
pull request we're getting better at
this
wait for these tests to complete be in
good shape in no time
cat says hi again what's up man you're
standing on my keyboard okay
let's merge this pull request please I'm
knocked over my water bottle it kicks
off another test test runs and takes
approximately 30 to 45 seconds
you now get to hear the cat sorry about
that
that is continuous integration step one
completed now step two for the actual
deployment we'll take a second to
recognize as I leaned around the cat
figure out what's going on here build
started
build succeeded hopefully now it binds
to the correct port you can see actually
that Heroku killed the old last one
because it didn't bind to the right port
where did it say that
yeah boot timeout web process failed to
bind to port within 60 seconds of launch
running on port it's changed from
starting up open app boom we are
deployed to the web now we have a
public-facing micro service in a staging
environment through continuous
integration from having a commit to a
repo to opening a pull request to
getting a tested to deploying it to
Heroku all with the flick of a wrist so
now any code that I deploy will go up to
this staging environment from my
environment so that my team can look at
it and then we can use this URL to test
in our staging URL piece of cake we
could also map this to a custom domain
if we like and really that's all there
is to it um yeah we accomplished a lot
today I got to learn a bit as I went I
wrote some kind of lame test cases maybe
next week we'll write some more tests
and all honesty I'll probably move into
doing a bit more of the dynamic work for
this some of the styling and all that
anyway I hope you enjoyed the stream
today I had a lot of fun I'm losing my
voice my throat hurts and there's a cat
that apparently needs attention so I'm
gonna get going thanks for hanging out I
will catch you guys next week if you
need to find me you can get me on
twitter at irreverent mike my email
address is my full go at a quick calm
yeah catch you next week see ya