in the last video we saw what closure is
let's repeat the same exact example we
used and show a few additional ones that
are a little bit more complex so to
start off here I created a program and
it's just a function this function has
another function nested inside of it so
we have three available scopes to us the
first scope is the global scope
represented in green so our whole
program is sitting inside of this global
scope next our Foo function creates its
own scope as well and it's everything
inside of the Foos opening and closing
code brackets so everything from here to
here last but not least we have our taz
function and our taz function creates
its own scope as well it's everything
from its opening and closing code blocks
so the scope is finally created when our
program executes so on line 13 foo is
invoked so the scope of foo is created
and then taz is invoked inside of foo
let's see what values each scope has so
the global scope has the Foo function so
I'll write that in green the Foo
function or the foo scope has the
variable a and it has the Taz function
and last but not least the Taz function
has the variable Z now notice what's
happening here
the taz function tries using the
variable a but Taz itself doesn't have
the variable a so it looks to its outer
scope and its outer scope the closest
scope it has a reference to is the scope
of foo so it finds variable a there and
it uses it so hopefully this was a good
review from the last few videos and this
is actually where our closure happened
we have a function sitting inside of
another function and it's using a
variable
in its outer lexical environment or its
outer scope so this is where the closure
happened right here let's see if this is
true in our chrome console so I'm going
to get rid of my diagram and run this
code through the rubb browser and when i
refresh this page so let me just delete
this I'm going to refresh this no it is
a is log to the console because we're
accessing the variable a and logging it
from to the console great but I want to
show you a quick tip using the chrome
console I'm going to put the debugger
inside of my task function and our
chrome console will tell us whether or
not a closure was formed so when i
refresh this page and i zoom out a bit
notice in our scope section we have
local global and closure and the closure
was created with the variable a that's
what we're accessing and where are we
accessing it from we're accident from
Foos scope so let's say we didn't use
any values from foo with this closure
still be created let's say we were just
console logging the values e so if i
refresh this and look at this code now
in my debugger notice the difference
here function Taz is only making use of
its local scope so that closure was
never formed we never had a look up that
scope chain and look in our outer
lexical environment and make use of a so
we're not using Foos scope so we never
formed a closure so this was a review of
the last few videos and now let's move
on to a more practical example of using
a closure I'll get rid of my code here
and I have some more code below
here's another example of closure it
should look very familiar from our other
examples with one small twist here we
created a function named increment
creator and a num x called variable was
defined and assigned to the value 0 now
we have a function which uses increment
I'm sorry which uses num x called and
increment it by 1 this function will
also then console.log the value of num x
called but here is the trick and here
where things is slightly different on
line 10 the Inc function is returned out
of our increment creator function so
just like objects numbers and strings
you can return functions from other
functions and this is the idea of
higher-order functions there's a video
dedicated to this idea so I highly
suggest reviewing it so since we are
returning Inc function my question to
you is since it's no longer sitting
inside of the increment creator scope
where num times called is created will
it still have access to num x called
inside of itself or inside of its own
scope let's take a look at this so in my
browser I'm going to refresh it and the
name of the function we want to invoke
is increment Creator and I will create a
variable called return func and this is
the variable that stores the value
returned from increment to creator which
is the ink func
and actually let me rename this all is
call this in func as well so we invoke
increment Creator and increment creator
returns the function Inc func so what
should in func do now let me first prove
to you that it is a function and I'll
call the to string method on it
so we can see it's code body notice it's
a function and it's supposed to
increment sometimes called
and then console.log num times call but
notice inside of this function num times
called isn't declared anywhere right
there isn't a VAR num Times called
equals zero anywhere so you would
probably anticipate that when we call
Inc func
we get some type of error that num times
call does not defined but notice the
value 1 is locked
meaning somehow we held or still have a
reference to num times called and we do
because of a closure so it doesn't
matter whether or not this function is
used inside of increment creator like in
our other examples since it was created
inside of the increment creator scope it
will always have access to the variables
and values it used in that scope and the
the scope of a I'm sorry the scope of
increment Creator is stored in something
called the heap which we aren't going to
get into now but it's not lost it's not
just erased from the JavaScript runtime
environment the JavaScript runtime
environment saves that scope so we can
access it later so the ink func is still
looking up at scope t chain thanks to a
closure which was formed and it has
access to dump times called so let's see
that in the chrome console what I'll do
here is inside of let's say I'm going to
do a deep inspection sorry I had to
gather my thoughts there I'll do a deep
inspection on ink func and I want to
look at its scopes so notice there's a
closure so this is part of its scope
chain and it's reaching this closure
from the increment creator function
and inside of that increment creator
function is where num times was defined
I'm sorry num times called was defined
right it was a Stan shader and assigned
to zero but since we invoked it at least
one time the value of it is now 1 and if
we look inside of this notice sometimes
called as 1 so this is the idea of
closure even if we return a function out
of another function but it was created
and defined inside of that scope if it
used any values from its surrounding
scope it will remember that chain and
remember all the variables that it had
access to and it will be able to call
them later on so I hope you enjoyed this
small introduction and light
introduction to closure there's a lot of
great practice exercises and tests first
so I hope you enjoy working through
those