what is scope scope is a way for your
program to determine whether or not it
has access to a specific variable or
value you can also determine based on
the section of the program you're
currently running at whether or not a
value belongs to that section
let's take a look here's an image of a
few coffee cups my friends and I enjoy
going to Coffee cafes but we always have
this problem I decide to get a glass of
water while my other friend decides to
go to the bathroom and my other friend
decides to add something else to his
order we do this all at the same time so
we leave our seats and then come back
let's say 10 minutes later and have no
idea which coffee cup belongs to him and
this is a problem and this is what scope
is trying to solve so let's take a
deeper look
as we mentioned scope is a term used to
describe what values your program has
access to scope can be determined
lexically so that means where it
physically sits in your program and
there are two main types of scope there
is a function or local scope and global
scope let's take a look at some real
code let's take a look at this example
so we create two variables two and three
and an add function inside of our add
function we use variables two and three
and add them together last but not least
we invoke our add function and check the
values of two and three after our
invocation let's see what it looks like
in the browser so after running this
code two plus three gives us five and
the habit in our add function we didn't
manipulate our two variable at all so
it's still two and three is still three
as well let me ask you a question what
would happen if we relocated variables
two and three to our function so they're
no longer so they're no longer sitting
at the top of our program they're now
sitting inside of our functions code
block do you anticipate any different
behavior well let's find out when i
refresh this page our add function works
perfectly fine too
plus three is five but then we get a
reference error two is not defined and
when we get this error our program stops
executing so we never get to line 14 but
why are we getting a reference error for
two we declare two inside of our add
function and that code block runs on
line 12 so it should be available
unfortunately it's not but this is the
idea of scope anything declared inside
of a functions code block is only local
to that function meaning anything
outside of this code block doesn't have
access to the variables declared inside
of there so we don't have access to the
two function or I'm sorry the two
variable or the three variable but if I
relocated this console.log statement
inside of our add function and ran this
code now if i refresh the page notice we
have access to the two variable and we
can run that console.log statement but
we can't run the console.log statement
for three because it's not inside of
this code block it's not inside of the
add functions scope let me reposition
some code again how we had it originally
in our first example we had two two and
three functions sitting at the top of
our program then when our add function
was invoked it was able to calculate 2
plus 3 which was 5 so how does our add
function have access to these variables
that are sitting just at the top of our
program or anywhere in our program
they're not inside of a function
anything that's not wrapped in a
function is considered to be in the
global scope and anything located in the
global scope is accessible to any scope
in your program it's the top level of
scope picture the prototype chain where
you keep looking at an object and Denia
look to the next object the same idea
applies to scope what happens on line 12
when the add function is invoked it
looks inside its current scope inside of
this code block and it says you know
what what is
is to variable or three variable do I
have access to this it looks inside and
nothing is declared locally so it looks
outside to its next scope that it's in
and since function I'm sorry since the
add function is sitting right inside of
the global scope it only has to look one
step up and it finds the two and three
variables here so it finds them and uses
their values and has access to them and
this is the idea of scope scope can be
created by functions as we saw here and
when we move these variables inside of
the add function these variables were
only accessible inside of the add scope
they're only available locally to that
function but when they're moved outside
of this function so they're placed
inside of the global scope they're
accessible to all functions and all
sections of your program now that you
have an understanding of global scope
and function scope in the next video we
will show an example of nested functions
and have an introduction to closure