now you haven't now that you have an
understanding of scope let's take a look
at a few more examples in this program I
created a variable in the global scope
and the name of that variable is global
scope
how convenient next there's a function a
and inside of it it has a local variable
Apple I use the phrase local because
it's locally scoped to its dysfunction
code block the global scope does not
have access to Apple let's run this in
our console so when i refresh the page
notice logged Apple from function a
scope excellent I also want to show you
a trick inside of the chrome debugger I
can put the debugger keyword inside of
my a function and when I run my code
notice this section over here called
scope inside of this section it shows
that I have access to two scopes the
local scope which is our current
function we're inside notice it has an
apple and the dis keyword if you're
unfamiliar with this keyword that's okay
for now and it has access to the global
scope that's at the top of its scope
chain let's take a look at another
example I'm going to nest another
function inside of our a function so
this new function I'm creating will be
inside a function a
scope so let's take a look the function
I'm creating is function B and function
B will console.log and I send copy and
paste this function B will console.log
the same exact statement but instead of
cot console logging it from a scope will
console.log it from b scope the key
concept to identify here is that we are
trying to make use of Apple and Apple
isn't defined locally inside of B so my
question is will it have access to the
Apple very variable inside of a scope
well let's take a look before moving on
I need to make sure to invoke our B
function now when i refresh this page
and open up our chrome console notice we
logged apple from a scope and we also
logged Apple for B scope so since B is
sitting inside of a it has access to all
the variables inside of a scope but this
isn't a two-way street
if I created a variable for B let's save
our banana assigned to the string banana
and tried using banana inside of a a
will not have access to banana so if I
ran this again notice we're getting a
reference error here and that's because
everything inside of B's scope is
contained to the B function when it's
invoked right here variable the variable
banana is not leaked lete to its outer
scope but when we use Apple inside of B
first it looks inside of itself and
can't find Apple and it begins
traversing its scope chain it looks one
once to its outer scope and five finds
Apple there so you will hear this term
nested scope and this is a general idea
of it it has to do with nested functions
it's also applying the concept of
closure here as well and we haven't
covered closure yet but let's read the
definition closures are functions that
refer to independent or free variables
these are variables that are used
locally but defined in an enclosing
scope so they're used locally but
defined in an enclosing scope and that's
exactly what we're doing here with our
Apple variable it's used locally inside
of B scope but it's defined inside of a
scope
so in the next video we're going to dive
deeper into what exactly closures are
and how to use them in programs