let's discuss the scope chain the scope
chain is the mechanism used by a
JavaScript runtime that represent scopes
to resolve an identifier when an
identifier is referenced but isn't used
in the local scope the scope chain
traverses up to a parent scope until the
identifier is found so here we have a
diagram showing our execution contexts
and a code example on the right-hand
side the code example is reflected in
this diagram so let's discuss how the
scope chain works in the green box here
on the right hand side we this is
demonstrating everything in our global
scope and global execution context so
peanuts and allergies are in our global
scope and if we remember back to the
global execution context section what is
created when a execution context is is
created right you have a global object
and at least the global execution
context you have a scope chain and you
have a disc binding we're gonna focus on
the global object and scope chain for
now attached to this global object is
anything in the global space of our
program or anything not wrapped in
another function so what are those
values well be a peanuts in our program
so that's attached to our global object
and we have the allergies function which
is also attached now the scope chain
that is created this is the the global
scope of our program and that this is a
top-level scope of our program so our
scope chain just has a reference to this
global object so anything in our program
can have access to the peanuts and
allergies functions and variables now
let's look at allergies and how is
allergies different done to this go
global scope well when allergies is
invoked it creates its own execution
context and what comes along with that a
variable object a scope chain and a dis
binding so inside of our allergies
function notice we don't make any type
of assignments and we don't create any
new values here so our variable object
is empty for now but notice that
reference is peanuts so how does it get
access to peanuts which isn't in its
current local scope and the way it does
that is through the scope chain
so first the allergies function looks at
its scope chain object here and it looks
at its variable object and it notices
peanuts is not to find anywhere on this
variable object so now goes to step two
which is it has to look at his parent
scope and its parent scope is a
reference to
the global object and the global object
has the Peanuts variable and it's
resolved here right we get access to it
and we use the value that we find at
this property on the global object so
let's take another look at this right
that was just a general overview of how
the scope chain works using some of the
knowledge we have with execution
contexts let's take a look at another
example but before we move into that
just keep in mind when we're talking
about the scope chain and its traversal
it can only move up so the allergies
local scope is kind of the child
of the global scope and allergies can
look up to the global scope but the
global scope can't look down into
allergies and find any of the variables
defined within that function and we'll
show an example of that so let's take a
look at nested functions a nested
function is this a function defined
inside of another function and our code
example here we have a few of them
notice we define Manhattan and inside of
Manhattan we define a Soho function and
inside of Soho we define Chelsea let's
take a look at how parent the parent
scope is defined for nested functions
and to do that let's outline all the
different scopes we have so we have a
global scope Manhattan has its own local
scope Soho has its own local scope and
Chelsea has its own local scope notice
all these functions are being invoked in
our program so the general rule of thumb
with our scope chain is that our scopes
can traverse upwards but we can't
Traverse downwards so this Manhattan
function can't get access to this Soho
LS variable inside of Soho right it's
inside its own scope and it's blocked
off here so we can't Traverse
down the chain and when you see all
these LS is here these are just
referencing local scope that's what the
LS is supposed to stand for so we know
Manhattan can't look down into Soho's
local scope but let's take Chelsea as
another example and let's look at the
other end of this can Chelsea traverse
upwards to find this Soho LS variable
and it can because Soho is the parent of
Chelsea's scope it's the parent in the
scope chain so we have a variable
essentially defined in every function
and let's look at this other diagram
here where we define everything in our
local scope
and what our parent scope is and we're
going to specifically look at the
Chelsea scope team so this is not
executable code here this is a diagram
to illustrate Chelsea's scope team so in
the local scope of Chelsea it has the
Chelsea LS variable and a reference to
itself so all functions always have a
reference to themselves let's say we
were trying to get access to this New
York boroughs array and in our code step
that we can see it's all the way up in
the global scope right so Chelsea has a
far way to travel well the first thing
Chelsea does is it looks on itself and
it asks well do I have New York borrows
in my current local scope it doesn't so
what does it do it checks its parent
scope which is Soho because Chelsea is
nested inside of Soho Soho is its parent
scope now Soho checks itself divide New
York boroughs
it doesn't so now Soho checks its parent
scope and what is Soho nested inside its
nested inside of the manhattan function
right that's its outer scope
so now Manhattan looks where New York
borrows it can't find it either so it
looks at its parent scope which is the
global scope as we can see right here
right here's Manhattan and its global
scope is New York borrows now let's take
a look at another example here all right
I changed our program a bit we're now
the Chelsea function is outside and it's
in its own scope right it's only really
nested inside of the global scope below
right here right so no longer nested
inside of Soho so let's define all of
our different scopes with the global
scope Manhattan has its own scope so has
its own local scope and so does Chelsea
but when we invoke Chelsea now what is
its outermost scope right how does it
get access to New York burrows how many
steps in the scope chain does it take
well here's our diagram again so the
Chelsea LS variable is defined and
Chelsea is also defined in our local
scope and when we look up at scope chain
notice it's only traveling up to one
scope and that's because Chelsea is no
longer defined inside of Soho so its
outermost scope now is the global scope
but let's say if I were to ask you well
what Soho's outer outer scope or the
next step in traversing the scope chain
it would be Manhattan so notice when you
have nested
functions but a function is nested
that's where that parents in our diagram
from before and excuse me for doing this
but before when we had this parents go
property in our scope chain it's defined
by the scopes it's nested inside and our
runtime does that for us
so hopefully have a better idea now on
how this scope chain works and I just
wanted to show you one last example of a
reference error so I'm sure you have
experienced a reference error before and
a reference error is just when your
runtime or your program can't find an
identifier so either a variable or a
function or something to find in your
program that it can't find it doesn't
have access to it traversed all the way
up the scope chain it gets to the global
scope and it says you know I still can't
find it here this must not exist here's
a function Manhattan very similar to the
examples we had before
and inside of Manhattan in the local
scope it has a Manhattan LS variable and
a reference to itself Manhattan but
notice it's using this identifier
Brooklyn so this could be a function it
could be an array it could be anything
we don't really know what it is yet it's
not defined it hasn't been resolved so
what does Manhattan do well it looks up
at scope chain and its outer scope is
the global scope and if we look in the
global scope notice that Brooklyn is not
defined anywhere and we get a reference
reference error here Brooklyn is not
defined so nine times out of ten when I
get a reference error it's either a
scoping issue or I just misspelled the
variable name so when you get a
reference error make sure to look at the
spelling and then double check that
wherever you're calling that variable
your program has access to it