everybody knows somebody who hates their
job and maybe that's somebody's even you
in fact half of the people in the United
States who work would do something else
for a living if given the chance
that's an epidemic Hey look I know it's
hard to change it's easier to stick with
the devil you know walking away from a
paycheck and benefits that doesn't fit
conventional wisdom and doing something
more meaningful I mean you know who
wants to make less money but when I
think about this subject I think of my
grandfather my immigrant grandfather who
left Poland alone on a boat at 17 years
old to go to New York City and I wonder
what he would think about us talking
about being happy at work happy he would
say happy at work put food on the table
that's happy what are you talking about
happy my dad first-generation American
he was the first to go to college the
first to have a good corporate job his
was the 1960s version of being happy at
work but he really wasn't and today the
research shows that to be happy at work
people want to be engaged they want to
have mastery over their subject matter
they do want to know that what they do
matters more than the Paycheck they get
so if we know that why is it that 50
percent of us can't figure out what we
want to do with our life well I think
it's because when we're in doubt we look
to our resume we look to our credentials
what we're qualified to do and what
we're qualified to do is not necessarily
what we're meant to do it isn't
necessarily what's going to bring us
satisfaction think of an egg if you will
from a little hummingbird egg to an
ostrich egg all of them are around a
shell for people that show
all our our credentials our track record
our accomplishments and our resume a lot
of us get attached to that shell it
becomes our identity and that's what
makes it hard to change but to get to
the good stuff you have to crack the egg
open because inside is the yolk the
golden center that's where the DNA is
that's what determines how each egg is
unique and for people I call that yolk
their life blueprint so everything that
can be taken away is the shell the
status your identity what people think
of you the perks the salary but we can't
be taken away is the yolk and that's
where the discovery of career
satisfaction can happen maybe it's more
important to understand that career
satisfaction doesn't come from what you
do it comes from who you get to be while
you're doing that job who your job
allows you to be that's where the
happiness comes from so the shell is
what you do but the yolk is who who you
get to be when I was in my 20s I wanted
nothing more than to be a Broadway star
well I did reasonably well I mean I got
my union card I worked in reputable
theaters and I gave myself five years to
make it and that you're eight I was
still waiting on tables and so I grew
despondent I really did I was almost
suicidal over the fact that I thought
that I failed at the only thing I ever
wanted why hadn't this dream come true
for me I'd worked so hard I invested so
much ten years after I left show
business I had an epiphany about this I
remembered a scholarship that I was up
for for an acting program where they
asked me what would be possible if you
were successful as a performer and the
answer came to me in a flash but I knew
it was like the right answer the Miss
America pageant answer the eldest child
answered the I'm going to get the
scholarship answer so I went up to the
mic and I said well if I were successful
as a performer people would see me on
stage and be moved to change something
in their life that answer got me the
scholarship but it wasn't until ten
years later when I realized what I
really had
ed the performer was the shell causing
change from the stage that was the yoke
that was me so I hadn't failed at my
dream after all
I just suffered from a misinterpretation
of my dream I needed to allow the dream
to change form and I think that's what's
wrong for a lot of us when we can't
figure it out as no-one's taught us to
pull the dream apart and understand the
true significance of it we're told we
can be anything we want to be when we
grow up but we go to pick that college
major though the question changes from
what do you want to be when you grow up
to how you're going to make a living at
that we haven't been taught what our
dreams and machination x' really mean to
our career trajectory John was someone
who heard me speak about this concept
and he was very skeptical
he said Laura I've accomplished
everything I've set out to do I've had
every dream for my career come true so
this cannot possibly hold any weight but
at the time that we met he wasn't sure
what he wanted to do next he was
struggling with that and I want to tell
you a little secret
I don't believe anyone who tells me they
don't know what they want to do I
believe they do know they're just too
afraid to speak it because then they
have to do something about it
so anyway back to John since he
challenged me I said okay John well what
were all your career dreams that you had
come true and he said when I was a kid I
wanted to be a magician as a young adult
I wanted to be an architect then I
wanted to change and be in advertising
and marketing and be responsible for
huge billboards in New York City he goes
and now I want to do something with my
love for the outdoors I don't know maybe
an adventure Travel Guide or something
but he couldn't reconcile how that fit
with the rest of his life but I could
see it so this is where I need your help
if you go and if you go out and you see
a wonderful magic trick one that blows
your mind what's your reaction show me
on your face what your reaction is Wow
so if you go to a city that you've never
been to and you're looking up at the
architecture what does your face look
like all right now if you've been to New
York and ever seen a billboard so large
that a woman's nabel's the size of a
cruise ship
what does your face look like so you see
everything that John did evoked a
universal human response across culture
language or age ooh
Wow all those jobs were what he did but
who he was was someone who inspired awe
and if you go out in nature you will be
in awe so it was completely in his
blueprint for him to go and become
someone who worked in nature and took
others into nature to inspire awe so
today he owns a company where he designs
and manufactures gear for outdoor
enthusiasts he found his way so the
formula seems to be something from the
past whether you had it come true or not
re-examined for its true significance
married with your skill set of today
equals a satisfying new chapter now
they're people who have said to me over
the years that they've never had a dream
that they never had anything that ever
called to them they don't have any
memory of everything anything they ever
wanted to be when they grew up
and over the years what I've seen is a
common thread among these people is that
they all had a rougher childhood than
most
they either grew up in a dysfunctional
home maybe there was raging maybe there
was alcoholism
perhaps they were worried that a
relative who was sick or sibling who was
sick they didn't know if they were
coming or going any child who has to
keep their guard up all the time it
doesn't feel safe can't dream and if
that's any of you don't worry there is a
solution for another time I've also met
people who have had a round of success
with their career but it was based on
something that was a reaction from their
past so they succeeded but now they
don't know what to do because they have
no criteria so that thing from the past
if any of you have ever made a vow
anyone ever said I won't be like my
mother or I won't be like my father or
I'll never be poor or I'll show them
that's a vow and if you did that it was
a reaction to circumstances of your life
and it probably served you well look a
lot of people have a lot of ambition
based on things they don't want in their
life but there may come a point where
that motivation
is no longer useful to you because
you've outgrown it and then what do you
do
so Karen was someone that I met in this
situation she was a top salesperson she
won all the cars all the trips but she
was started talking about how she was
feeling really anxious because she felt
like she was losing her mojo she didn't
know if she could keep up this pace and
she didn't know how to discipline
herself to be as ambitious as she was
before
now I suspected that there would be
something in her story that would tell
us what was going on so there it was at
17 she was ready to accept a scholarship
to play basketball for college and she
found out she was pregnant she gave up
the scholarship she had the baby and she
made a vow I will not be a teenage
statistic so she had that baby she had
another baby with the same guy then she
married him went to school got this
great job succeeded wildly and now she
couldn't figure out why she could make
it work well she wasn't a teenager
anymore and she had well proven that she
wasn't a teenage statistic so once she
had the awareness that she needed to
just change why she worked the
motivation for why she worked she was on
to new paths so you see your resume is
only part of the equation all the things
had happened you made that resume that
made your life story that's what reveals
your blueprint that what's reveals the
themes and the imprint that is your yoke
I want to live in a world where people
stop competing at work because they
realize that they are so unique that
there's nobody to compete with
everyone's unique we don't cross over we
don't have to compete I want a world
where we don't torture our teenagers to
figure out what what they want to do
with the rest of their life at 17 years
old because we've taught them that their
dreams have many ways that they can come
to be and I'd like to see a world where
nobody suffers to make a living because
they understand that they are not wedded
to the shell but they can evolve from
the yolk so before I told you that half
of the people in the US would do
something different if given the chance
half that is an epidemic but it's an
epidemic that has a cure and the cure is
understanding that career satisfaction
doesn't come from what you
do it comes from who you get to be while
you're doing it and the beauty is who
you get to be is the real you
you