the world is a huge place filled with
countless living things from different
species of animals that live on land
high in the skies and deep underwater
what we may spend a little less time
thinking about is all of the plant life
that thrives around us as well
one particular plant that we all see
just about every day yet never give too
much actual thought to are trees with
over 60,000 known species trees provide
all types of benefits that aid in our
existence and as we all know sometimes
we just have to take the good with the
bad and that exactly is what today's top
five is about so without further delay
today top five supreme brings you if you
see this tree run fast and ask for help
before we get started with today's video
don't forget to click the bell to get
notified every single day with the best
tops you'll ever see now let's get
rolling number five now the first tree
on this list may actually surprise you
but the apple tree can be deadly if not
handled properly
see the seeds and apples contain
cyanogenic glycosides which if consumed
in large quantities can lead to cyanide
poisoning now while a human would be
hard-pressed to consume about 200 apple
seeds or 20 apple cores which is the
lethal dosage pets and other animals
are at greater risk just because they
sometimes don't know when to stop eating
number four the sandbox tree is a member
of the spurge family and it grows up to
a hundred and thirty feet tall if the
daunting look of this tree equipped with
cone-shaped spikes that cover the entire
trunk isn't enough of a warning the
fruit that this tree bears is actually
poisonous if consumed then vomiting
diarrhea and cramps ensue almost
instantly if the SAP gets into your eyes
it could actually blind you found in
some of the most tropical parts of South
and North America the fruit of the
sandbox tree looks like little pumpkins
and when they fully mature the fruit
actually explodes sending out its seeds
at speeds of up to a
and 50 miles-per-hour a speed fast
enough to cause serious injury if it
hits in the right spot number three the
Bunya pine tree has been literally in
existence since dinosaurs roamed the
earth and is mostly found in Australia
and while it can and has certainly been
dangerous and even deadly to
unsuspecting passerby it does have its
positive features the nuts found in the
cones that are produced by this ancient
plant have supplied native people with
food for hundreds of years the only
problem is the cones can grow up to 20
pounds in weight and once they fall from
the tree they can cause severe damage
even some instances of death to people
walking underneath them number two the
suicide tree or the Sorbara odom is a
highly toxic tree found in swampy areas
of India in South America the tree got
its nickname because people who wanted
to die simply ate the fruit from it
while there are positive uses from this
plant like making certain deodorants and
bio insecticides an open nature this
tree should never be touched and the
fruit which looks like small mangoes
once they are matured should most
certainly never be eaten
number one the only tree on this list
that's actually listed in the Guinness
Book of World Records as the world's
most dangerous tree is the mankini oak
tree primarily found in the Caribbean
and Gulf of Mexico the bark that covers
this plant loses sap that causes
blindness and blistering of the skin
once it reaches contact with people or
animals standing beneath this tree
during a rainstorm is just as bad
resulting in skin blistering and
irritation if you burn this tree and
ingest the smoke you could even go blind
if that's not enough the fruit that
comes from the mankini Oh tree is also
known as the death Apple eating it can
cause death and even if you don't
swallow it the flesh of this fruit and
your mouth will cause boils to form on
your tongue throat and roof of your
mouth and that's today's video if you
liked today's video leave a thumbs up
and share it with all your friends and
don't forget to subscribe to this
channel so that you never have to miss
out on any of our interesting videos
ever
[Music]