[Music]
now let's talk about missing flights
because well this happens and what do
you do you don't want to lose all your
money right if you think you are going
to miss your flight you think you're
gonna be late the first thing you should
do is call the airline they could
potentially put you on another flight if
they're able to resell your seats but if
you just show up late and missed it you
didn't give them an opportunity to fill
that empty seat and likelihood they just
flew that plane nobody in that seat
number two is if you're running late and
you ride to the counter and you miss
your flight or you're not gonna make it
be very very nice and polite to the
flight attendants to the people checking
you in I've made this mistake before in
the past just being you know frazzled
and don't take your anger out on them
because they will just not help you also
don't be like I slept through my alarm
stupid me no don't be doing that because
they're not gonna care what you should
say is something like oh I they're just
a bunch of traffic outside maybe I got a
flat tire something related to the
airport it was difficult to get through
the gate or difficult to get to the
checkout counter kind of blame it on
that even if it's not exactly truthful
just don't put it on like you slept
through your alarm because no one's
gonna help that make it more of an
airport issue if you miss a connecting
flight but it's through the same airline
don't worry they'll put you on another
flight and actually if it's a really
long way until the next flight they
might even give you a food token they'll
give you a stipend and you can go buy
food from the food court for free
because of their inconvenience so never
worry about that well you do need to
worry about is if you're booking
connecting flights on separate airlines
and I really don't think you should do
that you never know what's gonna happen
flights can be delayed more than a day
the airport could close like you there's
so many things that could happen and
maybe it was cheaper to do it that way
but then something unexpected happened
and now you're gonna be paying thousands
of dollars so it's definitely not
cheaper anymore I pretty much never do
this I did do it once and that one time
almost missed my flight and it was a bad
one I was flying from Peru to Los
Angeles three flights on one airline and
then I was flying from LA to Bali on
another airline and that's you know
that's really far really expensive if
you miss it well guess what my very
first flight leave
Peru was canceled and so I'm in panic
mode I just missed the first flight of
like five for that day so I went to the
checkout counter really nice and I asked
them I need to be somehow put on other
flights I have another connection but on
a different airline and it's across the
world so can you please help me and they
did they actually put me on another
airline
I arrived 40 minutes earlier than I was
expected to and I made that connection
so like I said just being nice if you do
miss your flight you're not entitled to
compensation but you might be entitled
to get the tax back you know it's not
necessarily a lot but it could be up to
25% so it's better than nothing
let's talk about accommodation issues I
recommend when you are staying anywhere
in the world to be booking through third
party sites it's funny because I don't
recommend that for flights flights I
think you should book directly through
the airline but first thing in places
abroad I think third party sites like
booking calm hostile worlds Airbnb and I
say this because sometimes there can be
issues whether they don't have your
booking it's not up to par it doesn't
look like the pictures sometimes they're
not really willing to help you and now
you've spent all this money and there's
no service customer service to give you
back your refund when you deserve or
whatever you could just have issues we
actually stay in this hotel Malaysia and
when we were volunteering and we wanted
a nice fancy getaway so we got a luxury
suite
that wasn't so luxury it looks pretty
but everything was falling apart
bathroom was broken bed was broken TV
was broken like everything was broken it
just looked nice I took pictures and I
went showed the front desk her psycho
sorry I didn't care I wish that they
would have accommodated something or
giving us a discount or our money back
or something because they didn't care I
guess I could write a bad review but
that's not really gonna do me any good
personally but if you book through these
third-party sites they will help you and
they will evaluate the issue probably
give you your money back for example air
B&amp;B let's say you stay in a place and
it's it sucks or the host is really bad
you have back and forth drama so you can
talk to Airbnb about this they're gonna
evaluate both of you
the thing is they hold the money they
withheld it from the host until you
finish your stay so if Airbnb decides
that you are right and that the host
failed then they're gonna give you back
your money but if you went directly to
you the place they're probably not gonna
give you back the money I also had an
issue in Cambodia we went in to book a
hotel on foot we talked to somebody
there we gave him our passports we even
put a down payment and we booked this
hotel for two weeks and they said okay
everything's done but it's not available
tonight so starting tomorrow you have it
for two weeks come in the next day they
can't find their booking we told them
that we talked to this guy and he set it
up and they're like there's no one like
that who works here I still don't know
what happened like if some random guy
just sat at the front desk or if they're
pulling one on us bottom line is they
said they didn't have our booking and we
were there the night before and they
said they were completely booked and we
couldn't stay people came in right after
us and we're you know taken care of and
found a room so I don't know what that
is
those people have booked it online we
booked it in person so I just kind of
was like well I guess we should have
booked it online
although sometimes when you do booked in
person you will save money because you
can usually negotiate the price versus I
just don't think it's worth it for
example booking calm you don't even have
to pay right away you can pay when you
get there so if it's a crappy place I'm
not staying here and then you don't have
to pay now this topic I don't
necessarily have that much experience
with but I do a little bit so I'm
talking about things like volcanic
eruptions earthquakes tsunamis
hurricanes anything that can go wrong
fires when I was in Bali I did
experience one earthquake actually on my
birthday I didn't feel it though I'm a
very heavy sleeper and I slept through
it but my boyfriend and my best friend
did actually what they do in Bali when
there's an earthquake is everybody comes
out into the courtyard and they all
start screaming in Balinese I'm alive
I'm alive so that it like trickles down
to the other houses like a waterfall
effect they know who is in trouble and I
can they know everybody's okay so yeah I
felt the first earthquake in Bali before
like all the other ones that came after
it was the one that hit Lombok a 6.4
magnitude really wrecked that island and
you know even though that's not bali
bali zoo I doubt it so we felt it you
know thankfully we didn't have too much
to worry about but the people in Lombok
did so here's what you should do for
starters to be prepared in case anything
happens number one make sure you have
access to international calling and this
can apply to everything I talked about
today make sure you have both travel and
health insurance because this is the
type of situation
you're gonna need it make sure that your
family or friends have copies of your
passport visa pages and itinerary this
dish will make it really easy for them
or easier in case they need to be an
advocate for you need to know where you
are need to submit papers whatever to
get you the help that you need
make sure to familiarize yourself with
local conditions and local laws it's
always a good idea to have the local
Embassy the phone number in your phone
just in case something happens so let's
just pretend the worst happened you're
in an emergency situation what do you do
so for starters you need to evaluate if
you are in a safe area so if you're back
at the hotel and it's safe okay good
stay there if you're out and about
buying a place shelter where it's safe
and there are people and you can be
protected if you are close to an embassy
or consulate go there if it hasn't been
damaged you can go there and you can get
support food shelter and they can also
help you to getting back home if you
cannot reach this then look for law
enforcement look for medical personnel
look for people that can help you and
direct you what do you do especially if
you're injured once you are safe the
first thing you want to do is
communicate to everybody you know that
you are safe one for other people
freaking out and - in case you need more
help in case you need something if
you're injured or would the extent of
your injury you need to explain that in
case you need more help or what it is
you need to do going forward I've heard
that sometimes in these situations
making phone calls will be very
difficult probably because everybody's
calling and panic and that texting watch
should be easier you might get through
better so that could be something to
know if your calling is not working like
try sending a text but hopefully none of
this stuff does happen to you every
situation is different these are just
some preventative things you can do and
then what you can do if you're caught up
in this situation let's say that you get
lost or stranded somewhere in a foreign
country this has happened to me actually
right when I started traveling I feel
like I made a lot of mistakes when I
first started traveling I've gotten
better but I actually got stranded in
Costa Rica in the middle of the jungle I
find when you are in these kind of
frantic panic situations and you're with
another person one person takes the role
of panicking and freaking out and the
other one takes the role of okay calm we
need to do this when you do this this is
this is how we're going to
out of this in this particular scenario
the friend I was with was panicked
beyond belief she was crying she was
freaking out she was gonna have enough
food this girl ate all the time she's
like oh my god we're not gonna have food
and water I was the one who was
remaining calm and I was like okay we're
gonna look for cars we're gonna
hitchhike I never hit you like before
we're gonna hitchhike we're gonna get
out of the situation this is really good
because it's good to kind of have the
panic person to kind of motivate the
other person to be like okay this is
what we're gonna get done in Mexico I
was the panic ER and my boyfriend was
the one who's more calm but yeah in
these situations if you see people you
need to ask for help if you are lost I
mean this is why it's important to have
offline maps otherwise look for taxis
public transit look for any kind of
public area you could try hitchhiking I
know not everybody's comfortable with
that and it's not always the safest
option but you know you got to just
evaluate the situation and really just
try to remain calm because if you're
panicked you're not gonna make proper
decisions and then after the fact you'll
realize what you did wrong or right and
you can hopefully not make the same
mistakes this last one is kind of only
appliable to people who volunteer I'm
talking about this because this is how I
used to travel was just volunteering
because then I could have this amazing
local experience and then usually it was
in exchange for food and accommodation I
did this a lot but it wasn't always the
best experience and what I mean by this
is that sometimes those volunteer
opportunities take advantage of you and
maybe they're asking more work review or
I've been asking you for money or making
you do all these things that's not what
you're supposed to be doing and this is
what you need to understand and put it
through your brain you have the power if
the person or the people you're working
for are mistreating you leave don't stay
there don't put up with it because it's
not right you can go complain to if you
use work away or help X or whatever site
whooping you know complain to them or
you can write them a bad review but you
don't need to stay there and be taking
in all the bad stuff that they're doing
to you just walk up and go you have the
power this is your travel experience
again this is kind of something just
personal but I've had a few situations
where I was kind of taken advantage of
one of them I felt bad about leaving so
I kind of stayed longer than I should
have the other one I was like absolutely
not I'm leaving so understand you have
the power to go and go before and this
video
quickly give you some necessary apps
that you should have while traveling
because it can help in all of these
scenarios number one offline maps I use
maps me but make sure you download the
actual map of the area I tend to forget
to do this and then it's a useless map
next app you should have is an app that
you can use for international calling
this is super important I use this a lot
I happen to use Skype but you can use
things like viber and whatsapp this is
useful for a lot of different thing it's
calling your bank if you're in trouble
number three I recommend having the app
of your bank so that it's easy to log in
you can be monitoring your transactions
and then also police from my bank they
have an option for manage your travel
plans so every time I go to another
country I can quickly just post I'm
gonna be in this country from this time
and then I won't have any issues when I
go to use my card in that country
another app that may be important not
always is a translator depending on your
preferences but a translator can be very
necessary at times I also recommend
having VPN I used to only use VPN when I
lived in China because it was necessary
but now I honestly use it kind of all
the time even though I haven't been in
China and months just because I don't
trust these Wi-Fi networks the last app
that I recommend but it's not mandatory
is speed test speed test can be
important because you can test the speed
of the Internet when you go to places
finding out the upload or the download
speeds and this can be important because
maybe you need to contact somebody or do
something and go to this cafe and the
internet sucks and you already ordered
everything and now you're like crap what
do I do now so before even sitting down
you could do a quick little speed test
and find out the speed see if it works
properly alright guys that's all I have
for you today I really hope that you
found this video helpful or maybe you'll
learn something don't be like oh my gosh
all these bad things are gonna happen
just because you're traveling doesn't
mean it's gonna be any safer or any more
dangerous than it is back where you're
from so just be prepared and enjoy it I
mean all of these scenarios happen to me
except for the abduction one and kind of
the natural disasters and I still travel
I still love traveling this is life life
sucks sometimes but then life is also
great thank you guys so much for
watching remember to subscribe if you
like my videos you can follow my
Instagram if you want to see pictures
and I will see you next time bye in the
day
I met you I think I'm in myself I don't
ever wanna be with anyone else we got
the kind of story that the stories would
tell different than I've ever felt and I
know we've got our whole lives no ending
this inside