we all love hearing amazing travel
stories and about beautiful places
around the world but what happens when
something goes wrong what if you are
stranded somewhere or you're caught in a
natural disaster maybe you've got all
your stuff stolen you lost your passport
or you've been abducted these might
sound like oh this will never happen but
they do today I'm gonna be talking about
ten different scenarios travel
experiences that I personally had how I
dealt with them how I overcame them and
what I would do differently and giving
you a list of steps on what you should
do in response because we might be the
most prepared travelers maybe we're
expert travelers it doesn't mean we
won't find ourselves in certain
situations because we're human we're not
perfect what do we do when we're in
these situations how do we respond how
do we get through this that's what I'm
gonna be talking about in this video
getting your stuff stolen or worse
robbed if you've been following my
adventures for a while you will know
that my boyfriend and I got all our
stuff stolen when we were back in Mexico
right at the beginning of my travels we
had found this tiny little beach spot
nobody was there I thought I did the
smart thing and I actually hid my bag in
the plant so nobody would see it wasn't
visible to anybody as we're snorkeling
we did see a few people kind of pass
through but every time we'd be looking
and making sure it was okay and nobody
ever headed towards that bag at least
not that I thought and this is where I
think you know maybe these people had
been following us because I don't really
know how they found the bag but they did
and they took everything leaving us
stranded there in just our swimsuits
eventually I just started like flagging
everybody down I got the cops there told
them everything that happened they ended
up taking us back to the police station
because now we had lost the keys to our
vehicle so we couldn't even go anywhere
and there I explained the whole scenario
they wrote down the date and time I got
access to a computer which was really
good because then I could go and contact
everybody that I owned my family and
friends and tell them what had happened
which is very important I also contacted
our Airbnb because if we somehow get off
this island
we're not gonna be able to get into
where we're supposed to sleep at night
so I had sent a message there thankfully
the Airbnb lady had read my messages and
the door was unlocked we got back to our
place so we were able to
get in and have a place to sleep so that
was good but now we're faced with more
issues we have no money and we still had
another week to stay in Mexico I
honestly didn't know what to do at this
point I tried to get my bank card
shipped to us but I had some issues as
my bank and they didn't want to ship it
abroad for starters they wouldn't do it
any quicker was like five to seven
business days and I was like lady I'm
gonna starve in five to seven business
days you can actually wire money via
Western Union and you just need to have
a passport and then they'll give you the
cash and there happened to be a Western
Union in the Walmart if you do not have
your passport then you need to go to the
closest consulate or embassy when you go
there then they will help you to one
getting a new passport and they will
also loan you money if that's what you
need the other thing you need to do
which I messed up on is you need to get
a copy of that police report if you have
that police report you can give it to
the travel insurance and hopefully be
reimbursed for majority or if not
everything that you lost and then also
you need that copy the police report to
give to the Embassy or consulate it's
also a very good idea to keep a copy of
your passport in multiple places so I
have a photo on my phone I have a copy
on my email in case I ever need it and
then my parents have a scanned version
you never know when you're gonna need it
and more so for the consulate you know
you lost your passport you need a new
one you need to prove your citizenship
keep back up cash somewhere in your bag
if you travel with a credit card and a
debit card which I do keep them separate
do not keep them in the same wallet the
next thing I want to talk about is bank
fraud because this has happened to me
actually I think two or three times
since I've been travelling in two and a
half years and it can really ruin your
trip first of all make sure you're
constantly monitoring your transactions
one to help you with budgeting and two
to make sure there's no fraudulent
payments if it does happen first thing
you need to make sure you do is that you
have enough money on you in that
currency of that country to survive do
not call your bank and be like hey
there's fraudulent payments because
they're gonna cancel your card and now
how am I supposed to survive here
everybody's banks different I was able
to get a card sent to me in Romania when
I had bank fraud and they sent it for
free via us
mail took about five to seven business
days no actually at the time I didn't
pull out money so I had to borrow money
and that can be really awkward when
you're in a foreign country and you
don't necessarily know people and you
have to ask people for money to avoid
potential bank fraud make sure you're
going to ATMs that have cameras or that
they're attached to banks that's even
better
if you accidentally leave your card in
the ATM which I've done then you can
actually go to the bank and get it back
and - it's less likely that the actual
ATM is a scam which happens actually
back in bali kuta which is the area
around the airport is known for that and
so they always recommend don't be
pulling out of ATMs in kuta and bali if
you already have don't do that anymore
and actually I think that caused me to
have bank fraud when I was in Bali and
all of a sudden I saw on my bank account
that magically I was in Jakarta never
been did your car - the other thing when
you withdraw money a receipt drops from
the machine make sure you grab that
receipt don't be leaving it on the floor
I constantly see receipts on the floor
and that's not a good idea you don't
know who's watching from afar you don't
know if somebody is somehow gonna get
your PIN number now they've got this
receipt and put two and two together and
I would also avoid like train stations
and subways they also tend to take a
higher fee I mean honestly if you want
to be safe just look up where are the
safe places to pull out money the last
thing I would do is turn your VPN on
well first of all get a VPN I think it's
really important for traveling because
you're using in secure Wi-Fi networks
every time you go to a cafe or hotel or
whatever they could tap into your stuff
and steal your personal information
steal your bank cards my YouTube also
recently crashed out of nowhere I have
no idea why but I'm gonna blame the
Wi-Fi at the cafe I was using like I
don't know I don't I don't understand
computers so much I don't know what
people can do and hack your stuff but
like I don't want to risk it any time
I'm logging onto my bank I turn my VPN
on and I say I'm in the u.s. let's talk
about getting sick I get sick a lot now
first of all it's very important that
you have travel health insurance if you
don't have health insurance and you're
traveling and you get in some serious
health issues you get an accident I
don't know what could happen to you a
lot you might have to go to a hospital
and you're gonna be hit with a hefty
bill I mean I complain about student
loan debt that's gonna kill me but that
doesn't mean that you want to be going
to doctors all the time in all these
foreign countries so I also recommend
there are actually online
Jers are you like callin doctors you can
call them and explain your symptoms and
they can advise you on maybe what's
going on and what medications you should
take it also can tell you if it's worth
spending the money to go to the doctor
which it might not be it's a really easy
way to evaluate what's going on
especially if you're too sick to get out
of bed and you just call the doctor my
boyfriend's family happens to be like
all doctors so it's been really helpful
for us because since I'm always getting
sick I'm always calling his mom or
sister and so I've never needed to
really call the doctor that's because I
have these doctors to call you can also
just go to the pharmacy explain your
symptoms and a lot of times they'll tell
you what you need not always but
sometimes this does work you could try
the local medicine
I've definitely dried some natural
things and I don't know if they worked
but you do what you got to do if you
have stomach issues which can happen a
lot from traveling to foreign countries
especially when you're eating street
food it's delicious it's cheap but damn
it can cause some repercussions you want
to prevent it or want to help it by
yourself probiotics or just eat a lot of
yogurt and whatever foods have
probiotics I'm allergic to dairy so
that's not really an option for me that
would definitely make the situation
worse and then last stay hydrated you
really need to be drinking 2 liters of
water per day minimum
that's half a gallon you should drink
more than that I carry a water bottle at
all times because then I see it and then
I'm more inclined to drink it but
seriously water cures all now what do
you do if you get drugged I'm talking
about this issue because it happens all
over the world
honestly this is gonna be a lot worse if
you're traveling because now you're in a
foreign place you don't exactly know
where to get help you're maybe not
surrounded around people that you know
or feel like you can really trust this
happened to me in the Philippines I
talked about it one of my videos and it
was a horrifying experience but I got
through it mainly because I was with my
friend Jordan when I got drugged I
couldn't walk I couldn't see and my
friend had to take me back to our Airbnb
and I immediately threw up and that was
very good I threw up and then maybe five
minutes later I felt way better and I
didn't feel drugged anymore what I
realized is if you get drugged and you
realized something's wrong because at
that time I knew something was wrong I
was like
never had this experience before and it
escalated really quickly I did at that
time think I was drugged I was like
Jordan I think you need to call the
ambulance I think I should've at that
time honestly forced myself to throw up
and get it out of my system throw up and
drink a lot of water have somebody help
you get home
okay this topic I'm talking about not
that it happened to me but actually
happened to a friend of mine you know
this stuff happens so what do you do how
do you respond how do you get through
this so I'm gonna be sharing her
experience I met this girl right when I
started traveling when I first went to
Costa Rica and I was volunteering at an
organic farm and she was there with me
and she told me this story of when she
had been traveling in Africa with her
friend they had met some guy and they've
been talking for a few hours he was
super cool and he offered them a ride
back to their hotel she was already a
prepared traveler she's been traveling a
lot longer before that and she's
actually even that tour guide so she
runs tours in different countries so
she's prepared okay she's a travel
expert they had been talking to this guy
and thought okay he's really friendly I
mean specifically when you're traveling
alone like you do have to have faith in
humanity and you do need to like be able
to put yourself out there and meet
people and trust people the situation
yeah she shouldn't have gotten in a car
with this guy but she did okay so they
got in the car he was going to the hotel
and all of a sudden he took the wrong
turn he kind of took them to the middle
of nowhere stop the car and then a bunch
of guys jumped into the car with weapons
in their hands they locked it closed all
the windows and started driving and said
we're going to an ATM you need to pull
out money now of course they're in
severe panic mode so my friend she said
she was feeling kind of sick at the time
so she asked the guys can you please
roll down the windows a little bit like
I feel sick I need some air and they
said absolutely not so then she asked
well what about turning down the music
can you turn down the music because it's
hurting my head and this is what she
told me that I thought was very
important to note she said they turned
down the music and that's when I
realized I would be okay
they took them to the ATM she pulled out
all the money the maximum she could pull
out gave it to them and then they left
them on the side of the road now
obviously they did lose the money and it
wasn't the ideal situation but
we're not harmed and she actually did
get all the money back she has a bank
that's awesome or maybe travel insurance
I don't exactly remember she got all the
money back none of them were harmed it's
just more the experience that kind of
you know is scarring a bit you know I
think it's really important to
understand from this situation it is
number one remain calm as calm as you
can
causing more drama and then hitting or
anything can make the situation way
worse so remain calm just do what they
say make sure they're happy give them
the money and really look for those key
signs because she found that sign that
okay they're not gonna hurt us we're
gonna survive she was able to have a
little bit of peace and go about
whatever it is that they wanted she was
able to do it and get through it so
let's just pretend the worst happened
you're in an emergency situation what do
you do when I was in Bali I did
experience one earthquake actually on my
birthday it was the one that hit Lombok
a 6.4 magnitude I met you in the Sun so
my friends come undone cuz I knew you
were the one so we from Paris odd one me
with the letter and Tori
got married