On Saturday night, we provide great tips for trips.
It's time for Battle Trip.
We haven't been able to say hello in a while.
- It's been a while. / - It's so nice to see you.
- I almost forgot your faces. / - I know.
But Sikyung, you released two great songs
while we haven't seen you.
Those of you who know will know
but I recently made my debut in Japan.
- I released my first album there. / - A new start.
I felt so bad for my Korean fans.
- They seemed to hate it. / - Japan...
- Why? / - That I don't even...
Release a song in Korea but
I released an album in Japan.
So I wanted to do something for listeners in Korea.
Good job.
Sook, I assume you were very busy.
I was just working hard like an ant.
- Like a bull. / - I've been working very hard.
For me, without Battle Trip, it's always...
- What do you do? / - "The Return of Superman."
- Your life, you mean. / - Oh, your life.
But I think being a homemaker suits you
because you look so much better now.
Yes.
- I can see you as a homemaker. / - For real.
We haven't met each other in a while.
- So we've been chatting here. / - Yes.
But when it's starting to get cold...
People really enjoy Battle Trip as they can't get out.
- We apologize for not being here. / - I know.
First of all, we do have a travel request today.
Yes, we do.
- Let's see the request. / - Let's see.
Hello. My name is Shin Nayeon, I'm 21
and I'm a university student who loves to travel.
I've been to Taiwan, Hong Kong, China, Japan,
Vietnam and mostly countries close to Korea.
Among those, I've always wanted to revisit
Taiwan and Hong Kong.
I am trying to figure out which country to go to.
Other than already famous tourist spots
in Taiwan and Hong Kong,
I hope Battle Trip can introduce sites that are
not well-known in Taiwan and Hong Kong.
Before we split teams.
Taiwan or Hong Kong? 1, 2, 3.
Hong Kong.
Taiwan.
Taiwan or Hong Kong? 1, 2, 3.
- It's 2 to 1. / - I've never been to Taiwan.
- Me neither. / - I've been to both.
- Really? / - Yes, I've been to both.
I will be honest. Hong Kong suits me better.
The drinks and food suit me better.
- Really? / - Yes. It's like that.
- For me... / - Haven't you been to both?
- I haven't been to Taiwan. / - Me neither.
I've always wanted to go to Taiwan
but I haven't been able to.
People say Taiwan feels more like China.
Yes, compared to Hong Kong, that's true.
So I think the food will suit me better.
Battle Trip has gone to Taiwan and Hong Kong...
- Twice already. / - Yes.
- A movie trip to HK. / - With Hong Seokcheon.
- And Hwangbo went as well. / - Hwangbo went.
- She lived there. / - She acted as a tour guide.
- Our BTOB friends went to Taiwan. / - Yes.
And Ji Sangryeol and Kim Jongmin went too.
They lost so miserably.
- They really lost. / - Yes.
And Kim Shinyeong and Shin Dong
had so many great meals there.
- Right. / - Yes.
Hong Kong and Taiwan feel fairly close to us
but these guests found new sides to both countries.
Let's bring in our trip designers.
There's so much to do here.
Can we just have fun then?
Amazing!
Let's go!
It's like Hong Kong but not like Hong Kong.
Look forward to it.
- Yong Kong / - Byul Kong.
Kong, kong, kong.
Kong, kong, kong!
This is MAMAMOO's Solar and Moon Byul
who went to Hong Kong.
Welcome.
- 2, 3. / - Hello.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
- Byul Kong. / - Yong Kong.
- Moon and... / - Sunlight.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
Hong Kong!
Battle Trip!
I thought they were speaking Cantonese.
- It was so long. / - At the end...
They even harmonized.
- Really? / - We came up with it earlier.
- It's because they are MAMAMOO. / - I see.
I heard that Solar acted as the tour guide this time.
- The older member. / - Yes.
Actually, my dream was to become a travel guide.
- My gosh. / - So...
Now I'm a singer
but through this opportunity,
I could properly act as a travel guide.
- Really? / - Yes.
Usually, people who want to be travel guides
have lived abroad for a long time.
Or people who really like to travel.
I love to travel.
Where do you want to be a travel guide?
In Korea.
- A travel guide for foreigners? / - Yes.
- Something like that? / - Yes.
She must've done really well.
But you two have a lot on your shoulders
because they don't want a predictable trip.
The request was for an intermediate travel course.
We've already been there twice so there's pressure.
When many people think of Hong Kong,
after they get out of the airport,
they go to Hong Kong Island first for their trip.
Hong Kong Island.
Yes, but we spent 3 days and 2 nights
in Lantau Island.
- Lantau Island? / - Yes.
- I've never heard of it. / - It's unfamiliar.
If you look at the places we went to,
you'll be surprised that it's actually Hong Kong.
That's how I felt.
I'm so curious. Shall we hurry and see?
Then let's shout the tour name and take off.
- The tour name is so hard. / - Can you say it again?
- Do it one more time. / - Until the end.
- You have to harmonize too. / - Say, "Let's go" too.
- Until "let's go?" / - Yes.
Start.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
- Byul Kong. / - Yong Kong.
- Moon and... / - Sunlight.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
Hong Kong!
Battle Trip! Let's go!
You guys are so good.
Yeah.
They're so excited.
- My gosh. / - They're not drunk.
- We're finally here. / - Yes, finally...
We're going.
(MAMAMOO is such an enthusiastic group)
Oh, my eyes.
(Solar, real name is Kim Yongseon, in charge of fun)
What's the record?
(Moon Byul is a fun and quirky girl)
- This feels so unfamiliar. / - What did you bring?
This is our...
Travel destination.
Hong Kong.
These are all information on Hong Kong.
She's definitely very serious about her role.
She studied a lot for the trip.
Moon Byul, have you been to Hong Kong?
I've been there for a fan meeting and for work.
I didn't get to look around.
I'm thinking about being the tour guide
for this trip.
My dream used to be a travel guide.
Can I look forward to it?
- You can look forward to it. / - Okay.
So we're going to Hong Kong
for this trip.
The program has been to Hong Kong twice before.
- Already. / - At Battle Trip?
Yes.
So the viewers may be tired of
seeing Hong Kong again on this program.
- But there's nothing to be worried about. / - Why?
People will expect to see the famous night view
and buildings.
- Right. / - Hong Kong is famous for that.
That's what you expect when you think of Hong Kong.
People usually think of shopping and such.
And all those sites are focused on Hong Kong Island.
So here... Wow... They're so much to do there.
Shouldn't we visit here then?
- It's urban... / - We're not going there.
- We're not going there. / - Why?
We're going the opposite way.
- We're going to Lantau Island. / - Lantau Island.
I've never heard of Lantau Island.
(This is the Hong Kong we commonly know)
(Battle Trip has gone to Hong Kong twice)
Are you ready?
Everyone!
Come with us to Hong Kong.
Let's go!
This really doesn't feel like Hong Kong.
It's no joke.
It's bigger than my face.
- What was that earlier? / - Was that squid?
- It's squid. / - A king squid.
- For Hong Kong. / - Hong Kong.
(It's unpredictable)
Mickey, Mickey!
Oh, my eyes.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
Hong Kong, kong, kong.
Kong, kong, kong.
We're heading to Lantau Island.
You prepared so much.
- Right? / - Yes.
This is where we take the cable car.
She's continuing to search and study?
I looked up a lot.
This is really good because
you see as much as you know.
- You're right. / - You see as much as you studied.
I'm looking around places to go.
You're so obsessed with Battle Trip.
If we want to win,
I have to study this much.
I have complete faith in you.
(Their excitement explodes)
That's normal, right?
Let's go!
I can't reach.
You can do it. Stretch your arms.
Don't you get that excited when the date is set?
- Yes. / - Especially the day before leaving, right?
Usually, you can't sleep the night before
because you're so excited.
(First day, Disneyland)
(Second day, Ngong Ping Village, local food, cafe)
(Incheon International Airport)
(Takes 3.5 hours to Hong Kong)
It's Hong Kong!
Hong Kong!
There's no one here.
We're at Hong Kong!
We're here.
We have to go travel now
so I prepared this.
- You know I'll guide this tour. / - Yes.
- What's that? / - Look here.
No way...
You bought that?
No, I had this at home.
That's what the drill sergeants use.
You're right.
You bought this?
No, I had this at home.
It's buzzing.
Just a minute.
She's right beside you, you don't need a mic.
This is welcoming us to Hong Kong?
You have to hit it when it's not working.
It's working now. I have to hit it to make it work.
- Now... / - Where do we go now?
This is the place you wanted to go.
- I really wanted to go too. / - Our outfits...
Is it where you think?
- The perfect place for our outfit? / - High-five.
Today, we're going to...
- Disneyland! / - Let's go.
What was that pose?
- We have to get on a train. / - What?
- Train. / - Yes, train.
- Follow me, Moon Byul. / - I'm coming.
The sparrow goes...
(Sunny Bay Station, 10 minutes from the airport)
(Sunny Bay Station)
(There's a special train that goes to Disneyland?)
- We're here to take the train. / - Yes.
I'll tell you the details when it comes.
It's here!
This is it! It's the Mickey train.
- It's so cute. / - What is that?
- Mickey Mouse? / - Yes, Mickey Mouse.
It's so cute.
- Really? / - It's only at Sunny Bay.
- Mickey! / - Let's get on.
The train is so cute.
- Even the handles! / - So cute, right?
That's so cute.
- That's in the train? / - Yes.
I was so amazed how everything was Disney.
This is amazing.
- I feel like a kid again. / - Yes.
- What was this called again? / - Look at the handles.
It's Mickey.
- Look at that. / - It's cute.
- It will take only 3 minutes. / - Really?
- It's really close. / - Because it needs to travel back.
- It's only one station? / - Yes.
(While they laughed and chatted, they have arrived)
We're here.
My goodness. We're here.
We're in Disneyland.
Disneyland.
(Hong Kong Disneyland is located in Lantau Island)
(Opened in 2005, it's the 5th Disneyland in the world)
They even have Iron Man.
(They have various attractions)
There must be a lot of things to take pictures of.
There were so many.
I'd better pay extra attention to Hong Kong.
We're now at the ticket office.
I already bought our tickets and printed them out
in Korea.
- Thank you. Bye. / - Thank you.
I think we should do something like...
- You know? / - To fit in here?
We need some styling.
(Where are Moon Byul and Solar headed to?)
♪ Let's get going, full of excitement ♪
- Gosh, look at that hat. / - It's Mickey.
- Solar, look at this. / - Mickey is everywhere.
(The shop is full of cute souvenirs)
There's so much there.
(Impressed)
I want to try this on.
Isn't it supposed to be the other way?
You have to wear those over there.
- You need to. / - You're right.
You should try this on.
- It looks cute on her. / - How do I look?
Children would love this place.
There are so many things to buy.
Open it.
It's...
That's incredible.
Oh, my eyes.
What are you doing?
(Check out Solar and Moon Byul's fashion right now)
I'm so curious as to what they bought.
(On one sunny day)
(Solar and Moon Byul show up on the street)
It looks good on her.
I have a Mickey watch and Mickey earrings....
- Mickey earrings. / - Really?
That was funny how you revealed the watch.
We don't have that in Korea.
- They're both good. / - They're good.
- Seriously. / - The items look good on them.
A lot of people were watching us.
They don't even come near you.
You both look great though.
(They try their best)
This is what you call fashion.
Now let's go.
Mickey, let's go.
(They seem very happy all dressed up)
What?
- We're dressed up. / - Okay.
Shall we go meet the real Mickey?
- Mickey. / - Mickey, where are you?
- He must be over there. / - Let's go.
(It's crowded here)
Why are there so many people?
For photos?
Yes, to take photos with Mickey Mouse.
So many people were lined up.
We lined up as well.
To take pictures, we need to stand in the line.
- Are you sure it's here? / - Yes.
- It's over there. / - This is the queue.
Like this.
- Mickey and Minnie, wait there. / - Okay.
Did you have to wait long?
We had to wait for ages.
The queue doesn't seem to get any shorter.
- This queue is so long. / - I'm sweating so much.
There are two groups left.
We can finally meet Mickey and Minnie soon.
Mickey, Minnie, wait for us.
Hi!
- She sounds excited. / - Hello.
- Solar seems happy. / - Oh, my God.
- They seem excited too. / - Hi.
1, 2, 3.
I'd like to take pictures with them too.
(They met Mickey and Minnie Mouse in person)
(Where are they headed now?)
Isn't this it?
I think this is it. It's the roller coaster.
- It seems so. / - But...
I don't think it's as scary as we thought.
It didn't look so scary?
(It's a roller coaster in an American Western village)
(The most popular attraction in the theme park)
Isn't it pretty gentle?
We are not so good with scary rides.
We were quite scared.
This is how I go on rides.
Solar, I do this.
I always do this.
Even if it does an upside down turn,
I ride like this.
She looks obviously nervous.
What's wrong with your heart? It's beating so fast.
♪ Bounce, bounce ♪
She just can't stop.
It's just the start.
- The others are so calm. / - I can't ride that.
(The roller coaster is slowly climbing to the top)
The weather is nice.
(Relaxed)
- I'm scared. / - There's...
- A surprise here. / - There's a surprise.
What?
- It must've been scary. / - It wasn't that scary...
Until it suddenly started moving backwards.
Why is it moving backwards?
- Why is it moving backwards? / - Are you smiling?
Or are you crying? Which is it?
Look at them.
- Your mouth is wide open. / - Was I like that?
I was so surprised.
- What? / - What's going on?
It goes back and forth.
Solar's face is the most terrifying thing here.
It was so scary.
They are so loud. All the others are doing this.
The front seats are the least scariest.
(The roller coaster speeds up out of the cave)
(Moon Byul's face is hidden)
Oh, my...
At least she closed her mouth now.
(Glancing)
You're angry there, right, Sola?
It was pretty scary.
People are clapping and are all happy.
(Blank)
- My throat hurts. / - I'm dizzy.
Solar, where did all your joy go?
- Was it really scary? / - It was.
What's over there?
- Where? / - It must be "Toy Story."
It looks amazing.
A full day must not be enough there.
- It was huge. / - It was indeed.
One should enter the park as soon as it opens.
I feel like I'm in the toy world.
I feel like I'm back in my childhood.
Even the toilet is made of toys.
- Look at this. / - It's really well made.
Everything is made of toys. Come and have a look.
- I have Woody at home. / - Woody.
Woody.
- She just calls his name out. / - Woody.
You're posing.
Woody.
Woody is so cute.
(Toy Story land seems peaceful)
(Screaming)
What happened?
(Toy Story land seems peaceful)
(Screaming)
My gosh. What's that?
- But that doesn't look so scary. / - This one was...
It went so high up.
Solar, your mouth is so big.
(Her mouth is wide open again)
That one doesn't look so scary though.
This one was scarier.
- I'll lose your voice. / - I lost my voice that day.
(They noisily finished enjoying all the attractions)
- What an amazing sound. / - Sounded like a dentist.
- I'm getting hungry. / - I'm very hungry now.
Shall we go eat now? Where should we go?
Which restaurant should we go?
Where should we go?
How about...
Let's have a look over there. I see a menu.
Alright. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
I wonder what they sell.
The visuals and details are different.
- If you look... / - Really?
Food is here!
It's food.
We're finally having food.
The visuals...
It's a Mickey Mouse pizza.
That's so cruel.
So you're eating his face?
- From the ear. / - Starting with the ear.
(Rice topped with pork, $19)
(Mickey Mouse pizza, $18)
There's Italian, Thai...
- Lots of international dishes. / - Really?
- We just have to charge on. / - Okay.
Let me cut it.
It's somewhat cruel.
It's quite big.
- Let me taste one ear. / - Let's try it.
- To Hong Kong. / - Cheers.
To Hong Kong.
It's good.
- It was really good. / - Yes, it was very tasty.
I like that the dough is thin.
It's like chips.
It's so crispy.
It's tasty.
It's somewhat
cruel though.
We were complimenting on how cute...
- Mickey's ears are. / - That's so funny.
And we just cut them.
We're so into Mickey today.
(Rice topped with pork is tasty as well)
Is that rice?
It was risotto.
Both the dishes were tasty.
- It was a good restaurant. / - Yes, it was.
How is it?
- It's good. / - I want to try it too.
(She takes a big bite)
- I was worried... / - It's so tasty.
- That the food wouldn't be good. / - Me too.
But it's good.
All the dishes are tasty.
(They gobble up the food)
- It looks really tasty. / - It looks tasty.
- It wasn't there before. / - What? Only in Hong Kong?
The theme seems to be space.
That, that, that, that!
Iron Man.
Make sure you get the fast pass.
- Did you get them? / - Yes.
We got them when we checked in.
With them, you don't need to queue.
We checked in at the hotel
before we begin our trip.
Is the hotel in the park?
- Yes. / - Yes.
- Check in. / - Here it is.
Some information cards.
Very pretty card.
It's a little expensive
but it gives you a lot of benefits.
- I see. / - Fast pass tickets.
It includes the free pass tickets including the resort?
Yes, I thought one day of luxury was good.
Free pass tickets are already costly.
Thank you.
(This is the only place one can meet Iron Man)
It looks amazing.
What is that?
Even adult men would love that place.
Let's go meet Iron Man.
He's putting on his suit now.
He's waiting for us now.
I was good at this when I was in high school.
On the bars, right?
I'm so excited to see Iron Man.
You two seem to really get along.
My goodness.
(Staying alert)
Iron Man!
- Iron Man. / - Where are you?
- This must be his base. / - This is his base.
Let's watch.
It's not just for children.
- I'd like to go there too. / - Looking like that...
Let's go save Hong Kong.
It's from Iron Man's perspective.
Yes, it was really fun.
Being 3D, imagine how immersive it'd be.
(Seems like they're still being attacked)
No! No!
We were avoiding the enemies.
Hong Kong is safe now.
It's safe.
- This is... / - This is where we can see Iron Man.
- This is... / - And take photos.
I recommend this place so much.
You guys ready?
- Yeah. / - Yeah, perfect.
What's going on?
(Where is he?)
(Iron Man is landing)
- He comes down? / - Iron Man!
Yes, you can really see the silhouette landing.
Iron Man!
I got goose bumps.
Iron Man.
- Goose bumps.  / - It was cool. It was really cool.
I seriously got goose bumps.
Seoeon and Seojun would love this, wouldn't they?
- It would be more than that. / - Right?
It'd be like their birthday.
You should go there once.
You look very hot.
Iron Man, I'm so happy.
Standing here talking to Iron Man
and your answer wasn't awesome?
Okay, I'll try not to be offended.
- Yeah. / - Yep, take it easy.
Do you know MAMAMOO?
Yes.
What?
It's Robert Downey Jr.'s voice.
He was talking in that voice.
Yes, we could actually communicate with him.
- Really? / - Yes.
Search.
You should search.
Yeah.
Search MAMAMOO.
- Okay. / - Okay?
Absolutely.
Iron Man seems to be flustered.
- He's surprised. / - Yes.
Thanks to you, Hong Kong is safe.
Thank you for saving Hong Kong.
Thank you.
(They took pictures with the Iron Man)
It's like he's grabbing you saying,
"Please pipe down and just take the photo."
- Iron Man looks a little tired. / - He does, right?
We ran into Star Wars characters as well.
That's nice.
You took a lot of nice pictures.
Yes, we were so happy.
Awesome.
Then we went to watch "Lion King."
That sounds fun.
I feel like we're suddenly in nature.
Seriously, there are a lot of themes.
This place is huge.
What should we...
- It's really huge here. / - I'm confused.
We should...
It seems like there's a Korean guide as well.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Do you speak Korean?
I'm a guide who can speak Korean.
Is she from Hong Kong?
- Yes. / - Yes.
We would like to
watch "Lion King."
But we don't know where it is.
You can go straight this way.
- This way? / - This way?
Your Korean is really good.
- You speak Korean very well. / - Thank you.
I'm somehow happy and touched.
I'm happy to meet someone who speaks Korean.
Just seeing Korean writing overseas makes you happy.
- Thank you. / - Have a nice day.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
- This way? / - Yes.
It must feel weird to hear that kind of
Korean greeting from a foreigner.
- Thank you. / - You must have felt relieved.
I'm so glad that we met her.
I was very happy.
This is where "Lion King" takes place.
A lion is welcoming us.
Hello, lion.
Lion.
Lion King.
- It looks fun. / - I want to be there too.
It was amazing.
- It was fascinating. / - Was it like a musical?
- Yes. / - Yes.
It's beginning.
It's a live performance.
I told you it looked like a live performance.
You didn't hear me, did you?
I thought it wouldn't be.
It looks fabulous.
I got goose bumps.
(This show is particularly popular among Koreans)
(You can enjoy acrobatics as well)
I get goose bumps even by watching it on screen.
It was real fire...
They kept spinning on both sides.
(Simba regains peace and the show ends happily)
- Hi. / - Hello.
(The performance ends with high-fives from the actors)
I recommend you sit right in the front.
You can high-five with the actors there.
- You can connect with the actors. / - That's right.
It looks amazing.
It's time to eat something.
Tell me how hungry you are.
Okay. You're very hungry.
- Could you hear me? / - Yes.
Let's go eat something.
Let's eat something and...
I heard there will be a night parade here later.
It's so beautiful.
You shouldn't miss that.
- It's so cute. / - This is the highlight.
- It's a must. / - I love you!
I love you!
- Hello. / - Hello.
I love you! Yeah!
They looked at us!
They pointed at my hairband.
After we eat something, it will be the perfect time
to watch the parade.
Should we go over there?
- Okay. Let's go. / - Let's go and fill our stomachs.
Okay.
- It looks nice. / - This place looks nice.
We're going to eat something special today.
What is it?
Battle Trip has been to Hong Kong many times.
Right.
When you go to Hong Kong, you eat dim sum.
They had dim sum every time.
But there's something special about our dim sum.
The dim sum we're having
is not normal dim sum.
- Does it look like Mickey Mouse? / - It's different.
It's very unique.
It's here.
Their reactions are so good.
- What is it? / - I was very surprised.
- What is it? / - It's Olaf!
It's Olaf.
They made Olaf with dim sum?
- They were all characters. / - There was Baymax.
That's amazing.
- Isn't it so pretty? / - Kids will love it.
They'll be excited to see that.
(Little Green Men bun, $12)
(You can only enjoy this special dim sum here)
It's a lunch menu
but they cooked it especially for us for dinner.
If you're watching this on TV,
remember you can only have this at lunch.
How would you eat it though?
- It's so pretty. / - It was too cute to eat.
Do you want to try this Olaf?
Olaf?
How do we eat it?
How do we?
Just grab him.
He's staring at me. How can I eat him?
Then eat his eyes first.
It's red bean.
Gosh, look at this.
What's that?
Is it okay to air this? Isn't it too cruel?
What's this?
It's okay.
It's good.
I like the red bean.
- Me too. / - It tastes like steamed bun.
But this one looks a lot cuter.
- So visually it tastes better. / - It really is cute.
And it's good.
This one smells different. It's Star Wars.
(Star Wars bun, $9.70)
Can you eat this? Don't you feel sorry?
You bit off the head first.
That's right. This is manju.
It has nuts in it.
- It tastes like cinnamon. / - Right.
- It smells like cinnamon. / - That looks good.
It looks delicious.
It's crispy on the outside. When you take a bite..
It's crispy like cookies
but then it goes like this in your mouth...
You should show us.
It's really fun to eat them.
- It's hard to explain. / - Since each ones different.
Okay. It's in your mouth.
(Melting)
It's still there? It's not melting.
The dim sums look so cute.
What is this?
It's from "Big Hero 6."
- "Hello, I'm Baymax." / - Oh, "Big Hero 6."
- It's so cute. / - Baymax.
- I didn't know Baymax was so small. / - It's cute.
Baymax is pretty big in the movie.
He blows up, like this.
I'm sorry but I have to eat you. I'm sorry.
You might as well not say that.
This one tastes good.
It has nuts and meat in it.
- Like... / - It tastes like dumplings.
- It tastes like that. / - It tastes just like dumplings.
It's very detailed.
(What does this one taste like?)
It tastes like a dumpling.
This is good.
This is really good.
- It has meat and vegetables in it... / - You're right.
This is actual dumpling filling.
(The special dim sum pleases their eyes and mouths)
I don't think I'll order it unless I become a father.
We'll enjoy it with the babies.
Thank you.
- This is... / - This is suckling pig.
It's really good.
- I love it. / - It's great.
Is this a course meal?
I love that.
Look at the carrot.
The carrot is Mickey.
Oh, my. Oh, my.
Such details.
(Cute)
It smells like chips.
It goes really well with rice.
I can eat it forever.
- Is it good? / - It was amazing.
It's like chips on the top.
Right. It's very crispy.
- It's soft. / - That's so delicious.
- It's crispy on the outside. / - This is really good.
And it's soft inside.
- It looks like bread crusts. / - It's so soft.
- That'd be so good. / - Looks so good.
It's savory like scorched rice.
It's good.
- When you flip it over... / - That's good in Hong Kong.
- It's like... / - It's very tender inside.
It's really tender.
It feels like...
Everything is good.
- But we should eat rice. / - Right.
- Should we order a rice dish? / - Sounds good.
Excuse me.
Do you have rice?
- Rice? / - Rice.
Okay. Steamed rice?
No.
- Mixed... / - Fried rice?
- Yes. Fried. / - Fried rice.
Okay. Anything else?
No, thanks.
That was just appropriate. "No, thanks."
"No, thanks."
- Your English is good. / - Right?
I was good, right?
I didn't know you'd say, "No, thanks."
- People usually just say no. / - That's right.
Thank you.
(Chinese-style fried rice with scallops, $27)
- Hong Kong's fried rice is true fried rice. / - Right.
It was really good.
Is this anchovy?
It's anchovy and egg.
I think that's what's in it.
I wish they had kimchi here.
That'd be nice.
We just love kimchi.
Everything is good.
With something more...
It could be the perfect dinner.
Really?
You want?
- Without kimchi... / - Say, "Kimchi please."
No way.
- Pray for it. Kimchi please. / - To who?
Kimchi please.
I've heard your prayers.
"I've heard your prayers."
(Dreams do come true)
I brought it from Korea.
What was that?
- I brought kimchi. / - Really?
You're the best.
No joke.
We can't go on a trip without this.
We can't be happy without it.
It's kimchi in a can.
I'll grab one.
This is kimchi.
(Packed with food)
Are you going on a camp?
Is it stir-fried kimchi?
- You asked for permission, right? / - Yes.
Koreans need their kimchi.
- This is amazing. / - It was really good.
It's game over with kimchi.
- It was amazing. / - Fried rice with kimchi is the best.
Now it feels complete.
Yeah.
(It's not fancy but it's filling)
I'm so full.
- I really enjoyed it. / - You ate it all?
- You ate almost everything. / - We ate so well.
What's wrong, captain?
I like this watch.
- It's cute. / - We need to go see the parade.
What time does it start?
- The parade? / - Yeah.
Now.
- Right now. / - Aren't we late?
Wake them up. Wake up, guys.
- Wake up. / - Wake up.
We enjoyed dinner.
Don't embarrass me tonight.
Don't attract people's attention.
I'm so embarrassed.
- Let's go. / - Okay.
It was really good.
You two are like some...
You're like a comedy duo.
Watching them feels like watching comedian juniors.
(Night has fallen over Disneyland)
- This is the thing you must watch? / - Yes.
Everyone returns to their childhood.
Wow.
(Everyone has been waiting for this moment)
- All the characters must appear. / - Yeah, wow.
(Night parade)
Isn't that the Monsters, Inc. Right?
He's DJ-ing.
He was DJ-ing.
It was so cute.
So cute.
(Scream!)
(So much excitement)
Like this.
- Look at that. / - The Little Mermaid!
The Little Mermaid.
- She looks so splendid. / - She was so pretty.
Hello!
Hello.
Under the sea!
♪ Under the sea ♪
Under the sea.
It's Toy Story!
- Hey! / - I watched the movie!
(Men and women of all ages enjoy the parade)
- It must be entrancing. / - Really.
- You're so pretty! / - Pretty!
Pretty!
- Minnie will be here soon. / - Wait.
Let's get ready.
Mickey and Minnie are the main characters.
- Let's get ready. / - Let's get ready.
- Here they come. / - We can't lose.
Our rivals. Mickey.
- You have to get this on video. / - I love you.
I love you! Yes!
- She looked at us. / - She saw this.
They can't miss you.
Both of you are so loud.
Mickey!
Here!
Gosh. My throat.
- Minnie looked at us. / - Yes.
- She said we were cute. / - That's right.
- We were successful. / - We're successful fans.
We're successful fans.
We're a success.
- Nice. / - We succeeded.
- Was that the last thing today? / - Time for bed now.
- Okay. / - We did it.
- Let's go. / - Yong Kong.
Byul Kong. Hong Kong!
Kong, kong, kong.
Battle Trip!
(It was a wonderful first day in Hong Kong)
- They visited Disneyland. / - That was good.
First of all, the train
makes you get excited from the start.
- The train itself. / - Right.
That was great.
It was very close and had a lot of benefits.
You're tired at the end of the day
and the resort is right there.
So you can just go and sleep.
- It was so convenient. / - Such a great course.
- It was so great. / - Without moving around too much.
As I watched your day...
I was wondering when to go.
- When would be the best weather? / - Really?
- I worried about those things. / - For your kids?
Yes, because when I went to Tokyo,
I was there for 3 days and 2 nights.
And that wasn't enough to see everything.
- You couldn't, right? / - Because...
You have to wait an hour to get on a ride.
That's standard.
But had I known,
I would've stayed at the hotel in the park.
If I'd known about the fast pass.
But I didn't know.
When I go there next time, I'll stay in that hotel.
- Because of the benefits. / - Why will you go there?
- What? / - Why?
I feel like I should at least once in my lifetime.
Would you like to come with us?
- With my family. / - What? No. I'll go by myself.
For the first half, we watched the Disneyland.
I wonder where they went in the latter half.
I'm looking forward to it.
- Moon Byul, what comes next? / - In the first half...
You saw a lot of flashy things in Disneyland.
Yes, the fancy side.
Now you'll get to see the lungs of Hong Kong.
Ah.
You'll get to see the beauty...
- Of Lantau Island. / - Sounds good.
Let's check out the latter half of the trip.
Here's the latter half.
(The morning is announced by... A beast?)
(This is MAMAMOO's charismatic rapper)
(Moon-star's charming in the morning)
Who is that?
She'll transform soon.
(Her mission is to wake up Solar)
Yongseon.
It's time to get up.
(Solar is up)
It's cold.
I'll close the door.
Joking around as soon as you wake up.
Say, "Please open the door."
(Please open the door)
Where are we going today?
Somewhere new.
What was that? You're yawning like you're bored.
It's just too early.
Don't jump for joy because you're too excited.
How joyful. They used up all their energy...
- Had a good sleep. / - Right.
Then wake up and expend energy again.
- Start the day energetically. / - That's Solar.
It's a breakfast buffet.
- Does it include breakfast? / - Yes.
- There was so much to eat. / - There was.
I love this.
(They put a lot on their plates)
There's so much variety.
Everything is Mickey Mouse here.
You're right.
Let's eat his ear first.
(Chomp)
His ear is missing.
You're cruel.
He looks unbalanced. Shall I eat the other one too?
(You're such a cruel person)
(They don't stop eating)
Breakfast is delicious.
I hear Mickey Mouse walks around in here.
He's over there now.
He's super popular.
- They're dressed up today. / - Yes.
Will they come here?
I don't think so.
Shall I call them over?
Mickey Mouse and Minnie Mouse
take pictures with you.
Hi.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's do hip hop.
- We lined up to take a picture. / - We did.
- Did you? / - After you had breakfast?
- Yes. / - After breakfast.
The line was short because it was in the morning.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Thank you.
(Moon Byul kisses Minnie on the nose)
- He's a boy. / - It felt weird.
- Let's change. / - Thank you.
- Thank you. / - Nose.
(Moon Byul kisses Mickey too)
- Thank you. / - It feels weird.
- Thank you. Bye-bye. / - Bye.
His leg.
So cute.
(See you next time!)
That's nice.
(Spectacular)
(New Hong Kong)
Are you ready?
It's a part of Hong Kong that
doesn't seem like Hong Kong.
What's that?
This is the start.
This isn't the Hong Kong I know.
There's so much nature.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
Hong Kong!
That's nice.
(Day 2 in Lantau Island)
(Ngong Ping Village)
(40 minutes to Tung Chung Station from Disneyland)
Okay.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
- Yong Kong. / - Moon and...
Sunlight.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
Hong Kong.
(They're super excited)
(Congratulations on your 2nd day in Hong Kong)
(Why are they doing that?)
Applause please.
I have lots of equipment for today.
- A lot... / - Can you hear me, Moon Byul?
(Flag, loudspeaker mic, guide book)
- Do you know where we are going? / - Where?
We are going to...
Ngong Ping Village!
After Disneyland, we'll go down.
And we'll find Ngong Ping Village down here.
There's Ngong Ping Village.
They transformed a region into a village.
They have an enormous
bronze Buddha statue there.
- Are we going to see that? / - It's on the way to...
Ngong Ping Village.
We have to ride a cable car there.
- You like cable cars, right? / - Yes, I do.
(Cable car)
Cable car.
- 30 minutes? / - It takes 30 minutes?
- It's a really long ride. / - It takes 30 minutes?
Gosh, it's one of top 10 cable cars in the world.
- 5.7km. / - It's the longest in Asia.
(A mini theme park at the end of the cable car)
- It's a big island. / - Wow, what's that?
That's the Tian Tan Buddha.
- Is it on top of a mountain? / - Yes.
How did they make that with bronze?
You need to get a ticket to ride the cable car.
Did you buy it?
Of course. If you buy it online,
you don't have to line up.
With this ticket, you can ride the cable car.
Also you get unlimited bus rides
and boat rides.
It's 5.7m long.
- You mean km. / - Right. I'm sorry.
It's 5.7km. I forgot the K.
That makes a huge difference.
There are two types. Standard and crystal.
- They're the cable cars. / - What's the difference?
Standard is just standard.
Crystal is luxurious.
So we chose the crystal cabin.
- I see. / - Because it's our only trip.
I prepared something special.
Let's go.
Yong Kong, Byul Kong, Hong Kong.
(Let's start the Solar tour)
We're going to skip this line.
This is nice. If you buy the ticket in Korea...
- You don't have to wait in line, right? / - That's right.
Let's go.
Hello.
Okay.
Oh, yeah. Come on.
(Luxurious crystal cable car)
Please sit down.
This is amazing.
Be careful.
Now for 5.7km...
Welcome to the crystal cable car.
- It's like a ride. / - Yong Kong, Byul Kong, Hong Kong.
Welcome, everyone.
You would make a great tour guide.
It was so much fun.
The door has closed.
It means we're going to leave.
Let's go.
- It's fast. / - Wow.
Wow, check out the floor.
Oh, my.
- Wow. / - I got goose bumps.
The guide is scared so she's not saying anything.
Why won't you look at the floor?
It was scary.
The floor is awesome.
The ocean is emerald color.
Let's take a picture.
Can you sit down?
- Here? / - Yes.
Why don't you sit first?
Me? I can do it.
Wow...
It feels so close.
- From here... / - This is amazing.
- Wait... / - The angle...
(Taking pictures on the cable car floor)
Wow.
It looks like you're floating on air.
We can't capture...
Everything properly in the photo.
- It's... / - You're really bad at taking photos.
- How could you take it like that? / - Yes.
- Your torso looks huge. / - I know.
It's like I'm sitting on the ocean.
- Come forward. / - That's right.
It looks like computer graphics.
Should I sit like this?
Think of it as a core workout.
2, 3.
How did the photo turn out?
You can see a lot of the ocean.
- It looks like you're floating. / - Oh, oh.
Good photo, right? This is how you take photos.
Aren't the photos similar?
You have to lie down and take a selfie there.
The floor and the sides are
all made of glass.
It helps you enjoy the natural landscape.
(Today's destination)
- This is the Ngong Ping Village. / - We're here.
- There's a lot of people. / - Wait a minute.
- Why? / - I need to plug the mic in.
Let me test the mic.
Okay, it's working.
If you look to your right...
That's so big.
Can you see that? It's a giant Buddha statue.
That's where we're going.
Are you going to walk there?
Yes, it's close.
(Ngong Ping Village)
(A 15,000m² man-made village on Lantau Peak)
(Souvenir shops, restaurants and other amenities)
(It's connected to Ngong Ping cable car's last stop)
- There's also a tour guide here. / - Yes.
Hi.
That's the tour guide pride.
(Moon Byul's camera)
Puppy.
He's walking over there.
- What is that? / - What is that?
Cows wander around here.
Really?
(You can see animals roaming freely)
We've arrived at the Tian Tan Buddha.
Drum roll.
It's the biggest bronze statue of Buddha in the world.
It's so much higher.
There's a lot to see.
This is nice.
It weighs 202 tons.
- It was really big. / - It was really big.
Let me explain.
They call this place the Tian Tan.
If you stand in the middle and talk,
it will echo.
- Why? / - It echoes. Do you hear it?
I don't know. I didn't hear it.
It's echoing.
Wait a minute.
- It doesn't echo from here. / - Can you hear it?
- Yes. / - It's echoing.
I can hear echoes.
- This is awesome. / - Isn't it because of the mic?
This is so awesome.
- Try it here. / - You need to do it here.
Ah. You need to do it here.
It only echoes in the very middle.
This sound is from the mic.
You should turn the mic off first.
It feels like this.
- Yes, to explain it. / - I'm trying to explain it.
Over here it's normal. But here...
Ah. It really echoes!
It's really interesting.
Let me explain.
There are 268 stairs.
In Cantonese, 2 means "easy."
6 means "continues."
And 8 means "wealth."
So it means you'll get good fortune here.
- Do you want to run the stairs? / - No...
I don't want to waste my energy like that.
- Get ready. / - Ready.
How long will they be able to run?
She was so confident that we'd run to the top.
Wouldn't they get tired halfway?
Ready.
Set. Go.
You can't do two steps at a time.
One step at a time.
Why are you doing two steps at a time?
(Her desperate hand is flailing)
You can tell who's older.
I can tell from this.
- Is she already tired? / - She wanted to make a bet.
What are you doing?
Moon Byul really climbed up high.
I'm done.
- Yongseon. / - Moon Byul's stamina is amazing.
What's that?
You're the guide.
Solar, you wanted to do it first.
This is the first time seeing her frown.
She was always so bright.
This is amazing.
It's really big.
- So big. / - Super awesome.
(It's more magnificent from up close)
When you see nature like this...
It's magnificent but sometimes scary.
Why?
Because nature is so grand.
I think that's why it's sometimes scary.
(Day 2 of Lantau Island)
(Enjoy Hong Kong local cuisine)
Hong Kong local cuisine.
- We're going to another place. / - Where?
Where are we going?
Can you see that?
We're going to Tai O Village.
To another village?
- Okay, let's go. / - Let's go.
If you buy the 360 pass,
you can take this bus for free.
You have to buy the 360 pass.
It's really convenient.
(20 minutes from Ngong Ping Village to Tai O Village)
We're here.
- What is this place? / - We have arrived.
- Where is this place? / - This place is...
A village of floating houses.
We're here at Tai O Village.
Is that mic working?
It's run out of battery.
♪ My battery died ♪
♪ So I missed your call ♪
That's Unnies.
I love that song.
You carry around so much...
What's that?
(So bubbly)
She's bright again.
I brought another mic just in case.
- You're awesome. / - I am, right?
This place doesn't seem like Hong Kong.
It's Hong Kong but doesn't seem like Hong Kong?
- It's totally... / - Here, it's...
This isn't the Hong Kong I know.
It feels like we're in a different country.
It doesn't feel like Hong Kong.
Floating houses.
These are the last floating houses in Hong Kong.
They're being redeveloped.
These houses were supposed to go.
So the tourists flocked here.
People decided to preserve the floating houses then.
That's why it remains in here.
- That's great. / - Yeah.
(There's dried fisheries market in the village)
- There are floating houses here. / - Yes.
So a lot of dried fisheries are sold here.
There are a lot of interesting things here.
What are these?
There were a lot of interesting dried fish there.
Aren't these mussels?
They sell everything dried here.
What did she see?
You're not supposed to touch that.
- I was just looking. / - Oh, my.
This is really big.
- Why? / - Look at this.
I was so surprised.
What is this?
I think it's a dried shark.
- Wow. / - They dried a whole shark.
Where do they use that?
This...
It's awesome.
We didn't eat anything at Ngong Ping.
I'm hungry from this smell.
Oh, my. Is this a squid?
It's a really big squid.
- My goodness. / - It's really big.
- It looks good. / - It's really good.
- Really? / - Is it boiled?
- Yes. / - It's boiled.
How is it?
It's heavy.
It looks really heavy.
The color looks like pork hocks.
- It's bigger than our faces. / - Is it seasoned?
- Yes, I think it's seasoned with soy sauce. / - Right?
- They preserved it in soy sauce. / - It looks so good.
That is really good. I've had it before.
It was really good.
- Everyone is waiting in line. / - Wait a minute.
- Are they all in line? / - This place is popular.
There wasn't a line when we first got there.
Suddenly, A line formed...
People suddenly started to gather.
- They're mostly tourists. / - Yes.
Thank you.
(Ready to eat after adding special soy sauce)
- That looks really delicious. / - It tastes like?
This is really delicious.
It's firm. Should I say it's robust?
The inside is...
- So chewy. / - That's right, it's chewy.
It's really good.
As you can see,
it looks very chewy, right?
It really is chewy.
We've never had such thick squid before.
- That's right. / - The texture must be...
- Really good. / - Yes, it's really good.
I'm curious.
It's delicious.
Let's try another place.
(Take care)
I want to try some.
- If you look there... / - Wow.
It's really floating on the water.
It really is a floating house.
The locals really live here.
It's really unique.
It's not something you see often.
Nice.
It's really nice.
- Moon Byul. / - Yes?
I'm scared when you call me.
- Knock, knock. / - Why are you tapping my shoulder?
- Is your stomach okay? / - Yes.
- Oh, like this? / - I heard it rumbling.
- Did you hear it? / - Yes.
- Follow me. / - Is it here?
Squid wouldn't be enough.
- It's here. / - We were hungry.
It already seems delicious.
- Can you already tell? / - Yes, it's going to be good.
- Is it a good place? / - Yes.
It's going to be a good place.
Sikyung can tell from the door.
It looks delicious.
(Fusion cheese seafood with steamed pumpkin)
(You can enjoy both local cuisine and fusion dishes)
This is a floating house.
A fisherman who lives here
is running this restaurant.
I like places like this.
The food is really fresh at places like these.
I reserved this place about a month ago.
- You did? / - Yes.
It was really hard.
Are you friends with this fisherman?
Yes, I got to know him well.
I call him uncle. Uncle.
- I went too far, right? / - Yeah.
I didn't know that we would really eat
on top of water.
Look at that.
It's amazing. We could never see that in cities.
- It's different from the Hong Kong I imagined. / - Right?
For me too.
It must feel very unique.
- It feels special. / - I think so too.
Thank you.
(The food came while they were enjoying the view)
This is what we ordered.
- It's rice steamed in lotus leaves. / - Say it faster.
Rice steamed in lotus leaves.
(Rice steamed in lotus leaves in a bamboo steamer)
Is that meat inside the rice?
This is meat, this is squid.
- Anchovies? / - Anchovies.
The lotus leaves are hidden here.
Okay.
I want to give you a bite of everything.
1, 2, 3.
(Oh, my)
What does it taste like?
(Hmm)
It tastes like seafood.
That's because there's seafood in it.
(Analyzing the taste)
It's like when your mom always makes you
kimchi fried rice at home,
then she feels like she should make something else.
So she put anchovies and other healthy ingredients
and fried them to make a delicious dish.
That's what it tastes like.
What are you talking about?
Try to explain the taste.
It just tastes like seafood.
It tastes like seafood
but...
It has a mild and basic flavor.
- Perfect? / - They all go well together.
- Is it perfect? / - Yes.
Oh, my.
- This looks delicious. / - It is.
There are a lot of fusion dishes for the tourists.
That looks delicious.
Look how plump the shrimp is.
Let's try it.
(The seafood is so big, it completely fills the mouth)
It's so hot.
It's hot.
The cheese, pumpkin,
and seafood.
The seafood is really good here.
And it's all really big. The shrimp is big.
They don't skimp on the ingredients, right?
The dishes were plentiful.
This is really good.
The cheese and seafood inside the pumpkin
makes it seem like a cream pasta.
It's a diet food.
- What? / - It's a diet food.
With all that cheese?
- It has pumpkin. / - Yes.
It'll relieve bloating so it's a diet food.
- It's like cream pasta sauce. / - You're right.
- It's thicker. / - Yes.
While eating this,
this is cheese
and I don't like greasy food...
- Will she want kimchi again? / - It can't be.
It can't be.
- Do you want it? / - Yeah.
Close your eyes then.
- Make a wish. / - What kind of wish?
- Say, "Please give me kimchi." / - Give me kimchi.
Please give me some kimchi.
They really know how to have a good time.
Ta-da.
- Here. / - It's kimchi.
I remember eating this last time.
Does it melt in your mouth?
Eat up.
The restaurant thankfully allowed us to eat kimchi.
We could enjoy the food more.
- You're both in your 20s, right? / - Yes.
(Sunset cafe)
When the sun is about to set,
we're going to enjoy the sunset while relaxing.
You like that kind of thing?
- Relaxation. Healing. / - Rest.
- Healing. / - Right.
Relaxing while enjoying the sunset with friends.
(The sunset disappeared because of sudden rain)
- Did it rain? / - Yes.
It's even more beautiful with the rain.
- This is what it was supposed to be? / - Yes.
- You couldn't see this. / - You missed that?
This place has a unique vibe.
- Doesn't it feel cozy? / - Yeah.
This place is really cozy.
I heard that when it rains in Hong Kong...
- People like to drink hot honey lemon tea. / - This?
Yes, honey lemon tea.
Thank you.
- Thank you. / - It's really unique.
- It's like green tea. / - Doesn't it smell like citrus tea?
(Honey lemon tea, $5.30)
Cheers.
Cheers to Hong Kong.
It's hot.
I know why they drink this a lot.
- When it's chilly... / - You won't catch a cold.
It really warms you up.
It feels like your whole body is
calming down.
Finally, Solar...
- She's calmed down. / - She's calmed.
She only calms down when it rains.
I think it's been a long time since
I've drunk something from a teacup.
- When we go to cafes... / - That's right.
You use plastic cups.
- Or it's always paper cups. / - But an actual cup...
It feels quite different.
- It feels like we're being served. / - Right.
That's right.
We're coming to the end of our trip.
It's our last night.
What was the most memorable thing during this trip?
Everything was wonderful.
But Disneyland was the most memorable for me.
It was so fun for me.
I found it fascinating.
She screamed so much.
- Solar's mouth. / - For me...
I liked it because I could come here
and visit
nice places and enjoy good food
with people I like.
That's what I liked.
I'm going to dwell on this trip for...
- At least 3 months. / - Will you dwell on it?
I'm going to work hard while thinking about this trip.
Sounds good.
- I can last 3 months. / - Okay.
The month before the trip is so good.
- Right. / - Then you relive the memories...
- For about 3 months after. / - Right.
(To Byul)
(To Yongseon)
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
Hong Kong!
Battle Trip!
("I feel happy not when I reach the destination")
("But while I take a trip" by Andrew Matthews)
We saw a new side of Hong Kong.
Yes.
I don't think I've ever seen this in Hong Kong.
Shall we check your budget?
They had a fruitful trip in Hong Kong.
We saw a new side of Hong Kong.
The Yong Kong Byul Kong Hong Kong Tour.
Let's find out their final budget.
Our Yong Kong Byul Kong Hong Kong Tour spent...
- For 3 days and 2 nights. / - 3 days and 2 nights.
Final budge was...
- It was? / - It was?
- Per person. / - Per person?
$426.10.
- Well, with this... / - It's...
- It wasn't cheap. / - Right.
But consider visiting a theme park,
buying a free pass.
And staying at the Disneyland hotel.
- If you consider that... / - Yes.
I thought it would cost more.
They also looked around every corner of Lantau Island.
That's right.
Considering everything,
you really had a fruitful holiday.
Yes, we really did.
Hong Kong was like an onion
with its infinite layers.
We introduced a new side of it.
You said you'd last 3 months.
- It hasn't been 3 months yet, right? / - Right.
Call us if another hardship comes along.
We'll send you on a trip that will last up to a year.
- Really? / - That would be great.
- Latin America? / - Europe, maybe?
But can we come on this show again?
- Of course. / - Really?
Many people have come on this show twice.
- Really? / - In Sandara Park's case...
- She's been here 3 times? / - She's filming now!
- Really? / - Yes.
You two had such great energy.
- We all felt happy watching you. / - It was fun.
Next week, we'll see you again
with an intermediate course to Taiwan.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(Intermediate course to Taiwan, conquer the south)
(Chorong and Hayoung's Tour)
So fun.
- So pretty. / - Seriously.
Wow.
(Healing trip, great view before your eyes)
Amazing.
This place warms you up inside.
Wow, it's so pretty.
- This is amazing. / - It has hidden charm.
(Battle Trip)
("Holding On To You" by Sung Sikyung)