(One November day with beautiful fall leaves)
(Special Battle Trip for fall, a good time to get away)
(What is this place where things are busy?)
Welcome.
Welcome to Battle Trip Restaurant
for the gourmet trip special.
(Gastronomy)
(The country of gastronomy, Italy)
(Top 3 countries of gastronomy)
(Italy)
(We invite you to the world of gastronomy)
This really is the city of water.
This really feels like Italy.
(The country of passion with breathing arts)
(The ferocious battlefield of international chefs)
(Spain)
We've arrived here!
Wow, this is to die for.
It's not famous among tourists.
Where we can eat...
(Which team will be the winners of this gourmet trip?)
Gourmet trip is also war.
Battle Trip!
We have special episodes every week
but this is even more special.
With our two hosts, Lee Hwijae and Sung Sikyung,
we prepared a special battle between the hosts.
(The host battle is back)
Hwijae, please tell us about this episode.
We went on a trip for food, literally.
We have two chefs who traveled with us.
They are Lee Wonil and Park Joonwoo.
(Two chefs to adorn the gourmet trip)
We have the best chefs here.
And today, for this special episode,
we invited special judges here.
They are Lovelyz and PENTAGON. Welcome.
(Lovelyz)
I'm a little worried
because Hwijae doesn't eat a lot.
- I'm very picky. / - But...
When I heard Wonil went with you,
I felt relieved.
I have a close tie with him.
Wonil is acknowledged
to be the best Korean chef in the country.
He's the best...
- When it comes to eating. / - Right.
During my trip with him,
I thought he didn't have a throat.
(He just kept eating)
He's Lee Wonil.
Hello, hello.
Nice to meet you. I'm Chef Lee Wonil.
First of all,
it's important to eat a lot
but it's more important to know what we eat.
He used to be a journalist.
He has an extensive knowledge of Western food.
And he's a wine expert.
You'll be surprised.
Sometimes, he brings wine speaking in French.
I understand. He studied in Belgium.
- He's Chef Park Joonwoo. / - Welcome.
(Chef Park Joonwoo)
The important thing about travel
is the destination.
But it also matters who you're going with.
I was going to make a team with Wonil but
I was told we can't go through immigration that way.
- No one can stop you from eating. / - That's right.
They are matchless. They can't be together.
Who'd be able to beat them?
No one can beat them.
Maybe Kang Hodong and Lee Yeongja.
(Hodong and Yeongja might be able to beat them)
They can give it a try.
They're like Messi and Ronaldo.
You're right.
There are flags here.
This is Italy vs. Spain.
- That's right. / - What's important is...
Which city of Spain you went.
And which city of Italy you went is very important.
Which city of Italy did you go to?
It's the city of water and romance.
We went to Venice.
We went to one more city. It's the city of gastronomy.
It's called the city of fatties.
Fatties?
It's Bologna La Grassa.
It's the city of fatties.
You have to eat there.
There are many tasty things.
If you go on a gourmet trip to Italy,
all cities are perfect for that.
But you should go to Venice with a lot of seafood.
And Bologna, a center of trade.
They have the best food ingredients there.
If you want to enjoy gastronomy,
you should go to Bologna.
The judges seem...
- Quite tempted by Italy. / - I'd go for Italy.
They catch seafood at the sea and deep-fry it.
(Deep-frying?)
- It must be good. / - There's no need to say more.
Alright, Team Spain.
Which city did you go to?
When you think of Spain,
which city comes to your mind?
- Barcelona. / - Barcelona.
Barcelona!
Barcelona.
Messi plays for FC Barcelona.
And Valencia.
Lee Kangin plays for Valencia FC.
Enough.
But I gave up everything.
I focused on the food.
It's where gourmets from all over the world
want to go.
Barcelona is the battlefield of the best chefs,
so they say.
La Boqueria in Barcelona is called
the shopping basket of Europe.
There are a lot of food ingredients
in Barcelona.
We also visited Valencia, a hidden gourmet city.
- Valencia sounds unfamiliar. / - I know.
Valencia is where the typical Spanish dish...
- Paella was invented. / - Paella.
That's Valencia.
Now let me sum it up.
There will be matches between two cities.
One match is between Venice, Italy
and Barcelona, Spain.
And the other is between Bologna, Italy...
- And Valencia, Spain. / - Valencia.
The matches will be judged by our impartial judges.
Until now, our 100 judges were allowed
to vote for both teams.
But today, after watching the two cities,
the judges have to choose only one city
they'd like to go.
They can only vote for one team.
We have 8 judges and Sook, our main host.
- Including her vote... / - If we have only 8 judges...
It might end up tie with the score of 4 to 4.
If I vote as well, it will be an odd number.
I believe Sook will be honest and vote for...
- What she likes. / - Of course.
I'm very honest when it comes to food.
Let's forget about seniority here.
I hope you focus on
the food only.
We're here as gourmet judges
but we got nothing but some bread.
Aren't we getting any food?
- All we get is bread? / - We want food too.
Since we started talking about food,
we're getting hungry.
We're about to go on a gourmet tour.
And we can't on empty stomachs.
So I prepared something.
Please bring the food.
(Prepared for the gourmet trip)
(Today's appetizer)
(Jamon and salami)
Jamon was invented before
refrigeration was developed.
In order to keep meat from rotting for a long time,
people dry-cured meat, which is how
jamon was invented.
In other words, it's salted pork.
The jamon we prepared today is
not just regular jamon.
It's the best quality jamon. It's called jamon iberico.
It's made of a pig's hind leg that was fed acorns.
It's not so salty and it has an excellent nutty flavor.
We prepared jamon iberico today.
Do you see the bread in front of you?
It will taste amazing
with the bread.
It'll be perfectly seasoned.
Why does it smell like sesame oil?
- It's the lard. / - The oily scent is...
From the acorns.
You can smell the acorns from the fat.
- I can smell it. / - I can really smell acorns.
We prepared salami.
Salami was invented by farmers like jamon.
It's also dry-cured ham.
Salami is where all the dry-cured hams
were originated from.
- It's a very meaningful food. / - Right.
The word "salami" comes from a Latin word "salare."
It means to salt.
Pepperoni on pizza is also
a kind of salami.
Both are really delicious.
- They have different charms. / - How is it?
- Which one do you prefer? / - For me...
- I like fat on meat. / - I see.
I prefer salami because it tastes fattier.
So you prefer salami.
What about you?
The PENTAGON members are so busy eating.
(Focused on eating)
- It's tasty, isn't it? / - Together with bread...
Salami makes your mouth keep watering.
Which country do you want to check out first?
- Italy. / - Spain.
- Italy. / - Italy? I see.
It seems like the majority want to see Italy first.
You have to eat delicious food first.
This is just a small part of what we had there.
Brioche, espresso, cappuccino,
squid ink pasta, deep-fried seafood,
Spritz, Lugana white wine,
pizza diavola, pizza quattro stagioni, arugula pizza...
Caprese salad, monkfish, spaghetti alle vongole,
Venetian style liver,
Sangiovese red wine. Those are what we had.
We know some of the dishes on the list
but some of them we don't.
If you have any question, feel free to ask.
I wonder what Spritz is.
It sounds like...
A fizzy drink.
Spritz is a very famous aperitif in Venice.
- Aperitif? / - It's made with a strong liquor...
And carbonated water.
You can make it either bitter or sweet.
There are two kinds of Spritz.
We got you a glass of Spritz for each of you.
- Aperitifs. / - Let's drink it before we start.
(A glass of Spritz before the journey starts)
It looks so pretty.
It smells very refreshing.
It has a very sweet liquor in it called Aperol.
It's sweet Spritz.
This is what most people like.
It has carbonated water and ice cubes in it,
so it'll be less and less alcoholic as time passes.
It smells like a fizzy drink or...
A digestive medicine.
Do you see what I mean?
- Right? / - I know what you mean.
- I know that medicine. / - It smells like that medicine.
There's one thing you should know.
It has liquor in it, which is a strong alcohol.
It's brewed with herbs and spices.
Herbs and spices used to be
used as medicine for digestion.
So they might smell similar.
You don't drink a lot of this.
You moisten your throat with this
before you start eating.
This is why it's like a digestive medicine.
It helps your stomach get ready.
Yein doesn't seem to like it.
I like drinks that taste a lot like alcohol.
- This is too weak for her. / - She wants it stronger.
Now that we had an aperitif,
let's get started.
Before that, the corner inside a corner,
Sook's Choice.
Since the theme is gourmet trip,
there will be a lot of food.
I'm going to share how I change my mind
with you in real-time.
Now, we're going to go on a trip.
Excuse me, is "now" a new buzzword?
Before we start, let's hear your tour names.
- Want our tour name? / - Yes.
Pizza, pasta, espresso, wine, risotto, gelato,
deep-fried seafood,
Bolognese sauce, tortellini, mortadella steak.
We Will Eat Tour.
(The trip to Venice begins)
(1 of the top 3 countries of gastronomy)
Is it 1 of the top 3 countries of gastronomy?
(Italy)
It's so beautiful.
(It's the only city of water in the world)
It looks different.
(Venice)
(Italy's)
(It looks amazing)
(Italy's capital city of gastronomy)
(Bologna)
(Welcome to the gourmet world)
Truffles.
- Italy is famous for truffles. / - Italian truffles.
They look delicious already.
We've passed Venice and are here in Bologna.
We'll eat it all.
Banana is also acidic,
so if you make it well, it's refreshing.
"Casa" means house and "della" is like "of."
There are over 350 types of grapes in Italy.
The background knowledge makes the food
taste better.
Okay?
I'm Joonwoo.
(Withering as he says his greeting)
"Withered?"
His shyness is his charm.
I'm doing my best.
I'll work even harder.
What was that?
(Shyness is the most popular personality trait)
- I want to eat so much. / - I want to eat it all.
He's so cute.
Oh, my.
- So cute. / - He's pretty cute.
Although I'm not a chef...
It's perfectly moist.
It's like they just put starch over them...
I'm actually a little nervous right now.
I like this one.
Sikyung, you look thin there.
You gained weight.
(This is the side effect of gourmet trips)
(Delicious food can melt him down)
This is the face he makes when it's really delicious.
He makes this face when it's really delicious.
(Sung Sikyung, the gourmet celebrity)
Italy is love.
- This is so good. / - He just added 5 slices.
Like sprinkling vinegar in cold noodles.
The taste of the Mediterranean is olive oil.
Is that olive oil?
Sourness, bitterness and sweetness.
It all comes together. May I lick the plate?
I'm really done.
Amazing.
(We Will Eat gourmet tour in Italy, coming soon!)
(Joonwoo's restaurant, 15 days before takeoff)
You have a very big restaurant.
- He's not an entertainer. / - Right.
So some people might not know him
but his lemon tart is
the best lemon tart I have ever had.
He does make very good lemon tarts.
- Thank you. / - His lemon tarts.
- Thank you. / - Anyway, he's a writer...
So he has a deep knowledge of...
Food and wine.
I cook Western food and I'm a writer.
I'm Park Joonwoo.
(Chef Park Joonwoo)
(Did I say it correctly?)
Yes.
My biggest worry is...
That he doesn't eat much and he's not funny either.
He can't even drink a lot.
Wonil is a big eater.
He can eat almost as much as Jeong Junha.
(He's a glutton)
He does eat a lot.
As far as I know, when it comes to food,
France and Italy are the countries that come to mind.
So which city in Italy are we going?
It hasn't been long since Italy was unified.
He'll talk about history a lot.
Because of this unique history,
the regional traits are more visibly different
than those of east and west regions in Korea.
We must choose a city.
(Which part of Italy will be a good choice?)
Actually, Toy, Yu Huiyeol...
Which album was it?
He went to Italy and was lying down on a gondola.
Just like that. The album was called "Fermata."
Does it mean a break? It means a pause.
- I see. Time to regroup. / - At times...
- I did want to visit Venice. / - Okay.
Venice is one of the cities people must visit in Italy.
I went 10 or so years ago on a trip.
- You've been there? / - Yes.
- Yes, I have. / - Venice sounds nice.
What about food in Venice?
Do they eat a lot of seafood?
Since they're on the water, they do eat seafood a lot.
My mouth is watering already.
Don't you love seafood?
- I cannot leave out seafood. / - Right.
- You love every kind of food. / - Yes.
I must love all the food equally.
Venice is a city that belongs to the Veneto region.
- Veneto is famous for white wine. / - Wine?
- It's near Venice. / - We'll go to Venice.
- White wine and seafood. / - For white wine.
- We can enjoy this combination. / - That's the best.
Seafood and white wine make the perfect pair.
Wine. Seriously.
How about going to Bologna?
- It's not too far? / - This sounds a bit random, right?
But when people discuss food in Italy,
it's one of the cities known for its cuisine.
A sauce is named after the city.
Bolognese sauce is the origin of meat sauce.
I am curious how the original would taste.
Actually, I've never had that in Bologna.
This is too extravagant.
Kimchi from abroad may be good...
But it can't beat the one in Korea. Don't you think?
- Of course. / - Great. We'll go to Venice...
- And Bologna. / - Okay.
You must know a lot about Europe.
Please look up great restaurants.
I'll prepare activities we can try there.
Will we ride the gondola?
- We must do obvious activities too. / - Of course.
- Since we're all the way in Italy. / - We're on a trip.
We must take photos there.
- You must ride a gondola in Venice. / - We must.
Italy is famous for this one other than prosciutto.
Can you read this? Mortadella.
It's very soft and delicious.
That's the best. Hands down, mortadella's the best.
Is that ham?
I want to wash my face with that. I mean it.
I'm telling you. It's the best. It's soft.
(That sounds delicious)
Squid ink pasta, gelato and pizza.
We must drink coffee when we get up in the morning.
(He shows his cell phone without speaking a word)
Venice is beautiful.
It looks like the Rialto Bridge is really famous.
(He's planning the itinerary for the sightseeing part)
Doesn't this look European?
Great, this would be a great place to go.
We'll go...
And destroy it.
I'll show you how quickly a man can gain weight.
(Italy Gourmet Tour)
My gosh, I already feel full.
One pizza per person?
You have to have one each.
In Italy, it's always one pizza per person.
That's right.
Have you been well? Our luggage looks similar.
- Hello. / - Hi.
(The start of a trip is always exciting)
Direct flights to Venice are available now.
You can go to your gate by 9:45 a.m.
- Okay. / - Have a good day.
- Bye. / - Bye.
There are direct flights to Venice.
- Wait, there are direct flights? / - I was so surprised.
- They just opened a new route. / - I was surprised.
- This is great, seriously. / - It's awesome.
Come on.
(The city of water consists of waterways)
(This lively and peaceful city presents elegant beauty)
(The one and only city of water in the world, Venice)
Actually, Venice is a city of dreams.
- This is amazing. / - Gosh, Venice.
"Beautiful Venice." Did I get that right?
I don't know.
Anyway, this is the typical look of Venice, right?
We just came out of the airport.
- My gosh. / - Do people get on that?
What's that?
(Impressed)
Gosh, that's so interesting.
That's the front of the airport.
(The exotic scenery greets them from the start)
(Ocean view right out of the airport)
- Gosh. / - This is so cool.
This is my first time in Italy.
- This is your first time in Italy? / - Yes.
This is my third trip to Italy. I haven't been here much.
But I came to Venice 14 years ago.
This is my first time.
I'm not sure if we'll be able to communicate.
That's why I feel a bit anxious.
- It's a tourist destination though. / - English?
Wouldn't they speak English?
We can get there via bus
but we'll get there by water taxi.
- All the way to our lodging. / - Gosh, that looks nice.
Isn't water taxi expensive here?
If we take the bus, we'll have to climb up the stairs.
If we take the boat, it'll take us 5 minutes on foot.
Because there are a lot of waterways?
It won't be in front of the hotel.
- But there are waterways. / - That's convenient.
It'd be weird if we take the bus in Venice.
- Yes, it's a city of water. / - Right.
We don't have to get there by land.
- Let's go grab a taxi. / - Okay.
(They set out to get on the water taxi)
- Thank you. / - Even the boat was so luxurious.
(The water taxi cuts through the ocean)
- That looks so cool. / - We haven't seen this before.
There's the ocean right outside the airport.
You don't need anything else, just a water taxi.
You're right. This is so nice.
This is awesome.
(They admire the unobstructed view)
This is outstanding.
- Seriously? / - What is it?
I shouldn't be on this taxi with a bearded man.
(Gosh)
Why not? This is nice.
(Into the city of water through the vast ocean)
The view ahead of us is amazing.
We're going into the town right away.
Is he going to drop you off at your hotel just like that?
- 5 minutes after we get off. / - No way. Unbelievable.
- This is amazing. / - How can he go into the alleys?
- This is indeed a city of water. / - It's awesome.
Things look so interesting here.
We can still get to our destination...
- Without setting foot on the road. / - Right.
(They take in the scenery of Venice)
This place is incredible.
Everyone, you should come here.
This water taxi ride makes the trip worth it.
We get to look around the alleys on the boat.
This is indeed awesome.
My gosh, I sound like a country boy. I love it.
What can we do? We love it here.
- I was really excited then. / - Yes.
See? That's how it looks there.
It's really beautiful. It's so pretty.
This is a movie. It's a scene from a movie.
(They pass by a small water alley)
- Incredible. / - My goodness, hold on.
We got out of the alley and on the main street now.
Amazing.
This town is so strange.
Isn't that the water bus? It's the water bus.
This is the water bus.
- I only took that when I came. / - Why?
It was just a bus but it was fun to glide on the water.
It was nice and breezy.
Gondola.
(Hello, I'm a gondola)
It's so romantic. They're on a date.
Look at that.
That one is equivalent to a limousine.
Ours is like Uber.
(This is just a taxi, that's a limousine)
This is so intriguing. They get around on that.
I'm such a tourist.
(Venice makes even Sikyung take photos)
- He rarely takes photos. / - Right?
I took those photos.
(Arrived in Venice, expert photographer)
That's incredible.
It wasn't that I did a good job at taking photos.
In Venice, photos just turn out well.
(The scenery is picturesque)
That's why people go there.
He almost never takes photos.
It must be really beautiful there.
We have to brace ourselves today.
Let's rest up and have all of our energy tomorrow.
We must destroy Lee Wonil.
- That's your agenda? / - Of course.
We'll happily get some rest today.
(They will look around Venice the next day)
It was so beautiful.
(A relaxing morning of Venice dawns again)
- It's the morning of Venice. / - Venice.
What time did you wake up?
- Around 4:30 a.m. / - I woke at 5 a.m.
I went to the Rialto Bridge.
- Really? / - I'm a tourist. I'm serious.
Did you like it? How was it?
It was a nice to walk on while listening to music.
A morning stroll in Venice sounds pretty romantic.
I heard this a lot about Italians from Alberto.
They eat croissants and espresso for breakfast.
That's right.
Everything is beautiful and every dish is delicious.
I found this bar that the locals especially love.
That's where they have their breakfast.
(Bar, restaurants that only sell beverages and snacks)
In Korea, bars are strictly for drinking.
People call places where you drink coffee, bars.
- Coffee and snacks. / - Yes.
(Slurping it in one go is the key)
That's the bar. This part is a bit...
I don't even see a sign here.
Exactly. I heard that locals here frequent this bar.
That's why we're trying this place out.
(Italy Gourmet Tour)
(Italian brunch)
Gosh, Italian brunch.
- Look at the bread. / - I'm suddenly getting hungry.
- Good morning. / - Good morning.
They sell this with coffee.
- Brioche? / - Brioche.
- A brioche? Not a croissant? / - What's interesting is...
The brioche we know looks different.
Right. It's the fermented, round ball of bread.
In Italy, people call croissants brioches.
The wrong term spread but it stuck.
- So brioches are croissants? / - That's right.
(In Italy, they mean the same)
When you order, you can use both terms,
brioche and croissant.
Okay.
- Marmalade. Cream. / - This one has marmalade.
Should we try all of them?
- Yes, we'll have three. / - Let's try them all.
- Three? Okay. / - And espresso.
One espresso.
Espresso and cappuccino.
One cappuccino.
- Cappuccino? / - They drink this for breakfast.
(How did he know that?)
Italy is known for its espresso.
- Their coffee is truly amazing. / - Right.
It smells savory.
Gosh, cappuccino.
(Toasted brioches are served along with their coffee)
- Wonil's falling for it. / - Yes.
- You're falling for it. / - Yes.
I was biting my nails without realizing it.
(Italian brunch)
That's only 1.2 euros.
- Yes, it's so cheap. / - How much is that?
- About $1.40. / - About $1.50.
That's really cheap.
(Espresso $1.20, cappuccino $2)
(They grab a seat outside the bar)
Let's drink the coffee.
(What does Italian coffee taste like?)
- It's delicious. / - Gosh.
It's different.
- Well... / - How can coffee be so delicious?
It's addictive.
Italians in Korea...
- Miss this so much. / - Italian coffee.
- This is a necessity. / - I see.
A shot in the morning.
A shot during the day.
They need them
but they can't have them in Korea.
Actually, I drink iced Americano in the morning.
Because the cold coffee wakes me up.
But in Italy, they never put ice in coffee.
(Shall we try the pastry?)
They cut it and filled it.
(Brioche filled with custard cream)
- Gosh, that looks good. / - Goodness.
What's that?
What is that cream?
- That looks good. / - It looks delicious.
- It has vanilla cream. / - That's crazy.
You drink the bitter espresso
and then eat the sweet pastry.
You keep going back and forth.
You'd eat endlessly.
(Taking a big bite)
- How is it? / - It's good.
It's soft.
It has filling.
It's apricot jam.
Yes. It's good.
Apricot jam?
Wonil is nervous.
Don't do that.
Cup noodles are going down.
(Brioche takes no. 1)
I should have brioche.
- That's so good. / - I don't know much about bread.
Coffee is good too.
Bread and cappuccino have milk in them.
Each country's milk product tastes different.
Because the cows are different.
Italy has good pasturage.
So stock and chicken farming thrive.
Milk products are delicious too.
As you can see,
the bread is very white.
Because they put less butter.
- Butter makes it more yellow? / - Yes.
So it seems that they like to fill it
with jam or chocolate better.
- Right. / - Italian croissant is...
Different from French croissant.
It's just like bread.
This isn't heavy for breakfast.
So this filling goes well with it.
Rich French croissant with chocolate filling...
- Will be too much. / - It will be.
I finished my coffee too fast.
(Empty)
I basically downed it.
I'm using spoon to scrape coffee.
That milk foam on top of the espresso is so soft.
I ate it with the bread and it was so delicious.
It's so different from the franchised coffee we drink.
Order a triple shot or something.
It won't be enough.
But be careful.
If you drink 4 or 5 espressos,
you'll become too hyper.
But...
Sitting here like this...
"It's so nice to be here with you, honey."
It should be like this, for example.
(Laughing)
- I'm sorry that I'm a man. / - I mean, no.
I didn't say it to make you feel sorry.
- But that's what you meant. / - If you're having...
Coffee and bread here with someone...
You'll just feel special.
This is really romantic.
The weather was perfect.
I was happy just sitting there.
I want to have cream brioche.
This is a gourmet trip.
So we're going to do a gourmet assessment.
This will be a very personal assessment.
We can tell the viewers whether they should visit.
- The location is great. / - It's the best.
The price is the best.
Coffee and bread go perfect together.
Espresso first.
- Espresso. / - It must be good.
How many stars?
Italian espresso is the best. It wakes you up.
You can start the morning in Venice with coffee.
- Are you a writer? / - Yes.
- That was so good. / - Written by Sung Sikyung.
Wonderful coffee. Fantastic atmosphere.
There are so many bars like this.
It'll be nice to enjoy this if you visit Venice.
(4.5 stars for the Italian brunch)
Venice is famous for seafood.
We should really try...
Squid ink pasta.
In northern Italy, they normally eat fresh pasta.
So they use fresh pasta and squid ink sauce.
We should try that.
- Seriously. / - For drinks...
We need to drink wine.
That must be really delicious.
- White wine is famous there. / - White wine!
Squid ink pasta with white wine is amazing.
(Italy Gourmet Tour)
That looks pretty.
(Squid ink pasta restaurant)
(What will they do next in Venice?)
Here you have...
The first bridge built in Venice.
That's Rialto Bridge.
- That white bridge? / - Yes.
(Rialto Bridge was built in 1591)
It's big.
There are so many people.
It's much bigger than the bridges we saw.
It's the biggest.
Shouldn't we eat now?
Yes, we're going to.
Ristorante and tratto...
- Trattoria. / - What's the difference?
Ristorante is like a restaurant.
You can have a course meal. It's a formal restaurant.
I should write that down.
Below that is trattoria.
Pizzeria is where you can have pizza.
Bar is where we had breakfast.
You can have coffee and snacks like bread.
When you go to Italy,
depending on your budget, taste or situation,
you can choose where to go.
Somewhere delicious...
I chose this place because it had a good rating.
But...
They made it so that you have to be close.
- Like this. / - If you sit like this.
- Goodness. / - Gosh.
I hate that atmosphere.
(I wish I didn't see that)
You can't help but to be close.
If you sit like this.
(Love in Venice)
Like I said before, trattoria
is cozy and humble.
Hello.
(Making their first order in Venice)
Thank you.
- Here you go. / - Thank you.
People might find
the Italian menu difficult.
Antipasti is...
- Appetizer. / - It's a starter.
What's different in Italy is this.
They always have two main dishes.
2 mains?
First main dish is carbohydrate.
- Protein comes next? / - Second is protein.
That's interesting.
Next is dolce which is dessert.
We usually have meat first, then noodles.
But here, they have noodles first, then meat.
- Really? / - They do it the other way.
- First noodles, meat after. / - Okay.
- This is hard. / - What should we eat?
Antipasti...
It has a star next to this.
- This is recommended. / - Piovra.
- This is delicious. / - It looks good.
- Let's order this. / - Okay.
Venice is famous for squid ink pasta.
- Nero. / - Yes.
- I want to try it. / - Nero is black.
Seppie is cuttlefish.
So it's squid ink.
- Squid ink pasta. / - We'll order that.
We should order deep-fried seafood in Venice.
- This, no. 3. / - Yes, no. 3.
I'm drooling over wine.
(They haven't finished ordering yet)
Italy is about wine.
- First... / - White wine.
Rosso is red.
Biancho is white.
But it says bianchi.
That's plural.
With an "i," it's plural. Instead of "s."
- It's like white wines. / - That's right.
- They have this too. / - What?
Aperitifs.
Drink served before meals.
In Europe, they have a drink before drinking wine.
- Before a meal. / - Yes.
Sweet drinks have Aperol.
Bitter drinks have Campari.
- Different liquor then. / - Yes.
They mix different liquors.
You can choose.
Shall we have one each?
- Which one do you like? / - Bitter one.
- Then I'll order a sweet one. / - Okay.
This is it.
(This is it)
They add liquor in white wine.
- Over 20% alcohol. / - Adding strong liquor to wine.
It's like a cocktail.
(What does Venetian aperitif taste like?)
(Yummy)
With Campari, it tastes bitter.
With Aperol, it tastes sweet.
(Spritz, $5.20 per glass)
It's bitter, so it stimulates your appetite.
I keep drinking it though.
Because it's bitter, you keep sipping on it.
I keep salivating.
Rather than with sweetness,
appetite is often stimulated
with bitterness or sourness.
So this is a good aperitif.
Here it is.
(Their food is served)
There's the food.
(For antipasto, they're having octopus)
Octopus appetizer must be delicious.
(Wow)
Look at that.
- Amazing. / - Look at that.
(Octopus dish, $15.60)
Octopus is chewy in Korea.
But it is tender in Italy.
You can crush it with your tongue.
(He's excited to eat)
It's so tender.
It's so smooth.
(It's super easy to cut)
Sweet pumpkin sauce.
(Octopus with sweet pumpkin sauce)
Pistachio.
(Octopus with sweet pumpkin sauce and pistachio)
I want to eat octopus.
(They each take a bite)
(What?)
It's like fish.
Yes, it's like fish.
The fork goes right in.
- You're right. / - It's really tender.
You can crush it with your tongue.
- How did they do this? / - How can it be so soft?
In Korea, we usually blanch the octopus slightly
and enjoy the chewy and firm texture of the octopus.
But in Europe, they completely cook the octopus.
Just like pork slices are soft when we steam them.
Europeans thoroughly cook the octopus
so they're tender.
This is great. This is excellent.
(White wine is the best for seafood)
That wine was great.
(The wine is aromatic)
I like this wine.
I personally like this wine.
The wine goes really well with the dish.
Lugana. Both of them are from this region.
I'm going to eat the octopus.
(Sook has caved in after the consecutive attacks)
I'll put this on the bottom now.
It was really good. The wine was fantastic.
The dish and the wine make the perfect pair.
At this restaurant, make sure you order Traminer.
I was informed that this wine is a local one.
- It smells very flowery. / - It's aromatic.
- It's not dry. It has many scents. / - This is very dry.
This one is called Lugana.
It's not aromatic but it's refreshing.
If you like feeling refreshed, you'd like this wine.
- Ask them for aromatic and dry one. / - Right.
Tell them you don't want sweet wine.
I think they make a recommendation.
You ought to drink wine for a meal like that.
Since Italians enjoy drinking wine,
they produce a lot of it and it's cheap too.
When you go to Italy, you have to try their wine.
The octopus and the white wine must be...
- Really delicious. / - It is.
- It was great. / - When did that...
- When did you put it in 1st place? / - I put it in 1st.
I like the chewy texture of the octopus.
It's good. This place is great.
I was worried a little but this is pretty delicious.
I can't wait to try the pasta.
Our pasta is coming.
(Time for squid ink pasta)
- The squid ink pasta. / - My goodness.
I'm dying to try squid ink pasta. I'm so curious.
- We know how that tastes. / - It's really curious.
That's made with fresh pasta.
Really?
Alright. Let me try it now.
(They try Venice's representative dish)
They're eating it with gusto.
I really loved the pasta. They were perfect.
- That looks really good. / - Yes, it was really good.
That looks amazing.
The pasta is really unique.
This tastes really good.
I feel like I'm chewing thick buckwheat noodles.
Look. The pasta is shining because of the oil.
- I should try that in Korea. / - I should too.
I can taste the savory flavor of the squid itself.
I can taste the savory flavor from the squid ink.
- Don't you smell the olive oil? / - Right.
It's very simple, yet delicious.
(Slurping)
(This is killing me)
I've never tasted a dish like this one. I mean it.
The highlight of a pasta dish is the pasta.
- Yes, the pasta. / - They know how to enhance...
- The flavors to the fullest. / - Exactly.
I guess pasta is the best in Italy.
(Now it's time for the assorted fried seafood)
(Assorted fried seafood, $28.60)
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
(Now it's time for the assorted fried seafood)
It's the dish that everyone in the world loves.
It's fried food.
- My gosh. It's driving me crazy. / - It's seafood.
You have to fry seafood.
- Amazing. / - The shrimp and I made eye contact.
You guys are so cruel. This dish looks so delicious.
Should we try it?
(They keep on eating without a break)
- They perfectly seasoned it. / - Really?
The shrimp is great.
Their seafood is amazing.
Venice is known for its seafood.
(Venice has the best seafood)
They chopped the body of the squid.
It's not tough and not too tender.
- This is delicious. / - Seafood must be fresh.
Nothing more to it, right?
That's crazy.
Mayonnaise is the best sauce for fried food.
This is good.
- It's sweet. / - Yes.
When they make the frying mix,
they are really good at seasoning the mix.
Venice has its own method of frying food.
They soak the ingredients in milk,
coat them with flour then fry them.
The batter is very thin.
- They sliced the eggplants. / - This is to die for.
Fried eggplants are the best.
Hey, this just calls for beer.
(Beer is the way to go with fried food)
Seriously? You're drinking beer too?
- What? / - I ordered beer. I had to.
- Fried food and beer. / - This isn't a gourmet trip.
We had no choice. We were having fried food.
Exactly. Beer is the way to go.
With beer, everything falls into place.
Since we're in Venice, it's even tastier.
This is nice.
The white wine was great.
Both types of white wine were great.
(Sikyung recommends the squid ink pasta)
(Joonwoo also recommends the pasta)
(A meal that can be enjoyed casually)
(The total rating is 3.67 stars)
I think it had the opposite effect.
The trip became about food pairing for drinks.
When it comes to fine food, you also enjoy drinks...
- And the culture. / - You're right.
I should agree. It's true.
- We came all the way here. / - Okay.
- We must ride the gondola. / - That's right.
- If not, it'd be disappointing. / - Exactly.
(10-minute walk to gondola station from the restaurant)
(The stations are scattered all over the city)
(It's the symbol of Venice)
(And the most representative tourist attraction)
When we go underneath that...
You're going into the shade.
It makes you happy.
- I get why people go on gondolas. / - Right.
I really want to go there.
Especially for my honeymoon.
(Gondola)
Two men went on the gondola together.
(What a shame that it's just two guys)
You know what?
It felt much better than I thought it would.
Despite the fact it was just us two, it was great.
(The 20 to 30-minute ride, $104)
(A maximum of 6 people can ride it)
- Be careful. / - Thank you.
(They board the gondola)
We're complete tourists.
(They become tourists)
- We're off now. / - How is this moving?
What's happening?
Hey, this feels great.
This is the water scent we can smell on the water.
It's different.
It was nice to be over there too.
The atmosphere was great near the waterside too.
It's much better on the water.
(It was made in the 11th century to navigate canals)
- Look at the people. / - My gosh.
(Gondola means to shake in Italian)
(Hey, tourists, look at that over there)
- King palace? / - Yes.
(Doge's Palace is a museum now)
This is a museum now but it used to be a palace.
- That's the Bridge of Sighs. / - Yes.
Bridge of Sighs? That's the Bridge of Sighs.
That building was the court
and that one was the prison.
When they had to cross the bridge, they sighed.
That's where the name comes from.
I've heard of its name a lot.
(Even Casanova crossed the Bridge of Sighs)
Even that over there is pretty.
Everything here is pretty.
- So much detail. / - Yes.
The traces of history.
(The trace of a long history is visibly evident)
I've never ridden this because it's expensive.
But this is worth the money.
It's expensive.
It's very expensive but I hope you would ride it.
It was really nice to look at the alleys on the gondola.
I can see that.
I can just sit on the gondola...
To enjoy the atmosphere.
- Hello. / - Hello.
It's nice to relax
once in a while.
How could it not smell fishy here?
- It's cool here. / - It's so pretty.
It's so beautiful.
I told you. It's beautiful.
(It feels like being in a movie)
- It's like I'm in an Italian film. / - Right.
This is an interesting scene.
- That was really nice. / - My gosh.
(It's so peaceful that he even feels drowsy)
The air feels friendly.
- Yes, you're so right. / - You know what I mean?
- That was a great expression. / - Yes.
You can even fall asleep here.
(These two jump into Venice on their gondola ride)
If you think about it, we wouldn't be able to see
these waterways without the gondola ride.
I can't believe I got to ride a gondola.
- This is my first time. / - Same here.
Both of our first times are with a guy.
(Feeling bitter)
- Here's a surprise. Keep watching. / - What is it?
Gosh, he proposed?
- He proposed? No way. / - My goodness.
(He's touched)
- Who proposed? / - What is it?
(There's a proposal?)
(It's as if they're the only ones there)
- This is amazing. / - She must be so happy.
I can't believe it.
(The couple promise to spend their future together)
(They witness the proposal by chance)
I bet a lot of people propose to their loved ones here.
Oh, my gosh.
My gosh.
She's crying.
- She's crying. / - Oh, my.
(Watching quietly)
This is not a common thing to see in Korea.
Both of them are crying.
(It's so touching)
This is beautiful.
- People are giving blessings. / - We wish you joy.
I've never seen anyone proposing.
It's very romantic here.
I can't believe I just saw someone proposing.
Tell me about it.
(We wish your love lasts forever)
(The water of Venice is full of lovey-dovey couples)
I'm suddenly feeling very lonely.
- After seeing the proposal? / - Yes.
I can imagine.
I'll stay as far away from you as possible.
It's not because of you. I'm the one to blame.
I always sing at other people's weddings.
He sings at other people's weddings.
Speaking of which, who will sing at your wedding?
I guess I should.
(We invite a bride to)
(Sikyung's wedding)
Look at the picture. He took a great wedding picture.
- Self wedding photos. / - He did it himself?
Sikyung, you took such a nice picture.
(Everyone loves this Italian ice cream)
- It's gelato. / - It looks delicious.
Finally, this is Italian gelato.
- I love gelato. / - It looks so delicious.
(Everyone is holding this)
(Italy Gourmet Tour)
(Gelato)
(One peaceful afternoon in Venice)
Isn't Venice beautiful at dusk?
Our first coffee in Venice was great.
It was the best.
Let's go try our first gelato here.
- It's nearby. / - Our first gelato in Venice.
Exactly. This place is...
It should be delicious.
This place is famous for hazelnut chocolate ice cream.
It's a must-try in Venice. I heard it's very unique.
Okay. Where do we order?
I guess we can order here.
(Rich chocolate gelato with hazelnuts)
(Dipped in cream)
(Automatic reaction)
This deserves it.
- This is unfair. / - It's gelato.
(They order chewy original gelato as well)
(Hazelnut gelato and 3 scoop gelato, $8.50 each)
(They charge you for seating instead of tips)
(Here comes the gelato)
This has to top the chart.
(Lemon, chocolate chips, tiramisu)
- This is whipped cream, isn't it? / - Yes, it is.
Actually, I don't eat a lot of sweet things.
I'm more of a drinker.
- But he's an expert with sweets. / - I love sweets.
Since he's a dessert expert.
It doesn't have much sugar in it. It's okay.
- This one? / - Yes.
It has little bit of sugar in it.
The whipped cream has a very light texture.
This whipped cream is supposed to be eaten
with the ice cream.
Which means this gelato should be pretty sweet.
Let me try it first, since I don't like sweet things.
(What does the hazelnut gelato taste like?)
It was really sweet.
(Let me see how it tastes)
(He's touched by its rich flavor)
- Do you like it? / - It's very deep.
If it's supposed to be sweet, it should be real sweet.
It has chopped hazelnuts inside.
As far as I know, this is the Northern Italian style
to eat chocolate and hazelnuts together.
It's called gianduiotto.
If you're in this town, you have to try this ice cream.
Depending on your taste,
you can ask them to remove
the whipped cream and eat only the ice cream.
You can say, "Senza panna" to order
the ice cream without the cream.
So you can just eat the ice cream.
- "Senza panna." / - "Senza panna."
"Panna" is from "panna cotta."
- "No cream." / - You can say that too.
No cream.
It seemed like they could speak English.
I'm going to eat this.
(It's time to try the original Italian gelato)
It looks delicious. I want to try it.
Let me start with the lemon flavor.
I know people love Italian gelato.
But it shouldn't be that special.
That lemon gelato looks really delicious.
How is it?
(This is it)
It's really good.
- Is it? / - This doesn't exist in Korea.
(Happy)
- It was delicious. / - He looks so happy.
It's like sorbet.
They have great lemon gelato.
Italy has some good coffee and gelato.
It's very light.
It's supposed to be heavy
but it's so light in my mouth.
This one? Is it tiramisu flavor?
You should try tiramisu flavor.
Do you know the caramel flavored Korean ice cream?
It's like that but a lot fancier.
It's so chewy.
It's like a cheesecake.
(I love it)
You'll have to run 40km after eating all that.
You don't talk about calories when it comes to gelato.
It's rude to say that.
That was very impolite of him.
I never buy myself sweets
but now I get why people love gelato so much.
(Everyone loves the traditional Italian gelato)
I recommend the tiramisu flavor.
(Sikyung's favorite is the tiramisu flavored gelato)
If you come here with someone, try gianduiotto.
And if you come here alone, try the lemon gelato.
- What was lemon in Italian again? / - Limone.
Limone.
I usually don't like desserts but I ate most of it.
The lemon gelato was really good.
Seriously, it's pretty good.
I think Italy has the best gelato.
- My goodness. / - It looks so delicious.
(Gelato in Venice, 4.34 stars)
(Another day ends in Venice)
Street lamps are all we need
for the beautiful European night view.
It's because the buildings are so beautiful.
So this is Santa Maria della Salute.
- It's nice. / - It looks awesome.
Is this where you can see a beautiful view?
This is one of the places you can see
a beautiful sunset.
It's very calm and atmospheric today.
This is Santa Maria della Salute.
You can go to all those places by foot.
It takes 10 to 20 minutes.
It's nice here too.
But also is the terrace in the department store.
You can use the rooftop for
15 minutes with a reservation.
You can't eat anything up there though.
- Is the reservation free? / - Yes, you just need to book.
It's another nice sunset spot.
This is also a famous place.
It's so beautiful.
(The day slowly ends)
Oh, right. There's something I have to tell you.
It's fun to drink wine in this kind of places
but because of so many drunk people on the street...
Venice is considering setting up
an ordinance banning such actions.
- So please keep that in mind. / - That's sad.
I hope the weather is nice tomorrow.
I think it will be. I have a good feeling.
Since your an expert at food and wine,
I believe you've made reservations
for good restaurants.
- I did. / - Oh, well.
- What's with "Oh, well?" / - Never mind.
This could be a wallpaper.
(Hopefully they try more delicious food tomorrow)
I prepared something.
Something memorable.
Wow, it's so nice here.
Come over here.
Oh, my.
(When you're in Burano, you must take a picture here)
Sikyung is actually handsome.
(Really?)
What are they doing?
You can't help but do such things.
Honey, try this.
(Course meal with all typical Venetian food)
(It's good, isn't it?)
(It's good)
(Slurping)
Okay.
I feel like I'm falling in love.
Cheers to our special trip.
(Italy Gourmet Tour)
(It's their third morning in Venice)
(People start their days in their own way)
(They head to a coffee bar near their hotel)
Before we start the day,
we should keep drinking espresso before going back.
Espresso is delicious. We should drink it.
I heard it's delicious here.
We had coffee every morning there.
- You should. / - Okay. Thank you.
Did you have brioche again?
Every store has different brioche.
It's so nice here.
This bar had some delicious bread.
The brioche we had on the first day was a little dry.
- But this one is... / - It has much more butter in it.
It's much softer.
The brioche we had yesterday was plain
while this one is buttery.
This one is made of the same dough
but has blueberry jam in it.
- It's sweet and sour. / - It has jam in it.
It'll boost your energy in the morning.
It smells like rye and butter.
If I don't keep it together,
I might easily intake over 900 calories.
(It must be really delicious)
Now we need to go enjoy Venice...
With the energy from the coffee. Let's go.
It'd be very nice to start a day like that.
(Italy Gourmet Tour)
(Photos at the photo wall)
There's an island called Burano.
It all says how pretty IU is.
(Everyone says how pretty IU is)
I see. She made a music video here.
("Every End of the Day" by IU)
(Burano is where IU's music video was filmed)
Her music video was filmed there.
Look at this.
Photos with these buildings in the background.
You can also make it look like...
Andy Warhol's work.
You can get a picture like modern art.
You can take a waterbus to get to the island.
There's a waterbus.
It says that.
It's a waterbus.
(Waterbuses are an essential means of transportation)
If we take a water taxi,
it will cost about $10,000.
Taxi would cost a lot.
So we will take a waterbus for the first time.
(One ticket, $9.70, all-day ticket, $26)
Even if you bought it yesterday,
it starts to count down after you use the ticket.
It doesn't count down if you don't use it.
It starts as soon as you use the ticket.
Some people use waterbus like a tourist bus.
They buy an all-day ticket
and tour around the city.
- They go around the whole city? / - That's right.
It's like a cheap gondola.
(They head to Burano)
Even buses are fun in Venice.
This is a bus.
All I can see is water as I'm standing.
- We should sit to enjoy the view. / - We should sit.
All I can see is water this way.
My head is not supposed to touch the ceiling.
(He's so tall)
Sikyung,
you should open the hatch and look out.
You're too tall.
It's good that I don't need hand straps.
Because your head touches the ceiling?
My head hurts a little though.
(This is one good thing about being tall)
It's a new skill.
(After running on the water for a while)
It takes about an hour to get to Burano.
There's Murano and Burano.
Murano is famous for glass.
- Glass crafts? / - Yes.
- I see. / - If you go a little further...
You can get to Burano with colorful buildings.
(This is our destination, Burano)
I didn't know there was a place like that.
(Burano, a fairy-tale island with colorful buildings)
It's an island of love.
It's so beautiful.
How did they paint the walls so beautiful?
(The government appoints the colors of the walls)
It looks different on screen.
- It's so pretty. / - It looks like an amusement park.
The place is like an amusement park.
I see.
A well-made amusement park.
This is pretty.
Gosh, we can see the buildings here.
They have a lot of water fog here,
so they colored the walls.
To make it easier to find their own houses.
To make them stand out.
(They painted the walls in different colors)
(It's to help identify their houses)
- To be honest, one wrong color... / - Yes.
And it will just look ugly.
- Right. / - It might look tacky.
This is what only experts can do.
They look beautiful though.
(The pastel-colored houses are in harmony)
Let's go on a date now.
- What? / - Now that we're here.
You know what?
In Europe...
If two men walk together, people think that way.
That's true. They really did.
They misunderstood us.
- It happened to us. / - On our last day.
(A famous tourist attraction with colorful buildings)
(People take photos with the colorful walls)
My gosh.
We should take photos with 9 different walls
and put them together to get a great picture.
It's like 3 times 3?
And you should make 9 different expressions.
- How? / - I'll do this.
I'll take photos with the same expressions...
And just change the walls.
And you will make 9 different expressions.
Why should I do that?
- Because I'm older than you. / - I see.
There are many beautiful walls in this alley.
- Let's choose one. / - Sikyung.
Are you taking 9 photos?
- You know I hate taking photos. / - I do.
But I did it.
(Once you get into the narrow alleyway)
(You see many colorful walls)
It looks amazing.
- It's so cute. / - This is nice.
I see 9 different colors already.
Let's begin here.
This isn't good enough.
This isn't right?
(Now that they're here, Sikyung wants to do it right)
What about this wall?
It does look good because the wall isn't high enough.
We can't do this.
He's so sharp.
(Long after that)
Once Sikyung makes up his mind,
he has to do it right.
He's looking for the best spots.
(Will Sikyung be able to find a wall he likes?)
This is it. Stand here.
Go behind it.
(This is a perfect spot)
It was the only wall with that tone of yellow.
(A little awkward)
(Serious)
Do something with your look.
(What?)
We're the worst photographer and the worst model.
(It doesn't feel right)
Hurry.
(I have to try my best for every shot)
(Looks like a photo shoot for his new album)
It looked like an album cover.
(Passionate)
They worked so hard for this.
They're so passionate.
(He's being the most passionate now)
- Joonwoo. / - Yes?
You should lie down here.
(Shocked)
I was looking for a good background.
(What is)
(Happening right now?)
I can see this.
Move over.
I know it's a good idea,
but why did I have to lie down?
I wonder if it had to be me.
You should turn to the side.
(Serious, obedient)
I can see my feet.
Is it done?
There's an app where you can
put the photos together.
(What would the photo look like?)
I'm curious.
(Joonwoo's photo)
He's lying down.
(This is today's best shot)
(Sikyung's photo)
Sikyung is actually handsome.
It looks like your album cover.
You should use it for your new album.
- Sure. / - For your new album.
Okay.
If you come to Burano,
you should take photos with your lovers.
We didn't drink but we feel drunk.
- Shall we go? / - Let's go.
This will make you fall in love.
(It must be a dream)
(Italy Gourmet Tour)
(One pizza per person)
Everyone, you will be surprised.
Is it different?
It's so soft.
It was delicious.
It's savory and a little spicy.
You'll be surprised.
- It's hard to pick one. / - This is difficult.
What is salame piccante?
It's like chorizo.
Salame has just peppers in it
but piccante has paprika powder
and chili peppers in it.
Salami piccante is like spicy salami.
Then I'll order diavola.
Diavola and...
An arugula salad.
Contorni means a side dish.
I'll have an arugula salad for a side dish.
I'll eat it with the pizza.
That'd be good.
- It was the best choice. / - It was excellent.
(They start making dough in the kitchen)
That was just unbelievably delicious.
(Spreading tomato sauce)
It was good. Pizza is...
Always good.
(Putting on toppings)
The pizza is quite big for one person.
- But everyone does that. / - They eat a whole pizza.
This is a cute glass.
(They have some beer while waiting for the pizza)
Cheers.
It must be cool.
The pizza is here.
(The pizza is finally being served)
I'm so hungry right now.
That's right.
(Pizza diavola)
I'm telling you. You can eat it all.
It's really good.
I think we should change the ranking.
(I want to try it)
It's really good.
- This is pizza quattro stagioni. / - Right.
(Pizza quattro stagioni)
(Arugula salad, pizza diavola, pizza quattro stagioni)
They don't cut the pizza before serving. See?
I'm sorry but I'm going to be a tourist for a bit.
I should take pictures too.
I'll take a picture of you, honey.
(Acting natural)
Cheese.
Say I love you as I count to three.
Say I love you.
(Do we have to do this?)
I love you...
It's done.
(A pizza place full of love)
(They will try pizza diavola first)
It looks great.
Alright.
I'll put this on the pizza.
It was perfect.
You should add a lot of arugula.
(This is torture)
(It's Sikyung's arugula pizza)
The true taste of the Mediterranean countries
is olive oil.
I should drizzle it like this.
(Most of the provinces in Italy produce olive oil)
That's true.
- Even on pizza? / - Drizzle a heap and it's still okay.
That's unbelievable.
(He adds olive oil on the arugula pizza)
That must be really good.
- That looks good. / - Hey, it's good.
If you're going to eat an Italian-style pizza,
you have to add olive oil on it to enjoy it properly.
You have to add arugula
as a topping while adding olive oil.
- It looks so good. / - It's making me salivate.
You should really try that when you go there.
It's my wish. You should really try it.
I can't stand it. I can't stand it.
- My mouth is watering. / - I'm in trouble.
Pizza diavola.
The dough is so delicious.
The dough is nice.
I know that the origin of the word "pizza"
comes from "pitta," a type of flatbread.
It means that the main part of pizza is the dough,
not the topping.
When you see the dough,
it has all the conditions to taste good.
The flour itself is good but when they make the dough,
they knead it with olive oil.
- Yes. / - So it puffs when it bakes.
Yes, it becomes like that when it bakes.
(Surprise)
Chef Lee Wonil would eat like this, right?
(He burst into laughter)
(Shocking)
I'm imitating Lee Wonil.
Cross!
(The cross between Sikyung and Wonil)
It's nice to have a married man with me.
I'm just happy.
(They eat and eat again)
It's so good.
It really is.
They're not talking and they're just continuing to eat.
We couldn't help it.
(This team won't be easy to beat)
Our date ended.
So we will go back.
(Italy Gourmet Tour, Venetian feast)
(An hour water bus ride to Rialto Bridge)
Are we coming here again?
You must have really gone there for the food.
Weren't you interested in glass art at all?
You can't eat glass.
You should include shopping and sight-seeing
as you see fit.
We're only showing you the food.
- We're gourmet guides. / - Yes.
(Another peaceful afternoon in Venice)
We came back near...
- The Rialto Bridge again. / - Yes.
Can you see the Rialto Bridge there?
There are a lot of people.
- Next... / - Let's go eat pasta.
Pasta and...
Seafood.
- Frutti di mare. / - That's right.
What is frutti?
- It's fruit. / - Fruit?
They call it the "fruit of the sea."
You said it was near here, right?
There's a restaurant if you walk 5 minutes in the alley.
Ask the driver to leave you at the Rialto Bridge.
That's right.
Wow. What is the name of this place?
(It seems that something is hidden in this path)
Don't you think you can start smelling seafood?
I can smell something delicious.
It's a small piazza.
I didn't know that there was a place like this.
This place feels like it has good food.
- Is this the place from the photo? / - It is.
This is amazing.
This is my favorite place after coming here.
This has a nice vibe.
After Joonwoo ate...
He told the chef that he respected him.
(After the meal, he greeted the chef with respect)
He told the chef that he really enjoyed the meal.
The chef was a very old man.
It was so moving and meaningful...
To eat food made by someone like him.
- Isn't this monkfish? / - Yes, it's monkfish.
- They also have monkfish. / - Yes.
Are these king crabs? They also have them.
- I think it will be good, let's go. / - Looks amazing.
Oh, my.
(They have fresh fish)
Look at how taut the flesh is.
Is that monkfish?
I didn't eat it back then.
This place was really good.
(Beautiful and aromatic Venetian gourmet)
This restaurant specializes in seafood.
They put fresh seafood that
just came in on display right away.
When customers order, they give it to them.
The fish came in yesterday.
They also have Korean on the menu.
Look here.
They have a Korean menu.
- Why? / - They did a good job translating.
Please pick the dishes for us.
- Okay. / - Mister expert.
We have to order fish from here.
They have grilled fish and fish with sauce.
- What do you like? / - They had monkfish.
- I want to eat monkfish. / - Monkfish is delicious.
- Monkfish and... / - Okay then.
Do you know that they eat liver dishes here?
- I like livers. / - They have...
- A Venetian liver dish. / - I have a bad liver.
- That's so nice. / - A very oriental medicine approach.
- Let's order a liver dish then. / - The liver dish.
(Caprese salad)
- I also want to eat that. / - Vongole.
- Oh, my. / - Gosh.
- That looks good. / - That's liver?
(Roasted monkfish)
It's monkfish!
This is amazing.
(You can't leave out wine)
Let's celebrate our special trip.
We should drink it all at once.
There's almost no sweetness.
I thought you would like it since you like sourness.
I think it will taste better if it was a little bit colder.
- It's not bad. / - You're right.
I'm really worried.
What are you worried about?
(What is Sikyung worried about?)
- What are you worried about? / - I might fall in love.
(What is wrong with him?)
It seems that Sikyung is really lonely these days.
There isn't anything wrong with me.
I think that Venice is just a city like that.
(The appetizer came at the right timing)
(Salad made with mozzarella cheese and tomatoes)
- It's so cute. / - Oh, my.
They made it look like a doll.
The mozzarella cheese was amazing.
- Korea also has it. / - Shouldn't we also try it?
But it's too expensive.
(Joonwoo tries just the cheese first)
The mozzarella is delicious.
It's mozzarella that you can eat in Italy.
It's really fresh.
- It's really good. / - It looks really good.
- It looks really good. / - It smells like milk.
I always thought that mozzarella
should have a soft texture like this.
It's really delicious mozzarella.
- It looks so good. / - It looks so good.
- It's good. / - I think that probably...
The tomatoes will also taste good.
(He tastes just the tomatoes this time)
The olives should be salty to taste good.
This is why.
Aren't the cheese and tomatoes a little bland?
They go perfectly with olives than salt.
My gosh.
This tastes good.
- He makes it look so good. / - I know.
Isn't the arugula good too? The aroma is strong.
Yes. The arugula is a little like wasabi.
It tastes a little sharp.
The air is so clean,
they have an amazing amount of sunshine.
The taste of the vegetables
and tomatoes is different.
- Here's the spaghetti alle vongole. / - Gosh.
(The spaghetti alle vongole came)
I forgot to ask for more spaghetti pasta.
(He's upset because there's only a small amount)
- That looks good. / - Gosh.
That was really amazing.
- What is that? / - It's spaghetti alle vongole.
- It looks so good. / - It's the dish we know.
- But it was really well made. / - Gosh.
- That looks good. / - I'm hungry.
The spaghetti was dry but they cooked it so well.
- Look. / - It was so well mixed with...
The spaghetti water, olive oil and clam stock.
It was the best.
Please...
Okay?
Before I chewed this, the pasta touched my tongue
and I realized right away that it was delicious.
It's good.
This is the al dente we talk about.
The spaghetti is dry, so the core inside is still raw.
It's very firm as I chew it.
It has great texture.
- The clams are nice too. / - Yeah?
(The clams are also delicious)
I can eat 5 plates of that.
I can eat that much.
But why am I so happy watching the Italian trip?
- I don't know. / - Yes?
Hwijae, you look a little nervous.
It's not that. Food is surely amazing in Italy.
This will be a little salty for Koreans.
It tastes like eating a handful of seasonings.
But it's good for your health.
- It's not bad for your health. / - You're right.
It's really salty but it makes you feel really good.
It is very savory and delicious.
- You can't stop eating. / - My hands keep reaching.
It's really good.
(It's clean)
I was doing a good job on my diet.
I'll have to go on a diet now.
You have to eat the bread with the remaining sauce.
Hongseok, are you drooling?
- Hongseok, are you drooling? / - I'm going crazy.
(He's almost losing it)
(The next dish is the Venetian liver dish)
You have to try that.
You can't deliver the taste of the liver from the screen.
- That's right. / - Look at that side.
(Venetian liver dish, Fegato alla veneziana, $24.70)
(It's a powerful feeling)
- What is this? / - It smells good.
(The feeling of gourmet)
I think it will even taste good.
(If you take a piece in your mouth, you'll be surprised)
(You're watching Sikyung's reaction after eating liver)
Is it good?
It must be very soft.
- It's melting. / - Is the liver good?
In my view,
they fried it in a high heat with...
- Onions for a long time. / - The onion is delicious.
To extract the most sweetness.
This is the best dish here.
- The sweetness of the onions. / - Sweet onions...
- It's like foie gras jam on top. / - You're right.
- Is it really good? / - It was the best dish for me.
They put a little cream in it, so it was so savory.
It must taste really smooth.
I never tried anything like that before.
Cheers.
(They share this moving moment with wine)
(He's surprised)
There are 3 places that make the best wines in Italy.
They are Piedmont, Tuscany and Veneto.
This is one of the most famous wines from Veneto.
It will be nice to have this when you're here.
It costs about 30 euros. You have to drink it with this.
When you chew on this,
you should drink the wine before it disappears.
You will feel it strongly in your nose.
(The next dish to continue the moving moment)
- Gosh. / - I can't stand it.
(It's roasted golden brown)
(Roasted monkfish, $33.80)
(With the monkfish's appearance)
People call this the dismantle show.
(The dismantle show starts)
- They dismantle it for you. / - I see.
I want to suck on that bone. Hope they don't clear it.
(The flesh on the bone is the most delicious part)
It looks good.
(Gosh)
Look at the flesh.
(Ready to be eaten)
- The food is too good. / - The monkfish...
(You can feel the sweetness of the monkfish)
- How is it? / - It's good.
If you chew the flesh,
the sweetness of the fish sticks to your tongue.
That's a live fish. Live monkfish is really amazing.
This is powerful.
- It will smell like butter. / - You're right.
- It looks really good. / - Various kinds of fish are...
Prepared from the fish market.
You can choose it from them.
They have sole, halibut and bass.
I want monkfish.
Monkfish! Where is the monkfish?
You should come here. If you come to Venice...
You should come here on the first day
and come again the next day.
- It was so delicious. / - You really have to go there.
Where is that place?
- That's amazing. / - Look at that.
- It's almost a perfect score. / - That's amazing.
(Liver dish)
I want to come to this restaurant again.
(The perfect mix of seafood and wine)
(The final evaluation of Venetian food)
This is Bologna.
This is the alley full of food ingredients.
I'm so happy.
We just have to eat to the end today.
Will we eat less in Bologna? That's not true.
Wow, this is the best.
Should we eat while it's still hot?
Thank you for the food.
It's like art.
- I love it. / - Eat, enjoy and love.
This is Italy.
(Paradise of gourmandism, Bologna)
This is the corner inside a corner.
It ended up like this.
- What is Sook's Choice? / - Sook's Choice...
Has been changing among 1st, 2nd and 3rd place.
In the end,
everything fell apart.
I added these on top.
This is like celestial world.
- The celestial world? / - I never encountered...
Monkfish and the liver.
I thought that I should eat it at least once before I die.
We want to try the monkfish.
- The monkfish is nice. / - Yes.
What about Lovelyz?
We also want to try the monkfish.
The flesh looked so firm when they cooked it.
Yes, just like that.
It looks like this when you turn it over.
Yes.
(Sikyung is describing the monkfish flesh in detail)
- That's a perfect expression. / - That's it.
Both teams chose the monkfish as 1st place.
Including me.
What is the first place inside your heart?
I also choose...
(I also choose the monkfish)
Since today is a gourmet special,
they traveled to Venice, Italy.
They made the most of it.
We will reveal the food expenses,
not the total expenses today.
Did you receive the bill?
- Hongseok? / - Yes, I have the bill right now.
- Really? / - Yes.
- It's expensive, right? / - It seems expensive.
But the dishes are too high quality.
Yes. They ate too expensively.
For 2 nights and 3 days in Venice, Italy,
the total expense for 6 meals is...
- Per person? / - Yes, per person.
- 2... / - Is it $2,000?
(Did they really spend $2,000 for 6 meals?)
(What will be the result?)
- 2... / - Is it $2,000?
- $200... / - $200?
- $204. / - $204!
- We even drank wine. / - Do you know why?
- How could this happen? / - It's because wine is cheap.
If we ate this in Korea...
It'd be $2,000.
- It would be over $2,000. / - It would be about $2,000.
I'd like to request this to people.
I'm not saying you should drink enough to get drunk.
But you shouldn't leave wine out.
The liver dish and a sip of red wine are a set.
It's meaningless if you just eat the liver dish.
- That's right. / - Okay.
The Battle Trip hosts went on a gourmet trip.
We are planning to reveal the evaluation form,
restaurant locations and information
on the website later.
We saw We Will Eat Tour's trip to Venice, Italy.
Next week, we will go
on a gourmet trip to Barcelona, Spain.
(Next episode)
We've arrived at Catalonia Square!
True gourmands choose Spain.
The ingredients are so good.
The aromas are really unique.
It's so soft and chewy.
It's so savory.
It's called the kitchen of Europe.
They have the best foods in this market.
This is so delicious.
You have to see Flamenco.
(You must see Flamenco)
Barcelona is the Mecca for food enthusiasts.
Barcelona...
- Adios! / - Adios!
(Battle Trip)
(Those Days" by K.will)