I'm excited already.
I'm filled with excitement right now.
Look at this!
It's so beautiful.
I can't believe I'm here.
This my first overnight trip with a friend
without my parents.
No...
Congratulations.
- Yoobom. / - Nabom.
Let's go!
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Mina of Gugudan, Yoojung of Weki Meki)
(Park Jihoon and Park Woojin of Wanna One)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Continuing from last week,
we are with our trip planners who planned
a flower trip for 20-year-olds.
- Good to see you. / - Good to see you.
It feels like we're getting younger.
We have our 100 20-year-old impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips!
Nice to meet you.
Again, we have the special event
for watching our show.
We have a book now.
Post some photos on your social media
to prove you've watched our show when it aired.
We'll pick the winners and send you a book.
Please watch the show
and upload photos of you doing so.
Last week, Jooe
had a hard time watching the video.
She looked like she wanted to eat so bad.
What was the hardest part?
The meat.
The meat? Was it the meat?
The macarons? The latte?
- The meat. / - Meat.
The bulgogi.
I want to eat it so bad.
My members
love to eat meat.
The 7 of us went to a beef barbecue
and we ate 34 servings.
What on earth happened?
- So... / - That means...
Let's send them on a trip.
- To a country of meat. / - She said she'd go.
Jooe is willing to go anywhere.
- Really? / - She just wants meat.
- I can go anywhere. / - Where?
- Where do you want to go? / - Be honest.
First of all, Suncheon.
- I want to go there. / - Suncheon?
- You have to go there. / - Gwangyang?
- Then, Busan. / - Busan.
- Busan is nice. / - I only went there for functions.
- I've never had fun in Busan. / - Busan is nice.
- Busan... / - Busan is really nice.
You should ask him about good restaurants in Busan.
Nampo-dong is a good place to visit.
If you like beaches, Haeundae and Gwangalli.
OST, octopus, shrimp, tripe in Seomyeon...
I know.
I know, I know.
What was that?
Mina knows.
Mina knows what it is.
She's had it.
And Jagalchi Market.
OST...
Okay.
Today's theme of Battle Trip is
the spring flower trip of 20-year-olds.
The judges today are all 20-year-olds as well.
And we surveyed them and asked...
- Where they want to go when they're 20. / - Right.
And no explanation is required.
It's the top place.
Jeju-do was no. 1.
It means they haven't been to Jeju-do yet.
Who hasn't been to Jeju-do yet?
Jeju-do.
- There are many. / - Quite a lot.
Then, Busan was no. 2.
Then it was Jeonju.
Jeonju has become a lot more popular.
You're right.
What do you think they wanted to do the most?
What was it?
They're at the age when they can eat the most.
They have to eat.
- It's an eating show. / - It is.
They're at an age when they have the best metabolism.
And I don't really understand this one
but taking photos.
These days...
Look how happy she is.
You have to get take photo of a lifetime.
You must get at least one on a trip.
Do you like photos that much?
Yes.
I hated it.
And there are activities and extreme sports.
Something thrilling, right?
Did you expend some energy?
We expended a lot of energy.
We flew in the sky.
You flew in the sky?
I can't wait to see that.
Is there anyone here
who wants to go on a trip with someone else?
I know it's good to go on a trip with someone.
- Alone? / - But traveling alone...
Is also nice.
It's quite fun.
- He has a point there. / - Right.
It's different from a trip with someone.
Where do you want to travel alone?
There's something I've always wanted to try.
I've done pretty much everything,
but I haven't tried skydiving in Australia.
What do you mean you've done everything?
You've done bungee jumping and everything else?
Bungee jumping...
I enjoy jumping out of planes
in a parachute.
Why does it have to be Australia?
I heard Australia
is famous for skydiving.
They have fine views there.
I want to try it in Australia.
We'll give you a call
next time we go to Australia.
Oh, yes. Thank you.
Oh, yes!
Jihoon is a true man.
What about you, Mina and Yoojung?
We would...
- Like the... / - Two of us...
- Us two again. / - Another trip together.
What about overseas trips? Where do you want to go?
I'd like to...
If I could go overseas,
A hot spring trip
in Sapporo or Osaka.
- Hot spring trips are amazing. / - Hot springs.
She's a mature 20-year-old.
- A hot spring trip isn't easy. / - She loves them.
After enjoying the hot spring,
I want to drink some dark beer.
- A glass of beer? / - Have a glass of beer...
It's a dream of mine.
A hot spring in the snow...
- That's the best. / - You have to try it.
My gosh.
It has become the talk of the town.
A shower with cherry blossoms.
It's time to check out the Hadong trip.
A cherry blossom shower.
The fact that they showered in cherry blossoms...
That's the quintessential expression.
I feel pretty confident.
One of the most beautiful things on camera...
- Are cherry blossoms. / - That's right.
I think they would've taken some amazing photos.
There are many people who are too busy
to go and see cherry blossoms these days.
Vicarious satisfaction.
Because of the strong winds, all the flowers fell.
- Lots of people didn't get good photos. / - Right.
But you can enjoy them here right now.
The Yeouido cherry blossom festival was too short.
That's right. It ended too soon.
The actual cherry blossom festival is over, right?
There are a lot of flowers other than cherry blossoms.
Right now...
- With May... / - It's coming up.
It's the month of festivals.
There's a poppy festival in Hadong in May.
And there are seasonal foods
you can only eat now.
There's the lamellated oyster.
Lamellated oyster?
- Do you know what it is? / - Lamellated oyster...
They're these huge oysters...
That grow where the river and ocean meet.
That's right.
- They have a strong flavor. / - Oysters?
Oysters.
- I'm sure they'll eat it. / - Lamellated oysters.
Just be surprised and press the button.
Lamellated oysters and marsh clams.
- Marsh clams. / - Marsh clams!
- Marsh clams. / - They're really good.
- They're delicious. / - So good.
Marsh clam fritters and soup.
I rarely sweat when I eat
but I showered in sweat when I ate it.
They remove the toxins from your body.
You had a shower after eating marsh clams?
From what I can see,
Woojin just likes to shower.
Cherry blossom shower. Marsh clam shower.
Lots of seasonal foods and cherry blossoms.
Woojin, how do you get to Hadong?
Compared to Suncheon,
Hadong isn't an easy place to get to.
You can take a direct express bus
from Seoul to Hadong.
It takes about 3 hours and 45 minutes
to get there.
But we wanted to take a train,
so we went to Jinju before going to Hadong.
- I see. / - That sounds nice.
Please don't tell me
you just left Jinju without doing anything.
- Of course not. / - Of course.
I'm from Masan myself but there were a lot of
local delicacies of Jinju I hadn't tried.
You'll see.
I think the viewers should
boil water for some instant noodles
before watching our trip.
I see.
It means we can't watch it on an empty stomach.
- It's dangerous to do that. / - Have some carrots.
Carrots?
He says it dangerous...
- On an empty stomach. / - It's dangerous.
I can't wait.
From what I can see,
they went on the best flower trip possible.
Nothing could be better.
- Let's watch it together then. / - Let's do that.
- Can you shout your team name? / - Go on.
Ready, go.
- Pink. / - Sausage.
- Team. / - Cross!
Let's watch our spring flower trip of 20-year-olds.
- For real? / - We've won.
- Is this CG or what? / - Oh, CG...
Isn't this CG?
Not at all.
We've won.
It's an actual shower.
- I said it was a shower. / - It's so beautiful.
Hurrah!
- I thought it was snow. / - This is incredible.
It's like someone's pouring it on you.
All I want to do, Wanna One.
Hello.
I'm Park Jihoon of Wanna One.
I'm Park Woojin of Wanna One.
(Top 11-member group, Wanna One)
(Jihoon and Woojin are 20 years old, born in 1999)
Those angles...
Save in my heart.
We're finally
on Battle Trip to celebrate
the age of 20.
(Welcome, Wanna One)
I'm so glad.
Actually, I haven't
traveled a lot.
I haven't even been on many family trips.
Not even once?
Really?
Yes.
I don't know much if it's not my neighborhood.
This trip with you is my first time.
(He feels a lot of pressure)
Do you have a dream when you go on a trip?
It's his first trip.
My dream is
to watch the stars at night.
Have a barbecue
and talk about things.
What about you?
- My dream? / - Yes.
Not really a dream but something I've always liked.
What is it?
I...
Want to go to Hawaii.
Hawaii.
It's my dream since I was little.
- Going to Hawaii? / - I dreamed of being...
At the blue ocean of Hawaii.
Like on Waikiki beach?
The concept of this trip is...
Spring flower trip of 20-year-olds.
In my opinion, to celebrate being 20...
The cherry blossom festival will be over soon...
There are lots of places with cherry blossoms.
Gyeongpodae.
There's Gyeongpodae.
Cheongpung Lake, Jecheon?
- Oh, Jecheon. / - There are so many places.
Jeju-do is famous for cherry blossoms.
Jeju-do is very famous.
- It is. / - It's famous for cherry blossoms.
Huge cherry blossoms.
Jinhae.
- Gunhangje is really famous. / - Gunhangje.
Jinhae is really famous for cherry blossoms too.
But these places are too common.
- Let's find a new place. / - That's right.
It'd be good for us to find and share with the viewers.
They're really considerate.
They want to find new places instead of famous ones.
There are so many cherry blossoms here.
It's like a place from a fairy tale.
That's a flower road.
It's like a roof of cherry blossoms.
It's Hwagae, Hadong, Gyeongsangnam-do.
- Which area? / - Gyeongsangnam-do.
There's no direct train to Hadong.
We have to get off at Jinju Station
and take a bus.
I've never been anywhere like this before.
Nice, nice.
Here we go.
This looks so good.
(He's not picky about his food)
That looks good.
The view is so amazing.
If you're handsome, you look good even in that.
(Park Jihoon)
(In charge of activities, transport, accommodation)
I look weird.
You look fine.
I'm not trembling because I'm scared.
I'm trembling because I'm cold.
It's too high!
It's way too high here!
It's really high! It's really high!
It's too high.
You look a little strange now.
Did I really do that?
It's too high!
It's way too high here!
It's really high! It's really high!
It's too high.
This is a little...
Do it properly.
(Eating with passion)
This is impossible.
- It's marsh clam, isn't it? / - Yes.
He looks like a professional.
Okay good. You're doing well.
(Park Woojin)
(In charge of finding restaurants and cooking)
Cheers to being 20!
Challenge.
They must have gone camping.
That must've been fun.
We have our nickname for us two.
There's PST.
Pink Sausage Team.
We wore pink sweatsuits.
People said we were really cute.
So Pink Sausage.
- And we're a team so... / - Team.
Pink Sausage Team.
They made a team name for us.
(Cheerful and fresh)
(Pink Sausage Tour)
Let's go, go, go.
Let's go.
Why is he going that way?
(3 hours from Yongsan to Jinju)
(1 hour from Jinju to Hadong by bus)
(Pink Sausage Tour's overnight trip plan)
(1st day in Jinju and Hadong)
(2nd day in Hadong)
We're finally here at Yongsan Station.
Ta-da.
A fan suggested we carry these.
Since it's your first trip...
You need something symbolic like this.
Let's take a photo
since this is our first trip.
Let's start after that.
It takes some time
to get used to the camera.
This camera takes really good photos.
1, 2, 3.
- That's good. / - Okay.
It's exciting, their first trip after turning 20.
- Pink Sausage Tour. / - Let's go.
Let's go cheerfully.
It's your first time at a station just the two of you, right?
- That's right. / - Isn't that right?
It's my first time coming to a place like this.
I also like these.
Get everything.
Let's start with this happy mood.
The 8:25 a.m. train is heading to Jinju.
- We need to go down here. / - ??We're on a train trip ??
We entered the train.
(They entered the KTX train to Jinju)
Our seats are 2D and 2C.
- Here? / - Yes.
(Excited)
What is it like for only the two of you to travel?
Didn't it feel empty?
Since you're always in a large group.
- Yes, two of us... / - Right. Because...
Normally, it's loud and crowded but it was just us two.
- You relied on each other. / - That's right.
It's going, going, going, going.
It's moving.
Is this the front?
Yeah, this is the front.
- Really? / - Yeah.
- That means we're going backwards. / - Yeah.
I see.
Good, good.
Here we go.
Congratulations.
First love.
Good restaurants in Jinju.
We have to type in "good restaurants."
How about cold noodles for lunch?
There's one.
(Wow)
That's a big serving.
It's a seafood broth.
I've never seen that before.
Mixed cold noodles.
That really looks good.
Meat fritters!
(The women go crazy)
- Wow, meat fritters! / - You eat it with meat fritters.
I really like meat fritters.
The meat fritters...
- They had that. / - Look at that meat.
(Let's go to eat Jinju cold noodles)
Let's grab a taxi.
Hello.
- Hello. / - Hello.
(It's their first time riding a taxi together)
Look at the flowers.
??The day that cherry blossoms were falling ??
??We went on a trip ??
You can't help but sing
because you're excited.
- This place was the best. / - It already smells good.
I can already smell the cold noodles.
Oh, my.
It's served like green onion fritters.
- You're right. / - The meat fritters.
(Smacking their lips as they read the menu)
They have beef tartare.
Meat fritters.
Just order everything.
- They went all the way there. / - Just order everything.
- We'll pay for you. / - Order everything.
Let's eat this.
Order it if you can eat it.
One cold noodles, one mixed noodles,
one beef tartare, one meat fritters.
You're going to pay anyway.
What?
Where does that confidence come from?
This is quite expensive though.
What about this then?
Since we're eating traditional Korean food,
let's not use English.
That's difficult.
- Because... / - Right.
- More than you think. / - Things like cola...
There are so many English words we use.
Even "cup" is English.
- I saw something earlier. / - Yeah.
Aristocrats from Hanyang came here to eat this.
That's how famous
Jinju cold noodles are.
It's here.
(Wow)
- It's the beef tartare. / - Look at that serving size.
(The beef tartare makes you exclaim automatically)
The beef fritters.
If you eat the beef fritters with the cold noodles,
they taste better.
That's such a huge serving of beef tartare.
The beef fritters...
Dip them in these sauces...
Sauces...
- Sauce! / - Soy sauce.
He just said "sauce."
He said it.
(Confused)
Congratulations, you're paying.
What is this again?
(He finally realizes now)
1:0, 1:0.
I was just trying to tell you something.
I feel wronged so let me continue.
- Okay. / - The soy sauce isn't very salty...
So you can dip a lot into it.
- Okay. / - He's angry.
He's angry for real.
Let's get it.
Seriously...
Thank you, Woojin.
So the score...
Score?
Oh, right!
Score, score, score.
You saved me.
Let's eat.
That looks so good.
I'll have to eat meat fritters today.
Let's do that.
- Today's dinner is meat fritters. / - Dip it in soy sauce.
(Eyes widen)
It made his eyes widen.
That's a really fancy dish.
- Only the aristocrats ate it in the past. / - That's right.
This is the round meat.
Round meat.
This is great
but try the beef tartare.
- How is it? / - This is so...
It's so...
There's something different about it, right?
Look at this.
It's melting in my mouth.
Should we dig in now?
Okay.
The servings are so big.
The meat...
It's so big.
- Amazing. / - There's meat fritters in it.
- That's right. / - It's in the noodles.
You wrap it with the cold noodles.
There were so much meat fritters in it.
Isn't that banquet noodles?
- If you just order the cold noodles... / - It's so good.
- That's enough, right? / - Right.
They have the meat fritters and...
- Let's go! / - Inside...
- Let's do this. / - Let's go.
Let's do it!
Are the cold noodles
Hamheung style or Pyeongyang style?
Neither.
It's neither?
I've never tasted cold noodles like that before.
You can taste seafood in the broth.
It's true.
I saw earlier...
Normally, they just use beef broth
but here, they use seafood broth as well.
It tastes very different.
The toppings here.
They have meat fritters.
You're right.
That'd be so good.
(Jihoon slurps in the mixed cold noodles)
(This is good too)
They're silent because it's so good.
If you have this with the mixed noodles...
(Tip for enjoying Jinju cold noodles)
(Eat them with meat fritters)
Wow, this looks so good.
It really is good.
If I ever come back to Jinju...
I'd come back here.
I want to come back to eat this again.
Where will we go after this?
After this, we will...
(No English terms are allowed)
(We'll take a bus from the terminal and)
(Take a taxi tour in Hadong to go zip-lining)
Where are we going?
Come on, tell me.
Well...
- This is getting frustrating. / - My goodness.
There's this big vehicle that
comes every hour.
We'll get on that vehicle
and go to Hadong, Gyeongsangnam-do.
We'll do something very active.
- And very fun. / - Good, good.
That's what I have planned.
You just need to have fun.
Okay then.
Woojin will pay for the meal.
Congratulations.
I would really like to
help him out.
I realize why they never talked.
- Hey! / - $63...
- The result is... / - Hey!
That was his sneeze?
On purpose...
You did that on purpose, right?
Was that a real sneeze?
That's my real sneeze.
It is?
Let's do a high-five.
Sure.
- High-five. / - You've given up now.
Well, let's go. Let's go.
Let's get it.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Let's go, let's go.
Can you do activities in the sky?
I could never do skydiving
or bungee jumping.
But I'm not scared of the Viking.
Because you have safety gear
and you're sitting down.
Then I'll look for an activity
that you and I
can enjoy together.
(What is the perfectly safe activity Jihoon prepared?)
(She gets the goosebumps)
- That looks so much fun. / - That's scary.
It's scary.
It was really high.
(The zip-line is placed at a dizzying height)
(He's utterly nervous)
(What will happen to Woojin?)
The weather...
It's perfect spring weather.
We're finally here.
Hadong.
But how are we going to get there?
That's why I prepared this.
- What? Taxi? / - I... Yes.
It's not a regular taxi.
This isn't an ordinary taxi.
- It is... / - What is it?
It's a Hadong taxi tour.
It's $40 for 2 hours.
- Really? / - Yes.
He'll take us to our destinations.
There's such a thing?
- There's a taxi tour? / - That's right.
You can call them
but I already booked it online.
If it's $40 for 2 hours, that's so...
- That's really cheap. / - That's cheap.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. / - Let's get going.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
It's cool in here.
35 years with no accidents.
No accidents for 35 years.
That could be better in a tourist destination.
- Yes. / - Where are you going first?
Please take us to the zip-line on Geumosan.
Okay.
Thank you.
Geumosan zip-line?
Yes.
What's a zip-line?
The zip-line at Geumosan...
The whole route lasts for about 3,200m.
It's the longest zip-line in Asia.
It's the longest in Asia?
The longest in Asia?
- The driver... / - For 2 hours...
- He's lived in Hadong the whole time. / - He explains it?
- He explains. / - He was well-informed.
Hadong is 1 town with 12 townships.
The townships are all clustered around Jirisan.
Hadong is best known for cherry blossoms.
There's a river that runs along.
So different.
Is that a painting or what?
The flowers bloom so beautifully.
It's the most beautiful road in Korea.
The cherry blossoms there are over 100 years old
and from Hwagae Market to Ssanggyesa, for 5km,
they have been preserved as is.
Is it the perfect time to visit now?
It's the peak season right now.
You won't be able to close your mouth.
You'll be like, "Wow."
For the food in Hadong...
Right now, it's marsh clam season.
We're famous for marsh clam soup.
And the lamellated oysters from the river.
- They're from the river. / - So big.
- That's so big. / - The oysters were huge.
And green tea.
These are things you must try
if you visit Hadong.
That's Geumosan.
What do you think? Can you do the zip-line?
I don't know.
It... It's... It's probably high, right?
It's probably not that high.
You can do it.
(The zip-line course)
($40 per adult on a weekday)
- 120km? / - 120km per hour?
Check out the view.
(You can see the Dado Sea in Section 3)
(First, they weigh you)
Why? Why do they take your weight?
The safety gear differs depending on your weight.
Sook, you can't measure your weight?
I won't ride it.
It's not about the actual figure.
It's shows L, XL,
S. That's what it shows.
- Oh, really? / - Yes.
It's not the actual number.
- It doesn't tell the numbers. / - Then I can try it.
Then I can weigh myself.
You're right.
Want to go together?
Let's go together.
I can't wait.
- I hear it's really fast. / - Zip-wire.
Just wait.
We're coming.
(They arrive at the top of Geumosan)
No way.
This is amazing.
Great.
- This is scary. / - Let's try this.
I'm nervous.
(They bravely head to the deck where they'll start)
(Wow)
(Jihoon isn't scared at all)
Wow, he's on.
(He's still excited)
Hey, this looks scary.
Look at that.
Isn't it scary with your legs in the air?
(I'm not scared, I'm not scared)
Hey, right now...
I'm no trembling because I'm scared.
It's because I'm cold.
Okay, okay.
This is okay. I can handle this.
- Exactly. This is nothing. / - Okay.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3.
Okay.
Let's go!
What's going on?
I thought I was starting but I guess not.
That wasn't the start?
Here we go.
Excuse me?
1, 2, 3.
- What? / - Buckle.
(You startled me)
I didn't hear what he said.
1, 2, 3.
- What? / - Buckle.
(You scared me)
You scared me!
- We're starting now. / - Okay.
Go!
Is it Jihoon?
- Is it Jihoon? / - 4.
3.
2.
- Let's go. / - 1.
3.
2.
- Let's go. / - 1.
Go!
- Starting at the same time. / - I heard...
Jihoon was starting first.
Go!
It's so fast.
Wow, that's fast.
(Hooray!)
It really looks fun.
- That looks really fun. / - Here's something to note.
The further you lie back, the faster you go.
If you sit up, you slow down.
I'll have to sit up no matter what.
No, you need to lie back.
(They're having two completely different experiences)
(Jihoon is enjoying the ride)
(Enjoying the scenery and the thrill at the same time)
(Meanwhile, the scared Woojin)
My hair is prickling. It's prickling.
My hair is prickling my face.
Hey, this is awesome.
It's too fast.
What's going on?
(Even their landing reactions are different)
This is so fun.
It's so much fun.
I knew it.
Come down now.
Yes.
Release your grip.
(Yelp)
Where am I?
Oh, here.
Mina, Yoojung, are you good with rides?
I love things like this.
- I hate them. / - You do?
I get too scared.
This isn't too bad, right?
I can't even ride the Viking.
- I can't handle the feeling of falling. / - Exactly.
- I just can't... / - You should ride with Sook.
Want to try the Slingshot with me?
Sounds great.
- Do you know what it is? / - I don't.
What's that?
(The Slingshot is incomparable to a zip-line)
(It's better that you don't know)
Stretch your legs out.
Okay.
3.
2.
1.
Go.
Pink Sausage Tour!
- Hooray! / - But...
It'd be worth it for the view.
Jihoon got his arms in the air.
It's high. It's so high.
It's so high here.
It's really high up here.
It's so high.
It's too high.
It's really high up here.
You should've tried letting go.
It's too fast. Sit up.
Sit up more. Sit up more.
I'm just so...
(Woojin held onto the line tightly)
(But he succeeds in letting go)
Hooray!
I've let go.
I'm enjoying the view.
(He makes a scene when he lands)
You're starting to enjoy it now,
right?
He looks like a fool.
He's the famous fool at Geumosan.
Geumo fool.
We've completed Section 3.
We've come back after completing the zip-line.
I let go of the line at the end.
You did?
- Yes. / - You really did.
When I let go of the line,
it felt like my body was free falling.
(He reenacts the flapping since he's hyper)
(When he takes off the gear for the zip-line)
Is it my imagination?
- What is it? / - I feel dizzy.
Did your legs go weak?
I'm dizzy.
(Cracking up)
Are you alright?
(Don't talk to me)
Now that I know it's the longest zip-line in Asia,
I do want to try it once.
Right.
How long does it take?
The total distance is 3.2km. It takes about 6 minutes.
6 minutes?
It's really short.
(Day 1 of Pink Sausage Tour)
(Cherry blossom camping)
All long here.
It's like that in Hadong.
Is it all along the road?
Yes, it's around 28 to 30km.
This taxi tour is nice.
He'll wait for you when you get off, right?
That's right.
What the?
(Heart attack)
This is the best time of year.
You came at the right time.
We came at the perfect time.
Yes you did.
It's beautiful.
It's nice admiring cherry blossoms in a taxi.
(In no time, the sun sets)
Now, we are...
We have to buy the meat and food.
Here we go.
- We're at the supermarket. / - We're at the mart.
I'm going to
cook for you today.
I've never cooked this on TV.
- Park Woojin's recipe? / - Okay.
I like it.
I'm really good at cooking.
You're good at cooking.
I'm not that good
but I used to cook for myself a lot.
2 packs of pork belly and
1 pack of pork shoulder.
- By the way... / - Yes?
Since it's
our first trip as 20-year-olds...
I mean, we're here on a trip by ourselves.
Soda might not suffice.
It's not enough.
Why don't we get some other beverage?
- Today? / - Yes.
For the first time? Like adults?
Yes, we can get them for the first time like adults.
This feels like...
Can we do this?
I feel like I'm committing a crime.
I wonder if we're allowed to do this.
Then...
I feel like I'm committing a crime.
Let's do this.
You can't drink soju.
Let's go.
You can't even drink soju.
Hold on.
(He puts them back right away)
I think one of these is enough.
I'll have the same one then.
Nice.
Okay. We have our alcohol.
It feels weird.
You bought too much.
Ham and all... That's all included in the expenses.
(Cherry blossoms are in full bloom on their first night)
Welcome.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Hello.
- Come this way. / - Okay.
Hi.
How cute.
He's so cute.
(Wow)
This is it.
Thank you.
(Wow)
Wow, it's nice.
- Goodness. / - That was my first time in a caravan.
Yeah...
This could be better.
Yeah.
Once I get my license,
I'm going to travel in a caravan.
- Great idea. / - Right?
I didn't know it was that nice.
We have knives, spoons, and pots.
It's my first time in a caravan.
Me too.
- I've always wanted to drive one... / - Me too!
Bunk beds?
Should we...
Sleep together in the lower bed?
Hey!
Why?
Why? Why?
His sneezes are so unique.
Do you really sneeze like that?
- He does sound upset. / - It became a habit of mine.
So should we get started?
I'll show you my cooking skills today.
(Chef Park Woojin, the master of survival-cooking)
- Should I address you as Chef Park Woojin? / - Yeah.
(Assistant Park Jihoon, novice chef and traveler)
- Get me a plate. / - Okay.
Yes, chef.
Vongole for table 3.
- He has another special talent. / - Vongole.
- Hurry. Move quickly. / - Yes, chef.
You don't sound like him.
- I don't? / - No.
One order of vongole.
I think I sound like him.
- We should go out with the ingredients. / - Yeah.
I feel nervous since it's been a while.
Why am I getting nervous?
You can put them right away?
My gosh, thank you.
You have a choice.
Garlic fried rice.
Or just regular fried rice.
- Garlic? / - Yes.
I like the smell of garlic.
I always cook fried rice with garlic.
And this is...
That's the proper way to cook.
And stir-fry the spring onions.
(Stir-fry them with chopped mushrooms)
(Put the stir-fried vegetables on a plate for a while)
I love ham.
With that much ham,
it's impossible for it to taste bad.
(Mix in the egg and stir-fry everything together)
You have these leftover ingredients at home.
Right, right.
You can just cook with them.
It's delicious.
Since I like savory food,
I'll add sesame oil.
Can you grill the meat?
What?
I'm not good at cooking.
Try for the first time.
For the first time?
- Try grilling it by yourself. / - Okay.
It's hard to grill pork on the charcoals.
- He has to cook them thoroughly. / - Right.
He has to cook it right.
If it's too hard, it's better to grill them in a pan.
What?
Hey, give me a minute.
I haven't even started yet.
(Flipping)
You must wait for the right time.
Not yet. Not yet.
If you flip too many times, it doesn't taste good.
Wait.
(However, he flips it after a short while)
You're not too bad.
(When should I cut this?)
(Glancing)
- Not yet, not yet. / - It really was your first time.
It's not time yet.
(Is it such a hard task to cut the meat at once?)
(Am I doing this right?)
You're doing great.
- Me? / - Yes.
Right?
Exactly. I'm good.
Are you feeling confident now?
You did a good job.
- They're cooked nicely. / - Right.
(He eats one to see if it's cooked)
How can it not be delicious?
(Woojin's fried rice is finished)
That looks delicious.
It looks so good.
The color looks nice.
- That looks so good. / - Today, this is our meal.
Evaluate my dish.
Thank you for the food.
I'm going to be really honest.
(What's Jihoon's evaluation of the dish?)
(He's nervous)
(The fried rice calls for applause)
This is awesome.
It's so good.
- Really? / - Yes, it's really good.
Great.
Hold on. This is...
Are you sure it's good?
(He takes another spoonful since it's delicious)
Since it has a lot of ham...
I thought it'd be salty.
But it's not salty.
It's well-seasoned,
but not greasy.
Give me an honest score out of 10.
Be honest.
Out of 10...
I give it 10.
(Oh)
I want to try that.
I'd like to try that too.
You should publish this recipe.
- Really? / - Yes.
Success.
Evaluate my meat.
(Time to taste the black pork)
(Nervous)
How is it?
- How is it visually? / - It's nice.
- It looks really nice. / - Right?
(Munching)
Black pork is delicious.
- The meat... / - Yeah?
Never lets you down.
Did I do a good job?
(You did good)
Really?
Yours was a success as well.
It was.
Gosh, to be honest...
I was nervous. I really was.
They eat pork belly with water parsley.
It's a festival.
Water parsley.
Water parsley pork belly is really famous there.
- How do you eat that? / - Water parsley.
Hadong, Gyeongsangnam-do style.
You know, right?
If it's worth having a festival...
You wrap meat with water parsley and eat it.
- With raw water parsley? / - I know this.
(Straight to his mouth)
What do you think?
(It's good)
What's this?
(He keeps eating water parsley)
Are you a goat?
I love the smell of water parsley.
- Does it go well with pork belly? / - Really well.
It makes you healthy.
- It cleans your blood. / - Right.
(It suits his taste)
It doesn't have a strong smell.
(Mmm)
I get what you mean.
I like cooking...
And grilling meat like this.
Is it time for the beer?
Here we go.
I knew something was missing.
Anyway, we should finish pork neck.
Why am I nervous?
I feel like I'm doing something wrong.
Gosh. It's alcohol.
Anyway...
- We're grownups now. / - We're 20.
We're grownups.
Let's open them.
Go, go.
(They open the cans)
Pink Sausage Tour. To us at 20.
Pink Sausage Tour.
Cheers to being 20.
The way he holds the can looks a bit awkward.
- Right? / - It does.
It looks a bit awkward.
So it was your first time traveling,
camping and having a beer...
- Everything was a first, right? / - Yes.
It was our very first time.
Anyway,
it's nice that we're camping.
I feel comfortable.
There's no...
Stress.
We're freely traveling and drinking alcohol
just the two of us.
I can't ask for more.
Hey, look!
That's amazing.
Hey.
I was literally speechless just now.
I can't believe I'm seeing this.
We're watching the moon rise on our first trip.
I've never seen something like this.
I don't know what to say.
If I climb that mountain,
I feel like the moon will be right in front of me.
We picked the right day.
It looks beautiful.
I'm really looking forward to tomorrow.
Challenge.
- Challenge. / - The moon is beautiful.
Korea is so nice.
It's nice to go camping like that.
So pretty.
- This is the start. / - Is it the cherry blossom shower?
They're in full bloom.
(They wake up in Hadong)
(It's been a while since they had such a deep sleep)
It was really warm there.
It was so...
(Bedtime is over)
(Snorting)
(Look at his hair)
Both of them look funny.
(We're idol singers, we're Wanna One)
He's staggering.
(He's still sleepy)
Why don't you sleep more?
He looks like he's not really awake.
Oh, no.
(He brushes his teeth powerfully)
(He washes his face like a tough man)
(Lastly, he gazes in the mirror)
My skin is too...
He has nice skin.
Are you having a cup of coffee?
- It's plum tea. / - Plum tea?
- I drink plum tea in the morning. / - Look at his hair.
That's fur attached to the hoodie, right?
Yes.
Yes. Yes.
It's attached to the hoodie.
(In a furry hoodie)
(He drinks a cup of plum tea)
(Brushes his teeth with power)
(Where is the Pink Sausage Tour going today?)
It looks like it's snowing.
Amazing.
(Flower road tour!)
It's really long.
(They enjoy flower rain)
Oh, yeah.
(They drink flower tea)
(He looks cute with his snaggletooth)
(They drive on a flowery road)
(They eat oysters)
It's as big as his face.
(They ride a canoe)
(Enjoying the thrills)
This is amazing.
(Flower road tour, start)
- That's around 4 to 5km, right? / - So pretty.
- It's really pretty. / - Really...
I know.
This is...
The 4km cherry blossom road.
- 4km? / - Yes.
It's the Ssanggyesa 4km cherry blossom road.
Cherry blossoms line the road for 5km.
There are about 1,200 cherry trees here.
It's so beautiful.
If a boy and girl hold hands
and walk this road...
They can grow old together and live happily.
Wow, is that all connected?
I get why it's called a cherry blossom road.
Amazing.
The trees are huge.
I get why people say it's different here.
They're around 40 to 50 years old.
- Look at the flowers falling. / - It's like CG.
It's so beautiful.
- Cherry blossoms. / - Goodness.
It looks gorgeous.
It's beautiful.
It does take some time to get here
from Hwagae Market.
But you must visit here.
Look at the flowers on the wooden deck.
The cherry blossoms are falling.
Here you can see cherry blossoms are raining.
I highly recommend this place.
This is amazing.
If you put out your hand,
cherry blossoms fall on your hand.
That's not CG?
They're floating upwards.
It's really like that.
It's like a movie.
It's so beautiful.
Look at them flying in the wind.
It looks like it's snowing.
Wait a minute.
- It looks like an animation. / - My goodness.
You couldn't make that happen on purpose.
It's so pretty.
They're flying at you.
It really isn't CG.
Catch it.
He's trying to catch a blossom.
It's so beautiful.
Oh, my.
I must go there next year.
- Just watching it makes me happy. / - It's so pretty.
It's on a different scale.
- I'm hungry. / - Different scale.
I found a corn dog vendor.
I love corn dogs.
We have to play a game to eat corn dogs.
- Right. Everything is about games. / - How about...
A "flower" song contest.
Okay, sounds good.
One verse each.
Okay.
- I'll start. / - Go.
??Not spring, love or cherry blossoms ??
Please don't come too close.
That's too much pressure.
I'm trying to sing.
Why come in so close?
You scared me.
He zoomed in to here.
Normally, wouldn't you dance?
He scared me.
- Right. / - Your turn next.
??The day cherry blossoms fell ??
??That's when I first met you ??
??You are my flower ??
Your turn.
No more, right?
It's hard, right?
10,
9...
- Jihoon is... / - ??Buy some flowers ??
??Buy some flowers ??
??Oh, yeah ??
Don't you know this song?
Name the title and the artist.
- Really? / - Yes.
It's buy some flowers.
(First time they've heard this)
It's your turn now.
It's really hard to think of songs with "flower."
I thought of one.
??Come to me when the cosmos blooms ??
??Oh, yeah ??
Is he making up this song?
What kind of nonsense song is this?
What are you on about?
I've never heard of that song.
I understand if you don't know the song.
I don't know such a song.
You really don't know this song?
Who is the artist?
Park Woojin.
(It's my song)
The artist is Park Woojin?
The person buying corn dogs is Park Woojin too.
I couldn't think of any.
Hello.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Just two please.
Two corn dogs
and two peach ice teas please.
- Two peach ice teas? / - Yes.
- You look familiar. / - Pardon?
Aren't you on TV?
- Yes, we're on TV a little. / - Yes.
Goodness.
Do you know Wanna One?
- What? / - Do you know Wanna One?
Wanna One.
- Wanna One? / - Yes.
What's that?
Wanna One.
What is this?
It's sugar.
You dip the corn dogs in sugar.
(This is the best way to eat corn dogs)
That's delicious.
That's the trend these days.
- Thank you. / - It's salty and sweet.
It's self-serve
but I'll do it for you, since you're Wanna One.
Thank you.
- Thank you. / - Good-bye.
- Bye. / - Bye.
- Wow, corn dog. / - It's been so long...
Since I ate a corn dog.
- It's good. / - That looks so good.
- We had a snack. / - Yeah.
Now let's go for real food.
Since we ate while standing, let's sit down and eat.
We should eat while lying down.
Okay, let's go.
(Chomp)
(Pink Sausage Tour)
(Cross)
I don't know dance well.
What kind of dance is that?
That's random dancing.
That's nice.
Let's rest and drink some tea.
Tea...
It's high-quality green tea.
It's so nice.
(They even have delicious tea that has pretty colors)
- That's so pretty. / - That's amazing.
This place is nice.
What do people usually drink when they're here?
This is the town of green tea,
so people drink a lot of green tea.
- Green tea? / - Yes.
The ujeon leaf is the best one.
- Ujeon? / - It's the highest quality leaf.
I'll try the ujeon tea.
- We should also try the ice cream. / - Yes.
- I want green tea ice cream. / - That sounds good.
- About you? / - I drink more green tea than water.
We'll have green tea...
And red balloon flower?
Red balloon flower ice cream sounds fancy.
There are so many tea cups.
I was so shocked.
Why?
You'd feel like drinking tea there.
I was really surprised.
It's a terrace.
Like green tea field.
They made it like a green tea terrace?
Since green tea is the most famous here.
It's like a terrace...
What a great idea.
(Tea ceremony time with Jihoon)
This is called a "chaho."
- It's where the tea is stored. / - I see.
- Now you add some water to the "suku." / - I see.
Then you warm the cup.
That's the way.
Next.
- That's not easy. / - Next.
Pour water in here again.
Then you drink the tea in this.
Don't soak the tea for too long.
Just count to 15.
So around 15 seconds.
Just count to 15,
then pour it.
Then you can drink it.
- She's teaching them so nicely. / - Pour it like this.
Green tea tastes better like that.
- So they say. / - Yes.
The green tea is complete.
Drink up.
It's hot.
You filled it to the brim so I can't pick it up.
It's too hot.
This...
The ice cream is losing its shape.
Let's try the ice cream first.
Let's eat the ice cream...
- Until the tea cools. / - Okay.
- The red balloon flower. / - This is green tea.
- That looks so good. / - Try the green tea.
How good must it be?
It's different from ordinary green tea ice cream.
It tastes like we're really drinking green tea.
I really like it.
It has the sweet but bitter taste of green tea.
I'll try the red balloon flower.
I usually don't like balloon flower.
It has that strong bitter taste.
- It tastes healthy. / - Let's see...
If we're the same.
I really want to try that.
- The balloon flower? / - Yes.
We had a bias toward it at first.
Because it's balloon flower.
- I don't really like bitter foods. / - Try another bite.
I tried it out of curiosity.
(He quickly takes a bite)
Is this balloon flower?
It doesn't taste like it at all.
It's a flavor I never imagined.
It kind of tastes like coffee as well.
They made balloon flower taste really nice.
If you don't say it's balloon flower, no one would know.
- Really? / - Yes.
That's interesting.
If there was green tea grass,
I would eat grass all day.
If it tastes like this.
- It must be really good. / - You've fallen for it.
Hey, the soup.
- Hey, the soup. / - Soup?
Soup?
We have to try this.
It's not too hot now.
Soup...
(Tasting)
(Scratching)
Why do I taste green tea ice cream?
Me too.
They ate something too strong first.
It tastes like rinsing your mouth with water
after eating ice cream.
The ice cream is too strong.
It's too sweet.
- If you eat the overpowering one first... / - Right.
You won't taste anything.
We drank some tea and the weather is nice.
I'll write a poem.
Sounds good.
The thing I remember...
I'll recite a poem with red balloon flower.
Alright.
I'll do Hadong green tea.
You're going to break it.
Let's write it reverently.
(He writes with one stroke of a brush)
The green tea is so good.
(He poured to the brim again)
(Sighing)
It's hard.
Can I change my topic?
Is this also a competition?
Yes.
- It's a competition? / - It's a competition.
(That's his 10th cup of tea)
(He's had green tea)
- He's got a food coma. / - Food coma.
I'm done.
I'm finally done.
Okay, read it out loud.
You'll regret if I read first.
(Did he use his brain too hard?)
This is a wonderful poem.
I'll read mine.
Ha.
There's no other way.
Dong.
I can only stomp my feet.
Green.
When I knock...
Tea.
I'll kick you.
You failed.
What is that?
It's not about red balloon flower.
I wrote an 8-line poem.
That's difficult.
I did Scenic Road of Korea.
Scen.
There is a group.
(It's a good start)
Ic.
They were picked by the nation.
Ro.
They're like brothers.
Ad.
They have a lot of charm.
Of.
They're manly.
Ko.
They're good at a lot of things.
Re.
They gathered as one like destiny.
Now they...
A.
Want to reach the top.
(First place)
First place.
You win.
Complete success.
(Jihoon, buy 100 cups)
Didn't you enjoy the cherry blossoms
with your eyes?
Yes.
How about enjoying the cherry blossoms
with your mouth?
Yes.
That sounds excellent.
Let's put a flag here.
Here?
I thought it was a commercial.
(Lamellated oyster)
- It's finally here. / - Time for the oysters.
We finally get to see it.
(Plus enjoying the cherry blossoms while driving)
From Seoul,
they don't just drop by.
They come just to eat the oysters.
He's the driver from yesterday.
They did a taxi tour on the second day too.
The biggest oyster I've seen
was the size of two hands.
- An oyster? / - Yes.
It's bigger than these chopsticks.
It's as big as your shoes.
It's as big as their faces.
I have to go there to eat that.
(They also have this refreshing dish)
(Marsh clam soup)
That looks so good.
- They're so big. / - They're all shells.
Oyster shells.
It has that smell.
That oyster smell.
I smelled the ocean there.
- You're from Busan. / - Yes.
We never tried lamellated oyster, right?
- It's a first. / - Never seen them before.
Excuse me.
Here's the fire.
It's coal briquettes.
It's not coal briquettes, it's charcoal.
It's charcoal.
They're so big.
(Thanks to the generous owner)
That's so nice.
- Thank you. / - So big.
What is this?
Isn't this a shoe?
Isn't this a rubber shoe?
Isn't it too big?
It's bigger than these chopsticks.
It's really big.
It's about 5 to 10 times bigger
than ordinary oysters.
It can grow up to 40cm.
- 40cm? / - Yes.
How long do we have to grill them?
About 10 minutes.
10 minutes.
They're called "cherry blossom oysters" in Korea.
The reason being...
They live on the rocks under water.
Stuck on the rock, they open the shells
to catch their food.
Then you can see the white muscle.
So thousands of oysters are on the rock
with their shells open,
and it looks like cherry blossoms in bloom.
That's why they're called that.
(Some says it's because they taste the best)
(During cherry blossom season)
(He opens the shell)
It's really big.
Wow, that's so...
They're huge.
You'd get full off one.
That's incredible.
Now you can use this as a plate.
That one's all cooked.
It's bigger than my finger.
This is amazing.
With the kimchi.
Eat it with kimchi.
That looks so good.
- This is unfair. / - It looks delicious.
I'm so excited.
Try it.
Here we go.
How is it?
It's amazing.
Oysters are usually too small.
But this oyster is like...
Oyster in your face.
It doesn't have a fishy smell at all.
It goes perfectly with kimchi.
If you like oysters,
you should visit here.
It's really delicious.
I'm fascinated that they live in the river.
Actually, I was a bit worried
because I can't handle fishy food.
This doesn't
have a fishy smell,
yet it tastes richer and more
nutritious than normal oysters.
It has more nutrition in it.
Its texture is more delicate, right?
It's less chewy than...
- It's less chewy? / - Compared to regular oysters.
You could say it's softer.
But it has a much richer smell.
It must be really delicious.
It feels like "This is it," right?
You can't go wrong with chili pepper sauce with vinegar.
Yoojung, you're too into it.
- It looks so delicious. / - Marsh clams.
See the round things?
That's marsh clam.
This is marsh clam?
Yes, marsh clam.
I'm not sure why...
But marsh clam is not so tasty in other regions.
True.
There are a lot of marsh clam restaurants in Seoul.
They do.
But you have to go there...
- It tastes richer there. / - You can only taste it there.
It's exactly the same.
It's the same as the soup I had as a kid.
Having marsh clam soup and rice in the morning
is the best.
You put rice in the soup?
Yes, put the rice in the soup.
I always ate it like that.
(The sound is appetizing)
You eat it while cooking it.
It looks amazing.
I can't believe this. It's exactly like how I remember.
It tastes exactly the same as
the one I had when I was young.
With this, clearing a bowl is not a problem.
Marsh clam used to be common in the past
but it's quite rare these days.
It's incredibly delicious.
It looks so delicious.
(Staring)
Are you here to eat oysters or to sweat?
You must have really enjoyed the food.
It's been a while since I had such good food.
The taxi driver mentioned...
That people from Seoul come here just for this.
If I knew it'd be like this, I would have come as well.
- The oysters... / - I totally recommend the oysters.
They're a seasonal food, right?
Yes, they're in season in spring.
They're in season when the cherry blossoms bloom.
That's right..
Then,
now that we've eaten and replenished our energy...
Let's see who is stronger.
Let's do a proper match.
To see who's stronger?
Sounds good.
I didn't expect I would
have to showcase my strength here.
Strength battle.
(If that's what you want)
Thumb wrestling.
Hang on. I'm really bad at this.
What are you doing?
Hang on a second.
Woojin can bend his thumb all the way
to the back.
Then...
(It looks amazing)
Give me power, oysters.
Ready.
Set. Go.
I have a bending technique.
Press it.
It's like a switch.
- It's a switch. / - How do you do that?
I never lose this game.
What is he doing?
(I got you!)
(Why you!)
- This is so boring. / - How does that work?
Like this.
I can't do that.
That's incredible.
That's weird.
He can do it as well.
- I can bend mine this far back. / - Interesting.
- What? / - It bends a lot.
You can do it just like I do.
I can't bend it that much.
I've never met someone who can do this.
(They're searching activities in Hadong)
It says you can canoe along Seomjingang.
It looks fun. There seems to be a strong current.
Look at the cherry blossoms.
I want to do this.
Canoe? Me too.
You do the research on it.
Alright.
Hold it straight.
Things like that might not look fun
but they're actually fun.
You're right. It was a lot of fun.
Because we don't do it often.
Just staying on the boat would make you feel good.
Pull the row to your body.
This hand is just supporting.
Before you start canoeing,
let me teach you simple warm-up moves.
I've done this in Mungyeong.
It was so memorable.
(Heh)
I'll show you my power.
Turn it 360 degrees.
Oh, hey.
- 1, 2. / - It's swaying.
- 1, 2. / - 1, 2.
- 1, 2. / - 1, 2. Good, good, good.
- We're doing well. / - 1, 2.
1, 2.
- Hey. / - What?
I can't see the bottom.
You're scared?
You're the opposite.
- Jihoon's scared of water. / - You're scared of water.
I have a slight fear of water.
If the water is black,
I get scared.
- It's scary because it looks too deep. / - 1, 2.
1, 2.
- Hey... / - It's not swaying that much.
- It's quite stable. / - It is. It's fun.
By the way...
I just learned something.
As you paddle...
If the boat is going to the right,
I can turn the boat like this.
(Wow)
I think that's how you control it.
There are a few people who learn this by themselves.
- I'm impressed. / - Actually, canoe is...
A very fancy sport in many foreign countries.
(I'm a canoe genius)
Hurry up.
Although it started off slowly,
our teamwork seems to be
accelerating the canoe.
Pink Sausage canoe.
Fire!
Canoeing at Seomjingang is great
because the cherry blossoms are next to the river.
We're going straight.
- Straight. / - They're really good.
We can see the cherry blossoms from here.
- It's all pink. / - Even without the cherry blossoms...
It'd be so fun to go there now.
I feel like we're canoeing in a fairytale
and we're sailing in between.
We have a great view
and a great breeze.
We have great water and great air.
It's cool here too.
It's so beautiful.
The river is so blue.
It's so amazing.
It really looks incredible.
Floating on the river
gives you real inner peace.
- I bet it does. / - It really does.
I can't wait to feel...
The waves.
- The waves? / - Yes.
There will be rapids on the way.
Your boat will start swaying there.
Then hit the water like this.
It's stabilizing.
Then it will stabilize the balance of the boat.
As you go...
The canoe might flip.
It's coming. It's coming soon.
You just scared me.
Let's go!
We're almost there. We're almost there.
We're going to the enemy camp.
Gosh, I'm getting nervous.
Row harder!
Alright! Let's go!
This is the fun part.
It's over there.
Do you see the bubbles?
Let's go over there.
Hey, it looks tough.
It's going to be fun!
It'll be fun!
Oh, no. Hit the water.
Hit the water.
It was a little scary.
Right?
It was so much fun.
That's a strong current.
It looks fun.
I love the water too.
He keeps hitting it.
This is the fun part.
- Yes. / - This part of the course.
I was really happy.
I just...
Canoeing while watching the view was amazing.
I haven't felt this way in a long time.
I'd like to suggest this activity to those who are 20.
Seriously.
We're all busy studying
and working hard for our dreams.
But here,
you don't have to think about anything
but the view, the air, the wind, and the water.
It's very peaceful there.
Exactly.
You had a great trip.
Now we're getting to the highlight.
Korean beef is the best kind of meat.
Korean beef.
- Korean beef. / - Korean beef!
It's a golden pig.
- It's a golden cow. / - A golden pig?
It's not a pig. It's a cow.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
You must eat Korean beef in Hadong.
Because the cow feed is made of pine needles,
so one must try beef here.
Which cut is your favorite?
I like all cuts.
I see.
Let's take a look around.
I'd like to eat ribs.
Ribs.
The side dishes cost $4.50.
It grills well.
I want to travel there for the food.
If all 11 of us come here to eat meat,
the restaurants will have to be shut down.
We'll eat up all the meat.
We all like meat.
We shouldn't go to buffets.
It'll be big trouble.
Open wide.
How is it?
The tenderloin I gave you...
Is it tender?
It's...
It must be tender.
(This is it)
(I'll give him some too)
(You can have two)
It's too much.
Come on.
(Yummy)
They went right in.
That looks delicious.
He doesn't even eat any lettuce.
It's just meat.
That's hardcore.
I wanted to taste the true flavor of the meat.
He looks like a true meat eater.
It can't get more tender than this.
Tenderloin is tender and flavorful.
Sirloin and rib-eye
taste like they're seasoned.
- They're fatty. / - Sirloin looks so good.
It's the final course. We're eating Korean beef.
The most memorable thing was...
Cooking, which I haven't done in a long time,
and sleeping, playing and eating in the caravan.
Camping itself was the most memorable.
We visited too many places and
saw cherry blossoms.
- That place was so pretty. / - And we took pictures.
We sang cherry blossom songs too.
That was really memorable.
So many petals were falling down.
I remember that the too.
We have a really busy schedule.
Yet I got to do a great show
with you, going on our first trip
as 20-year-olds.
It was meaningful. We took on challenges.
I'd say
it was a great success.
- You're right. / - That's so nice.
We played games too.
Will we get to do something like this again?
It makes me wonder.
Let's toast with water.
And end it here.
Not that.
Let's end it with what we always do.
Let's do that.
Pink Sausage Team, cross!
At first, you seemed awkward.
But at the end, you seemed so close.
They like each other.
You look like you had a good break.
- You're right. / - The two of us are...
Both 20 years old in Wanna One.
We're friends,
so we feel comfortable with each other.
I love their team
because they ate until the end.
They started with cold noodles and
ended with Korean beef.
Was it your first time eating Jinju cold noodles?
Yes, it was the first time.
Tell us how your first ever Jinju cold noodles tasted.
Be honest.
First of all,
it doesn't need any other words.
You just have to go and try it.
Should I have cold noodles or mixed noodles?
I suggest you to have mixed noodles.
What about you, Woojin?
I suggest cold noodles.
Then I should have both.
Because...
I think she's been to Hadong.
What do you want to eat the most?
Actually,
I want to have the red balloon flower ice cream.
I really love the herbal stuff.
She's like a middle-aged man.
I really want to try it.
20-year-olds don't usually like herbal stuff.
I thought Hadong taxi was
really interesting.
If you don't have a driver's license,
it's not easy to move around.
But the taxi driver showed them around.
That's right.
The taxi drivers can actually give you a tour.
Famous restaurants recommended
by local taxi drivers are the most trustworthy.
You're right.
Not those places on the internet where tourists go.
Right!
But the places they take you are good.
- They're delicious. / - They're really good.
Problem is, I think they spent too much money.
Because they had Korean beef too.
Camping wasn't cheap.
- That's right. / - They spent some money.
Men usually eat more.
- Right. / - They also did a lot of activities.
They did many activities.
- That's right. / - Let's check the costs.
Last week, Yoobom Nabom
spent $162.85.
Let's see how much Pink Sausage Tour spent.
Not including transportation...
Without transportation cost.
For our 2-day trip in Hadong,
Pink Sausage Tour spent...
How much?
- Per person. / - Per person!
$298.00
What?
Wait. Per person?
Per person?
Because...
People...
They rode the zip-line.
They wanted to show you too much.
They did the taxi tour.
- They didn't waste even a minute. / - Right.
- Even more. / - They packed their schedules.
They wanted to show you as much as possible.
- Even more... / - You don't have to spend $290.
We showed you everything so you choose.
Anyway.
The fact that they're talking so much...
- Means they're in shock. / - No...
They shocked.
You guys are shocked.
Will you go to Hadong planned by
Pink Sausage Tour?
Please vote.
(Spring flower trip of 20-year-olds to Jinju and Hadong)
(What will the judges choose?)
A girly trip with flowery memories
and charming tourist spots.
Will you choose Yoobom Nabom Trip
in Gwangyang and Suncheon?
Seasonal food, activities, cherry blossoms,
Korean beef, and cold noodles.
Nothing you can leave out.
Will you choose Pink Sausage Tour in Hadong?
What did the judges choose?
Their choice?
It's so...
This makes you nervous.
I really can't tell.
- Let's see. / - We'll see.
The last digit.
If the first digit is the same, it makes you nervous.
Last digit!
- This side is ours. / - It's one vote.
- Be the same! / - One vote difference
Same first digit!
- Same first digit! / - 8.
- 7, 8, 9. / - 8.
8.
(Jinju and Hadong wins with 86 votes!)
They won by 9 votes.
Woojin, say a word.
First...
I think they chose us
because they felt our happiness.
I hope they visit the same places...
- And feel happy too. / - That's nice.
Even though you lost, you had a good trip.
Yes, Yoobom Nabom did great too.
What's funny is that we rode Bus 77,
and we got 77 votes.
I think we're really lucky.
Seriously...
You should've taken Bus 100.
Special host Jooe, what did you think?
I came here as a special host
but being here together,
it felt like I went on the healing trip with them.
I'm so grateful.
Next time,
I'd like to be
the trip designer.
- Yeah. / - You must.
Please invite me back.
Alright.
We've always been doing it
and we'll still continue.
Next week is another special.
Next week will be very special.
We had the domestic
flower festival specials for 2 weeks.
Next week, we'll check out international festivals.
We'll have
3 weeks worth of international festivals.
There must be so many of them.
We'll keep having festivals.
Please enjoy the festivals.
We'll come back next week.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
Thank you.
(Next week)
Myanmar feels like a world of mystery.
It really makes you feel refreshed.
Sobang Tour!
The colors are so pretty.
My word.
It's so nice.
The sun is still rising.
It's like a dream.
This is so scary.
It's no joke.
It's so pretty.
Let's relax.
Makes us relax.
It'll be fun.
Look forward to it.
("Time for the Moon Night" by GFRIEND)