This is Xiamen.
(Xiamen, China)
- It's so nice here. / - It's so great.
It's so pretty.
I'm really looking forward to this.
This makes me happy.
Agar taste very good.
It's just my style.
Walking around together all day long.
It was such a precious day.
Best of the best.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Yang Heeeun, Yang Heekyeong)
(Mijoo and Jisoo of Lovelyz)
(Special host, Heo Youngji)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip.
Just like last week, we have the trip planners
who went on special trips with their sisters. Welcome.
(Highly recommend the itinerary they planned)
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
(100 judges in the audience)
Heeeun's concert tour is about to start, right?
Yes.
- What about Heekyeong? / - What about you?
I'm on a new KBS show called...
- "Twilight Delight." / - "Twilight Delight."
That airs every Tuesday at 11 p.m.
- I'm on the show with my two sons. / - That's right.
I'm busy these days with that show.
On weekends, I'm in a play called "The Mousetrap."
You're in a play.
- Both of you are so energetic. / - They really are.
- We're just doing our best. / - That's the best.
So many people wanted to go to Xiamen
after they saw your trip.
- There were a lot of them. / - Youngji said...
She should go there herself after watching their trip.
Yes.
- She wants to go there for food. / - To Xiamen?
- Youngji and I made a promise. / - That's right.
- She and I... / - What?
- Sorry. / - Are you telling her to come here?
Come here. It's okay.
- I'm sorry. / - Hey.
I forgot I was in this team.
(She's supposed to be on Lovelyz's side)
- She's so cute. / - Youngji, go to Xiamen first...
- And then ride a boat to Taiwan. / - He's right.
- You can go to Taiwan in one hour. / - You're right.
- I'll go to Taiwan first... / - Yes.
And have a lot of fun there.
Then if I have some time left, I'll go to Xiamen.
Alright.
If that's what you think, you might regret it later.
If you have some time left?
You'll regret it thinking you should've come here first.
- She'll want to stay longer. / - Right.
Have you been to Taiwan?
- I haven't. / - You should go there soon.
- Yes, I'm going to. / - You should go there.
Today, we're going to check out...
- Their trip to Taiwan. / - That's right.
We have never heard of this place before.
There's renting and venting and...
- Kenting. / - Kenting.
- Renting, venting... / - It's Kenting.
- Let's see where it is. / - Let's check out the map.
- It's in the south. / - It's down there.
- It's in the south. / - It's further south than Kaohsiung.
It's like Yeosu in Korea.
- Yes, it is. / - We've seen...
- Taipei. / - Kaohsiung and Taipei.
- But Kenting is further south. / - Exactly.
Is it hotter there?
No, the weather was really nice.
It's not that far from Kaohsiung, is it?
It's about 2-hour drive.
- 2-hour drive? / - Yes.
Daejeon is not necessarily warmer than Seoul.
That's true.
But it's different.
- There's a difference. / - So, there's a direct flight...
To Kaohsiung and you have to drive from there?
- I see. / - Yes, you have to go a bit further.
It's a shame that there's no direct flight.
After 3 hours on a plane and 2 hours on a bus...
- You'll be exhausted. / - That's true.
- No. / - No, it's fine.
- You can look at the scenery on the ride. / - So tiring.
The sky and the buildings were so beautiful,
so we were busy enjoying the view.
You can definitely see the sky
once you lie down from exhaustion.
It was nice looking at the scenery out the window.
Is this place popular among Taiwanese people?
This place is comparable to Jeju-do.
- So it's a vacation spot. / - It's like Jeju-do.
- I see. / - The weather is nice...
And the air is clean.
The ocean is beautiful as well.
It's very blue.
It's where Taiwanese people go for vacation.
And Kenting is the first city to be designated
as a national park in Taiwan.
- That's amazing. / - It's very cheap there too.
- That sounds amazing. / - It does.
Taiwan is in the sub-tropical climate zone.
And Kenting is the only place
that has a tropical climate.
- Kenting. / - Yes, Kenting.
Because it has a beautiful sea,
many people come to surf and snorkel.
So it has a tropical sea.
- It'd seem so. / - Then...
You must have done some activities in the sea.
Yes, we did a lot of activities.
We found a perfect activity for us in the water there.
- Perfect? / - Did it go off?
- Yes, it was perfect for us. / - It did?
- It's going off. / - It goes off.
Are you a thrill seeker?
I'm scared of the water.
But I overcame that over there.
You overcame your fear of the water?
I'm not lying.
It's not easy to overcome the fear of water.
- It's not. / - It's because it was so fun.
Activities are good and all,
but Taiwan is known for having a lot of great foods.
How was it?
We usually don't like exotic spices
but Jisoo loved the food there.
- Really? / - Yes.
- The foods didn't smell exotic. / - I see.
All the foods were delicious.
I liked the savory dishes and rich soup.
You were lucky with the food choice.
Do you drink alcohol?
- We love drinking. / - Awesome.
Awesome!
The beach was nice, the weather was nice,
the food was nice and they had alcohol.
It really went off!
We won.
Let's check out Going Off Tour in Kenting, Taiwan!
Let's go.
(A trip to Kenting starts)
2,3. Hello, we are...
Lovelyz...
We really have terrible teamwork.
We should get the greeting right.
Let's just go with, "We are."
Ready, go. Hello!
- We're Lovelyz. I'm Mijoo. / - I'm Jisoo.
(A lovely group of 8, Lovelyz)
(Jisoo has a sweet voice)
(Mijoo has a refreshing voice)
(Whenever there is a camera)
What's going on?
Is that the way to work?
Mijoo is famous for posing creatively.
(What a funny girl)
(A charismatic model on the way to "Music Bank")
(When she poses for photos or takes them)
(She poses naturally like a model)
So our plan is...
Please spin the camera.
Exactly. Just like that.
(Passion that causes strain on her joints)
(Energetic attention seeker, Mijoo of Lovelyz)
I haven't seen her like this before.
She wasn't like that in the past.
It's cheaper to buy a round trip.
We have no licenses.
Okay?
I prepared these in case it'd be hot.
(She's like a sweet and caring older sister)
It's going off.
(A well-prepared beginner traveler, Jisoo of Lovelyz)
- We have different tastes in music. / - That's true.
We have different tastes in food and sense of humor.
- When Jisoo laughs, I don't. / - That's true.
The gap between them is getting bigger and bigger.
Let's get closer.
We both love getting attention.
- We're both attention seekers. / - Attention seekers.
- Attention seekers. / - I've hardly traveled.
Same for me.
You haven't traveled either? We're so doomed.
- If you haven't traveled either... / - That's right.
Since you both started working at a young age...
- They didn't have time. / - I see.
It was always my dream to travel.
- I can imagine. / - I can understand that.
- Let's find places we want to go. / - Okay.
It looks so delicious! What's this?
Was it also your first time planning a trip?
- Yes, it was my first time. / - Yes.
- I didn't know where to start. / - I see.
Snacks to eat.
- Taiwan is famous for their snacks. / - Right.
I had a lot bubble tea in Taiwan.
When we went to Taiwan...
- I had an ice cream. / - Yes.
The egg roll.
- Do you remember the long cookie? / - It was good.
- You remember? / - Yeah.
(The list of snacks goes on)
It was really delicious.
I really wanted to eat desserts in Taiwan.
You're more interested in desserts.
Yes, I am.
When we were in Taiwan, there were so many fans.
- They dig the way we look over there. / - Right.
What if the people in Taiwan get so excited about us?
Taiwan? Taiwan? Taiwan?
Let's go to a special place.
Battle Trip has been to Taiwan many times.
That's true.
We've introduced Taiwan a couple of times.
You have.
- Taipei. / - Taipei.
Check this out.
We should go to a place they haven't been before.
A place that hasn't been on the show.
- I searched Taiwan's vacation spot. / - Yes.
And Kenting comes up as a related search term.
Kenting in Taiwan.
- Kenting? / - It's Jeju-do of Taiwan.
(Kenting is Jeju-do of Taiwan)
It was very beautiful.
- The weather was great too. / - That's true.
- It's the southernmost city in Taiwan. / - Jeju-do?
The beautiful ocean of Kenting.
- Wow. / - It was so amazing.
- Isn't it Hawaii? / - Is there such a place in Taiwan?
- Isn't it beautiful? / - It is.
(Mijoo and Jisoo's destination, Kenting)
- How to get to Kenting. / - How do we get there?
- It's all written there. / - It looks complicated.
"Kenting, effective sightseeing in Kenting."
Let's just rip this page and take it.
Let's plan one day each
and take full responsibility for the day.
Let's say the planner of the day is
the elder for that day.
- We are! / - Going off!
(Mijoo and Jisoo, I'm the elder today in Kenting)
I'm the elder today.
I'll show you something you can't do in Korea.
Faster!
I'll buy you everything you want to eat.
Just say the word.
(She feeds her little sister, Mijoo, well)
That's delicious.
Shrimp cooked in salt.
Jisoo, I'm your elder today.
(A special course prepared by Mijoo)
We're going to become mermaids.
It's good.
- That's it. / - Looks so good.
That looks so good.
It was so good.
It looks like glass noodles.
(They have a lovely time together like real sisters)
We are going off!
They really did go off.
Let's go. It's going off.
(Going Off Tour, Jisoo's Day)
They're so pretty.
(Going Off Tour, Mjoo's Day)
(Flight from Korea to Kaohsiung)
(2.5-hour drive from the airport to Kenting)
Here we are.
- I can't believe I'm here. / - We're here!
Now, we should go to Kenting.
How do we go to Kenting?
- Isn't this place Kenting? / - We need bus tickets.
We have to buy the bus tickets at the booth.
It's over there.
- To Kenting. / - The next one departs at 1:50 p.m.
There's one every hour. There are a lot of buses.
Yes, there's one every hour.
- Hotel? / - Yes.
Hold on a minute.
- What's the hotel name? / - Hotel...
Jisoo is very meticulous.
- Here. It's right here. / - Thank you.
I have no idea what they're saying.
♪ Not a clue ♪
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
- There's the schedule. / - I don't know what she said.
A round ticket is cheaper.
- So I got us round tickets. / - So you did?
- Yes. / - Where is the bus?
That's the bus. When we show the driver
our tickets with our hotel name on it...
- He'll take us there? / - Yes, we can get off there.
This bus drives us all the way to Kenting.
- It's an express bus, right? / - This is convenient.
- It takes 2 hours and 20 minutes. / - Wow.
The ride is quite long.
They were at the airport 2 hours before the flight.
It took 3 hours to get to Taiwan.
- She's good. / - If they miss the hourly bus...
- They have to wait. / - They'll be in the sun.
- Then 2 hour and 20 minutes. / - Right.
- The airport is cool. / - They'll waste a day.
- On our way there... / - Their whole day is gone.
- The side views were pretty. / - That's right.
The sky was beautiful. Look how pretty it is.
"The side view" is pretty?
- You can take photos. Time flies. / - Right.
- You can take the best photos. / - That's right.
(A direct bus to Kenting takes 2 hours and 30 minutes)
(Traditional Taiwanese lodging, Longpan Park)
Duck? What's that? I'm nervous.
That sounds delicious.
- I get the feeling. / - You already think it's tasty?
(Jisoo found this traditional Taiwanese lodging)
- Look at the lodging. / - It's a traditional house.
- Wow. / - I didn't know about that.
- We picked a nice lodging. / - This is amazing.
Now that we are here,
I can feel that I'm in a foreign country.
You made the right choice.
- Right? / - How did you find this place?
The Taiwanese government built these houses
to rent out to young adults at cheap prices.
- This looks very traditional. / - Right.
- Just like hanok stay? / - Did you stay there?
- Yes. / - Well done.
It was so nice because
we got to experience the traditional house.
(Behind the houses, there's a private beach, Xiaowan)
- It's very pretty. / - Right?
(There's a park with Cingwashih, Frog Rock)
It was really interesting.
It's so amazing that you can see that rock.
I agree. What do you think is over there?
It really feels like this is a painting.
(Follow the road to witness the beauty of Frog Rock)
This looks very Chinese.
It really does.
It was really pretty.
- It's like you're in a Chinese movie. / - Exactly.
It feels very traditional.
What is that?
- We saw that when we walked in. / - It's a table.
(A shared living room unfolds when they open the door)
- A shared living room? / - Yes, there are two rooms.
- It's really nice and clean. / - A shared living room.
- That's nice. / - Yes, indeed.
- Very traditional. / - You'd feel like you're on holiday.
Hey, Jisoo.
The inside of the house feels very different.
- Hey, I really like this place. / - It's going off.
(The lodging is going off)
- You're singers after all. / - That's right.
- They are funny. / - They're hilarious.
Good night, Battle Trip.
- We just arrived at our lodging. / - Yes.
- I researched. Let's rent scooters. / - What do we do?
- We can rent scooters and ride it. / - Scooters?
- We don't need a driver's license? / - No, we don't.
(They can drive along the most beautiful coastal road)
- We can ride scooters like that. / - Right.
- Look at the sky. / - Yes, it's really beautiful.
- The sky is beautiful. / - Look at the beach.
- The beach is beautiful. / - It's a tropical beach.
- It looks like Jeju-do. / - It does, doesn't it?
Riding on a motorbike.
People ride scooters more than
they ride taxis or buses.
To ride scooters,
we need to have a good sense of balance.
- Both of us can't ride bicycles. / - That's right.
- I'm not sure if we'll be okay. / - What do we do?
You don't know how to ride bicycles?
No, we can't ride two-wheelers.
I can ride one with training wheels.
Not the two-wheelers.
(They set out to rent scooters)
Look at the traffic light.
They're holding hands while walking.
- That's cute. / - The lights are very romantic.
- The traffic light is beautiful. / - Isn't it so romantic?
- Right? / - Let's hold hands.
- Just like this. / - What about the red light?
Yeah, what about the red light?
- It's so cute. / - We should check out the red light.
A couple is walking together.
What about the red light?
- They love each other. / - He's proposing to her.
Lots of people must go there for their honeymoon.
I guess so.
- We're here. / - Pictures on the scooters are cute.
- Right? / - Yes.
(They suddenly get excited after seeing the scooters)
(They get playful after seeing the scooters)
We have no licenses.
Okay, scooters don't need licenses.
- That's an electric scooter? / - Yes, that's why.
- Hence, you don't need a license. / - They're charged.
They charge scooters depending on the distance.
You must switch batteries for extra distance.
That's environmentally friendly.
I'm scared.
- They give you a training lesson. / - Yes.
They instruct us first.
(Their first time trying to ride scooters)
(Will she learn how to ride it successfully?)
(Screaming)
(She's practicing in an empty parking lot)
(She can't stay balanced)
I can't stay balanced.
(Meanwhile, what about Jisoo?)
(She's also struggling to stay balanced)
It was so hard to stay balanced.
She's struggling to stay balanced.
You couldn't balance it because you did this.
She couldn't balance the scooter.
(She can't control the scooter on her own)
(Jisoo fails to ride the scooter as well)
What do we do?
I think we'll hurt ourselves on the road.
- We definitely will. / - It's too much for us.
If we ride this on the roads,
we could get into a big accident.
Let's come back here after we get our licenses.
- We can't ride bicycles. / - Both of us can't ride.
- We can't ride this. / - We were meant to ride this...
Along the scenic road over there. That was my plan.
I had no idea it would be this hard.
Can't the camera directors drive us?
I really want to ride this. Can you do it for us?
They're asking for a big favor.
- They'll drive the scooters. / - They're so nice.
- They'll sit behind. / - Yes.
We had to act really cute for this.
- But they edited it all out. / - You're right.
- I'm sure there was a good reason. / - Must've overdid it.
- It must've been hard to watch. / - I guess so.
I'm sure they had a good reason to edit it out.
- Director... / - Director...
(It's better not to watch things like this)
Let's go. Move.
I wanted to drive it.
Seriously, it's quite a shame.
- Excuse me. / - Okay.
- Go. / - Hold on.
This is awesome.
(She looks the happiest)
- My goodness. / - I want to sit in the front.
Go!
This is fun.
(Riding to Longpan Park along the coastal road)
- Please go faster. / - This is amazing.
(But when they actually go faster)
(Screaming)
Riding on the scooter...
- You can really enjoy the view. / - Should've said...
"Go, honey."
I did say that.
"Go, honey!"
- She did say that, my goodness. / - What a surprise.
- "Go, honey!" / - She did say that.
Hello. Hi.
What's the speed limit for the electric scooters?
- Around 40kmph. / - I don't think I can ride that.
(They can see the beautiful beach face to face)
(As they ride along the coast)
Even the sky is so pretty.
It would've been more fun if we were driving.
- Yes, it would've been more fun. / - That's right.
That was a bit disappointing.
- Right. / - Yes, that was disappointing.
Let's come back with the rest of our members.
Go!
- It was so pretty. / - Yes, I bet.
The beauty couldn't be captured on a camera.
- Look at that. / - You'll end up in the clouds.
Isn't that pretty?
- It's beautiful. / - Yes, indeed.
The clouds and the sky look so beautiful together.
- The weather's so good. / - If you drive...
- You can't enjoy the scenery as well. / - Right.
Among all the clips of sky on our show...
- I think this is the best. / - It was so amazing.
You have to come here yourself.
(16 minutes to Longpan Park by scooter)
This is fun.
- Thank you for your help. / - Thank you.
Gosh, seriously. That was really fun.
It was so much fun.
(We have arrived at last!)
We're at Longpan Park now.
We can see the best scenery from this park.
It's a must-visit place in Kenting.
- It looks like Saipan. / - Doesn't this look great?
- The color of the beach is pretty. / - It's breezy there.
Isn't the ocean so blue?
The color of the water matches the color of the sky.
Yeah, I can't tell them apart.
This is crazy. The view here is crazy.
This is so beautiful.
Usually, people come here to watch the sunrise.
- Sunrise? It must be pretty here. / - The sunrise.
(Longpan Park is famous for sunrises and sunsets)
It must've been so nice.
- It was so pretty. / - I can see how pretty it can get.
Had I known this, I should have dressed better.
Looking natural is the prettiest.
Right. You know people with jeans...
♪ Women who look great in jeans ♪
You know the photos boyfriends take for girlfriends?
Take my photo.
(She strikes an ordinary pose)
- You have to take one of that. / - That's right.
The so-called photo of a lifetime.
Great. Those are great photos.
- Hold on. I'm saving them. / - Okay.
(The best scenery in Kenting, photo of a lifetime)
That's good.
Hi, we're Jisoo and Mijoo.
- Where are we right now? / - Yes.
- We're in Kenting now. / - Ta-da.
- That's a beautiful scenery. / - Really.
- It's really beautiful. / - The nature is beautiful.
- It's so pretty. / - It refreshes your eyes.
I would think so.
- You chose a great outfit. / - The green is so lush.
- Yes. / - It's like CG.
It's hard to tell the sea and the sky apart.
It's like that in the tropics.
It became like this because of the sea water.
- It eroded. / - Yes.
- The cliffs eroded like this. / - Yes.
- It's so interesting. / - Waves came up to here?
Shall we go down?
(A different landscape unfolds)
Look at this. Come here.
Stand right here.
Stand here.
(A thrilling view at the edge of the cliff)
It's so cool here.
Wow. This place is awesome.
I feel electrified.
- Right? Like the tips of your toes. / - Yes.
This is nature.
- This is nature. / - Wow.
- It heals you, doesn't it? / - Yes, it does.
Bye!
It's going off.
(Famous duck restaurant)
- Famous duck restaurant. / - Nature is so beautiful.
- Finally. / - Finally.
- From all over the country... / - Duck is a must?
Of course, you must eat duck over there.
It's really popular among the locals.
I want to try something traditional.
This looks good.
(It's a traditional duck restaurant loved by everyone)
Look how crowded it is.
(What does the duck meat taste like?)
(They're practicing Chinese)
Jisoo prepared a lot.
Yes. Just in case.
Order, please.
This is the order sheet.
You take this and order the food.
- If you look here... / - This...
- Duck. / - It's all in Chinese letters.
Rice.
Duck with rice.
Noodles.
Duck with rice noodles.
You just need to know that.
- How did you know these? / - These letters?
I studied them.
- Did you study? / - Of course.
I studied so I can feed you well.
I should study too.
What should we eat?
People eat rice a lot.
- But you can have noodles too. / - Okay. Let's go.
(They head out to place their order)
Let's go.
There. Look.
You choose what you want to eat from here.
Even the sign looks delicious.
You can choose different parts.
You choose the parts you want to eat.
Choose what you want to eat from here.
You choose different parts.
(Every part of a duck is here)
- There are heads. / - Can you choose parts?
- Should we use just one bowl? / - Yes.
- Duck feet? / - They eat every part.
- Wings, necks, heads, beaks. / - Yes.
- They eat beaks. / - There were heads too.
Aren't those duck feet?
- I'll try this. / - Let's go with the basics.
Look at this. Can you eat this?
What is it?
It's a head.
Goodness.
- Duck heads. / - It's a duck head.
- Is it good? / - You strip it down.
Like chicken neck. It's delicious here.
- Like how the cheek is delicious. / - Right.
- Thank you. / - Please make it tasty.
(In synch)
That looks good.
Do they warm those up?
- Yes, you pick. / - And they bring it to your table.
(She is worried after seeing the duck heads)
Will it be tasty?
I think it'll be good.
Though we have different tastes.
People from other countries come to Korea and say,
- "How can they eat that?" / - Yes.
- But we eat it. / - Yes.
I think it's the same idea.
(They want to try the local food with that attitude)
- It's here. / - Ours is here.
- Thank you. / - We...
We did order a lot.
(You have to bring your own chopsticks)
- Chopsticks are over there. / - What?
Chopsticks.
- Will you bring them? Okay. / - Okay.
You call her respectfully only at a time like this.
Well, since I was the older one that day.
- It's fun to order them around at times. / - Right.
When else would I order her around?
(Getting spicy sauce)
The sauce was unique.
I think it might spill over.
- Thanks. / - Let's try it.
I'm so hungry.
It looks like...
- Duck meat over rice. / - Yes, it's rice with duck.
- It's sliced. / - Yes.
- It's garlic sauce and onion sauce. / - And onion.
Does it suit the Korean palate?
Yes, it was delicious.
That rice with duck was so good.
(Perfect for the Korean palate)
(She tries the duck rice)
What is it?
I didn't think it'd taste like this.
- Really? / - Try it.
(Jisoo takes a bite too)
It's like the onion chips.
It tastes like fried rice with onion and garlic.
After hearing what you said...
- It tastes like chips. / - Right?
- They put that in there. / - It's onion flakes.
- It's onions and garlic. / - Garlic.
They fried garlic and onion.
Because it has fried garlic and onion,
it suits the Korean palate.
It makes you want to eat more.
Yes, it's a flavor that makes me keep wanting more.
(Different parts of boiled duck meat)
- Boiled duck is delicious. / - The parts we chose.
(You can choose the parts you want when you order)
Didn't you order beer?
- No, not yet. / - Gosh.
- You have to have beer with that. / - My mistake.
(What does boiled duck taste like?)
- It tastes like pork hocks. / - It does.
It tastes like duck but it's just like pork hocks.
You're right.
How can it taste like this? It's interesting.
It doesn't smell strong.
I didn't even know it smelled.
Right. It just smells like meat.
(She takes the duck leg)
How is it?
(Chomping)
This one is chewy.
The skin is delicious.
- I like the texture of it. / - The texture?
- Duck feet. / - Duck feet.
(Here come the duck feet)
They're two for 50 cents.
(Two duck feet, 53 cents)
(The girls bravely try the duck feet)
(Mijoo tastes it first)
(Having a hard time)
- Is there anything to eat? / - You have to eat here.
Like Sikyung said, you should eat this part.
This part has meat.
You'd better use your hands.
(She fails)
No?
(She tries for the second time)
Chicken feet is like...
- Her face is awesome. / - This is crazy.
Pork rind...
Let's see who wins.
- Seriously, it's tough. / - Pork rind...
That means ducks are more active than chickens.
They're very chewy. The webbed feet is good.
- Webbed part? / - Yes, that part.
- It's gelatin. / - I love this texture.
- I like it. / - It's gelatin.
- You like chicken feet. / - It's chewy.
I like chicken feet.
Because it worked out a lot, the meat is tough.
So...
- It's chewy. / - You're right.
It's very elastic.
I think this will be good for your skin.
People who love chicken feet would love this.
Yeah.
- I'm wondering... / - Yes.
If you can express what you've eaten so far
with your body.
I'll give a score to your menu.
(High expectation)
It's going off.
(They are embarrassed for her)
- This much. / - Really?
- It's not a high score. / - Not a high score?
- I give it this much. / - I see.
What about you?
It's pretty good.
(It's alright)
That's basic.
I wanted something different.
Don't they sell other things?
They have pig tail, tofu and other things.
- Pork rind too. / - Pig tail is delicious.
- Yes. / - It's good.
- It's really good. / - Yes.
I prepared this as a hidden card.
Night market.
- Let's go. / - Taiwan is famous for night markets.
Night market sounds good.
(Going Off Tour, Jisoo's Day)
(Kenting night market)
- It has a great atmosphere. / - Right?
Young people are here buying night snacks.
- There's so much food at night markets. / - True.
The night market is full of things to see.
You can smell delicious food on the street.
Isn't it amazing?
This is my first time at a night market.
- Me too. / - I didn't think...
The night market was on a road like this.
- Is that the Kenting night market? / - Yes.
During the day, it's just a regular road.
- But it transforms at night. / - I see.
- I made up my mind. / - Did you?
- I won't be on a diet. / - No? Okay.
This one, please.
(Chicken skewer, $1.40)
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(They start their food tour with chicken skewers)
Isn't it good?
(Mijoo will not watch what she eats today)
- Fried milk. / - Let's go.
- Fried milk? / - They had fried milk.
Goodness, that's interesting.
Iced milk?
(They fry frozen milk)
Why doesn't it melt?
It melts in your mouth like cream.
- It's really sweet. / - That looks so good.
I'm really looking forward to this.
(Yummy)
- This tastes like something. / - This is...
- Vending machine milk. / - It looks good.
- It tastes like milk from a vending machine. / - Yes.
- It's like condensed milk. / - Like condensed milk.
That's famous in Taiwan.
- Yes. / - Fried milk.
(It's hot)
(Jisoo takes a bite)
It's crispy.
But as soon as you bite it...
- It becomes liquid. / - You're right.
It's delicious. I get why this is famous here.
It's delicious.
(At that time, they hear club music playing)
It's impossible for them not to dance.
(They fluster the locals)
(Mijoo's excitement explodes)
(Dancing vigorously)
(Gosh, this is hot)
(Jisoo is going crazy because the food is hot)
(Mijoo is just going crazy)
(She goes crazy in Taiwan)
- It's so exciting. / - It's so different from last week.
- I'm digesting the food I ate. / - Right.
You have to keep moving while eating.
(Exuding swag with their street dance)
- You dance whenever there's music. / - We do.
(They're excited at all times)
It was so fun.
Are you going to keep eating?
- It's not over yet. / - First trips are bound to be fun.
(It ends with a low score)
- One more, one more. / - One more.
One more.
- She's good. / - She's good.
I heard this stall sells good fishcake.
Let's eat it.
- There are different flavors. / - Let's get spicy.
Should we? Should we order just one for now?
- Spicy one. / - One.
(She pulls out her secret weapon)
How much is it?
60.
It's expensive. It's expensive.
50.
(She successfully bargains and gets a discount)
It worked. He gave me a discount.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
- Thank you. / - You're pretty.
- This is crazy. / - Which one of us is prettier?
- Between you two? / - Yes.
- Both of you are pretty. / - No!
No!
One, one.
(He chooses Mijoo)
(I'm prettier? Gosh, you have good eyes)
(You're pretty because you're funny)
- High-five. Thank you. / - What's going on here?
Did you get drunk from the fried milk?
Did it contain alcohol?
- Thank you. / - My pleasure.
I'm so curious about the fishcake. It's really big.
They cook it right on the spot.
- It was really delicious. / - That looks really good.
- That looks nice. / - Seriously.
It's nice that they fry it on the spot for you.
- They contain squid. / - That's the tastiest.
- Thank you. / - That ought to be delicious.
(She blows on it and has a bite)
- It's delicious. / - Thank you.
- Is it good? / - Yes, it's good.
It's hot. It's hot. Isn't it good?
It's really plump and delicious.
- That looks really good. / - It looks so milky-white.
- Yeah. / - It was plump and tasty.
The more white the fish cake is, the more tastier it is.
- It's really chewy. / - At first...
I thought it would be plain
but with the squid, its texture is chewy.
- The texture is great. / - You're right.
What else is famous here?
What else?
There's milk tea made with black sugar.
- Milk tea made with black sugar? / - Yes.
- It's bubble tea. / - Yes, it is.
I love bubble tea.
I could taste the boiled-down black sugar.
This is good.
(Sipping)
This isn't bad.
- Jisoo. / - Yes?
- Tell you what. / - Why are you calling me like that?
- You're making me nervous. / - A while ago...
- You're making me anxious. / - As we were walking...
I saw a massage shop.
Let's get a 10-minute massage. Gosh, my shoulders.
Hold on. Jisoo...
- There's a 10-minute massage? / - Yes.
- A 10-minute massage. / - Near the doctor fish?
Yes.
A 10-minute massage?
Yes, it was at the night market.
- My shoulders hurt a lot. / - When did you see it?
I'm in pain right now.
Jisoo.
I only call you nicely when I want something.
- Jisoo. / - Okay, let's check the price first.
- Where is it? Is it this one? / - Yes, it's this one.
Fine, I'll let you get one.
(She's utterly excited)
She's so happy.
- Does it hurt? / - He didn't start yet.
- Wow. Okay. / - What am I going to do?
Okay, okay.
- It's only for shoulders and neck? / - Yes.
- That's nice. / - You can request specific parts.
- I should get a massage. / - Yeah.
- It was nice that they had that there. / - Right?
Wait.
- Relax. / - Hey.
I can't believe that there's a massage shop here.
Thank you. Thank you.
(She's not cursing, she's thanking him)
- She's so funny. / - Mijoo, this was a good call.
Jisoo, I suggested this. I did it.
This is nice. Should we get 10 more minutes?
(10 minutes pass by in a blink of an eye)
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
- That was it. / - Which one of us is prettier?
Which one of us is prettier?
- You asked that to everyone? / - No!
- The massage was really good. / - One!
No! One!
(Jisoo got picked)
Oh, no. She's mad.
- Oh, dear. / - Oh, no.
- Oh, dear. / - What is she going to do?
- I can't watch this. / - Excuse me.
- This is so funny. / - Which one of us is prettier?
- She's angry. / - He picked the boss.
(Mijoo loses again)
Thank you. Thank you.
- Thank you. / - Okay.
She asked until someone chose her.
We can have raw shrimp here.
- Really? Where? / - Yes.
It's right here.
(5 raw shrimps, $7)
5 shrimps cost about $7.
- It's really cheap. / - It's so cheap.
They raise the shrimps themselves.
- They do? / - They raise shrimps themselves.
(They cook them right on the spot)
- The shrimps were strong. / - They're jumping.
They raise the shrimps themselves.
- The shrimps were really fresh. / - My goodness.
I'd like to order.
These two, please.
(Garlic stir-fried shrimp, grilled shrimp on salt)
That looks really good.
- You ate that without beer? / - That's salt.
- No, we both had one. / - Coarse salt.
- Beer was a given. / - Really? Well done.
- We had it with draft beer. / - There's a big one.
- Oh, no. / - You know what?
- I love grilled shrimp on salt. / - I do too.
- They'll jump around, right? / - Probably.
They must know what's happening.
- It looks delicious though. / - Mijoo.
(A big scoop of garlic into the oil)
(Sizzling)
It wasn't spicy. It was delicious.
- It was sweet, actually. / - The spiciness from garlic...
I want to eat that.
It's not the same spiciness from chili powder.
I really want to eat that.
It was to die for.
- That's the best. / - My Gosh.
My goodness.
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
- That looks amazing. / - I bet it smelled divine.
- The smell of garlic was awesome. / - Of course.
The beer!
(Sizzling)
It wasn't spicy. It was delicious.
- It was sweet, actually. / - Spiciness from garlic...
I want to eat that.
It's different from the spiciness from chili powder.
I really want to eat that.
It was to die for.
- That's the best. / - Wow.
(Shrimps cooked to a nice red color)
- That looks amazing. / - I bet it smelled divine.
- The smell of the garlic was awesome. / - Yes.
- Beer! / - Exactly.
- "I'm sorry, shrimp." / - "I'm sorry, shrimp."
- Do you have beer? / - Beer?
(They don't sell beer)
(You can drink beer over there)
- Thank you. / - That must be the sign for the beer.
(Jisoo happily pays for the meal)
- Let's go find beer. / - Okay.
Is it that stall?
You can take your shrimp and eat it there?
- Yes. / - That's nice.
You can take your food and drink beer there.
You can buy food and eat it there?
(Shrimp dishes and beer, $7 each)
- That looks good. / - Right.
- I was about to get frustrated. / - I know.
(The cool beer quenches their thirst)
This is so good.
(It picks up her mood)
This is good. It's good.
- Should we start eating? / - Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
Should we eat the original first?
Grilled shrimp is very affordable.
- Yes, $7 for each dish. / - $7 each.
$7? Since it's near the beach.
It's an island.
I bet it's delicious.
Hey, this one is plump.
- Peeling them is fun too. / - It must be so good.
- It was really delicious. / - It was so good.
- It was plump too. / - Right.
People who live near the beach eat the shells too.
- They do. / - That's true.
Even when eaten as a whole, it was so good.
Sweet and tasty.
The shrimps are so plump.
It was grilled with salt but it's not that salty.
The saltiness is just perfect. It's savory.
Yes, you must eat the head.
- The sauce in the head... / - You must eat the head.
When you eat that...
That's worth the entire shrimp.
(The flavor calls for beer)
This is going off.
(With beer, this is paradise)
This is a paradise.
One must drink beer at night markets.
- The moment you drink it... / - I know the feeling.
- You have no worries. / - You're right.
I felt like we were there alone.
- It looks good. / - We can get drunk without beer.
You can get drunk on the mood and the music.
We can get drunk.
I wonder what this would taste like.
(Stir-fried shrimp with garlic)
(The very look of it makes your mouth water)
- It tastes good with beer. / - This is amazing.
(She takes a piece to her mouth)
This is really delicious.
- Garlic is sweet when it's cooked. / - That's true.
(She tastes a piece of garlic)
I just ate a whole piece of garlic.
It's delicious. Do you know garlic pork hocks?
The garlic they use for that is finely mashed.
But here, you can chew on the garlic.
However, it's not spicy.
It's not spicy at all. It goes nicely with the shrimp.
- This one? / - Was it tasty?
- It was really good. / - It was sweet.
When small snacks like this add up,
the total price becomes quite high.
Of course.
What was your favorite food here? On the count of 3.
1, 2, 3.
- Shrimp! / - Shrimp!
I think it's a good idea to order these 2 dishes.
- And beer as well. / - They're a perfect match.
I love this.
I love the night of Taiwan.
I'm going to miss this place once we leave.
Right?
It was a spectacular day today.
I'm happy I planned the trip
and did all the things I wanted to do.
And it's meaningful to me that I did it with you.
- With me? / - With you.
It's meaningful to me.
Cheers.
Jisoo.
What is it?
I love you.
You didn't look me in the eyes as you said that.
No, I couldn't.
- Going Off Tour! Let's go! / - Let's go!
(So excited)
You guys can leave first.
We'll hang out here a little more.
- We'll hang out more. / - Thank you.
- We have many places to go. / - I'll clap the slate.
- 1, 2, 3. / - Where are you going?
- We went to hang out. / - To hang out.
Goodness, where are they going?
You went to a club, didn't you?
(Today, Mijoo is the elder)
I'm the elder today.
Hello, ma'am. To tell you about this place...
Oh, Mijoo.
- What is that? / - This is so much fun.
- My goodness. / - You're wearing mermaid tails.
- We were mermaids. / - Is that a swimming suit?
Hengchun 3000 Brewseum.
- There's a beer museum too? / - It's so good.
A beer museum?
Beef noodle soup.
- That looks so good. / - Beef noodle soup.
(Precious time in Kenting)
- We are... / - Going off!
- Yeah! Go! / - It's going off!
- Are you swimming? / - Yes.
(The sun rises in Kenting)
I love this lodging.
I like it too.
It was very comfortable.
(Mermaid experience)
Mermaid experience.
- Mermaid experience? / - Yes.
What is a mermaid experience?
Hey, check this out.
Mermaid experience.
This must be that...
(It's a special activity in Kenting)
It looks pretty.
Is that you two?
- You have to swim well. / - No, it's not us.
With just the top and the tail, it looks really sexy.
- Let's do this. / - It looks fun.
I like it.
I want to give myself a challenge.
I want to get over my fear of water.
Jisoo, you said you're scared of water.
Yes, I'm scared of water. I almost drowned as a kid.
But I overcame it.
- Jisoo. / - Yes.
Today, I'm the elder.
- Okay. / - Show some respect.
Okay, Mijoo.
We're going to take pictures in mermaid costumes.
Shouldn't we practice first?
We should work on our poses to look pretty.
Like this.
(How do I look?)
I should get going first.
Be bold.
Like a mermaid, you don't have a voice but have legs.
Hello, Jisoo.
(Mijoo is excited as always)
Jisoo looks a little embarrassed.
- Like this. / - I don't want to be a mermaid now.
(It takes 10 minutes by foot)
(Mermaid experience, from 9 a.m. till 2 p.m., $122.50)
$120? Yes!
- It's a little expensive... / - $120?
Photo shoots and video editing are all included.
After saving money on food...
(Here come the amazing girls)
- Anything you want to say? / - Anything to say?
- Do we look pretty? / - She has too much bounce.
Yes, we do! How much?
This much!
I'm so excited.
Okay.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Hello. / - Thank you.
- Oh, my. / - She must be the Little Mermaid.
She must be.
I will teach you how to swim like a mermaid.
- So, just like... Wave. / - Oh, my.
Body wave. Lovelyz are experts at that.
It's like...
I didn't know there would be a mermaid teacher.
(She can do amazing body waves)
Unbelievable.
(Stiff)
I'm so stiff.
But you're an idol.
- I didn't expect this. / - My body is very...
- You can't do the wave? / - I'm actually quite stiff.
(Mijoo does it pretty well)
- Okay. / - Am I good?
Now we're finished with the practice.
Where is... Little Mermaid... Princess costumes?
- Okay, let's go. / - What did that mean?
- How did she understand? / - She understood it all.
How did she understand that?
This is interesting.
(Turning into mermaids)
Does she help us put it on?
Goodness.
I guess she has to help you get into that.
You can choose the color of the tail.
(Laughing)
(Floundering)
That's why it looked familiar.
That was excellent editing.
That was so good.
(She managed to put on the mermaid costume)
She's not a mermaid. She's a rockfish.
I'm a flatfish.
- A flatfish? / - She's a flatfish.
Wait, wait.
(Let me get ready)
(How does Mijoo look in the photo?)
(Forget the flatfish)
She looks great in the picture.
As long as you look nice in the photo.
You can pick the color of the tail, right?
- Yes. / - Yes, we picked them ourselves.
You look so pretty in it.
- That's a pretty picture. / - Wow.
(She helps her with the pose)
(Satisfied)
You got some great photos.
- Yes. / - They take videos of you too.
This is why it's a little pricey.
- They even edit the video for you? / - Yes.
The photo, video shooting and costume hire.
She must be taking a video now. That's amazing.
They even teach you how to pose.
It's like a magazine cover.
Like this? Do I look okay?
- Jisoo. / - Yes.
I feel like raw fish.
- I have a lot of fat. / - Do you?
- You'll taste good then. / - Real good.
- Like... Lay. / - Lay?
Imagine you're a princess.
Yes.
- What is this? / - Is this a penalty?
(This is hilarious)
Is this a penalty?
(It's suddenly become a military drill)
This is so funny.
(Mermaid drill in Kenting)
- This one is nice. / - This one is good.
They take all the pictures for you.
Right.
There's a deep section.
You take pictures underwater.
- I'm scared. / - Do I look like that too?
It must be scary.
- It's because your feet are tied together. / - Right.
That's true.
How does it feel to be up here?
I miss my parents and members.
- Can you do this? / - When was that?
I think that was 2 years ago.
It's cool in here.
Wait, wait, wait.
(Hard to balance in the tail)
Swim and breathe.
Turn and breathe.
(Nervous)
I know how to swim but with my feet tied...
- I don't think I can do it. / - It's hard.
It was hard to get out.
We both can't swim.
- You can't? / - No.
But if you could do it,
it means people who can't swim can do this as well.
- That's right. / - It looks so pretty.
(The instructor will demonstrate)
That's so pretty.
That man is so flexible.
But he's not wearing a tail.
He's not wearing the mermaid suit.
See? You can't stand in that suit.
Still, it was so brave of you to give it a try.
- Such things are hard to overcome. / - It was.
Why don't you two try that mermaid experience?
- I strongly recommend it. / - You want to try?
- It was so fun. / - No...
(They can't be mermaids if they are afraid of water)
You're lying.
Thank you so much.
(Jisoo gets a 1 on 1 lesson)
(Swimming lessons are for free)
(Jisoo tries to overcome her fear of water)
That's not easy.
But since I was there, I really wanted to make it work.
But...
It's surprising how stiff you are.
(She practices over and over again)
But through this trip...
If you overcame your fear of water...
- That's the best reward. / - She did it!
(Jisoo is overcoming her fear of water little by little)
She's doing it.
She does look like a fish.
Fish?
Fish? Not a mermaid?
I got it!
I think it's working.
I should give it a try again.
But I know I should relax my body.
I'm not very good at swimming and I'm afraid of water.
I think I can do it 10 tries.
Try?
(She gives it a try with confidence)
That's so...
- Is that right? / - She's like...
- It's more like shrimp than a mermaid. / - Shrimp?
- Shrimp. / - It's shrimp.
(Mijoo completed her swim)
(Groaning)
My ears...
Mijoo, it looks like you're at a sauna.
Wow, this is nice.
This is refreshing.
(This is how a mermaid has a sauna)
My goodness.
(What about Jisoo?)
(She dives deep in the water without fear)
- She looks pretty. / - She's doing it.
- You're doing it. / - So pretty.
Wow, this is amazing.
(Jisoo has become a real mermaid)
(A round of applause)
This is touching.
In 4 hours.
- 4 hours? / - Yes, it took 4 hours.
It's amazing that she managed to do it
despite her fear of water.
- This is fun. It's really fun. / - It is, right?
It's so fun. It really is.
You did well.
- What? / - You did well.
I win.
I think I just overcame my fear of water.
- Really? / - Yes.
That's right. She overcame it.
- That's what's important. / - Right.
It doesn't matter whether she's a mermaid or shrimp.
(The legend of the Kenting mermaids)
(They are unbelievably beautiful)
(Mermaid Jisoo who overcame her fear of water)
(And mermaid Mijoo live under the sea)
- She looks like a real mermaid. / - The shrimp.
She's a shrimp.
(Hello)
She's relaxed now.
- So good. / - That looks so pretty.
Jisoo is very flexible.
Jisoo looks much more flexible in the water.
(Sometimes they look like seaweed fulvescens)
(If you want to be a real mermaid)
(Come to Kenting!)
How was it?
I had so much fun,
so I didn't even think about my fear of water.
- I mean it. It was a lot of fun. / - Right, it was so fun.
- I'm hungry. / - Me too.
- Are you ready to eat? / - Yes.
- I'm totally ready. / - I'm totally ready too.
- I'm so hungry. / - Let's go.
- How did you do that? / - The tail is heavy.
She can't get out of the water.
Grilled fish!
Stop it.
Whatever they eat, it will taste so good.
- Right. / - We were really hungry.
They swam for 4 hours. They must be very hungry.
- We failed to ride a scooter yesterday. / - We did.
So I called a taxi.
- I think that's it. / - Is that it?
It's a taxi.
- A taxi tour is famous in Taiwan. / - Right.
- We will use this taxi today. / - Really?
- So it's like we have a chauffeur. / - Our chauffeur.
You don't pay for distance.
- We rent it for a few hours. / - For the time you want.
- So it's like your chauffeur. / - Right.
The driver is with them the whole time.
- Hello. / - Hello.
The driver is a woman.
- This is nice. / - She opens the door for us.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Something smells good in here.
(They head for Hengchun)
(20 minutes from Kenting to Hengchun by car)
(Hengchun)
(Humming)
Everyone, this is the garbage truck of Taiwan.
In Korea, they take the trash for you.
But here, the people have to load it themselves.
Look. They are coming out with the garbage.
- They're in a hurry. / - Yeah.
They are busy dumping the garbage.
- Wow. / - They dump the garbage themselves?
They do it themselves.
Some people were running out as they were late.
- Do you know where we are? / - Where?
- This place is called Hengchun. / - Hengchun?
Right, this is the old downtown.
So this place feels old and young at the same time.
There are stores like this.
In Korea, this place is like...
Seongsu-dong or Gyeongnidan-gil.
You're right. It has that feeling.
Hengchun is near Kenting.
It's Hengchun.
- This is the South Gate. / - It's Hengchun.
It is Hamchun in Korean.
(Lots of old restaurants and traditional stores)
It means always youth.
(There are also small shops that sell pretty items)
There are a lot of pretty shops.
It looks pretty.
(Young artists settled here and the visitors grew)
(Hengchun)
(Traditional restaurants and trendy streets)
- Everything is nearby. / - Yes.
It only takes about 5 to 10 minutes on foot.
I'm really hungry.
I found a good restaurant.
Let me tell you about it.
This place is good for people like you,
who don't like spices.
It's traditional but trendy.
The place looks clean.
I know. It's clean and the food is good too.
- I think it looks good. / - You can look forward to it.
I've never let you down yet.
They said a lot of visitors go to this restaurant.
Oh, it's beef noodle soup.
Beef noodle soup.
- This one looks good for beer. / - It was really good.
Wow, what's that?
This one looks delicious.
It's beef noodle soup with different noodles.
(How does the original beef noodle soup taste?)
This place is just like the one we visited yesterday.
- It's a self-serve restaurant. / - Really?
Think about it. I served all the dishes yesterday.
Chopsticks.
You'll go and get it? Okay, thanks.
- Right, Mijoo really used her. / - Jisoo.
- The sauce is self-serve as well. / - Okay.
I won't complain and get it for you.
You're dead tomorrow.
Jisoo. Jisoo. Jisoo. Jisoo.
- Jisoo. / - Okay, fine. I'll go.
Fine, I'll just do it.
Geez.
- I'll go bring water. / - You should do that.
You bring the side dishes.
What is this?
What's that?
They even have soft drinks.
(The new paradigm of side dishes)
This is Korean kimchi.
We can pick the side dishes we want.
- You have to pay. / - You do?
- They have kimchi? / - Yes, they do.
They make it themselves.
- Do they? / - It's raining here too.
It's raining.
It's coming.
(What is the first dish?)
(A dish that's fun to pick out what you want)
(Taiwanese assorted boiled meat, $7)
- This one looks good. / - It's assorted boiled meat.
- It's intestines. / - Assorted boiled meat?
Yes.
It's the stomach of a cow.
It's the stomach.
(She tastes it without hesitation)
What is this? It looks like mushrooms.
Wow, this is so good.
It's delicious.
It's good, isn't it?
(Nice)
- This is so good. / - This is like smoked pork hocks.
It smells like that.
It must be good. It's braised in soy sauce.
I like this one better.
This is...
It's chili oil.
It was good.
Isn't this just meat?
(Beef leg with chili oil)
- Boiled meat. / - Boiled meat?
Just tastes like boiled meat?
Yeah.
(Chomp)
I don't like it much.
It's beef so if you boil it too much, it gets dry.
(It's a little dry and tough)
- I like this one the best. / - Me too.
The stomach was the best.
It's really good.
It's a good cut.
- It's chewy. / - I'll eat it for dinner.
- I guess this is it. / - Beef noodle soup.
(They ordered two kinds of beef noodle soup)
(A clear soup and a red soup)
You can choose the soup
and the type of noodles you want.
(Adding spring onion oil broth)
It was really good.
Did you see the chili oil at the bottom of the bowl?
It floats to the top.
The hot soup makes it rise.
(What does the soup taste like?)
(They raise their heads at the same time)
This is so good.
The noodles are like udon.
It tastes like udon.
I think it tastes like hot pot
without spices.
I've never tried hot pot, so I don't know.
- I think the oil would taste good. / - Yes.
It was really good.
The spring onion oil.
The noodles are coated with spring onion oil.
That's right.
- This is really good. / - I love it.
I want to visit this place again later.
We picked a good one.
Hey, it's me.
- I picked it. / - Okay.
I admit it.
Try the meat.
That's the highlight of beef noodle soup.
- Wow, it looks so good. / - It was great.
- It was filling, right? / - Yes, it is.
- It was very plump. / - I can see that.
It doesn't have a smell.
(Yum)
The meat tastes really clean.
The texture is like tender braised beef.
- Yes, it's like braised beef. / - Right?
They boiled the beef but it has a very clean taste.
- It's so tender. / - Right?
- The soup must be good there. / - Yes.
The soup was so rich, so it was delicious.
(Taiwanese style glass noodles in red beef soup)
You can also choose the meat.
- The glass noodles look good. / - Meat, glass noodles.
- That looks good. / - I really like glass noodles.
- Koreans all like glass noodles. / - Everyone likes it.
(They take a sip of the soup first)
It's good.
It's really similar to those diet noodles.
- She's eating it together. / - It's like konjac noodles?
Yes.
It's really chewy.
Konjac noodles taste like you won't gain weight.
Those noodles taste like you'll gain weight.
It's chewy and delicious.
It was delicious. The glass noodles...
If it's chewy and tasty, it will make you gain weight.
- It has a lot of starch. / - Yes.
But it's zero calories if you enjoy eating it.
- That's a lie. / - Who said that?
A friend of mine said that while
mixing rice with sausage stew.
- If it's good? / - If you enjoy eating it...
- It's zero calories. / - As he was eating sausage stew?
Let's also try this.
I like these noodles because they're so chewy.
- It's not that thick. / - Yes.
It doesn't taste dry and it tastes clean.
I think Koreans will like it...
If you sell this in Korea.
- Yes, I agree. / - It suits our palate.
If you go to the market in Busan...
- They sell glass noodle soup. / - Right.
I'm curious.
- The noodles that I, the elder, chose. / - Elder...
She loves being called that.
It could've been difficult to eat.
But I didn't feel that way at all. It was fine.
The price is also really cheap.
I think you can eat it easily, so I really liked it.
I really want to eat that with glass noodles.
- Me too. / - It was really delicious.
- With the red soup. / - Me too.
- My score is... / - Yes?
It's going off.
(Hahaha)
What do we do about her?
- It makes me tear up. / - It was that good.
Was it enough to make you stand?
Everything was perfect.
The aroma, texture...
It suited my tastes... I liked everything about it.
- She liked everything. / - I prepared this.
She liked everything.
- She liked everything. / - It was better after a swim.
- That's right. / - Everything tastes better that way.
- We were so hungry. / - That's right.
It will taste good.
(They move to the outskirts of Hengchun)
- This place is... / - It says Hengchun.
- This place is... / - Yes.
Hengchun 3000 Brewseum.
- It's a museum? / - Yes, it's a museum.
It's my first time at a museum.
I was looking for a place that would feel new
and memorable with you.
- Can you try the beer? / - Yes, you can also try it.
- Of course. / - So we'll go...
- That's amazing. / - Let's go in.
She's salivating even before she goes in.
(Named after the 3,000 beer glass collection)
Beer museum.
- Yes. / - I've never seen this before.
("Mona Lisa" made by beer labels)
(You can understand the history and culture of beer)
How long would he have had to collect for that?
- Right? / - The owner really likes beer.
(It's the only place you can taste Kenting beer)
(Admission, $3.50 with 1 free can of beer)
- It's $3.50 admission? / - Beers are fattening.
They're tasty but...
- In the old days... / - Wow.
Isn't this beer?
I think it's a beer mug or bottle.
- This is really interesting. / - Yes.
This is the oldest canned beer.
- Really? / - It was made in 1935.
- That's so amazing. / - They have old beers too.
The oldest beer in Belgium.
How did they drink this?
- I think they bore a hole to drink. / - I see.
That's the old can opener back in the day.
- The triangular ones. / - Yes, triangular.
You're right.
That's right.
Oh, this... This is this.
This must be during prohibition.
That's why everyone is protesting.
- That must've been during prohibition. / - I see.
We want beer.
We do want beer.
Where is it?
- Where is it? / - What is this? Do they sell this?
It's written "Kenting" here.
They named it after the region.
- It was named after Kenting. / - Cute.
- It's a local beer. / - Yes.
You get a can of that with the admission.
- You have to try it there. / - Yes, you have to try it.
- It will be good as a souvenir. / - Yeah.
- And display it after you drink it. / - I want to do that.
Oh, my. What is this?
What is this?
Thank you. Oops, what am I saying?
Sir, what is this?
- It's a can sealer. / - Okay.
- It seals the cans. / - Yes.
They put draft beer in the can.
You can only drink draft beer here.
Oh, my.
- They seal the can like that. / - That's right.
(Turn it with all your might)
This is how you operate it.
This is so amazing.
(Canned beer is complete)
- How is it possible like this? / - It's like...
It doesn't leak at all.
It's so amazing. Wow.
(Even if you shake it hard)
It doesn't pop.
- This is so amazing. / - What if it suddenly bursts?
- You're right. / - Let's try this later...
- And ask for a sampler. / - Sampler?
- Do you want a sampler? / - Yes, a sampler.
- Please. / - Okay, sure.
- Sure. / - Wow.
(Sampler set, $10.50)
- They must brew that beer there. / - Yes.
You can taste it there.
Can you take it home after they make it there?
- Yes, you can. / - They gave one draft beer each.
They only sell draft beer there.
(Saison, Chuhou, Kenting)
You shouldn't drink this up in one go.
- That's right. / - You have to drink elegantly.
Drink it like wine.
(Feels awkward doing this elegantly)
How is it?
- It's really good. / - Is it really good?
It's not that bubbly.
Isn't this really good?
The beer looks so good.
- It's sweet for a beer. / - Yes.
It feels like it will be hard to get drunk from this.
You know how to drink.
You say, "I could drink this."
And this is the type that gets your blind drunk.
- Especially for people like you. / - Is that so?
This has overwhelming visuals.
You might like that the best.
- It kind of smells like coffee. / - Yes.
I think it feels like oriental medicine.
Really? I made a name for this.
Coffee vodka.
It tastes like coffee on its way to oriental medicine.
(The person who likes to drink feels bad for her)
This will be strong for...
- People who don't like to drink. / - True.
- They give two more free drinks. / - Yes.
I prepared a place with...
- An atmosphere that we will like. / - Really?
Mijoo.
- I think we should get wet. / - Okay.
- Get wet? / - Let's get wet.
- Okay. / - Let's go.
(Going Off Tour, Mijoo's Day)
(Beach bar)
- A beach bar? / - Yes.
(It takes 10 minutes by car to South Bay)
(South Bay)
It looks like Jeju-do, Hawaii,
and Saipan.
(It's secluded and relaxing)
(They came to the blue sea)
- It's so beautiful. / - It really is.
- It's so beautiful. / - I'm not lying but...
- It's the best ocean I've ever seen. / - Me too.
Isn't the color of the cloud pretty?
- It looks pink and orange. / - It's so pretty.
(Pink clouds and a sky blue sea)
I can feel the inner healing...
- By just looking at it. / - You're right.
Looking at this...
Makes me feel like I'm also there.
- Yes. / - That's why people watch this program.
You can watch it as you're filled with
dreams and excitement.
It feels like we're there with Lovelyz.
You're right.
(The sun of Mijoo's day is setting)
(It's finally the last itinerary)
I don't know why, but that place is nice.
I wanted to come here because
I wanted to go somewhere with a good atmosphere
and have a cocktail with you.
That's why I brought you here.
You're so considerate.
Look at the stars.
There are so many.
You can't see this in Seoul at all.
It's so pretty.
It would be nice if you just lie down...
- And watch the stars. / - Yeah.
It must have been nice.
Cheers.
Okay.
(As they drink the cocktails)
(Mijoo and Jisoo end their trip)
It makes me feel so happy
after drinking this cocktail.
Did you choose your top 3 favorite things?
- It's the long-awaited list. / - Did you choose?
- Did you choose the top 3? / - I'm still in dilemma.
(Should we start from 3rd place?)
3rd place?
This is so difficult. Can't we have a joint winner?
Let's choose the 3rd place. 1, 2, 3.
- The park. / - The night market.
(They're different)
- They just don't match. / - They don't.
I really felt that we're really different right now.
- You ready for the 2nd place? / - Yes, I am.
- 2nd place. / - 1, 2, 3.
- The night market. / - The mermaid experience.
How can you match that?
We're really different.
(It's fortunate they didn't fight on this trip)
Until the very end.
I'm curious about 1st place. I hope we get this right.
- I think they will get the 1st place right. / - Yeah.
I've decided.
- 1, 2, 3. / - 1, 2, 3.
- This place. / - Scooters.
(How can they be so different?)
- They're different until the end. / - So different.
They are not compatible.
I chose this place because
out of all the places I've been...
It provided the most inner healing.
I think that's right.
The wind that hits you as you ride...
It relieved all of my stress.
We also screamed.
Yes, I think that people should really try that.
I think Jisoo will learn how to ride a bike
and return to drive that scooter.
Yes, I really want to.
I think it will be nice...
If we get our license and learn how to ride a bike.
Yeah, it'd be nice to return here and do it again.
That's why I thought it was a very fun experience.
- Everything was fun. / - That's right.
Everything was also fun for me.
- It was hard to choose. / - It really was.
Everything is a good memory
and an interesting experience. I loved it.
- I couldn't leave anything out. / - Yeah.
We beginners ended this trip well.
- That's right. / - I thought it'd be so hard.
- But it was a success, so I'm happy. / - It was so good.
We learned how to travel.
And how to have fun.
- Let's travel a lot from now on. / - Yes.
- We're really different but... / - Let's travel a lot.
- Okay. / - Let's try.
- Cheers. / - Let's go off and party.
- Cheers to Going Off Tour. / - Let's go.
(The end of Going Off Tour in Kenting)
(Kenting is a place that people really want to go)
You had so much fun.
They really went off.
Were the scooters that much fun?
- I really liked it. / - Yes.
As we rode down that road...
It felt different to the coastal roads in Jeju-do.
It felt refreshing while going up on a hill.
I couldn't believe what I was seeing.
I thought I was looking at a picture.
Can you rent scooters without a license?
- You can. / - You don't need a driver's license.
It's electric and the maximum speed is set to 40kmph.
- That's probably why. / - So it's safe.
I don't think there were a lot of rented cars.
Taiwan doesn't issue international driver's licenses.
So you can't rent cars.
That's why you rent a taxi for a day.
- That's a good idea. / - It was under $100, right?
Yes.
Yes, that's not bad.
You overcame your fear with the mermaid experience.
That was great. I want to her applaud her again.
- It looked really unique and fun. / - Yes.
How was it really?
I was so scared at first, but I enjoyed it in the end.
I think my fear of water is gone.
How about going with a mermaid concept
for your next album?
Comeback as mermaids.
It was so nice,
so I want to introduce it to my members.
- Was it that good? / - Yes.
There are packages where you can go out to sea.
Yes, I saw that.
- That'd look even prettier. / - Yes.
- That's why it was expensive. / - Yes.
We have to look at how much you spent.
- The mermaid experience was expensive. / - It was.
They were there longer as well.
Fortunately, they only used one room.
- They used one room. / - They did.
And the food was really cheap.
- We went to Taiwan a lot before. / - Yes.
- We did. / - Let's see the prices.
First, let's see how much Shin Dong...
- And Kim Shinyeong spent. / - Is that Shinyeong?
Yes.
- They went to Taipei. / - How much did they spend?
Let's see how much they spent.
- They must have spent quite a lot. / - Yes.
That's a lot.
- It's $346.80. / - Yes.
Apink's Chorong and Hayoung went to Kaohsiung.
- They also used $340. / - I guess that's the average.
- It's around $350. / - That's right.
Okay. Let's see how much Going Off Tour spent.
The amount that Going Off Tour spent over
3 days and 2 nights in Kenting is...
Is?
- Excluding airfares. / - Excluding airfares.
- Per person. / - Per person.
- We spent... / - Total?
- $360.20. / - $300?
($360.20 per person)
- Wait... / - It was similar.
We invested in our lodging.
- They invested in activities. / - Being mermaids.
- The activities. / - The taxi rental.
- Right, they rented the taxi. / - Right.
Please stand up and tell us your final thoughts.
Kenting has all the delicious food of Taiwan.
Plus the romantic atmosphere of a tropical region,
the relaxing waves and beautiful sky.
If you need some inner healing,
I strongly recommend Kenting for your holiday.
Please vote for us.
- Okay, good. / - Would you go to Kenting, Taiwan...
According to Going Off Tour's plan?
Please vote.
(Would you go to Kenting or not?)
(A sister's trip to Kenting)
(What will the judges choose?)
Will it be Unexpected Gift Tour to Xiamen, China?
Or will it be Going Off Tour to Kenting, Taiwan?
What will the judges choose?
(Kenting, Taiwan vs. Xiamen, China)
Which tour will win?
- Will it be the calm gourmet tour? / - Oh, no.
Or will it be Going Off Tour
filled with activities and energy.
- What's going on? / - What's going?
- The last digit is the same. / - It's the same.
- Is it a tie? / - A tie?
- A tie? / - It's a tie.
Did everyone vote for both teams?
- It's a tie. / - Did everyone vote for both teams?
We won.
(Xiamen, China won with 80 votes)
You're so surprised.
I'm so surprised.
- I was surprised. / - I wasn't expecting to win at all.
I never won something like this.
My mind was blank.
- We won. This is fun. / - Really...
- What an unexpected gift. / - Unexpected, indeed.
I think the mothers in the audience voted for you.
I think this was thanks to them.
You won by 10 votes.
They have no desire to ride scooters.
Outdoors. Good job, everyone.
Please tell us your thoughts.
It's been a long time since we traveled
just the two of us.
We made time from our busy schedules
and went on this trip.
We enjoyed it so much.
- I really want to go there again. / - Me too.
I want to go there again.
Thank you.
We were with Youngji for 2 weeks.
- I really want to go... / - You want to go, right?
- Yes, I do. / - With who?
I want to go with Mijoo.
With Mijoo?
And have a fun trip.
Thank you.
For our next episode...
It's the perfect weather to go traveling these days.
It'd be perfect to leave now.
So we prepared autumn trips in Korea.
- That's nice. / - Yes.
And they were special trips.
We went with experts in good restaurants and history.
I'm sure a lot of you are looking forward
to a weekend getaway.
Don't miss the next episode of Battle Trip.
Please look forward to autumn trips in Korea.
- We'll see you next Saturday. / - I want to go too.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
(Next episode)
We are full of fun!
This place is huge.
It's the most beautiful of the 8 views in Danyang.
It's good.
It's good, right?
It's so good.
Nilriri Mambo.
You have to chew it carefully.
You're right.
Night, rain, bridge, alcohol.
What else could you want?
(Battle Trip)