(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
Travel is war...
Battle Trip!
We have a reliable special host here today.
It's Kim Hwan. Welcome.
- Nice to meet you. / - Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
Do you like traveling?
- I like it a lot. / - Okay.
I really do but I don't do it a lot these days
because of the baby.
- You have a baby? / - Yes, she's 7 months old.
7 months? You can't go anywhere then.
- I can't even leave the house. / - I see.
Actually, the weather is really nice these days.
- It's perfect for traveling. / - Right.
It's the best season for domestic trips.
- That's correct. / - Where do you want to go?
- Me? / - Yes.
There's a ginkgo forest in Hongcheon.
- A ginkgo forest? / - Yes, there's a ginkgo forest.
- This place is... / - Stop it.
Just thinking about it makes me so sad.
- Why? / - Imagine you walking in the forest alone...
- In fall. / - What about it?
I'm going to go there with a wedding dress on.
- You'll take pictures alone. / - I need to take photos.
I think it'd be really nice to dress up and go there.
You're not going to just see the trees in Hongcheon.
I'll eat chili pepper paste pork belly
while I'm in Hongcheon.
The charcoal grilled one.
I should eat a piece of that.
Since it's fall, many people go see the foliage.
Different regions have different times for foliage.
So we prepared a 2018 fall foliage map.
- There's a fall foliage map? / - That'll be great.
- Shall we have a look? / - Let's check it out.
- So this is how it looks. / - Like this.
It starts from the top.
- It starts from Gangwon-do. / - From October 20th...
- October 17th. / - It goes down south.
Until early November,
you can see the foliage in Mudeungsan in Gwangju.
The further south you go, the longer you can enjoy it.
You're right. It'd be great to travel every week...
- Until early November. / - That sounds great.
Check out the foliage here...
- Then go down south. / - Go south to the next area.
All the way to the end.
If you're wondering what to do
besides seeing the foliage,
you should check out the domestic trips on this show.
If you want to go to Seoraksan,
check out our Sokcho and Yangyang episode.
It's packed with great information.
And if you're going to Jirisan,
our Hadong episode will be really great.
Actually, today's theme is domestic fall trips.
Battle Trip will not just let...
- This fall pass by. / - That's right.
- We prepared... / - I love domestic fall trips.
Hidden cards to...
- Make the trip even better. / - Hidden cards?
- Yes. / - Each team has a hidden card.
So please stay tuned until the end.
You'll be very surprised by the hidden cards.
Now, let me introduce the trip planners.
(Who are the trip planners?)
They're holding their hands.
(Kangnam, Tae Jinah)
(Mun Cheonsik, Shim Hyunbo)
Actually, our team has an advantage.
Jinah has more than 300 concerts
per year in Korea alone.
300 concerts a year?
- 300 concerts a year. / - That's almost one every day.
- It's almost every day. / - It's almost every day.
He's been to everywhere in Korea.
He knows a lot of great restaurants.
After work, you go to the local restaurant, right?
So he must know a lot about local restaurants.
He surely must.
Since "Okgyeong" totally flipped...
- People usually say, "It's a big hit." / - Yes.
But in Chungcheong-do, we say, "It totally flipped."
The song totally flipped and I traveled the country.
And this year, I released "Jangjigijang."
- Did it flip over again? / - That flipped too.
It kept flipping over.
- So... / - It must be your fate.
Did your trip flip over too?
- We went on a trip! / - Yes.
It totally flipped there!
It was insane. You'll see soon.
Because Kangnam was hanging out with me...
- He almost... / - I gained weight.
You did, right?
- You gained a lot of weight. / - He looks like he did.
- I think he gained about 5kg. / - I gained about 5kg.
Was it because of the restaurants?
We're always in the countryside, at good restaurants.
After the concert, we eat again.
He always says I should lose weight but
he always feeds me.
- Then today... / - Then...
How did your trip flip over, Hyunbo and Cheonsik?
Before we talk about our trip,
we should talk about Sikyung first.
- He's right. / - Really?
- When Sikyung was a radio DJ... / - Yes.
We were guests on his show.
Since Sikyung was the DJ, we went drinking often.
We naturally became close. We're soulmates.
So you're drinking buddies.
- Exactly. / - How was it?
I heard you two didn't travel alone.
- Hidden card? / - There's a highlight.
We prepared a hidden card for our trip.
The hidden card joined us for the trip.
- Isn't it cheating? / - I know.
- The hidden card joined you? / - Then the trip...
They could have brought...
Hong Jinyoung too. That would have been really fun.
- Actually, we had someone like her. / - You did?
- Hong Jinyoung? / - Did someone else join you?
That's a secret.
- Someone like her? / - Someone similar to her?
- No one can be like Jinyoung. / - No one is like her.
They do things like, "You?"
- This person is almost like her. / - Almost like her.
- Really? / - This person flipped over too.
- You'll see. / - You'll see.
- Hong Jinyoung? / - And...
Both Kangnam and Cheonsik...
Once won on this show.
Right.
- You did? / - Yes.
- Really? / - This can be a title match.
Where did they go then?
Cancun.
- Cancun. / - Cancun was a lot of fun.
- What about you, Cheonsik? / - Tokyo with Sikyung.
- Tokyo? / - You went to Tokyo?
They had egg sandwiches and...
Shouldn't I go there? That's my home.
No, Kangnam, you can't.
Let's get back to today's theme, fall trip.
Where did you go?
- Our trip was... / - Yes.
- About history. / - History.
- Goguryeo. / - Goguryeo.
- Silla. / - Silla.
- Baekje. / - Baekje.
Many KBS historical dramas
were set in this place.
That's where we went.
There are 10 minus 2 peaks there.
- 10 minus 2 peaks? / - 10 minus 2.
- You mean 8? / - Yes, 8 peaks.
- I think I know where it is. / - You said it weird.
- It's in Chungcheong-do. / - Yes.
- Danyang. / - Danyang.
I went there on "2 Days and 1 Night."
It's really beautiful there.
Danyang is in the center of Korea,
so you can get to any place
within 3 hours from there.
- It's in the center of Korea. / - Exactly.
It's within easy access of everywhere.
- It is. / - It was very beautiful too.
- It was incredibly beautiful. / - Danyang is famous...
- For the 8 beautiful views. / - It is.
Alright. And where did our team go?
Fall is when you're allowed to gain weight, isn't it?
- We wanted to have a gourmet tour... / - Yes.
So we went to Jeolla-do.
- Jeolla-do. / - Food there is delicious.
Jeolla-do is famous for great food.
We have a good chance to win.
- Where in Jeolla-do? / - Where?
Let me give you some hints. It's a harbor city.
- Harbor? / - It's a harbor city.
It's a city of art and culture in the south.
It's obvious.
♪ Mokpo is a harbor ♪
It must be Mokpo.
He got us.
He knows all the cities in the country.
He knows the place right away.
He spoiled the fun but yes, they went to Mokpo.
(Mokpo, Jeollanam-do)
On top of that, we had fermented skate and octopus.
Fermented skate and octopus.
Heuksando has amazing fermented skate.
That's true.
They have the best fermented skate.
You don't say you had fermented skate in Mokpo.
You say you had long-legged octopus in Mokpo.
This is what you should say.
You can't say you had fermented skate in Mokpo.
It sounds like Mokpo has fermented skate.
While we were in Mokpo, we had...
- Fermented skate from Heuksando. / - There you go.
They sell good ones in Mokpo.
By any chance...
It's very tense today.
Mokpo is actually...
- Pretty far. / - It is.
It's at the end of the country.
But it's very easy and convenient to get to Mokpo.
With the high-speed train,
it only takes 2 hours and 20 minutes.
Besides, once you get out of Mokpo Station,
you don't have to move far by car.
You can get anywhere in the city by foot.
- That's true. / - That's very nice.
You can go to all the restaurants by foot.
- Exactly. / - That's how we traveled.
As you can see, our team name is...
- Nilriri Mambo. / - Yes.
We walked a lot, ate and walked again.
We didn't suffer much to enjoy the trip.
- That's Mokpo. / - That's right.
You said we had a hidden card as well.
They said they have someone like Hong Jinyoung.
It's making me nervous. What's our hidden card?
Our hidden card won't lose out to theirs.
- Are you sure? / - Yes.
- I'm very sure. / - Alright.
It's a battle of fall trips, Danyang vs. Mokpo.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
I think it'll be hard for them to be impartial.
- They're all fans of Jinah. / - Thank you.
- Wow. / - His fans.
- We're going to lose. / - We'll lose.
Okay.
Let's check out Danyang first, since it's closer.
Could you tell us what we should focus on?
Something to focus on...
Danyang is at its
most beautiful this time of the year.
It's even better than when we were there.
- You have to go there now. / - Because...
The leaves are starting to fall now.
- He's right. / - It's beautiful right now.
Let's watch the trip to Danyang.
(He has over 300 concerts a year)
He debuted 46 years ago.
- He's amazing. / - He looks great in yellow.
(Tae Jinah and Kangnam)
Look at the green and the red.
(Jinah and Kangnam are the father and son of trot)
(Tae Jinah and Kangnam, their first trip together)
1, 2, 3.
(They already have great teamwork)
Father.
I've been there.
- Where? / - Battle Trip.
- I've been on this show. / - I see.
You looked thin then.
Yes, after a week, I gained weight again.
I went to Mexico.
- That's far away. / - It was.
It was incredibly fun. It was the best.
He's right. This trip was amazing.
- It was really nice. / - It was so much fun.
I'll plan one day. You plan the other day.
- The itinerary? / - Yes, but if you plan it bad...
It'll be the planner to blame. It'll be no fun.
- That will trouble the show. / - I see.
And we will disappoint a lot of people.
So we have to plan well.
- Then you do it. / - No, we should do it together.
- But you've done it before. / - I have...
But back then, the tall guy planned almost everything.
So this time, you should help me.
Do you know any good places?
This week's theme is a domestic fall trip
with a hidden card.
Hidden card?
- Hidden card? / - Hidden card.
- It means a card that is hidden. / - A hidden card.
- A card only I can see. / - Exactly.
Where should we go?
(Recalling all the places where he had concerts)
I once went to... Where was it?
- A place called Danyang. / - Danyang.
- What is it famous for? / - The 8 Views of Danyang.
It's very famous.
It's a truly beautiful sight.
- It really is incredible. / - It's amazing.
- Danyeong? / - Danyang.
- Dang? / - Dan.
It's hard to learn the regional names.
That's right. I'm working on it.
I have to study more.
Geez, give it to me.
I'm doing this all the time.
Am I his secretary or what?
- Is it Dan? / - Dan.
- Yang. / - Yang.
- It came up right away. Right? / - Wow.
Dodamsambong, Gudambong.
These are all peaks. Mountain peaks.
What is a peak?
We call that a peak.
- That's a peak? / - Yes, it's the mountaintop.
- It was tiring to explain it. / - How much explanation...
Does he need?
- It's right here? / - Traveling with him will be hard.
There's a peak on the mountain just like this.
This is a peak?
- No, it's the mountain. / - So...
If this is the mountain, there is a peak here.
I still don't know what a peak is.
- "Peak" is a hard word to know. / - Exactly.
- Right, it's hard to explain. / - First time I heard it.
- Do you know what it is now? / - Now, I know.
It took me about 3 days.
- Hold on a second. / - I'm so curious to what it is.
- Is that a peak? / - Let me give you an example.
- This thing... / - This is on a mountain?
He said that's on top of the mountain.
The mountain has this kind of shape with a peak.
This came out of nowhere. This is it?
This peak would be made of stone.
If there are three peaks, we call it Sambong.
- That was part of the name earlier. / - That was.
- Right. / - There are three peaks in Danyang?
That's right. There are three peaks.
We have to see those peaks. I'm so curious now.
Let's go there.
I think it'd be good. There's lots to eat as well.
(To the mystical place with three peaks)
(It encloses Sobaeksanmaek and Namhangang)
- Look at the weather. / - I should visit Danyang.
- The scenery is beautiful. / - The weather was great.
- Korea is pretty and cozy, right? / - My gosh.
(It's more beautiful with fall foliage)
- Where is that? / - The foliage...
Isn't that CG?
(Korea's green rest area, Danyang)
When I went to Mexico with Taegon,
we named our team, Tequila Bros.
What should we name ours?
- Peak Brothers. / - What?
- Peak? Because it's about peaks? / - I'm curious.
Peak Father and Son.
- Let's be rich. / - We're father and son.
- Right. / - You and I are like father and son.
Peak Father and Son.
- You know SHINHWA's slogan? / - I see.
We are... Peak Father and Son!
Hello, I'm Kangnam.
- You planned the trip? / - A filial trip.
He's like my father. That's why I'll try to think of
things that he will like when I'm planning the trip.
- He's so kind to focus on that. / - He's so nice.
There must be things he wants too.
Fall Trip Week. I didn't know this existed.
(It's a special week for fall trips)
We're going to Danyang.
- Garlic dishes. / - Right, it's famous for garlic.
- There's a market there. / - It's all garlic.
- We should visit the garlic market. / - A garlic market?
- Wow, paragliding. / - That looks fun.
I have never heard of anyone
who would take the elders paragliding.
- What? / - Paragliding for the elders.
- He is too young to be called elder. / - That's right.
- Since it's Kangnam, this is new. / - It's his father.
Look at this place. There's this place in Danyang.
Isn't this nice? We can end the trip there.
That's pretty.
- We can wrap up there. / - He even thought of that.
Jinah can shed some tears here.
- Okay. / - It's like he's signing a report.
(He looks like a CEO signing a report)
- He looks like a CEO. / - He does.
For this trip, I have a hidden card.
I'm going to teach Kangnam
Korean history during this trip.
I'll teach him about the 8 Views of Danyang.
(History)
(Hidden card)
(Trip planning)
(Battle)
(Calling someone)
- The hidden card? / - He's calling someone, right?
Hello, teacher.
- Teacher? / - Teacher?
- Hello. My gosh, hi. / - Hi.
Hello, teacher. This time, I'm going to...
(He's calling someone to prepare the hidden card)
It must be someone who knows a lot of history.
- Really? / - I see.
- No, no. / - They're talking for long.
Thank you. I love you.
- He's calling him teacher. / - Teacher?
If I call someone teacher, it could be Song Hae.
There are a lot of people.
"Do you know how delicious this is?"
- It could be her. / - Lee Hyejung?
Yes.
As for food, when all is said and done...
Danyang is famous for garlic.
We'll get garlic short rib patties.
Goodness.
Next, we'll have hot and spicy Mandarin fish stew
which will go really well with soju.
We're going to eat that.
Kangnam ought to eat something like this.
(2.5 hours by bus from Seoul to Danyang)
2 hours and 30 minutes.
It takes 2 hours and 10 minutes by train.
We can even drive down there ourselves.
- It takes about 2 hours. / - It takes only 2 hours.
Whatever you take, it's around 2 hours.
- Wow, son. / - Yes.
- Let me tell you where we are. / - Okay.
Just like its name, this is the Ondal Tourist Site...
In Danyang, Chungcheongbuk-do.
- This place is huge. / - You really wore that outfit?
- Yes. / - Were you trying to...
- Express the foliage? / - No, listen.
- We had to express foliage. / - That's why.
This place is huge.
As for this place, a lot of dramas were filmed here.
- Is that so? / - Yes.
What is this place?
- This place... / - This must be a set for shoots.
Has the Ondal Cave, Ondal Train and Ondal Fortress.
- It's a set for dramas. / - I see.
- It'd be nice to take photos there. / - Yes.
- A lot of dramas were filmed here. / - It says that...
Dramas and movies were filmed on this site.
So many of them were shot here.
I guess they film most of the historical dramas here.
Hey, they filmed "Yeon Gaesomun" here too.
- Father. / - Yes?
Don't we have a hidden card?
We do have a hidden card.
It was so hard to invite this person.
- It's a guest? A guest? / - What?
- You don't know Korean history. / - The hidden card?
- History? / - See? I was right.
- I don't know much about it either. / - Okay.
But this person is like a walking encyclopedia.
- Is that so? / - Yes.
We will get to meet this walking encyclopedia.
Our team name also means "to meet."
♪ Not just anyone can be a history teacher ♪
A history teacher?
- Please come on out. / - Come on out.
Come on out.
(It's their hidden card)
- He'll come out from there? / - Yes.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Hi. / - Hello, hello, hello.
It's nice to meet you.
Hello.
(The hidden card is)
(Choi Taeseong)
(Star lecturer, Choi Taeseong, appeared on)
("Infinity Challenge," "History Journal, That Day")
(He is the pride of Korean history education)
(He is a walking history textbook)
- He holds a lot of lectures. / - Is that so?
He makes it easy for us to understand.
Actually, history comes across as a hard subject.
- But it's fun with a great teacher. / - That's right.
His lectures are easy.
Doesn't he resemble Hong Jinyoung a bit?
- Hong Jinyoung... / - In what way is that true?
- He has a similar vibe. / - Does he talk like this?
- He talks just like this. / - He laughs a lot too.
Hello, teacher.
This time, I'm going to ask you for a favor.
I'll try to get some time off by all means.
It would be an honor for me if I get to travel with you.
Then we'll meet in front of the Ondal Tourist Site.
- You must've felt reassured. / - Right.
He's here to teach you about Korean history.
- This is Choi Taeseong. / - Choi Taeseong.
- Hidden card. / - He's great with his words.
- Our hidden card. / - He is.
(General Ondal)
General Ondal.
This is a beautiful place.
This place has deep roots in history.
This is where Ondal's love story began.
They were both of Goguryeo decent.
Pyeonggang was a princess.
At that time, Ondal was known as the local fool.
A fool and a princess got married?
Yes, that's right. That's how Ondal the fool...
Became a general for Goguryeo.
This area used to belong to Goguryeo back then.
- This area? / - Yes, but they lost it to Silla.
He was resolute to
win back the territory they lost to Silla.
He swore he wouldn't return without winning it back.
- He's so cool. He's not a fool. / - Right.
- Pyeonggang Princess fixed him. / - She taught him.
- That's so cool. / - That's how he came here.
He came here. If you look at the back,
you can see a mountain.
- If you head that way... / - The mountain.
- There's Ondal Fortress. / - Fortress.
- He built the fortress there. / - He built it there?
- That's how he took it back. / - They fought here?
You can find the historical traces here.
- There used to be a house there? / - That's right.
If you go down, you'll see Ondal Cave as well.
- Really? It's still there? / - Yes.
Even though they built a new tourist site here,
that cave is real?
Yes, Ondal Cave and Ondal Fortress
have always been here.
- They just built the site here? / - That's correct.
This is interesting.
You can find many traces of Goguryeo here.
Pay attention to the flags.
Flags? There they are.
- Take a close look... / - Gosh, they're pretty.
And observe the symbols on the flags.
That's called the "Samjoko."
- "Samjoko?" / - Yes.
- "Sam" means 3. / - 3.
"Jok" means leg.
- It means a 3-legged crow. / - 3.
(It's a legendary bird from Goguryeo)
The people of Goguryeo believed
that they were from the sky.
That's what they believed in.
I can see it from the above.
I can see the three-legged crow.
- It's more fun with explanations. / - Since...
- He talked well, he got me hooked. / - Right.
- I was so focused and it was so fun. / - This place...
Demonstrates a lot of traces Goguryeo.
That house looks amazing indeed.
I know, right?
I want to live in a house like this.
It's pretty with the rain.
There aren't that many people.
- Doesn't it have a sense of beauty? / - Yes.
- This place is beautiful indeed. / - Right?
- Father, can't you buy a house like this? / - What?
- You can buy a house like this. / - Right.
Personally, instead of houses like this one...
- Do you like apartments? / - Yes, I like apartments.
- But, teacher. / - Yes.
There's an old saying that goes like this.
"A full stomach should always come first."
Right.
- Are you hungry already? / - Yes, I am.
- We didn't walk a lot though. / - We did.
Walking this much is a lot for me.
- Yes, you should eat something. / - Of course.
I hope their food isn't that good.
But I can think of...
- Some great dishes in Danyang. / - Exactly.
(They're off to find the flavor of Danyang)
- Do you know a good place? / - Of course.
-  The Danyang rib patties... / - Yes.
This place is where it originated from.
- Really? / - Yes.
- Eating comes first when traveling. / - Of course.
Yes, you have to eat well.
- That's right. / - Eating is so important.
(Peak Father and Son Tour)
(Garlic short rib patty)
(35-minute drive from the Ondal Tourist Site)
Gosh, look at this place.
This place is really awesome.
We get a great view.
That's cheating.
That view is amazing.
We're reminded of this song...
When we see a great view.
(Singing)
(Dancing)
- I just realized something. / - What?
I just realized that this was a microphone.
(Anything he holds becomes a microphone)
- I just realized. / - Gosh.
I already ordered.
- What a great location. / - They'll bring out the best.
This place is famous, right?
Yes, this is the famous Danyang garlic short rib patty.
Garlic short rib patty.
This restaurant is the original.
You can see the grease oozing out.
It tastes better when it's a little burnt.
- This place is the original? / - Yes, the original.
Goodness.
Thank you. He just brought out garlic.
- He brought more garlic. / - Most of the side dishes...
Are made of garlic.
- Pickled garlic / - Mustard garlic?
Danyang is the best region...
For raising garlic because
it's in a limestone plateau and it has a huge...
Daily temperature range, so garlic grows well.
Here it is.
(Garlic short rib patty is finally here)
Their short rib patty isn't round.
- They cut it. / - It's cut.
They have spicy and regular flavors.
There's garlic in the patty.
They're all cut and then brought out.
The view is amazing, isn't it?
(They enjoy the view while the meat cooks)
Do you know what river this is?
- Do you know its name? / - I don't know.
- It's Hangang. / - The view is wonderful.
- Hangang? / - No way.
Hangang is in Seoul.
The Hangang in Seoul flows all the way down here.
This is Namhangang.
- Really? / - I just thought it shared a name.
- It's connected? / - Yes.
If you take a boat up the river...
- Can you reach Seoul? / - Yes.
So in Joseon Dynasty,
people took a boat here to Hanyang.
- That makes sense. / - Yes.
- Because there were no roads. / - That's right.
This short rib patty is so juicy.
Look at how juicy it is.
(The cube shaped short rib patty is very juicy)
- You can see the juice. / - Yes.
- Alright, it's all cooked. / - Is it?
- Thank you. / - Try it.
- Thank you. / - It looks delicious.
(Yummy)
- This is really good. / - Isn't it?
- It's so good. / - It's really delicious.
Because it has garlic, it doesn't taste greasy.
So you can't stop eating it.
You can taste more than just meat.
It has spicy and sweet flavors too.
The red one is spicy.
- The one that's not red is sweet. / - It's not spicy.
- That's not spicy. / - I see. It's good.
I like the spicy one.
- Really? / - Yes.
- I like the non-spicy one. / - Really? The sweet one?
I prefer the sweet flavor.
(They can choose the flavor they like)
In the old days, ribs were for commoners.
Really?
(Were ribs for commoners?)
In the old days, ribs were for commoners.
Really?
Rich people in the olden days...
Didn't think it was very graceful...
To gnaw the meat off a bone.
So they took the meat off the ribs...
Minced the meat...
And made it into a garlic patty.
- Short rib patty. / - They made it easy to eat.
That's right.
Is there a certain way to eat this?
You just eat it however you want.
Put a piece of meat, garlic...
- And yellow garlic. / - That looks good.
That's pickled garlic.
You can do so many things with garlic.
Put a perilla leaf over it.
- Do it like this. / - Like this.
(A wrap with meat and garlic is the best combination)
I see.
Just one please. I can eat that.
Korean lettuce wrap is really great.
- It's great. / - Yes.
- It's really healthy. / - It is.
(Jinah makes a wrap and gives it to Kangnam)
- It's nice to add garlic. / - It's spicy.
Add a clove of garlic.
There's garlic in the short rib patty.
- That's right. / - Seriously.
They minced garlic and meat together.
The garlic is so spicy.
It's in the meat but it's still spicy.
The spicy flavor lingers in your mouth.
The sweet juicy meat mixed with the spicy garlic.
I can't stop eating.
(Kangnam devours the food)
(Jinah is happy to see him eat so well)
- Now we'll go outside. / - Yes.
- There's a cruise ship ready. / - A cruise ship.
We'll get on the cruise and
look at the 8 Views of Danyang.
- A cruise ship? / - A cruise ship.
On Namhangang?
(The beautiful landscape enjoyed by the ancients)
(The 8 Views of Danyang is a famous tourist site)
(Cruise ship around the 8 Views of Danyang)
(Danyang cruise ship)
- I've been there before. / - Yes.
It is very cute and charming.
- I like that better. / - It's like Korea...
- I love that. / - Rather than...
- Too vast... / - It's not overwhelming.
It's as if you've become a part of the landscape.
- It's so nice. / - That's very tranquil.
The moment we got on the ship...
It stopped raining.
- That's good. / - It stopped raining...
And the mist covered the mountain peaks.
You'll see.
We'll look at the 8 Views of Danyang on a cruise ship.
You can see the fifth and sixth views
of Danyang only on the cruise ship.
- The fifth and sixth views. / - Yes.
- What's interesting is... / - Yes.
There's a love story.
- Love story. / - I like love stories.
Earlier you told me a story of the fool.
Ondal the Fool and Princess Pyeonggang's love story.
- This is part two. / - You're a great storyteller...
So it's so interesting to hear.
- I should date. / - May I ask...
- I haven't been on dates. / - How old you are?
Jinah is sleeping in the back.
- 32? / - Yes.
- He's sleeping. / - He must be tired.
You aren't sleeping, are you?
Father.
- Father, we're on a trip. / - I'm sorry.
You always fall asleep after eating.
I feel sleepy after eating.
You always sleep after you eat.
Let me sleep for 10 minutes.
You're really like a father and son.
- He needs a nap. / - He should sleep at night.
(It's a 30-minute ride to the cruise ship quay)
(They arrive at the quay)
We can see the peaks already.
- Are those the peaks? / - Yes, Peak Father and Son...
Are here to see the peaks.
- We're getting on that cruise ship? / - Yes, that's it.
- Now that we're here... / - Yes.
I can feel it.
- Right? / - It's nice.
It's really pretty.
Isn't it?
- There are waves. / - Because it's windy.
- It's because of the wind. / - I see.
- Hello. / - Hello.
(Cruise ship, $13 per person, you need ID)
Get in.
- That looks amazing. / - It's nice.
The weather is actually perfect for sightseeing.
- It was better with the mist and clouds. / - Exactly.
- This is amazing. / - That is so pretty.
Choi Taeseong is going to
tell us about the history of the 8 Views of Danyang.
It's exactly what the name says.
- It's the 8 views of Danyang. / - Yes.
It looks beautiful in fall.
Wow. It'll turn orange then.
In fall, this place will match our jackets.
The leaves will turn red.
This place is really beautiful in fall.
- It's so pretty. / - That's how it looks.
We should've gone at this time.
You can see that if you go there...
- After watching this Battle Trip. / - It'll be...
Perfect to go now.
(Fall is the most beautiful season to enjoy the view)
When it's sunny, the shadow is...
Reflected in the lake.
- That must be wonderful. / - The sky and the nature...
Get reflected in the lake.
Our ancestors came here a lot too.
For example...
(Many ancestors visited this place)
- This person. / - What?
This is Yi Hwang.
(Toegye Yi Hwang)
He was a Confucian scholar.
- He studied a lot. / - I see.
Scholar Yi Hwang.
- You know him, right? / - Yes.
- You see him when you use cash. / - Yes.
- I see him often. / - Of course.
- Alright, look over there. / - Okay.
Do you see a tomb down there?
- Do you see it? / - Yes, there's a tomb.
It's the tomb...
Of a woman named Du Hyang.
- Du Hyang. / - What? Why is it there?
- Her name is Du Hyang. Yi Hwang... / - Why?
Came here as a district magistrate. Do you know it?
- I know what that is. / - Yes, the district magistrate.
Du Hyang fell in love at first sight with Yi Hwang.
She fell totally in love.
But Yi Hwang couldn't stay here for long...
So when he left, she gave him a present.
An apricot flower. Do you know what that is?
- What is that? / - It's a flower.
Yes, it's a flower.
When Yi Hwang was about to die...
His last words were...
"Water that apricot flower tree."
I just got goose bumps.
- Wait, Yi Hwang was a romantic? / - So beautiful.
That's so... I got goose bumps.
Is the statue of Yi Hwang
holding the apricot flowers?
Is he? That's so pretty.
- Water the apricot flowers from her. / - Right.
Then it wasn't a one-sided love.
- But we don't know that. / - They did love each other.
But he had to leave for work.
It wasn't a one-sided love.
I'll leave it up to your imagination.
- You can imagine that, Kangnam. / - Who says that?
- It's part of history. Right. / - Is it written somewhere?
- Then... / - That's why...
- What do you see on this bill? / - Apricot flower!
- That's right. Hence, the flowers. / - Apricot flowers.
- Those were apricot flowers. / - Yes.
- Really? / - Seriously?
I had no idea.
Right? Isn't this amazing?
- He's such a great teacher. / - The flowers are here.
- These are big apricot flowers. / - Right?
You can really find apricot flowers on the bill.
- The flowers are really pretty. / - Right.
I didn't know.
Gosh, this teacher is fun.
(The apricot flowers are drawn on the bill)
This is a touching story.
- I loved the story. It's touching. / - When you...
When you look over here,
you can see the 5th View of Danyang.
- This is called Gudambong. / - Is it that one?
It was so close.
- That's right. It's close. / - It's so close.
Tell you what.
- I felt a presence from the steps. / - Exactly.
- I saw that right away. / - That's right.
- That is Gudambong. / - Gudambong.
(Tomb of Du Hyang, Gudambong and Oksunbong)
The shape of the peak looks like a turtle
from bottom to top.
And the shape is reflected on the water.
You can't see it well because of the weather today.
On a sunny day, you can see the reflection.
It looks like a turtle climbing up.
That's where the name comes from.
You are one amazing teacher.
- There are no trees just here? / - As we go around...
We can see its shape better.
Here's the thing about the rock.
When you go around the rock
and see the rock at this angle...
- You can see the shape of a turtle. / - A turtle?
- There it is. / - That part looks like a turtle.
You know those rocks?
I've seen them a lot in China and Vietnam.
It's my first time seeing one in Korea.
There are a lot of rocky cliffs here
because this place is mostly made up of limestone.
- Many cliffs are developed here. / - I see.
Yi Hwang came to this place...
And had the same reaction.
- Remember the cliffs in China? / - Right.
He said that these were much more beautiful.
- He said this was magnificent. / - Like Indiana Jones.
- This is such a beauty. / - Right.
They're all rocky mountains.
This is amazing.
(As they enjoy the view, they arrive at the last stop)
Now, among the 8 Views...
- This is Oksunbong, the sixth view. / - Oksunbong.
Let me tell you why this is called Oksunbong.
- Do you know bamboo shoots? / - Yes, I do.
It's sticking out just like bamboo shoots.
- This is called Oksunbong... / - You're right.
Because the trees are white and dazzling.
With the Oksunbong,
it's one of the 8 views of Danyang
but isn't actually in Danyang.
- This one isn't? / - Is that so?
- This is included in Jecheon. / - Jecheon?
This is part of Jecheon.
Let me tell you how this happened.
Yi Hwang came here as a district magistrate.
There is this story. Du Hyang asked Yi Hwang...
To include Oksunbong under the area of Danyang.
After listening to Du Hyang,
Yi Hwang thought it was a good suggestion.
He went to the magistrate of Jecheon.
- You think the magistrate agreed? / - No.
Of course he wouldn't agree.
Yi Hwang came here.
If we go that way, we'd be in Danyang.
He engraved letters to let people know that
from this point on, it'd be Danyang.
- Is the sign still there? / - Now it became a dam.
- Is it at the bottom? / - The letters are at the bottom.
He did a fantastic job of writing it.
That's the story how it made it to the list.
When the tide goes out, you can see the letters.
- When it goes out. / - When the water goes down.
- What a sight. / - It's a superb view.
It'd be so fun to travel while learning about the history.
It was because the stories were connected.
- It's also moving. / - When you come here...
- You'll get to relax. / - Right.
You've been busy
but as you admire this beautiful nature...
You can feel as if you're part of it.
I hope you can enjoy this feeling.
- It's great. / - Isn't this great?
(A relaxing time to admire this beautiful nature)
- Alright. / - Okay.
- We saw a lot, didn't we? / - Yes, we did.
- Wasn't it beautiful? / - It was.
However, we still haven't seen...
The most beautiful place of the 8 Views.
- It's not here? / - No, it's not here.
- That will impress you even more. / - Really?
Let's set out to see the most beautiful view of all.
- Okay, let's go. / - Let's go.
- Where are you going? / - That's the highlight of...
- The 8 Views of Danyang. / - I see.
- He's signing again. / - Yes, that's right.
It was in the drama, "Jeong Dojeon."
Jeong Dojeon's nickname is Sambong.
- Dodamsambong. / - This one was beautiful.
- He explained that earlier. / - Dodamsambong.
- That's right. / - He did it with the water bottles.
- There's a pavilion. / - My gosh.
There are three peaks. Look.
That looks magnificent.
It's so picturesque. Photos would look great.
- Isn't this beautiful? / - Yes.
(30 minutes by car to Dodamsambong)
- This is... / - Yes?
Dodamsambong which
Danyang is the most famous for.
- Jeong Dojeon was a great scholar. / - Jeong Dojeon.
His nickname is Sambong.
- Isn't it? / - Yes, it is.
That's the extent of my knowledge.
- I see. / - He will explain the rest.
- Dodamsambong. Got it? / - Okay.
Dodamsambong.
I'm so relieved it rained.
It looks so pretty on a sunny day.
- For me, I'm very relieved. / - But...
Since it's raining, doesn't it look like a movie?
- It looks classical. / - It has that classical charm.
- Right? / - It's interesting. And a pavilion.
I love pavilions the most. That.
It's right there.
- Do you like pavilions the most? / - Yes.
That pavilion over there is indeed beautiful.
- It looks bigger up close. / - Isn't this beautiful?
This is the best viewpoint.
- This is the viewpoint? / - Yes.
It was chosen as 1 of 100 places to visit in Korea.
For 3 years in a row.
The most popular tourist spot in Chungcheongbuk-do.
This is the Dodamsambong.
- It is 1 of 100 places? / - Yes.
He was the architect of the new Joseon Dynasty.
- That's Jeong Dojeon. / - Jeong Dojeon.
I heard that Jeong Dojeon...
Loved Dodamsambong.
This is the place where you can see
the peaks the most clearly.
- Oh, yeah. That's why he's here. / - That's why...
They set up a statue of Jeong Dojeon
in this very spot.
(Sambong Jeong Dojeon)
- Have you been to Namdaemun? / - Yes, I have.
- I often go there. / - He named the very building.
- Seriously? / - Yes.
- He named Namdaemun? / - Yes, that's right.
He named Sungnyemun and Heunginjimun as well.
We still use those names. This is the place...
- Where Jeong Dojeon was born. / - I see.
- The story is told until this day. / - In this area?
Because he loved this place
so much since he was young...
- He chose his own nickname... / - His nickname?
To be Sambong to dedicate it to the three peaks.
That's how the story goes.
- Here's the second story. / - Okay.
Actually, some say that these three peaks...
Didn't belong here.
- Really? Did they bring the peaks? / - Yes.
These three peaks flowed down from Gangwon-do.
The rocks moved down little by little?
It floated on the water and drifted all the way here.
It floated on the water?
- That's the story. / - I see. It's a story.
- It's a story. / - I see.
The peaks floated down here.
The government officials from the province came.
When they came to check, they saw these peaks.
They asked how they could end up here. And made...
The people in Danyang pay taxes for the peaks.
When this happened, a young boy who resided here...
He asked why they were forced to...
- Pay taxes to Gangwon-do. / - That's right!
- He has a point. / - He told the officials that...
The peaks didn't belong to them,
so he told the officials to take them back.
- But they can't. / - That's right.
- "Take them with you." / - He was very smart.
That's right. He told them to take the peaks.
We think that this young boy
must have been Sambong Jeong Dojeon.
That's how they didn't have to pay taxes anymore.
That's another story.
The last story was so fun.
- Right? / - The one with the young boy.
And since you two are in front of the peaks now...
I'm sure there will be a story of your visit here too.
That's my humble thought.
(History is a collection of moments)
All the stories are connected.
- That's right. / - This is so much fun.
I told stories about Yi Hwang and Jeong Dojeon.
This story is more interesting than Yi Hwang's story.
- Right? It comes with a great view. / - Right.
Here's one more dish we ought to try in Danyang.
It's spicy mandarin fish stew.
- Come on. / - Spicy mandarin fish stew?
I love that stew.
Spicy mandarin fish stew.
We have to try that.
It's really delicious.
I didn't know you'd react like that.
It's so good. Mandarin fish in Danyang is amazing.
- Let's go eat spicy mandarin fish stew. / - Let's go.
We ought to have the spicy mandarin fish stew.
Spicy mandarin fish stew in Danyang
is tastier than stew from other areas.
- Is that so? / - Is there a reason for it?
Because the river here is so clean.
(10 minutes by car to the Mandarin Fish Street)
(Darkness blankets the street in no time)
There's this street.
- It's Mandarin Fish Street. / - My goodness.
- Really? / - There's a street for that?
- Mandarin Fish Street. / - Mandarin Fish Street.
It was beautiful. It's perfect for a date.
This street must be the Mandarin Fish Street.
- Look at that. / - There it is.
- Is that a mandarin fish? / - It's a mandarin fish.
You said it's red.
- It has many red dots on its body. / - I see.
Freshwater fish are the best. I love spicy fish stew.
- Let's go eat spicy mandarin fish stew. / - Let's go.
- Let's go. / - Mandarin fish is really tasty.
You add the noodles, right?
- We should add noodles in it. / - You know how to eat.
(Spicy soup)
(With a whole mandarin fish)
(It's Danyang's specialty, known for its light taste)
(Spicy mandarin fish stew)
(Spicy soup)
They put freshwater shrimps too.
(A Danyang specialty with a clean taste)
You have to cook this stew for a long time.
I think it's been like
over 10 years since I had spicy mandarin fish stew.
- The fish is really tender. / - Yes.
Finally, we are at...
- Our last stop today. / - Spicy mandarin fish stew.
It'll be so delicious.
- Can I take off this jacket now? / - Take it off.
- I can't pull my arms together. / - Take it off.
(They're getting ready to chow down)
Finally, you're taking off the jacket.
Back in the days,
spicy mandarin fish used to be called water pig.
Water pig?
- Pig? / - Yes.
- Because it's like pork? / - It's pork of the sea.
- Really? / - Yes.
Mandarin fish live only in clean water.
You'll see it soon, but it's very chewy and delicious.
- Thank you. / - Hello.
- Here come our side dishes. / - Hello.
Look at all these side dishes.
- What is that? / - This is doribaengbaeng.
- This is doribaengbaeng? / - Yes.
It's made with minnow or smelt.
- What is that? / - It's doribaengbaeng.
- Doribaengbaeng. / - That tastes amazing.
- It was made with smelt. / - I love that.
- Smelt? / - Smelt.
- It was really delicious. / - It looks so pretty.
It has some sauce on it.
Doribaengbaeng.
It looks really delicious.
You eat the fish with the vegetable.
The fish are fried.
- Is it fried? / - It tastes amazing.
- It's really good. / - Totally flipped.
If you go to Danyang, you must try it.
Doribaengbaeng.
It's stuck.
- Is it stuck? / - Yes, it's stuck.
You have to scrape it like when eating scorched rice.
- It's stuck. / - Like this.
- Pick the head of the fish. / - Oh, the head.
The head is hard.
- So like this. / - Like this?
- It was really delicious. / - It looks so pretty.
- It's like spicy raw fish salad. / - You're right.
- How do you like it? / - It's fried.
How do you like it, father?
(Curious)
How does it taste?
How is it?
(Curious)
- Father. / - It's delicious.
Is it good?
(Yum)
Like this.
(How 66-year-old fathers express the deliciousness)
The more I chew it, the sauce spreads in my mouth.
- Is it crispy? / - It's very crispy.
(They're admiring the taste)
You're right.
This is a great restaurant.
It's really delicious.
- To be honest... / - Be objective.
It was better than the spicy fish stew.
- Really? / - Really?
This was really amazing.
- So the spicy fish stew wasn't good? / - What's in it?
That was good too.
But I haven't eaten something like this before.
It was really delicious.
- That's how it's cooked? / - Good restaurants...
- Move you, right? / - It's unique.
That's how I felt. I was touched.
I wanted to keep eating it.
- It's unique. / - We need that in Seoul.
(Doribaengbaeng is crispy and savory)
- It's really good. / - It is.
With the vegetables.
(Gobbling down)
Eat a piece of garlic.
It tastes amazing with garlic.
Try it.
Try some garlic with doribaengbaeng.
It's good.
- It's good together. / - It's pickled garlic.
You're right. It's good.
This place is really good.
This is like that thing.
"Shirasu" in Japan.
Is there such a thing?
- Shishamo! / - Yes, shishamo.
- Shishamo is a Japanese word. / - Grilled shishamo.
- This is delicious. / - It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
This is amazing.
- I think I can eat just this. / - It's addictive.
It is.
There's pepper paste with vinegar on the vegetables.
And there's bean sauce on the fish.
Creamy bean sauce.
Together with the fish, it tastes amazing in my mouth.
It's like a work of art.
- It's the sauce for spicy chewy noodles... / - Right.
With fried fish that tastes like marinated chicken.
- Wrapped together. / - No.
It's not?
- Not at all. / - Is it not like that?
It tastes like a fancy...
- Fancy? / - Fancy what?
Side dish.
How can I put it?
I don't really remember.
This is an amazing restaurant.
It's your first time eating this, right?
I haven't tasted something like this before
but it's touching.
If the food touches your heart, it's a good restaurant.
(You're so touching)
(Empty)
- Can we get one more doribaengbaeng? / - Yes.
- You eat so well. / - This is really delicious.
This is the reason why Kangnam gained weight.
(Doribaengbaeng is the reason he gained 5kg)
Here it is again.
- ♪ Bang bang bang ♪ / - ♪ Bang bang bang ♪
(Doribaengbaeng, bang, bang, bang)
(This is an amazing restaurant)
Spicy mandarin fish stew is supposed to be the main.
It's finally here.
(Even higher expectations on today's main dish)
(Spicy mandarin fish stew)
It smells so good.
Dough flakes go well with this stew.
Dough flakes...
It looks really delicious.
I feel like some soju.
(Spicy mandarin fish stew)
(2 portions of spicy mandarin fish stew, $60)
The soup...
(You have to taste the soup first)
- It has a refreshing taste. / - Refreshing?
It's refreshing. It's really refreshing.
The reason for that taste is the freshwater shrimp.
(The freshwater shrimps makes the rich flavor)
That's where it comes from.
- The freshwater shrimp. / - I see.
That makes it refreshing.
- That's why it has a clean taste. / - Exactly.
There's more soybean paste than chili pepper paste.
That's great. Soybean paste.
I love it. It's delicious.
Try the mandarin fish.
See how it tastes.
- It just falls off the bone. / - I see.
It's insane. It just falls apart.
So when you scoop the soup, the flesh comes with it.
That's the charm of spicy mandarin fish stew.
- I want to cook it a bit longer. / - Are you sure?
But this is a big one.
I'll wait a bit more.
Wow.
(Surprised)
(So tender)
- Is it soft? It's good, right? / - The flesh is...
So it's really soft.
- So soft. / - Freshwater fish has a different texture.
Have you tried spicy freshwater fish stew in Korea?
I've tried spicy catfish stew.
But this was much more tender.
- It wasn't fishy? / - It wasn't fishy at all.
(Just a touch makes the flesh fall apart)
You can remove the bones so easily.
It's good, isn't it?
- This fish smells different from other fish. / - Right?
Does it?
I know why this is expensive now.
- It melts in your mouth. / - The texture...
- It's melting in your mouth, right? / - Yes.
It's soft but has a strong flavor.
- It's tasty, isn't it? / - It's delicious.
(Everyone compliments spicy mandarin fish)
- It's good, isn't it? / - It's amazing.
I love that it's spicy.
Can we get some noodles here?
(The soulmate of spicy fish stew)
- Instant noodles. / - You put instant noodles?
Yes, we put instant noodles.
We've won.
- Instant noodles instead of dough flakes? / - Right.
Spicy mandarin fish stew doesn't have...
- A clean taste like regular spicy fish stew. / - Right.
- It has a very rich flavor. / - Yes.
- I love that. / - It's so good.
(Instant noodles, $1)
(So firm)
Instant noodles.
(Yum)
It's good.
(Slurping)
Seriously.
- It's so good. / - So good.
(Instant noodles equal love)
(They are totally focused)
Could you three please say something?
He doesn't talk much when eating.
- It must be good. / - Since it's good.
- No talking when eating good food. / - It was so good.
Who thought of putting noodles in soup?
I prepared many things for tomorrow.
- Really? / - Yes.
- Are you the guide tomorrow? / - Yes.
Today, he was my guide.
Tomorrow, I'm his guide.
- Tomorrow is going to be a bit different. / - Yeah?
Thank you so much for your help today.
You told him about Yi Hwang...
- And apricot flowers. / - Apricot flowers.
- I had goose bumps. / - Starting with that.
And even the peaks.
I learned about history
that even I didn't know about.
I felt that not anyone can be a history teacher.
- Please stay healthy. / - Thank you.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
- Thank you. / - Thank you, Kangnam.
Thank you.
Kangnam and Tae Jinah are here.
- Hello. / - Hello.
A day of respect.
I'll be guiding you today.
- Anything to eat? / - To eat?
A new type of taste.
(Food that shows his consideration to his father)
What's that?
- This is too strong. / - That was so good.
The second day was even better.
- Deodeok? / - Deodeok.
Deodeok!
It wraps around it.
This place is good.
(A new sight of Danyang from the sky)
- You went paragliding! / - Paragliding!
Do you like it?
(A romantic night view of Danyang)
- What is that? / - It's beautiful.
- That's the highlight. / - That's pretty.
(The father and son tour continues)
(Food at Gugyeong Market)
You should go to a traditional market.
- Right? / - You should go to a market.
Every market feels different.
I know a famous food of Danyang's traditional market.
- What is it? / - I only heard about it.
- Garlic? / - Fried chicken.
- Fried chicken is famous. / - Right?
- You will see. / - I think I heard it.
- Today, we are going to... / - Yes.
A traditional market.
(Namhangang runs along the edge of the town)
(And on the other side of the river)
So, this is Danyang Gugyeong Market.
Gugyeong Market.
- It's very famous. / - I like the name of the market.
- Gugyeong Market. / - So pretty.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Tae Jinah! / - Hello.
Chestnuts are out already?
- Hello. / - Ma'am.
Hello.
(People gather around Jinah)
That's what happens when Jinah
goes to a traditional market.
Everything comes to a halt.
Isn't he the BTS of traditional markets?
Of course.
- He's BTS. / - He's EXO and BTS.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- They're so cute. / - Hello.
(Relaxed and distrait)
- This is so nice. / - Ma'am.
You are the king at a traditional market.
We just went around the whole market.
- We went around the place. / - Right.
Now, we should eat.
I prepared something for you.
This is the place?
(It's the specialty of Gugyeong Market)
(Danyang's specialty, garlic)
- It's garlic. / - There's a garlic alley.
There's a garlic alley in the market.
Let's check it out.
- This is the alley? / - Yes.
Gosh, you're right.
My goodness, it's all garlic.
This is a garlic alley.
It's all garlic.
(Garlic blood sausage)
- Blood sausage made with garlic? / - Garlic?
It was amazing.
- Garlic blood sausage. / - What is this?
- Garlic stuffed bun? / - It's a bun stuffed with garlic.
- It sounds a bit weird. / - Stuffed with garlic?
(Black garlic croquette)
- Black garlic croquette? / - Black garlic.
(A lot of food made with garlic)
- It's a crepe. / - Right.
Garlic goes with any dish.
- Garlic blood sausage looks good. / - You're right.
(What is the first dish that will stimulate their appetite?)
Is it dumplings?
- It's blood sausage. / - Blood sausage?
- Dumplings! / - It's garlic dumplings.
Garlic dumplings.
- Perfect bite-sized pieces. / - Yes.
Garlic.
Is that shrimp?
With shrimp?
- This is garlic shrimp dumplings. / - That looks good.
(The dumplings are steamed for 10 minutes)
- And the price is reasonable... / - Yes.
- In the traditional market. / - Shrimp looks so good.
It looks beautiful.
What kind of dumplings are famous here?
Shrimp garlic dumplings, rib patty garlic dumplings
and kimchi garlic dumplings.
It all has garlic in it.
What do you want? All of them are good.
Let's order shrimp garlic dumplings first.
One shrimp garlic dumplings please.
Thank you.
And kimchi... We will have all three.
- We'll have all three. / - Right.
Kangnam, this is why you're getting fat.
- While they're there, they should try them all. / - Right.
They're on a trip, they should just eat it.
(Freshly cooked dumplings are here)
- Ma'am, is this the shrimp dumplings? / - Yes.
This is shrimp, rib patty, kimchi.
- And kimchi dumplings? / - Yes.
(All dishes are $5 each)
Thank you for the food.
I'll try the kimchi dumpling first.
- You should try the shrimp dumpling first. / - No.
You should try the shrimp first.
What do you think?
(He tastes the garlic dumpling)
Is it hot?
- Is it spicy? It's too hot. / - It's hot.
- It was really hot. / - Careful.
It's hot and spicy.
(He takes a bite of the hot dumpling)
(Hot)
The dumpling...
(So hot)
(It's hot)
You just asked me if it's hot.
I said it's hot.
It's tasty but it's too hot.
Dumplings taste good when they're hot.
Dumplings should be hot...
- Because they are juicy when they're hot. / - Yes.
(Warning, it's hotter than it looks)
Be careful.
- You're cooling it down. / - Yes.
We're cooling it down.
- I bet it tastes good even when it's cold. / - Yeah.
Rib patty.
Rib patty dumplings were amazing.
- It looks delicious. / - It was.
It's a little sweet.
This is good.
It has a glossy coat.
- It's really good. / - It's good.
And this is the shrimp dumpling.
It must be delicious.
It's really good.
- I'm curious about the shrimp. / - I want to eat it.
- It must be good. / - It looks tasty.
(They have a bite each)
This can't be not good.
The shrimp is so good.
It looks somewhat fancy with shrimp in it.
- Yeah. / - Right?
And I like the texture.
And it's a little...
I like the scent and texture of shrimp.
Ma'am, the dumpling has the whole shrimp in it.
Look at that sweet shrimp.
- It has the whole shrimp in it. / - A whole one.
It's not that it just has shrimp at the end.
- They put stuffing on the shrimp and roll it. / - Yes.
Which one did you like the most?
Me? I liked the shrimp the most.
- The shrimp dumpling. / - I knew it.
Because of its texture.
The texture makes it so good.
I should go pack some shrimp garlic dumplings.
Father, this place is famous for stuffed pancake.
It's black garlic stuffed pancake.
- Really? / - Isn't it fascinating?
(Stuffed pancake with garlic in it?)
It's black garlic stuffed pancake.
It's stuffed with garlic?
Or is it in the batter?
Look at the color of it.
It's black. It's pretty.
(The batter is darker than normal stuffed pancake)
- I'm so excited. / - Yes.
They make a dish with it.
(The black garlic stuffed pancakes are served)
- What is that? Cheese? / - Yes, this one is cheese.
This is the original.
- Is this... / - Excuse me.
We ordered stuffed pancake not a salad.
This is a salad.
Salad?
(A round ordinary pancake)
They cut it into small pieces?
What is that?
- They cut it like that? / - They cut it.
Then...
And they serve it like a salad.
- It has onions on it. / - And cheese.
- They add cheese like pizza. / - Torch?
- Yes. / - It's like a meal.
It's stuffed pancake pizza.
- Curious, right? / - It's sweet and salty.
It's the best sweet and salty dish.
It looks delicious, but I'm worried about the calories.
That's why Kangnam's so fat now.
(He keeps teasing Kangnam)
(Original pancake, $2.50, cheese pancake, $4)
It has black garlic on top.
- The black pieces are garlic. / - That's right.
You can eat all the garlic you want in Danyang.
It must be good for your body.
(The spicy sauce is the highlight)
(Don't be surprised if you can't see the pancake)
This is very unique.
I'm so curious about the taste.
- We should mix the onion, cheese... / - Cheese.
- And black garlic together? / - Yes.
To be honest,
I wanted to have a round stuffed pancake.
I didn't want to have a salad.
Stuffed pancakes should be eaten while walking around.
I'm sorry. I didn't know that.
I didn't know you liked a round stuffed pancake.
He's cute.
It's not about being round.
- That's not the point? / - No.
You don't have to eat it. I'll eat it all.
- I should try it though. / - I'll buy one in Seoul.
- I should try. / - No, I'm serious.
- You don't have to do that. / - Still, I should...
You don't have to do that for me.
- I'm curious. / - No. Please, I'm serious.
- I can try though. / - No. Stop.
- Why? / - Because it's tough for you.
You don't have to eat something you don't like.
I know it's for a TV show but you don't have to do it.
You're the best singer.
Just give me that.
- Give it to me. / - No, then...
- No, no, no. I'll do it alone. / - I'll try it.
- You want to try it? / - No. I'm just...
- Do you want to eat it or not? / - I want to eat it.
Right?
(Kangnam knows how to tease him)
- He's amazing. / - What a tough cookie.
I knew it. You should've said that in the first place.
This is my first time to try something like this.
You should try it.
(He tries the new stuffed pancake)
I'm curious though. It must have that chewiness...
That's important.
It tastes like a salad with rice cake, right?
A salad with rice cake.
The sauce has a strong taste.
This is amazing because of the honey in the pancake.
The honey goes well with the sauce.
The sauce and honey go well.
It really looks like pizza. It looks like olives are on top.
(Perfect combo of sweet and salty)
But it looks unfamiliar.
We only saw round stuffed pancakes...
- With dripping honey. / - That's right.
It has an interesting taste.
- It's charming. / - Yes, it's charming.
I'm curious about the cheese taste.
It's spicy stuffed pancake, isn't it?
Cheese went well with it, better than I thought.
(The cheese stretches)
Just like natto.
(He rolls the cheese and takes a bite)
- It's good that it's not a predictable snack. / - Right.
This is good.
(Yum)
- This is good. / - Yes.
- This is good. / - It's like pizza.
The youngsters will like this.
- Kids would love it. / - Exactly.
I think college students will too.
- Let's check this out. / - Should we try it?
- I'm curious about this one. / - What is that?
This is...
- Have a taste. / - Scorched rice?
It's black garlic scorched rice.
It's scorched rice that has black garlic in it.
They have black garlic in the middle.
They press it with a machine.
They squish it.
Then what happens?
- Then it becomes one. / - Scorched rice.
- Is it a machine that makes scorched rice? / - Yes.
Really?
They press it hard and make it like crackers.
This is...
They must mix it with sweet and spicy chicken.
They put it on top of the chicken.
Really?
I heard people line up for that.
- That looks good. / - That looks good.
(Crush the black garlic scorched rice)
(Shake and mix with the chicken)
(Scorched rice sweet and spicy chicken)
Eat the scorched rice first.
- Then the chicken once it cools. / - Got it.
(Black garlic scorched rice chicken, $18)
- He told us to eat the scorched rice first. / - Yes.
(What does the scorched rice chicken taste like?)
It's good.
You can really smell the garlic in the scorched rice.
You can also taste the savory scorched rice.
It goes well with the scorched rice.
The chicken is similar to the scorched rice.
- I think the texture will be interesting. / - That's it!
Looks like Shim Hyunbo is on our side.
He eats so deliciously. He eats it so well.
(The ultimate crispy dish)
This is really interesting.
- I can't stop eating. / - How did they think of this?
- I can't stop. / - The scorched rice...
Makes it unstoppable.
(The scorched rice is the cherry on top)
It'd be good just to eat the scorched rice.
Is it possible to eat that without beer?
It will be really good if you eat it with beer.
Cold beer.
- Cheonsik, aren't you being too absorbed? / - No.
What do you mean no?
I know Cheonsik well.
- We had him at the mandarin fish. / - Right.
To be honest, I almost ordered some soju.
- Father. / - Yes?
- The 8 views yesterday... / - 8 views.
We saw it while riding a boat and walking, right?
We will see those from the top today.
Not from the bottom. We'll see it from the top.
Are we going to ride an airplane?
Will we ride a helicopter?
- We won't ride an airplane. / - Helicopter?
No.
(You saw it from the shore)
(And you saw it from a boat)
(This time, it's from the sky)
(Danyang is the sacred place for paragliding)
- Danyang these days... / - That's right.
- It's famous. / - Perfect place for filial piety.
The sacred place for paragliding.
Filial paragliding.
It really comes to mind when you think of Danyang.
- Did Jinah really try paragliding? / - That can't be.
- They have coaches. / - Right.
- So it's extremely safe. / - Really?
(We will go to the sacred place of paragliding)
(Peak Father and Son Tour)
(Paragliding)
(20 minutes by car to the paragliding spot)
Where are we going?
We're climbing up now.
- To the mountain? / - Yes.
- We're going up the mountain? / - Yes, up there.
As soon as we reached the mountain...
- It started to rain. / - Yeah.
It was suddenly pouring.
Then you can't paraglide.
- Can you do it in the rain? / - It was dark with fog.
You probably can't in the rain.
There's nothing here.
Father,
people come here for paragliding.
- Huh? / - Paragliding.
Sell what?
- He can't speak English. / - Paragliding?
- "Sell what?" / - We're not taking a plane.
You jump and fly around.
- Yes, like this? / - There's a balloon on top.
- Where people fly like this? / - Yes.
They have a balloon on top and connects it with rope.
- Really? / - Yes.
- I've never tried it. / - It's really thrilling.
A father would never go...
- If the son doesn't take him. / - Right.
- If it rains... / - I've been there.
When you lie there before your jump on a sunny day...
Really?
It feels like you're floating in the sky.
(The paragliding site)
Do you fly from here?
- You do, from here. / - Really?
(Will we paraglide here when it's so foggy?)
Actually, this place is really famous.
You can glide 60 days per year on average in Korea.
But here, you can glide 300 days out of the 365.
- Virtually. / - Why?
Because the weather here is perfect for paragliding.
But the weather's really bad because you're here.
It's good weather for 300 days, only 65 are bad.
But we came on one of those bad days.
- We came on one of the 65 days. / - Yes.
Isn't that actually amazing?
- Then... That's so... / - It's virtually impossible.
- I wanted to watch him paraglide. / - What a shame.
- Jinah should've paraglided. / - What a shame.
You can do it under most conditions here.
Even if I'm acrophobic,
I wanted to try it for Battle Trip.
- Come on. / - I mean it.
He's smiling as he says that.
Do you think you would've tried it
if the weather was good?
I think it would have been too hard for me.
- It's such a pity. / - Come on.
I really wanted to show my son.
You almost got angry at me.
No, I really would have tried it.
The weather might get better in the afternoon.
- Try again in the afternoon. / - You just have to wait.
- It's not over yet. / - No.
He's not smiling again.
Do you mean that we could do it if it doesn't rain?
I want to do it with you.
Sure. Since we're here, let's do it.
You know for sure that it won't stop raining?
- That's such a pity. / - Yeah.
- But there was a cafe here. / - But we waited.
- Really? / - We waited for the rain to stop.
- Let's wait for a little bit. / - Alright.
- If it doesn't stop, let's go somewhere else. / - Okay.
I think the rain stopped a little bit.
Doesn't the weather make it
look like we're on the ground floor?
You can't paraglide with the fog...
- Since you can't see anything. / - In good weather...
This is what happens.
You just jump from here.
You sit here and wait, then jump off from here.
Isn't it amazing?
That's what we should've done.
That's how it looks.
- You can see all of the view. / - Yes.
This is what's supposed to happen. We're so unlucky.
You have a driver in the back.
- Driver? / - You get on with the driver.
- The driver does everything. / - The driver...
You say start and he starts the meter.
Anyway...
We can't do it today.
Let's try it next time again.
Let's come here together.
It's a trip for him.
I don't know what I should do for a hidden card.
(Focused)
You have to eat when you're on a trip.
We should eat something he likes.
You know that thing.
The Korean cuisine with lots of dishes.
Korean table d'hote.
- Yeah. / - Oh, my.
- You have to eat that in Danyang. / - This is it.
- Korean thistle rice? / - Korean thistle rice.
That alone tastes good.
- It's good. / - Deodeok and balloon flower roots.
Is this grilled dried pollack? Do they even serve this?
This place is nice.
The side dishes are all of his favorites.
Grilled deodeok is really good.
This is my hidden card.
That's your hidden card?
- Danyang Korean table d'hote? / - A full dinner.
They have rib patties and everything.
They have everything.
(30-minute drive to the restaurant)
- You're hungry, right? / - Of course, I'm hungry.
- It's over there. / - Where?
- It's written here. / - It's over there, right?
It's iron pot Korean thistle rice.
Korean thistle rice.
- Iron pot Korean thistle rice. / - You know it, right?
Park Hyunbin.
♪ Gondeure mandeure ♪
Go, go, go.
Korean thistle.
- Korean thistle rice? / - Yes.
- This place has a 60-year tradition. / - 60 years?
The herb dishes here are really good.
- They're really good for you. / - Herbs.
I wanted you to get energy from good food.
So I looked this place up.
I looked this up on the internet.
They don't have Korean thistle rice on the menu.
But you can change it to that for free.
- Can you change the rice? / - Yes.
You have to eat Korean thistle while you're there.
I'll have to try it to see how good it is.
Gosh, Korean thistle rice.
(Sizzling)
It's here.
What's sizzling?
- So many dishes. / - Korea's so good for this.
The side dishes are like a work of art.
Deodeok.
- Rib patties. / - That fish was good.
- What was it? / - Dried pollack.
That was so good.
They raise the vegetables there.
- They farmed it themselves. / - Right there?
- Imagine how fresh they'd be. / - Harvested there.
All the vegetables are from their garden.
(Korean thistle medicinal herb meal)
(Hidden menu 1, iron pot Korean thistle rice)
How good would the Korean thistle be?
Korean thistle smells really good.
You add soy sauce to it.
- Right. / - It tastes great just with soy sauce.
- Of course. / - Right.
(They move the Korean thistle rice from the iron pot)
This is scorched rice.
(Making Korean thistle scorched-rice water)
It's better if you put the lid on.
(Add soy sauce seasoning according to your liking)
(Mixing)
I've never had this before, so I'm curious.
Mix it well.
Fresh Korean thistle is good.
- Yes. / - There is dried Korean thistle.
Right.
There is also fresh Korean thistle.
How is it?
(Will the hidden card work?)
Yes, it's his hidden card.
There's no way that this won't work.
(He thinks carefully)
(He likes it)
It's good.
(It suits Jinah's taste perfectly)
(It also suits Kangnam's taste)
The balloon flower root...
They put garlic in the Korean thistle rice.
- Yes. / - They put garlic in there.
You can smell the garlic aroma.
And the aroma from the Korean thistle.
It's really fragrant.
- That's right, it's fragrant. / - Yes, it's fragrant.
- That's so good. / - The aroma was amazing.
It increases your appetite more.
How was eating Korean thistle for the first time?
It increases your appetite.
- It increases your appetite? / - Yes.
It made me more hungry.
- Let's try the dried pollack. / - Grilled dried pollack.
The grilled dried pollack was amazing.
They seasoned it so well.
(Hidden menu 2, grilled dried pollack)
Let's try some of the grilled dried pollack.
(Will this also suit Tae Jinah's taste?)
(He smiles)
If he reacts this quickly, it means that it's good.
The taste already blows you away.
(Kangnam also tries a bite of the grilled dried pollack)
(It's delicious)
This place is good.
There's a scent to it.
There's a scent of dried pollack.
The more you eat it, the more flavorful it is.
Right?
- It's really good. / - It is good.
I want to bring my mom here.
- What? / - I want to bring my mom here.
(A fall delicacy, grilled dried pollack)
Since we ate grilled dried pollack,
we should try the grilled deodeok.
- Deodeok. / - Deodeok is also amazing.
- It's really good. / - It's amazing.
- It's like art. / - I like it better than pollack.
You have to eat it.
- Is it a meal with 11 dishes? / - Yes.
(Hidden menu 3, grilled deodeok)
(Looking forward to the taste of grilled deodeok)
(He also smiles this time)
Grilled deodeok.
Wow.
The texture is amazing.
It's like crackers.
(He's displeased)
Why do you always talk about crackers?
Isn't the texture similar?
The texture that I experienced...
The deep aroma of deodeok
comes in through my nose.
- That's right. / - The crispy texture...
And the chili pepper paste scent comes up as well
and it dances in your mouth.
It's really good.
(Their appetite explodes)
It's so good.
Now it's time for this scorched rice.
It's become something different.
You need Korean lettuce kimchi for this.
The Korean lettuce kimchi.
They had that?
- What a perfect combo. / - How was that kimchi?
You end the meal with that.
We ate a lot but we were still hungry for more.
- Is the bitterness okay? / - I liked it.
Korean lettuce kimchi is the best.
- It made me hungry again. / - The Korean lettuce...
It made me eat so much.
- Father. / - Yes?
How was my hidden card? All this food.
Jinah eats a lot.
- We really ate all of that. / - It was good.
- Was it good? / - Yes.
It's the best thing you've ever done today.
- Right? / - It's the best he's done today.
- I did good, right? / - Yes.
Give me your credit card then. I have to pay for this.
- What? / - Give me your credit card to pay.
- Thank you for the food. / - It was good.
They're really like father and son.
- The final stop. / - Is there something at night?
Yes, there's something at night.
The highlight of all.
- The night view. / - It was really pretty.
(They drive 13 minutes to see the night view)
(The last destination in Danyang)
It would've been more picturesque with the fog.
This place is...
Isn't it pretty?
It's the perfect place to go on a date.
You have to propose here if you want to propose.
(Several thousand LED lights light up the night)
(LED Park)
(The first LED tunnel in Korea)
- It's pretty. / - They're all LED lights.
- There's a tunnel as well? / - A tunnel.
(Decorated tunnel and garden, popular photo spot)
Father.
Isn't it so pretty.
- It's really pretty. / - Isn't it?
- Seriously. / - Perfect spot for dates.
I never imagined that there'd be something for night.
If you go there, your heart feels warm.
- You have to go with your lover. / - Yes.
- Many lovers were there that day. / - Right.
It makes your heart feel warm and nice.
(It's perfect for a date location for families and lovers)
- The last is nice, isn't it? / - Of course.
- I did a good job, right? / - Yes, today was nice.
- Wasn't today nice? / - What a great spot...
- For a great ending. / - For a great ending.
It's the first time his outfit doesn't stand out.
- It's the first time. / - It doesn't stand out.
- So natural. / - It's like a stage.
- It's so pretty. / - It's like the climax of a movie.
It was a great trip with my son.
- For 2 days, right? / - 2 days.
We saw lots of nice things.
We learned about history, and ate a lot.
I really enjoyed it.
As a son,
thank you for having so much fun on this trip.
Of course. I will remember this forever.
- Today's trip. / - Really.
- Forever. / - To end it, give me a hug.
- A hug? / - Yes.
(Hug)
- I love you. / - I love you.
- So nice. / - Thank you.
Thank you.
I honestly felt like I wanted to go there.
I liked the food and everything
but if they had gone paragliding,
I would have gone there.
I want to see the mandarin fish statue.
- The big mandarin fish. / - I've never seen it.
I've never seen a fish statue before.
You should see the fish statue and eat the fish stew.
- Also the garlic liquor. / - The garlic liquor.
What was the most delicious thing you ate there?
- You ate so many delicious things. / - Bang bang?
- The bang bang dish. / - Doribaengbaeng.
I still think about it.
- Simply put, it's smelt. / - Yes, smelt.
- Smelt only lives in really clean water. / - Right.
They only live in such environment.
- The doribaengbaeng of Danyang. / - Bang bang.
Jinah, was the doribaengbaeng your favorite too?
The doribaengbaeng was good too
but the short rib patty is really the best in Danyang.
Alright.
Because of Choi Taeseong,
we learned so much about Danyang.
It felt plentiful after hearing the history.
Right.
- Now... / - Let's talk about the expenses.
I'm a little worried about the expenses.
- The cruise ship. / - Excluding transportation.
Let's find out how much they spent.
The total amount that we spent was $167.
- $167? / - Per person.
- Per person? / - Including accommodation?
Yes.
That's cheaper than I thought.
They needed to do the paragliding.
- Right. / - Then it'd be over $200.
It could've been over $300.
- Let's vote now. / - Let's vote.
Will you go on Peak Father and Son Tour
to Danyang, Chungcheongbuk-do?
Please vote.
(They planned a domestic fall trip to Danyang)
(What will the judges choose?)
Next week, we'll go to Korea's representative port city.
- It's a trip to Mokpo. / - Mokpo.
Please also look forward to next week.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(Next episode)
(Domestic fall trip to Mokpo, Korea)
Nilriri Manbo.
You must be together.
(Create a special normal day)
- I prepared a lot, right? / - You did.
(From mugwort rice cake to fermented skate)
(This dish will make you happy)
You have to chew carefully.
Night, rain, bridge, alcohol.
What more do you need?
(Battle Trip)
("One More Time" by Super Junior)