(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Hwijae, special host, Eric Nam)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
The special host for today is Eric Nam.
Nice to meet you.
- Wow. / - You actually...
Have this image of a traveler.
It's because he's famous for those commercials.
When you look at his name...
It doesn't seem like he's from Korea.
Eric Nam?
There are people who don't know where you're from.
I'm from Atlanta, U.S.
Were you born there?
- Yes, I was. / - How long did you live there?
I lived there until I was 20.
That means when you go to Atlanta,
you know all the places to go there.
- From the eateries... / - That's right.
There are a few things
you must try when you go to Atlanta.
It's in the southern part of U.S.
so they have a lot of fried food.
There's fried chicken.
It's a little crispier than Korean fried chicken
and you can taste a lot of pepper.
So you must eat some chicken...
And you know the soda brand.
- The "C" company? / - Yes.
- That company started in Atlanta. / - Atlanta?
You can enjoy soda
from all over the world there.
That sounds exciting.
You could think the other way around.
Let's say your friends from Atlanta come here...
- You can plan the trip around Korea, right? / - Yeah.
Where would you take them?
First, people like Gwanghwamun a lot.
People from other countries like
to take photos there since it's so beautiful.
They love Gyeongbokgung.
Going there dressed in hanbok.
They like those places.
And I live in Hannam-dong
so I take them to my hangouts to have drinks.
We have Eric Nam here for a reason.
We can trust him when it comes to traveling.
It has something to do with today's theme.
Special trip planners planned today's trip.
The trips were planned by locals.
It's a local's travel plan special.
So the people living in there
plan the trip for visitors.
It's game over.
It's a course that experienced travelers really want.
They don't want tourist sites.
- Locals. / - Not where tourists go...
- Only what the locals know. / - That's right.
- The hidden eateries. / - That's right.
Places where only locals eat.
It looks more delicious.
It feels like I've visited a special place.
It's fun pretending to be a local.
That's right.
We're looking forward to which locals
planned these trips.
The destinations for the battle today are
Vietnam and the Philippines.
Vietnam vs. the Philippines.
I'm curious about who planned the tour.
Is there anyone we know who lives in...
- Vietnam and the Philippines? / - There is.
- Is there? / - Currently, in Vietnam...
The Hiddink of Vietnam lives there.
- Head Coach Park Hangseo. / - He's there.
And also...
There's a famous person living in the Philippines.
Who?
He's a legendary boxer.
- Pacquiao? / - Pacquiao?
Of course. We can't forget him.
- Will Pacquiao be on Battle Trip? / - He's here?
Will he plan a trip for Battle Trip?
That's amazing.
That'd be so fun.
I know that Lim Sungeun
has lived in Boracay in the Philippines
for a long time.
Or else, we need Sandara Park.
- Sandara Park... / - She needs to come.
- Sandara... / - The Dara Tour was such a hit.
- That's right. / - Right.
Let's see their photos first.
- The photos of the planners? / - Yes.
These are the local trip planners
who planned the trips for today.
Let's meet them.
The Philippines... Oh, him.
- Ryan Bang. / - Recently...
He's 100% a local.
He's the Yu Jaeseok of the Philippines.
- Ryan Bang. / - Ryan Bang.
- That's right. / - He's very famous.
And on Sandara Park's
Dara Tour...
- Ryan Bang was in it. / - He visited.
They had delicious food together.
Everyone.
This time, it's the local planner for Vietnam.
- Who is it? / - Please show us.
It's Yeom Gyeonghwan.
- He lives there? / - It's Yeom Gyeonghwan.
He immigrated there.
- Thing is... / - With his family.
But with Battle Trip,
normally, you plan your own trip.
- But since we have locals... / - It's convenient.
You don't have to study about anything and...
- Just go like a travel package. / - That's right.
That's the best.
- That's so convenient. / - Right.
We will meet the travelers
who went on this tour.
It will be very loud today.
Today will be the loudest day.
Come on out!
(Choi Eunkyeong, Ahn Sunyeong)
Why are you doing slapstick?
We'll do our entrance again.
I'm sorry.
Let me do a backflip as I enter.
Actually, Eunkyeong...
- I'm pretty close with Gyeonghwan. / - Yes.
Was the trip okay?
To tell you the truth, our reaction was also like this
when we first knew that we were
going on the Yeom Tour.
We had no expectation.
- So... / - Less than none.
We were worried it'd be bad
so we did all the research ourselves.
We made a wish list from 1 to 10.
Telling him what we wanted to do.
However,
we didn't miss out on a single thing.
If I could go on the Yeom Tour one more time...
- I would go again. / - Seriously? Gyeonghwan?
I can't believe it.
- We were also like this. / - That was our reaction.
Because we had low expectations,
the joy became multiplied.
It was amazing.
- This is good. / - It was amazing.
Our team should talk about their trip too.
How was it?
For us, actually...
What do you think is the most important thing
when you go on a trip?
The food.
Money.
- This wasn't what I was expecting. / - Language.
- Are they all wrong? / - What was wrong?
- Let's do it again. / - We'll do it again for you.
- What is it? / - Go again.
What's the answer?
She says it's language.
What is the most important thing
when you go on a trip?
- The food. / - The language.
That is correct.
The language!
It is language.
I told you that it would be a little loud today.
Good job.
- Good work. / - She's right.
If you can't communicate, you feel like an outsider.
But if you can communicate,
they won't look down on you.
- That's right. / - They will accept you.
That's right.
I wanted to tell you that.
Ryan Bang is as popular as Yu Jaeseok
over there...
- He's so popular. / - Just say he's like Hwijae.
Say Lee Hwijae instead.
Oh, he's like Lee Hwijae...
So...
He's the Lee Hwijae of the Philippines.
That's how we saw him.
That's why there were no communication problems.
We didn't feel uncomfortable at all during the trip.
Gyeonghwan also did well at everything.
First off... Everyone...
It's Vietnam vs. the Philippines today.
Let's see where they went.
- We went to the capital of Vietnam. / - The capital.
- It's the center of Vietnam. / - The center.
It has a history of 1,000 years.
Vietnam's....
You go to Hanoi!
They planned it.
- Why? / - Wait a minute.
- Why? / - They planned it.
So what? We practiced it.
- We prepared it. What's wrong? / - No...
- I really liked it. / - We...
It's our style.
Okay.
Hanoi is too...
Hanoi is too common.
- People have already been there. / - Too much.
- It's possible to think so. / - Actually, we know...
When it comes to Hanoi,
it holds the record for the highest by-minute rating.
- With Ok Taecyeon... / - The snakehead.
- The snakehead noodles. / - That's right.
We didn't eat snakehead noodles.
You had to try that.
You have to eat noodles.
There are certain things you expect with Hanoi
like eating Vietnamese rice noodles and so forth...
You didn't eat rice noodles?
- We did not eat rice noodles. / - Not even once.
That's the same as...
foreigners not eating bulgogi in Korea.
They sell bulgogi overseas.
- Korea has a lot of rice noodles. / - Lots of good places.
We didn't eat rice noodles.
"In Hanoi?" "This food exists in Vietnam?"
- We ate everything that makes you say that. / - Really.
I get what you're talking about.
The real...
"You must go and eat this."
- You'll see a list of such foods. / - Everyone...
Grab a pen and write it all down.
I'm so intimidated.
You're both former shopping network hosts
so you speak really well.
I feel confident already.
I don't need to do anything.
- I almost ordered it. / - Everyone...
You will end up ordering Hanoi.
Because...
The thing is...
We can't lose.
Please introduce your trip.
The island with white beaches and a fantastic sunset.
The island that gets more glamorous
in the night when the stars come out.
Let's shout it out together.
??Cay, cay, it's Boracay ??
They planned it too.
People are very interested
in Boracay these days.
There are lots of articles about it too.
- There are environmental issues. / - Isn't there a problem?
- Is it okay? / - Because of the environment...
They're planning to close the island for a while
but it hasn't been decided yet.
We'll give you information on that today.
We'll tell you what it's actually like there.
I've been to Boracay and
I'm sure that a lot of people have.
- Boracay... / - If you took the usual course...
- People might get disappointed. / - Right.
Do you have anything special?
It's not the common course at all.
We were shocked because...
We thought it was the obvious course too.
But the plan that Ryan made was really new.
We saw the land, sea
and sky of Boracay.
Our trip includes everything.
Once you watch, you'll sing this song...
??Cay cay, Boracay ??
They're supposed to be singers. Why are they so off?
- Why is their harmony so off key. / - I'm sorry but...
Anyway.
Today's Battle Trip
is Hanoi, Vietnam vs. Boracay, the Philippines.
Let's see how the trip planned by locals are.
We have high expectations.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
- Nice to meet you. / - Welcome.
Wait a minute.
It's his fault.
I did it without realizing.
There is no vote after the first half today.
Normally, we have the vote halfway
that doesn't determine the winner.
But today, we'll just do one final vote for each trip.
It will be a single round match.
- You're right. / - Right.
We will reveal
the Yeom Tour in Hanoi first.
Let's start the Hanoi trip.
Hanoi.
- It's like art. / - Did you go there?
- Those mountains were like art. / - Did you go there?
- That's all the places we went. / - Really?
(Vietnam is affordable and safe)
(Danang scored 99 votes last time)
(Hanoi had the highest recorded rating at 11%)
(Battle Trip went to Vietnam 4 times already)
Many people have been already.
You can expect even more than that.
The view is amazing here.
What is that?
I've never been there.
I really want to go.
It's so nice.
(The secret Hanoi that people are dreaming about)
So good.
I thought it'd be to your liking.
- You have to give up on diet here. / - It's over.
- Why diet when you have this? / - That looks good.
It's great we came here.
(Watch with caution if you're hungry)
You filmed it like that on purpose?
- That was my idea. / - We did slow motion shots.
- That's so pretty. / - So funny.
That was good.
- You even wore matching outfits. / - We rented them.
(D-15, Hanoi, Vietnam)
It's been about a year and a half living here.
I go back and forth between Korea and Vietnam,
and I'm preparing to open a business.
The kids are going to school here
and my wife lives here.
I think Gyeonghwan's doing more TV shows
after moving to Vietnam.
He's so busy these days.
I've been to almost every place
so I can introduce it to people.
I've been to a lot of places.
He really went to all of those places...
For us.
(Yeom Gyeonghwan)
(Been living in Hanoi for 2 years with family)
Do you know that Vietnam was
on Battle Trip several times?
I saw a few of the episodes.
I saw Kwangkyu and Taecyeon
drinking egg coffee.
I'm going to places even locals don't know about.
Tourists will obviously not know about these places.
I will reveal places that
even Hanoi locals haven't visited.
I'll show it all to you.
I'll reveal them.
(Where could it be?)
- Hanoi. / - Hanoi.
You go to Hanoi.
- We should've planned. / - Right now...
Look at this.
Here.
I marked the places with red dots.
- Trip designer. / - I marked them.
I always research before my trip.
The other colors are the places I want to visit.
- I always do my research. / - I looked them up.
I usually ask my friend who lives in that country.
And so now...
We have a friend who lives there.
I found out that we do.
Yeom Gyeonghwan...
I'm not happy about him.
That's what we were like.
Sunyeong didn't like it at first.
I thought we wouldn't be a good fit.
There are places that women want to visit.
He's a great senior.
He's so good-natured and kind,
but I don't feel he'll give us what we want.
Like wearing elegant dresses revealing our backs...
Taking 50,000 photos.
Places where you can take 500 photos over a cocktail.
He won't take us to nice places.
I feel like he'll just take us to markets.
He'll just take us to markets.
- I like markets. / - I don't mind them either but...
You have to go to markets and also nice places.
We can't just visit the market.
- The places that women like. / - Then..
- No. / - Will he know those places?
But if we tell him in advance,
he'd check it out by himself.
He'll get the help of locals.
So if we make a list for him...
I want to dress in ao dai...
- And eat banh mi. / - A banh mi...
I was going to eat banh mi 3 times a day.
And we should drink Vietnamese coffee.
Condensed milk coffee.
- They're planning the scenario. / - Okay.
Why am I getting excited for the trip?
It's worth getting excited about.
Your wish list is full.
(This is the wish list in question)
He seems clueless.
He doesn't look happy.
But the weather
isn't that warm yet.
Hanoi's winter
is similar to Korea.
Of course, it doesn't snow and it isn't that cold.
- But it can get suddenly cold. / - He looks sad.
I'm not sure if this will work.
I want to eat healthy food...
- That's his wife. / - That's his wife.
Our reinforcements.
I was thinking about
recommending health foods...
No, they're on holiday. Why would they eat that?
He wanted to feed us health foods.
He suggested we eat turtle.
And goat!
This is the type of trip that women like.
They like going to nice bars
and taking photos.
I think a trip they can enjoy would be nice.
I think his wife saved your trip.
You're right.
Isn't that cheating?
- Shouldn't Gyeonghwan plan this? / - I got goose bumps.
- This isn't Yeom Tour then. / - Here it comes.
- Oh, dear. / - So beautiful.
This is women's only trip, right?
So it's a trip for people who are married
or to go with friends.
It's a trip that every woman can enjoy.
- Sounds fun. / - You get the best of both worlds.
(Korea)
(Hanoi)
(The flight takes 4 hours)
Xin chao, Hanoi!
(Arriving in Hanoi)
(As soon as they arrive, they burst out laughing)
Xin chao, Hanoi!
Why am I embarrassed?
Geez...
Do you like it?
- There's a photo too. / - Of course.
- It's round. / - It's so cute.
- I was going to make one. / - He put his own photo.
Isn't that cute?
It is cute.
- "Customers of Yeom Tour." / - Really.
He put a lot of thought into it.
We haven't met in ages so I shouldn't say this but...
- I'm already sick of you. / - Listen.
How long have you been waiting like that?
Why are you wearing sunglasses now?
- You're inside the airport. / - We're embarrassed.
You're embarrassing.
Let's get out of here first.
- Can't we just say bye here? / - Yeah.
- I have to guide you. / - I've planned everything.
I know everything.
Don't take us to boring places.
Come on out. Just trust me.
Why do I have a heavy heart?
Get in, please.
Oh, no.
Get on.
Hoan Kiem please.
You're getting on too, right?
Yes, I have to get on too.
- You're not just sending us? / - Right?
No, no.
Don't worry.
We'll head out now.
We're not going to a temple, right?
They're bickering at the start...
If this continues, we'll win.
- No, you'll be surprised later. / - There's division.
Do you know what we like?
- Of course. / - Like what?
You like good food.
Places where you can show off.
- Show off? / - Yes.
- Well... / - What do you mean by that?
All women like...
- To take photos for SNS. / - You mean selfies?
- Places for nice photos. / - You know such places?
- You? / - Of course.
There's so much distrust right now.
Even the driver...
They're so quiet. I feel bad.
This bridge will lead us downtown.
- The river below is the Red River. / - Red River?
- The color of the river is red. / - Because it's red?
Red River.
Are houses more expensive near the river here?
Yes, the view is also an important factor here.
When they build apartments,
they make a lake.
They make a lake.
We asked him all sorts of things and
he knew the answers.
- Apparently they do. / - What does that mean?
So that you get a better view,
they build an apartment and then dig out a lake.
That's amazing.
This is an interesting country.
How's the cost of living here?
I was here 15 years ago.
Beer is cheaper than water here.
I'll drink beer with every meal.
I can't drink beer.
If you just walk into any restaurant on the street,
a meal would cost $1.50 on average.
$1.50.
- $1.50? / - $1.50?
I really want to visit Vietnam.
It's going to get really good soon.
Things are going to pick up now.
It's the best.
(Noi Bai International Airport)
(40 minutes to Hoan Kiem Lake)
($15 by taxi)
Hoan Kiem.
This is the busiest place in Hanoi.
Tourist hot spot.
Central area.
This is a famous tourist attraction, Hoan Kiem Lake.
Many Westerners, locals,
and even Korean tourists come here.
They enjoy their date around this lake.
With this place as the center,
there's Dong Xuan Market to the north.
I know it.
To the west is the hero of Vietnam,
the Ho Chi Minh Museum.
To the east is the opera house.
A Vietnamese opera house.
To the south is where
the middle class live.
It's a residential area.
- Where all the locals live? / - The main street.
- Right. / - So this is like Seokchon Lake.
- Precisely. That's it. / - I understand now.
Let's get something to eat first.
Let's get some delicious food.
I want banh mi.
You want a sandwich?
I want bun cha.
Sandwich and bun cha.
You've had plenty of that in Korea.
I want local beer.
Let's get going then.
You have to eat something
that's never been on the show.
- This is what we want. / - That's the way.
Gyeonghwan is doing a good job.
Trust me and follow me.
- I have a bad feeling about this. / - Follow me.
Go, go, go.
- It's the alley across the street. / - Where are the lights?
You have to learn to cross on your own.
- On your own? / - So basically...
Never run.
See those motorbikes?
What you do is,
just walk at your pace
and the bikes will drive past you.
The traffic will avoid you.
What if they don't?
They will.
- He wasn't kidding. / - They never hit you.
- You can't stop. / - You must not stop.
That's basic info you must know before you go.
My goodness.
A lot of people just cross the street.
We have to walk while keeping the same pace.
Don't be scared.
- We don't need to do this? / - We don't?
Let us cross the street now.
Since the cars are coming from this side...
Why aren't they coming from both sides?
Just look to your right.
It's one way here.
That's right. Look to your right.
(They take a step onto the road)
Look to your right.
Just a minute.
- You scared me. / - The car.
It was coming at us.
So the thing is...
That person in front is walking so casually.
That van! That van!
No, don't.
That's it. You're doing well.
- I don't think I can do it. / - That's the way.
- Like a local. / - You're doing well.
- You're doing well. / - Oh, my.
- The cars are just coming at her. / - Be careful.
- I don't think I can do this. / - You're doing well.
Just walk like that.
But don't mess around.
Don't mess around too much.
Let's cross. Just look this way.
- If you're scared, just look ahead. / - Follow me.
Why aren't  you coming?
- You shouldn't do that. / - You shouldn't.
If you do that, the scooters can't judge.
No, don't do that.
Just walk. Don't run.
I told you not to run.
That guy honked at me.
You have to walk at a constant speed
for the bikes to avoid you.
But you stopped halfway.
Then you ran.
That's dangerous.
I didn't know.
But I feel like I lived here in my previous life.
- This place... / - This place feels familiar.
This alley is 1,000 years old.
- Really? / - Yes.
We should take photos then.
Take a photo of us.
Do you want full-length shots?
- Yes. / - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
- You're good at taking photos. / - Isn't this nice?
I really like this.
I'm starting to like my guide, little by little.
It's important to upload photos on SNS for women.
I graduated art school.
I am an art school graduate.
You were?
He took such a nice photo.
This way please.
- That was when... / - That's so nice.
We started to like Gyeonghwan.
It really makes you open up
if they're good at taking photos.
I love this.
That's a pig's hoof.
How cute.
- Hello. / - That's so cute.
There are so many flowers.
- We'll eat here. / - Is this the place?
- Here? / - This is where we're eating.
- I love it. / - It's here.
Please go in.
- My gosh. / - Was he a regular there?
- This is so cute. / - Yes, he goes there often.
He takes his kids there often too.
(What do you associate Vietnam with?)
- Pho. / - That looks delicious.
- You did eat rice noodles. / - Looks so good.
- No, no. / - Banh mi.
- There're so many good restaurants. / - Banh mi.
So you didn't eat any of that?
We don't.
Watch this.
- Sticky rice. / - What is that?
- That looks good. / - Vietnamese sticky rice.
- What is that? / - Isn't that amazing?
- What? / - First time you've seen that, right?
People in Vietnam also eat sticky rice.
- Sticky rice? / - Sticky rice?
So in Vietnam...
Don't people in Vietnam eat Indica rice?
- But... / - I like that kind of rice.
Everyone's tried that rice already.
Corn sticky rice.
I love corn.
White sticky rice.
- I strongly recommend this. / - It sounds delicious.
Garlic.
Garlic sticky rice sounds good.
They eat a lot of garlic here too?
It's not like we have
anyone to whisper to here.
We'll breathe on you.
Just eat a variety.
I recommend...
There's a Vietnamese soy drink.
Soy milk?
It's soy milk.
- I'd like that. / - I'd like that.
He's funny.
- He prepared sticky rice and soy milk. / - Right.
- I never imagined it. / - That's right.
Here it comes, here it comes.
Goodness.
It's like red bean dessert.
- This is... / - Where's the rice? Wait.
- This is... / - Where's the rice?
The rice is in here.
- Wait a minute. / - The rice is inside.
There's dust in my food.
No, this is pork.
- What? / - Really?
They dried the pork.
- This? / - And seasoned it.
And then cut it like string.
No way.
That's pork.
- Like in China. / - Pulling it like this.
- They eat it often in China. / - But that...
It was meaty without any fat.
- It must be dried. / - Yes.
What is this one?
That one.
They made beef jerky into jelly.
What about this one? Is this liver?
It's Vietnamese ham.
- They made it here. / - Ham?
- It's good. / - That looks good.
Traditional Vietnamese ham.
So you eat them like side dishes?
You can eat everything together.
What?
Why? Is it no good?
What? What?
It's so good.
Unlike Indica rice, it fills your stomach.
(Yum)
The garlic is good.
It's chewy. The garlic is good.
I strongly recommend it.
I could hear the sound of the motorcycles,
people talking,
bargaining in the market...
You feel like a local.
You know the yellow corn they sell at Myeong-dong?
- The white one. / - Not the imported ones.
- The white waxy corn. / - Yeah, that.
So this is the Vietnamese style bibimbap.
It's got all the garnish you need.
Vietnamese ham, fried egg,
dried pork,
sausage.
You can eat it how you like in DIY fashion.
That's the joy of it.
It's different to Thai sticky rice.
- It's different. / - Thai or Hong Kong sticky rice...
Is really glutinous.
Rice wrapped in banana leaf is...
Sweet even if it has salty meat.
That's why it tastes like a dessert.
- This isn't like that. / - This tastes like a main.
It's in between our sticky rice with grains
and the stone pot rice.
It's good.
Hey, this is really good.
Thank you.
Vietnamese soy milk.
- Oh, that... / - Soy milk.
- I liked it so much. / - It's so good.
It's delicious.
That's tasty.
How do you say thank you?
How?
Cam on.
- Cam on. / - Thank you.
- Cam on? / - Cam on.
- Cam on. / - Yeah.
Cam on.
Miss, cam on!
It's like halfway between soy and regular milk.
Welcome to Hanoi.
This is so good.
It's soy milk...
Soy milk.
Made from beans.
Goodness, she's drinking it all.
- Goodness. / - Bottoms up.
She's drinking bottoms up.
Look at her neck.
- Are you okay? / - She's like us.
You're with us if you drink bottoms up.
Is it that good?
It was so good that I...
This is really good.
This costs 50 cents.
This equivalents to 50 cents.
- It's 10,000 dong. / - 50 cents?
Pho that you eat anywhere here
is 30,000 dong.
This is with all the garnish
and it's 40,000 dong.
So that's...
- $2? / - $2.
- It's so cheap. / - Not $20?
Compared to pho...
This is 50 cents more expensive.
One more thing.
I have another place in mind to visit after this meal.
- You said you love coffee. / - Yes.
We're going to drink some coffee.
It's not just regular coffee.
It's incredibly good coffee.
Plus it's the best location
for the show off photos you want.
Let me get changed first.
Can we get changed?
It doesn't matter but isn't it a bother?
Not at all!
We have to take photos at a beautiful cafe.
Let's go then.
You have to get changed 3 times a day on a trip.
I think Gyeonghwan is sick of you now.
He kind of was.
It's only been a few hours since you met.
Isn't it so pretty there?
- I love it. / - I love it.
- You must do this. / - That was on our wish list.
Taking photos in Vietnamese traditional garments.
Everyone should try this.
On your wish list,
you wrote that you wanted to take
5 million photos in beautiful ao dai.
We're in a foreign country so
we should try foreign dress.
That's right.
Let's choose your dresses first.
These are too small.
Are we going to buy them?
They have large sizes.
- Really? / - Don't worry.
They carry every size.
Thing is,
because I'm tall...
I was really worried.
You can rent these. It costs $10.
Why don't we take a look?
Let me give you a tip.
Married women choose colorful clothes.
Single women choose rather plain clothes.
- Why? / - Why?
That's discrimination.
- That's the Vietnamese culture. / - Why is that?
If I don't, is that a violation of the law?
No, it's not a violation.
It's true that I'm married
but I don't have to show that off on a trip.
- In the photos... / - That's right.
I'll just wear the one I like.
Choose whatever you want.
Some dresses cover necks and some don't.
This is pretty.
Is this considered plain here?
(They said they didn't care)
Oh, madam.
Madam!
- Madam! / - Madam!
- Madam. / - That's for Madonna.
That'd suit "Golden Oldies."
No, no, no.
- Madam. / - Life is...
??What should I do? ??
??Amor fati ??
??Ao dai party ??
(Ao dai party in the middle of the day)
They're so good.
(Let us present you the chosen dresses)
So pretty.
We hired that for an entire day for $10.
But we ended up
buying them at the end.
It cost $40 to purchase.
We paid $30 more and bought them.
(Tall height makes people think she's from Europe)
Doesn't she look like German?
- She's too big. / - Don't say that.
That was XXL.
It was XL.
Mine was XL.
(Poke)
It's good you went together.
They're the best of friends.
- They make a good pair. / - Aren't you sick of us?
They look like game characters.
- I must be crazy. / - They're shooting a commercial.
(Comedy that knows no boundaries)
The people behind...
What's going on?
What is this?
- The people behind... / - What is this?
What is going on here?
That's the men's ao dai.
Men's.
Are you a coed group?
Gyeonghwan looks so funny.
He looks exhausted.
You look like you were born here.
This suits you so well.
- I changed my name. / - To what?
- To E.C. / - What?
Eye-Catching.
- What? / - Eye-Catching.
Let's change his to Yeom Jiangshi.
You're E.C. and he's jiangshi.
It has to be like this.
Let me stick a talisman on you.
You look like a group.
I'm so happy right now.
How should I say this?
I feel confident after wearing this.
Everyone should rent this here.
This is happiness for $10.
For the entire day.
Even the door over there looks so pretty.
Even these hanging things are so pretty.
- Why are they so pretty? / - That's laundry!
Eunkyeong, how about the garlic laid out to dry?
Even the garlic is pretty.
Can you take a photo of us sitting over there?
- Take it with this. / - This one.
One more time. To the side.
1, 2, 3.
- It's a postcard. / - Look at the color.
You included the rail track.
I took one with the track and one without.
- So pretty. / - Do you like them?
- My word. / - He's so good, right?
How?
He knows how to frame the picture.
You're right.
It really is pretty.
- Dressed in the local clothes. / - We bought them.
- There are cafes here. / - And small galleries.
People actually live here too.
There are cafes and galleries.
A long time ago, Kwangkyu and Taecyeon
just passed by here.
- Oh, here! / - It's completely different.
- They didn't go inside. / - It feels so different.
So different to Yeom Tour.
He's so exhausted.
- It's different with the ao dai. / - On Yeom Tour...
It's beautiful here...
But over there,
you'll see the perfect cafe.
- Gyeonghwan is a great host. / - That's right.
He planned the best course.
It was perfect.
Coffee.
Vietnamese coffee...
You've seen plenty of coconut coffee.
Something a bit more unique.
A cafe that has never been introduced.
Their coffee is the best.
He sounds like an expert.
- I know. / - You must go here as well.
I looked up so many cafes before going there
but I couldn't find that place.
That place was nice too. Where are we going?
Once we're at this cafe, you'll be shocked.
Really?
It's the perfect shock.
(It's a little off the train track)
Finally, we're at the cafe I'm taking you to.
It's so pretty.
- So pretty. / - It's really pretty, right?
This place looks like something from a fairytale.
It's not only pretty from the outside...
If you go through the side here...
- There's a space at the back. / - Let's go in.
- That's the best part. / - Let's go in.
- It's so pretty. / - Let's go in.
My goodness.
- It's so pretty. / - It'd look pretty on rainy days.
- So pretty. / - It's so green.
They're all alive.
There's a reason why you shouldn't miss this place.
It not only looks good but they have great coffee too.
With the photos...
I'll give you a picture of a lifetime.
It's so... Wow!
- Photo time. / - Hurry.
Photo.
Now he takes photos without being asked.
I've adapted already.
He's adapted on the first day.
I've adapted.
- 1, 2, 3. / - We can trust him now.
- He's a good photographer. / - Look at the pictures.
- Art school graduate. / - So good, right?
- Yeom Tour will definitely happen. / - It's perfect.
- Let's order the coffee... / - Coffee.
You have to start the Vietnamese trip with coffee
on the first day.
- Caffeine is a must on trips. / - I love coffee.
We should know
the price of coffee before we order.
This area
is like Garosu-gil
or Gyeongnidan-gil in Korea.
- Then black iced coffee would be... / - It'd be costly.
$7 or $8.
- If you add something, then it'd be $10. / - Over $10.
So here...
You can use the internet and take photos as well.
Is there free Wi-Fi?
Yes, they have everything but
coffee is a little more expensive here.
How much?
$2.80.
- Then it's more expensive than the food. / - It is.
- It's really expensive. / - Wasn't pho $1.50?
If you compare it to pho,
the coffee here costs two bowls.
But still...
We really need pho...
- But women really need good coffee... / - Right.
- Something sweet. / - And a pretty location.
In terms of value,
it's definitely worth the two bowls.
Let's use the restroom twice to get the most out of it.
Eunkyeong.
Since we're middle-aged women.
Goodness! That was so good.
(Coconut milk coffee)
(With coconut topping)
It's here.
I can't look at it.
Thank you.
- My goodness. / - It looks delicious.
- Is yours cocoa? / - Yes.
- This is cocoa and that is coffee. / - My gosh.
Thank you.
Busy taking photos again.
- Geez. / - You need photo time here.
Come to me...
Have a taste.
With reverent hearts.
Spoon.
It's like a fantasy.
This is insane.
Game over.
- It's all over here. / - It's that good?
- How does it taste? / - Beyond your imagination.
It's over here.
Seriously...
It's not dried. It's fresh pulp.
It's fresh.
Seriously...
What's she doing?
Thank you so much.
- What was that? / - Seriously...
She's expressing respect.
Do you believe?
- I believe. / - This is amazing.
I believe.
Is this fresh cream and coconut pulp?
- No. / - It's fresh coconut pulp.
This white thing is coconut cream.
I love that they put coconut pulp in it.
I love coconut water.
I love pulp too.
I never imagined anyone would add this to coffee.
This is on a whole new level to adding ice cream on top.
If you don't like sweet stuff, you must drink this.
- I'm going to rent a room here. / - Drink this.
I'd drink this every day.
I'd like to try that.
We have something just as good, right?
Something like that, right?
Don't worry.
They're too good.
Previously, on the Ho Chi Minh City episode,
they went to a bean cafe
and had coconut coffee.
But I personally prefer this place.
- Do they put this in as well? / - That place is...
Do they give you this?
No, they don't.
That cafe was a franchise.
It's in Ho Chi Minh City and Hanoi.
- It's everywhere. / - You're right.
I don't count franchise coffee as coffee.
Coffee aficionados...
There has to be only one store?
There has to be only one original store.
Let me try cocoa as well.
Try it.
It's made of cocoa instead of coffee.
Try it. It's good too.
It's completely different taste.
It is, right?
Children would love this too.
They love it.
My kids, Eunyul and Eunu...
- Finish one each. / - They'd love it.
They love it.
If I had to choose between pho and this right now,
I'd choose this.
- More than pho. / - Because we're women.
- I'd eat both. / - I know what women want now.
Put on your best dress
and come with me.
What's the atmosphere like there?
Lots of trendy and show off people of Vietnam
are there.
- Okay. / - Okay!
- We had beer there. / - I won't lose to them.
- We won't lose. / - We won't lose.
- So this is what it's like. / - Of course.
Okay then.
Dress in your prettiest clothes
to outdo those people.
Once you're done...
- I'll guide you. / - We have to finish this first.
Bottoms up.
(It's a sin to leave this coffee)
Even the pulp.
(Shame... I ate it all)
(Coffee left over from the shoot)
I had three of those.
- Isn't that the staff waiting for you? / - Yes.
I had a sugar rush.
I feel like flying over there to drink that right now.
So you've had 5 drinks so far?
Yes, 5 drinks.
- As soon as you arrived... / - In half a day.
(They arrive at the final destination for today)
(He knows what his clients want now)
You should escort me.
Escort me.
Height, 187cm.
- The tallest in Hanoi. / - They're not kill heels...
They're just kill.
The tallest.
Goodness.
There's no one here.
- Just walk along. / - There's no one there.
Goodness.
I'm so embarrassed.
- What is this? / - So funny.
My goodness.
I had nowhere to wear that outfit.
Once we got out and walked along...
Everyone there was like...
They all took photos of us.
It was like, "Who's that?"
It's over here.
Yes.
This is so funny.
So funny.
We'll go to local eateries and have
banh mi, pho and bun cha.
We can do those things but
we should also dress up at least once...
When we travel.
Dressing up and
putting on thick makeup to go to
a classy bar is no. 1 on my list.
What is this?
You want to bare your back here?
I can easily grant this request.
But...
A place where you can
show off your figure and take photos.
(This place is lights up when the sun goes down)
(It's a rooftop pool bar)
What is this?
You've never seen this in Hanoi, right?
You can see the whole city.
- There's a hot pool. / - They had a pool.
- Is that a hotel rooftop? / - No.
- Just a rooftop. / - Just a new, hip cafe.
In order to cater for you two.
I told them to cover the elevator in this.
That doesn't sound right. It looks really old.
It's not.
I always dress like this
and go to the zoo and botanical garden with the kids.
- You walk around like this? / - Yes.
I dress like this when I go to throw out the trash.
This is my outfit for throwing out the trash.
But you should dress comfortably...
We're very comfortable.
- It looks really tight to me. / - It's not tight at all.
- Not at all. / - You look really uncomfortable.
Want me to show you again?
My ears are popping.
We're very high up. Is this the tallest building?
Let me show you poolside first.
The view here is so nice.
- Can you swim here as well? / - Yes, you can.
They have pool parties as well.
I thought you'd like this place.
I'd love to come here for brunch...
- Rather than for a pool party. / - Gyeonghwan.
Can we...
Many people come here for their wedding shoots.
- He looks cold. / - He's working so hard.
If there's lots of water, there are lots of mosquitoes.
A dagger stabs me in the heart.
Why?
But don't worry.
Hands are faster than eyes.
1, 2, 3.
- Let's take one more. / - So the water is in the shot?
- You need the pool. / - It needs to show.
You should really thank Gyeonghwan.
Did you tip him well?
Of course.
(Great pictures on Yeom Tour)
That photo.
- I've seen that photo. / - Picture of a lifetime.
Let's go up even further.
- There's no one here. / - My goodness.
- Isn't this just a rooftop? / - To the left.
Welcome.
- Hello. / - Hello?
It's "H" for hello.
- You can see all of Hanoi here. / - What's this?
It's a shrine.
(Flustered)
I think we'll get a great shot. It's okay.
Very good.
We have foreigners here
to get their picture of a lifetime.
(This is nothing)
We're going to get competitive now.
- Right now... / - I don't believe this.
Don't compete over things like this.
That's just natural for them.
Me too. Made in Korea.
- Your mom will see this. / - What?
Dads and moms will watch this.
Since you're celebrities that represent Korea...
- Then how about... / - What kind of shot?
Let's all do one each.
Why me?
- Just do it. / - We have to take your photo too.
- I'll just take photos for you. / - No way.
- Should I take this off? / - Just put that on.
This?
- To show the Yeom Tour. / - Pretend you're a model.
- That must've been so tough. / - Is this "Extreme Job?"
"Extreme Manager."
We talked about it later and he said he enjoyed it.
Turn around.
- Turn around. / - He's enjoying it.
- Gyeonghwan likes stuff like this. / - So cool.
Take a look. You look really cool.
Look at this.
- Gyeonghwan. / - Look here.
This is what I'm talking about.
Why am I wearing this?
- You want to make Yeom Tour famous. / - Right.
(It's a slow video)
It's cute.
Joy and love to you.
We'll give you a memory that lasts a lifetime.
Director, please shoot us.
- Yeom Tour... / - Film us coming from afar.
- How? / - The three of us...
Excuse me, but how many photos did you take?
Around 40,000.
- The capacity was full. / - It was about 2GB.
Sunyeong's the only one that looks rich.
Among them...
I look like I'm there to buy a building, right?
We laughed so much later when we saw these.
This is all that you have left later.
Yeom Tour's satisfaction is rising.
It looks cool now that it's night.
(Just like the old days before we got married)
Something I'm really proud of...
When you have kids...
- You only go to resorts. / - Right.
Leisure sports, playing in the sand. That's all you do.
But before I got married,
I'd hang out like this with friends.
We'd pack suitcases of clothes.
We'd do our own photo shoots.
We'd act all pretty.
But I'd forgotten all about that.
You can't go on trips with your girlfriends...
- When you're our age. / - It's hard to leave the kids.
I'm the youngest and prettiest today.
Women age as each day passes.
I didn't realize.
When you came with that hairband at first,
I was a little concerned.
I was like, "What is he doing?"
"Is he going to make us get foot massages?"
- Doing things other people always do. / - Yeah.
I was so worried that we'd do all the obvious stuff.
These aren't places that you can look up with ease.
You actually went out of your way to find them.
I was so thankful for that.
You really look like you've been moved.
That evening breeze was so nice.
You can't see many Koreans.
I haven't met one.
That's why the place I've planned tomorrow is
a spot where I've never seen Koreans to date.
Are there more places like that in Hanoi?
Even the Korean residents don't know about it.
Really?
We'll visit there for the day tomorrow.
Wow.
Now, we're moving on to the second half.
Was Hanoi ranked no. 1?
I'll beat that.
I'm so nervous.
Do you even know what we like?
Of course.
It's so good.
(Satisfaction is growing)
Thank you so much.
I believe!
We'll take one more.
This isn't your ordinary Yeom Tour.
Hanoi beer.
(More upgraded service)
The second half is incredible.
- The first day was nothing? / - It was nothing.
The first day was great for friends who are single.
This time, it's for old ladies.
What is Vietnamese style sausage stew?
It tastes good already.
(Eunkyeong and Sunyeong's hotel)
It's the next day now.
He's waiting for them with his safety belt on.
These ladies are late again.
Hello.
Goodness.
- Look at their clothes. / - Gyeonghwan.
Ladies, we're hiking a mountain today.
He's calling her ladies.
They're going hiking.
- But you've got sandals on. / - Look at their dress.
How can you wear sandals?
We have two pairs of sneakers in here...
They have so much.
They are all in here.
I just packed lightly.
Two pairs of pants...
After the hike...
- We'll have a delicious dinner. / - I know.
Since you're going to suffer...
We prepared caffeine. Down it.
She prepared caffeine?
He doesn't even have hands left to hold it.
Anyway, we don't have time so let's get the car.
- That word means... / - Over here.
I'll tell you about the car rental.
For a 7-seater car,
it's about $90.
- All day? / - What about the cost of fuel?
- Includes fuel. / - What?
- Includes cost for the driver. / - What?
- It includes parking and everything. / - So cheap.
It includes everything.
It includes parking fees and tolls.
That's incredible.
Where are we going now?
Now, we're going to Ninh Binh Province first.
Think of it like Ha Long Bay.
Ha Long Bay of the inland.
(Sunyeong's face is getting darker)
I've been to Ha Long Bay before.
It became too popular.
- I was so shocked. / - You've seen this, right?
Yes, this is a common site.
It takes about 3 or 4 hours to get there.
Ha Long Bay takes about 4 hours.
But you can tour here in half a day.
1 hour 40 minutes.
To tell you about Ninh Binh Province...
You can go there and back in a day.
It's the Ha Long Bay of the inland.
It's the backdrop of "Indochine."
There aren't many people there so it's really quiet.
It's really relaxing.
That's where we went.
You can feel the magnificent view of Vietnam.
I didn't see one Korean person there.
- Not one? / - It's a hidden gem.
Goodness. What's that?
That's a cemetery.
Did they make them look like houses?
The tombs?
My goodness.
(You can wait for the train to pass by)
(You can see various parts of Vietnam on the way)
(Gradually, the cars on the road become scarce)
We'll go to Ninh Binh...
And do the Galaxy Grotto tour first.
Galaxy Grotto?
We'll head in now.
- What's this? / - What is it?
The hat.
Today, the Yeom Tour is different.
Props like this are so important for photos.
You really need those.
Yeom Tour is great.
Wow, what is this?
Look at that mountain!
Are we going to take one of these?
Yes, we take this and follow this waterway
and head all the way in there.
- Really? / - Into that mountain.
They've already started business even though
it's only us here.
I promised you.
I won't take you to places with lots of tourists.
- It's really quiet there. / - It was only us.
With Yeom Tour, we're the only ones.
Didn't they close down?
They set that up only because it rained a lot, right?
No.
This is so interesting.
Bye.
(Heading off on a boat, a dream of all Vietnam trips)
All I hear is the water.
- This is so nice. / - This is so nice.
Over there...
- That really looks like Guilin. / - Guilin?
When you go past here, you'll see rice paddies.
I love rice paddies.
(Moved)
It's pretty.
We're going in between the paddies now.
There's no one here. Oh, my God.
This is so awesome.
It's so beautiful.
On that boat, only the sound of rowing could be heard.
There's a special food to enjoy on the boat.
It's lunch on the water!
- Yeom Tour is so... / - He just took that out in a hurry.
It's banh mi!
- It's banh mi! / - Banh mi.
Did you hear her voice? "It's banh mi!"
She was so happy.
- It's banh mi! / - Banh mi.
(Before the start of the tour)
- Four banh mi's please. / - Gyeonghwan is the king.
He bought that in the morning.
You won't find a better guide.
He even bought that banh mi from a famous place
where people line up to buy.
Once they make the banh mi,
they put it in the oven one last time.
They warm it up once more.
Their baguettes are made of rice so they taste better.
- And it's easier to digest too. / - Amazing.
There's coriander inside.
- I want a lot of coriander. / - There's a lot.
Thank you. You're the best.
And since you're in Hanoi,
Hanoi beer!
This guide is too good.
- Isn't he the best? / - I want to go on the Yeom Tour.
Me too.
I can't drink but I want to join in
- That sound! / - Check it out.
This sound.
Oh, my God. I'm so happy.
So good.
- Gyeonghwan is so thoughtful. / - I love it.
Cheers.
I don't drink beer but I drank some that day.
(They happily drink beer on the boat)
When will I ever drink beer
on a boat on Ninh Binh in Vietnam?
Thank you so much, Gyeonghwan.
- Is this okay? / - Yes.
You look really handsome right now.
You should look forward to the end of today.
How much is this banh mi?
- $1.50. / - $1.50?
A meal for 4 people costs
only $6.
- Make sure you buy some beforehand. / - Amazing.
- It's the best to eat like that. / - With some beer.
This place seems frozen in time.
It's very quiet there. It feels so different.
Gyeonghwan.
- My mom would love this. / - Right?
- Next time... / - Mom loves things like this.
Let's come with our mothers next time,
the four of us.
These places remind you of family.
So you have to take a boat there?
At the end of the road is a cave.
What's interesting is that this road leads to a cave.
No one would know about this place.
(Today's weather in Vietnam is as hot as summer)
We're almost there.
Please hang in there.
It doesn't look like there will be a cave here.
You might not think we're near a cave
but once we go up here,
there will be an amazing cave.
- It's not a winery? / - I thought it was a vineyard too.
It felt like going to a different world.
I felt like I was in "Indiana Jones."
Can you feel the cool wind?
You can feel the air conditioner breeze, right?
What is this?
- My goodness. / - It's so cool.
What is this? Where are we?
- Amazing. / - It's so cool.
Starting from here...
This is unbelievable. It suddenly dropped 5??
It must be like the ice valley in Miryang.
In the cave, you'll be surprised again.
So take a flashlight.
Flashlight?
Follow me. Watch your head.
- I really like Guide Yeom. / - Me too, I love him.
Gosh, it's big.
There are lights here as well.
The deeper you walk in, the nicer it becomes.
It looks like a rose. This is like the movie, "Alien."
- It's like a movie. / - It's like the movie, "Alien."
- It looks like there could be aliens in there. / - Yeah.
"Prometheus?"
I felt like one could film "Star Wars" there.
Here and there...
It's really pretty.
- Water drops. / - There's water.
It must be really cool in there.
Once you walk up the staircase,
stand in the center and look up.
- He even knew things like that. / - There's something.
- He's a true guide. / - He was great.
Oh, my.
Check it out.
It's amazing.
- Is it open? / - It looks incredible.
- You can even see the sky. / - No joke.
- My gosh. / - It looks so cool.
- I feel like I'm in a movie. / - It's amazing, isn't it?
This reminds me of...
"The Dark Knight Rises."
- In the movie... / - The basement...
Up there...
Yeom Tour is really captivating.
You can climb up the stairs?
Gosh, this is amazing.
I wonder how they built the stairs here.
If you come up here...
There is another space like this.
It looks so amazing.
There's the bird-shaped rock.
I can see it. I see the beak.
It looks so nice there.
If you see that in person,
it's 100 times more touching.
We'll go deeper into the cave by a boat.
- There's a boat here? / - There must be a boat.
Goodness.
- There are boats in the cave. / - All this costs $6?
I think Yeom Tour will soon open its business.
- They must. / - It's like they're making a package.
- There's no reason not to. / - Amazing.
- We're now heading to Hang Mua. / - Hang Mua.
This is where you must visit before you die.
Yet, it's not very well-known.
This place looks amazing.
On the top, you can see a dragon and a pavilion.
What's that?
This place is amazing.
- It looks a bit similar to the Great Wall. / - Right.
You'll tear up and think of your family.
That's the type of view I prepared.
(The entrance fee is $5)
You'll go to the top through the stairs here.
It's actually higher than you think.
If you're tired on the way, you can take breaks.
Let's go up.
It was quite hot that day.
It's difficult to climb...
- When it's hot. / - Gyeonghwan nearly collapsed.
But it gets cooler as you climb.
There are cool spots.
Once you reach the top and look at the other side,
the view there will make you tear up.
The other side.
- You must see that. / - Got it.
Go and see it.
Gyeonghwan.
That's where he stopped.
- We must go. / - Gyeonghwan is suffering the most.
We work out every day so...
We loved being able to burn the calories.
Sweating makes me feel good.
It's like Gyeonghwan is aging rapidly.
He seems so.
Look, there...
- It's a kiosk. / - There's an observatory here.
There's a kiosk on the way.
It's a cute kiosk. They were selling coconuts.
Why did I follow them?
I'm tired.
I don't see Gyeonghwan.
Gyeonghwan.
He can't go further.
Please go ahead, ladies.
Ladies?
So cute.
This is a great workout.
- Look at the stairs. / - It looks very nice.
The higher you climb, the more beautiful the view?
Since you can see farther.
People are waiting in line to take pictures.
(Without taking any break, they keep going)
(They don't stop climbing)
I'm so exhausted.
Gosh, this is tough.
- You'll soon see an interesting thing. / - Are we there?
There's another interesting thing?
It isn't over.
They're doing their wedding shoot here.
Here!
She was doing her wedding shoot.
In the boiling weather, wearing heels...
Unbelievable.
Unbelievable wedding.
They really love each other.
She wore that dress up the mountain.
- Up to there. / - She beat us.
Unbelievable.
- They're amazing. / - True winners.
Congratulation!
(Meanwhile, what's Gyeonghwan up to?)
Even the little kid went up.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
I feel like death.
I can do it.
Let's go.
Amazing.
The view from up there must be beautiful.
It's so nice here.
I got teary.
Seriously.
- There's a dragon. / - Where?
Over there.
Where is the dragon?
- It's huge. / - It is.
It looks awesome.
1, 2, 3.
- Is Gyeonghwan still not there yet? / - He couldn't.
He's doing a photo shoot with that person.
Are you kidding?
(Embarrassed)
It's tough even when you're dressed like this.
How did she climb up here with a wedding dress on?
She's amazing.
My goodness. Aren't you tired?
Gosh, you're amazing.
(He's finally near the peak)
Excuse me.
Dad, dad.
Did you drop by somewhere?
- I've been climbing the whole time. / - Close-up.
Close-up first.
(Eunkyeong's close-up pictures)
- There's your profile picture. / - You should work out.
- Mothers are always on the run so... / -  Gyeonghwan...
The view from this side is amazing.
Is this what you meant earlier?
It's amazing.
What is that?
This canal is connected to Trang An.
Try to...
Stand here and think about nothing for 10 minutes.
It'll be an unforgettable memory.
It looks like a painting, isn't it?
It's so beautiful.
- It's a beautiful place. / - This is amazing.
The view is incredible.
I'm going to send these pictures home.
(They want to share this view with their families)
Being up there reminded me of my family.
I took pictures of the view and sent them to my family.
- We've been working hard. / - We have.
We should work harder when we go back.
Let's work hard.
Are we going to eat now?
We'll go back to Hanoi
since a day trip is possible.
Our driver drove us back to Hanoi
with the rental car.
What is that? It's so shiny.
This is a great restaurant in Hanoi
that I want to introduce to everyone.
I have never seen any Koreans here ever.
Today, on Battle Trip...
Is it the first time revealing it?
This is the hidden card.
Vietnam style sausage stew.
What is this?
- Oh, my. / - Really?
- "Lau." / - "Lau."
They add noodles at the end.
- What is that? / - I come here often with family.
Even the kids like this.
It's a good place to bring the whole family.
I really want to eat this.
It's not ordinary noodles.
We wouldn't have known this if it wasn't for Yeom Tour.
- Isn't the atmosphere amazing here? / - I love it.
(Gyeonghwan says hello to someone)
They must be friends.
- I come here often. / - Really?
(Gyeonghwan orders the food)
That burner is so interesting.
Oh, they put two together.
(We'll have the usual)
It's delicious.
It's here.
This is amazing.
- It's lau. / - It's lau.
- It's lau. / - I'm so proud.
These are just the basic ingredients.
These are mushrooms and meat sausages.
Like Sikyung says, it looks good as is.
- Just. / - It has every tasty ingredient.
It has squids, shrimps and clams.
- What is the soup made of? / - Fish.
They usually just make the soup
by themselves with herbs.
For 5 people, it only costs about $35.
This place is amazing.
- Just put everything in. / - Everything?
- Tofu. / - Everything.
Everything is healthy.
It's starting to boil.
- Let's put the vegetables. / - We really like this.
- Let's put this much in. / - All you can eat.
nfvlf
You can keep asking for vegetables.
Look at this. This is amazing.
It looks like me. Why is it so long?
- Let's just put a few in. / - I want that one.
This is fried tofu paper.
I think I ate about 40 pieces of the fried tofu.
- That's really delicious. / - To make it spicy...
- Put this in. / - I need to buy that.
- Put this in. / - I'm going to take one with me.
- We bought it because it was so good. / - Line up.
- The soup is amazing.  / - It's amazing.
- We could put more in. / - Add more?
- Let's make it really spicy. / - I love it.
This looks really good.
I'll make the sauce.
Squeeze some lime.
And put the chili peppers in.
- Where did you dip it? / - Right there.
It's so good.
- Dip it in the sauce. / - That looks so good.
What is delicious in Vietnamese?
nn
It tastes so clean.
- It suits the taste of Koreans. / - We like soup.
- Meat. / - It's good when you want soup.
It just looks good.
(She taste the fried tofu paper)
Eat the small one.
It's like fried tofu.
Because it soaks in the soup, it tastes like dried fish.
- It's soaked in the soup. / - That's right.
You can get more vegetables for free.
- More vegetables for free. / - Vegetables are expensive.
- It's really cost-effective. / - Yes.
I really need to go there to meet Gyeonghwan.
They add noodles later, right?
It's fantastic.
- It's here. / - Is this the noodles?
Why is it so cute?
Noodles?
- Noodles. / - What's this?
The noodles are good even if you eat it plain.
It was so delicious.
Put it in.
- It's so adorable. / - It's floating.
- Let me try the plain noodles. / - The plain noodles.
The noodles are really thin. Try it.
(Crunch)
We have to put noodles in this kind of soup.
This is that thing.
It's the ramen snack my son eats.
- That taste. / - It was so good.
I bought a box of it.
Didn't you bring it today?
- I ate all of it. / - I'll send you some.
They have different flavors. Shrimp, beef...
- Chicken. They have a variety. / - I want it all.
The shrimp flavor was the best.
- Highly recommend it. / - Shrimp flavor.
I don't think you'll gain weight with these noodles.
(It's zero calories if it's delicious)
(Slurping)
I really need to drink the soup.
(The spicy soup relieves upset stomachs)
I can't help it.
Since we're in Hanoi,
we need to try Hanoi vodka.
That's amazing. You need to remember this.
- What is that? / - It's the Hanoi local vodka.
Try some Hanoi vodka.
Is it okay for you to drink today?
- Did you video call your family? / - Yes.
The kids are all sleeping.
- Can I give you a drink now? / - Yes.
Okay.
First...
I can't drink alcohol
but he made such a delicious drink.
- It's cider. / - I was so surprised.
Yeom's cocktail.
Here, it's really cool. Take this.
Put a lime in there.
- Oh, my. / - It looks so good.
- That's amazing. / - You have to put a lot in it.
It's so nice that a local is making that for you.
The locals drink like that.
I love this.
You did a good job going up the mountain.
Let's end today with this.
- Cheers. / - 1, 2, 3.
1, 2, 3.
- It's so good. / - It's really good.
- It's so good. It's not the time to take photos. / - Try it.
How is it?
- I thought you couldn't drink alcohol? / - It's so good.
- Please don't over drink. / - That looks so delicious.
Your little finger goes up when something's good.
It makes you like this.
Who gave me sugar water?
I put vodka in it.
- Are you okay with another drink? / - Yes.
I did a food show for 5 years.
One of the best was noodles made
from freshly caught crab from Yeongdeok.
This beats that.
It's the best.
Vietnam is too good.
The votes might be the highest ever.
- Isn't it amazing? / - Yes.
I prepared something else tomorrow.
(The next day, there were only 4 hours left)
(Until the plane departed)
- What is that? / - Till the end.
We went there for a short time but it was packed.
Ta-da.
This is the last day today.
I prepared something meaningful.
- Should we go inside? / - It's a restaurant.
Where are they going?
(Is the last course a restaurant?)
(Where did he confidently lead the mothers to?)
The building is big.
- The building is endless. / - It's connected.
It connects to the next building.
- Ta-da. / - It's a cooking class.
We completed our bucket list.
We didn't know that he would complete the entire list.
- Are you ready? / - We're ready.
Today, we will cook banh xeo.
You've heard of banh xeo, right?
It's like a pancake.
It's kind of like a wrap.
It's like a Korean fritters.
We're going to make it ourselves and eat it.
That looks really good.
It's perfect with beer.
Bean sprouts,
chives, and onions.
- It looks like mushrooms. / - We have all this in Korea.
Mung beans.
- They sell banh xeo powder. / - It's like pancake mix.
Let's buy this.
Inside...
We have to take this out.
- It's turmeric. / - It's a spice powder.
You don't have to buy it separately.
It's convenient with that powder.
It's for three people.
- 1, 2, 3. / - 1, 2, 3.
(Add half of the turmeric powder)
(Add 3 spoons of coconut milk)
Okay.
- Add water. / - Water.
(Mixing)
Salt? Okay, add some salt.
- You sieve it. / - Yes, we have to sieve it.
Banh xeo.
It's clean now. Look at the bottom.
- It's so pretty. / - It's smooth now.
Look at this.
- Let is rise. / - Rise.
Rise for 10 minutes.
(They are preparing the other ingredients)
- We do this for glass noodles. / - Right.
(Take the shell off the shrimps in the middle)
(Make little cuts in the body)
Oh, this...
She looks like a chef.
- It's looking good now. / - Isn't the color so pretty?
Oh, my God.
Okay.
This is important.
The paste.
(The paste is thicker than water after 10 minutes)
He uses a lot of oil.
Heat the oil first.
It's like deep frying.
He's throwing it out.
I see.
He covered the pan completely with oil.
It was so fun and memorable.
(Pour the paste in the hot pan)
Put the onions in.
(Add toppings)
- That looks good. / - There are a lot of ingredients.
- I'm generous. / - It's like an Asian taco.
It's like Korean fritters.
- Like a seafood fritters. / - Right.
(Banh xeo with love)
Let's go to a nice place
to taste the dish we made.
- That's so simple. / - That was a famous restaurant.
They set the table so we can enjoy the dish there.
It's part of the cooking class.
Please come in.
You get to eat good food...
- Check out the table. / - This feels awesome.
We dressed up to the end.
- Are they the dishes we made? / - Amazing.
- It's all decorated... / - This restaurant is so nice.
So we made this?
Can we cook these dishes here?
You can cook all these dishes.
- It looks amazing. / - But we only made banh xeo...
- To save time. / - So good.
You can choose three dishes and make them,
which costs $55.
Let's try banh xeo that you made first.
- There are two kinds... / - It's like pizza.
Of banh xeo.
There's one folded in half.
- That one's common. / - This is the other kind.
But this is what we made.
Cut it and
wrap it with rice paper.
- That's unique. Watch carefully. / - Isn't it unique?
- Put it on your plate. / - He didn't dip in water.
Without water.
That's the rice paper you eat without wetting them.
- Put a piece of banh xeo on it. / - Add this...
- A few slices of pineapple. / - I'll add some peppers.
- Cucumber. / - I like chili peppers.
Then roll it.
It's not like the wet spring rolls
we usually eat at a Vietnamese restaurant.
- See? It's very crispy. / - It does look crispy.
- Like that. / - You're right.
- Enjoy it. / - Let's try this one.
- What is it? / - It's so good.
Oh, no. I'm in a hurry.
- What do I do? / - Give me some scissors.
- Hello? / - I'm in such a hurry.
It's so good.
- Then this... / - Add this...
Shrimp on top.
- You're chefs already. / - Wrap it up.
- Oh, dear. / - Oh, dear.
- Don't be so greedy. / - It looks nice, doesn't it?
You know I'm a modest woman.
(Modest women eat in one bite)
- Sunyeong is being greedy. / - I look modest, right?
Are you fighting with the food?
- Is it good? / - It's so delicious.
What should I do?
It's amazing. You'll be surprised.
It's unbelievable.
Roll it up.
That's right. She's doing a good job.
That's right.
It's nothing like our fritters.
It's between scorched rice
and a crispy thin pizza.
- It's hard to watch. / - Right?
It was really good.
- You can cook it now, right? / - Yes.
- I'll definitely try this at home. / - That looks so good.
I'll cook banh xeo every day.
Let's finish this and go to a market
to buy the ingredients.
- We bought all the ingredients. / - Banh xeo ingredients.
We bought all the ingredients there.
Did you buy all that?
We used three carts for that.
We completed our bucket list in such a short time.
Yes, we did.
Thanks to the Yeom Tour
with all the information that
even local residents don't know,
I was so happy.
And we completed our bucket list during our trip.
Oh, dear.
- Thank you. / - Thank you so much.
We had a wonderful time at the top of the mountain.
It will stay with us as a happy memory
for the rest of our lives.
We meditated for about 10 minutes there.
- I cried at that time. / - I missed my family.
The whole thing is what you've learned
the hard way by living in Vietnam.
You showed us the essence of Vietnam.
I'm glad that you've met a lot of good people.
I'll introduce you to my friends
when they go on a trip to Hanoi.
- He's Yeomnoi. / - I'll introduce Yeomnoi to them.
- Did you just call me Yeomnoi? / - A new name.
It was the best.
I love the Yeom Gyeonghwan Tour.
Gyeonghwan looked great during the trip.
I'm nervous. They're talking about a celebratory drink.
Let's have a celebratory drink.
Everyone, please come to Hanoi.
It's so cool.
It must've been real nice.
It was really nice.
I'm so nervous now.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Eric, how did you feel?
You watched it without saying anything.
I was so jealous watching it.
I really want to go there and try the food.
What would you like to eat there?
- Lau looked good. / - Right?
I want to have a drink with lau.
- Do you drink? / - I do.
Really?
And Gyeonghwan had a hard time there
but it's a lot closer than Ha Long Bay.
It's called Ha Long Bay of inland.
You should go to Ninh Binh
if you want to go boating.
Ninh Binh is famous now
so it has a lot of tourists.
But we went to a hidden attraction
a little further in.
Yeom Tour was the first one to show the place.
- That's why the place was so quiet. / - Right.
- You should find hidden attractions. / - Right.
- Let's stand up. / - It's time...
To check the cost.
The total amount we spent for 3 days...
- In Hanoi. / - The total cost...
Excluding the airline tickets.
- Per person... / - Per person!
We spent $217.70.
What did you say?
- $210? / - $217.70.
- What... / - For 3 days?
- For 3 days? / - We ate all that food.
It's good. Let's vote right away.
- Stand up. / - $210.
Would you go to Hanoi
according to the Yeom Tour plan?
Please vote.
(Yeom Tour made a new plan for Hanoi)
(What will the judges choose?)
Boracay next week. What will you do?
- What? / - We're fine.
- Don't say weird things. / - We're fine.
- Seriously... / - If only you didn't do that.
- I know. / - I'm so worried.
Boom, Jihye, you have something special, right?
Don't worry. Our trip will be totally different.
(Next week)
This is amazing.
Boracay is incredible.
This is Boracay.
I prepared a talent for you.
Koreans don't know this course.
It's lifting.
It's the hottest place.
(No more obvious trips, new Boracay)
We met a new Boracay.
??Cay, cay, Boracay ??
("Jealousy" by MONSTA X)