(An emerging vacation spot, Phu Quoc, Vietnam)
Song Vacation!
It's the world's second largest safari.
Hey!
The world's longest cable car.
It feels really different.
It's just like a painting.
1, 2, 3.
We have to eat this.
This is it!
(Who will be the winning team?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Hwijae, JR of NU'EST W)
(An Mina, Park Eunhye)
(Song Haena, Song Kyunga)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Just like last week, today's theme is
the emerging vacation spots of 2018.
We will give out books if you take a photo of you
watching Battle Trip and post it on your social media.
We look forward to your participation.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
Alright. The vacation season has begun.
JR, do you have any good tips
when going on vacation?
- Actually, I studied it a little. / - Good.
An airport is where you start your trip.
You can check congestion levels of
the departure lounge beforehand.
You can check it online...
- Right. / - Or a mobile application.
It shows the current congestion level
and the expected level for tomorrow.
- That's amazing. / - I had a problem with it once.
During the Pyeongchang Winter Olympics...
It took twice the time to go through departure.
So you'd better...
- Check it before you leave. / - He's right.
And there's an important thing.
You take a lot of photos and upload them on
your social media when you go on an overseas trip.
But it's very dangerous
to upload a picture of your airline ticket.
- Why? People do that a lot. / - That's because...
It has a barcode on it.
The barcode contains a lot of information
as well as a lot of personal information.
Some bad people could use it
to leak personal information.
- We should be careful. / - Make sure...
Not to show barcodes.
- I'll remember that. / - And when you buy tickets...
You look for cheap ones.
But you can't buy anything just because it's cheap.
Some special deals offer
0kg of baggage service.
It means you have to pay extra.
You have to pay extra for every kilogram,
So it can be more expensive than the regular price.
Make sure to check it before you buy airline tickets.
These are the tips for overseas trips we prepared.
Last week, we went to Phu Quoc, Vietnam.
And today, we're going to Khao Yai, Thailand.
- Are you going to be okay? / - To be honest...
I liked their trip.
But I couldn't wait to show you our trip.
Think about it.
Why do you think our trip is introduced later?
Why do you think our video is played later?
I guess you don't watch our show much.
We play the fun ones first.
They said Phu Quoc is like an unknown world.
But all we didn't know
was the name, Phu Quoc.
But our trip to Khao Yai will show...
- A whole new world. / - It's that good?
The whole thing is a journey into the unknown.
- Alright. / - Everything is unknown.
What else?
Khao Yai is not
well known to foreigners...
But it's a perfect place for eco-tourism...
And the best vacation spot for Thai people.
Eco means it's clean.
Eco means it's hard.
No, it means it's relaxing.
Eco means low tech. And it means inconvenience.
So do you like polluted places?
No.
- Alright, then. / - People lie so much...
Let's watch their trip to Khao Yai
and enjoy the unknown world.
- What's your team name? / - 1, 2, 3.
- An Park Tour. / - An Park Tour.
Let's watch it together.
(An Park Tour to Khao Yai starts)
I'm excited.
- It feels real now, right? / - Yeah.
This is my first time to go on a trip for a TV show.
My heart is pounding.
What should I do?
We shot a movie together before.
It's called "Steel Rain."
I didn't belong to any agency at that time.
And she introduced me to her agency.
She took good care of me.
- In fact, she's well known... / - Me?
For taking good care of other people.
- What a nice friend. / - You're very kind.
I think we'll hit it off on a trip.
While I'm clumsy and careless...
Mina is meticulous...
Quiet and organized.
She speaks English well.
Did you live abroad?
- I used to live in New Zealand. / - New Zealand.
Unless she's not drunk...
What are you talking about?
Do you have drinking habits?
She becomes cute when she's drunk.
- She becomes cute. / - Doesn't she become too cute?
- Yes, she's really cute. / - I see.
No.
Is it hard for you to travel far since you have kids?
I don't feel comfortable traveling far without my kids.
And I won't be able to have fun either.
Stop lying.
We'll see if you're having fun or not.
After I had my kids, traveling destinations
became places that my kids could go too.
I had to go to safe and clean places
and places where I could feed them.
I had to choose places I could easily feed them.
I thought it might be nice to go with the opposite of that.
A place I wouldn't normally go to?
- I like adventures. / - I see.
I'd like to help you get out of your daily life.
Let's go to a place no one has visited before.
I've been to Thailand about four times.
- I'm as good as a local. / - She's been there a lot.
(She asked her friends in Thailand for recommendations)
(She obtains special information from Thailand)
I asked around a lot this time.
There's a huge national park in Thailand.
It's called Khao Yai National Park.
There are wild animals and it's a jungle.
We ought to experience something like that.
(Khao Yai is located in the northeast of Bangkok)
(An unknown land of grand nature)
(It's Thailand's very first national park)
- What's that? / - Look at that.
- What is that? / - Wow.
That's a wild elephant. It's not kept in a cage.
We have to come up with the name of our tour.
How about An Park Tour using our last names?
It also represents that I want to be outside
of the national park while you want to be inside.
- That's true. / - An Park Tour.
Okay. An Park Tour. Like this?
- An Park. / - An Park.
An Park Tour!
Let's do it again.
(Will they be okay in Thailand?)
An Park Tour!
We're headed to Khao Yai National Park.
Inside, there are wild animals.
It's really magnificent here already.
- It's real Mother Nature. / - That's a real jungle.
It's very different from what you'd expect.
(The mission is to find the hidden traces of wildness)
You have to see deer like that.
It's fascinating.
(This is so interesting)
Will this get edited out if we don't see an elephant?
Gosh, what's that?
It showed up as if it was waiting.
Today, it'll feel like a farm in Italy.
It's the largest winery in Khao Yai.
How is there a winery in Thailand?
This! I like this!
You went to a night market too!
- Thailand is known for night markets. / - Great, great.
It's not like the commercialized night market.
It's a real, local night market.
There's so much water.
Normally, it's three times a year.
This is Thai style sausage.
I enjoy adventures.
- Mina was a guide on this trip. / - Yes, indeed.
It must've been so convenient.
(Her preferences are clearly defined)
It does smell.
Wow!
Hey, that looks good.
I like this.
Can we eat this at the hotel?
What's that? What's that?
What?
(She's innocent and gets easily scared)
You startled me.
(Park Eunhye)
An Park Tour!
(5 hours and 45 minutes to Bangkok from Incheon)
- We've arrived at Bangkok. / - Right.
There aren't any currency exchange places
in Khao Yai.
- Really? / - Yes, so...
- We need to... / - Because it's the countryside?
Exchange the money here.
For convenience.
- To baht? / - Yes, baht.
We exchanged the money to Thai baht.
Can't you use your cards in Khao Yai?
It's a rural area, credit cards aren't widely accepted.
- You use cash then. / - It's better to bring cash.
(How to get to Khao Yai, 120km away from Bangkok)
(It takes 1 hour and 43 minutes by car)
You can get there by bus or train.
The train runs only twice a day.
It's hard to get on a bus too.
(It takes 6 to 7 hours by train)
(It takes 3 hours and 30 minutes to 4 hours by bus)
- For now... / - How about the taxi?
We can get there by taxi...
But it'd be hard to get around the place that way.
Why? Aren't there any taxis in Khao Yai?
Khao Yai doesn't have taxis.
- We'll rent a car and drive there. / - A rental car.
I'll drive since you prepared everything.
Driving in Thailand is harder than you think.
But you'll get used to it quicker than you think.
Can you trust me?
Aren't you scared?
- Alright. / - Hold on.
- This is on the left side... / - This is automatic, right?
Please drive safely.
(They head to Khao Yai which is 2 hours from Bangkok)
I'm looking forward to it.
(They set out with high expectations about their trip)
(How to get to Khao Yai, 120km away from Bangkok)
(It takes 1 hour and 43 minutes by car)
Let's get some sleep.
Tomorrow... Khao Yai.
(The first day of their trip has finally dawned)
For breakfast today, we'll go to
a pretty restaurant only locals go to.
- Great, great. / - They don't have an English menu.
- I bet the air is really fresh. / - It really is.
(A local restaurant in nature)
(Eunhye has the left lane to herself while driving)
Look at that. It's so pretty. I love roads like this.
- I love these kinds of trees. / - Right
This must be it. Gosh, it's so pretty. What is this?
Hey, I didn't know such a place existed here.
(The peaceful nature is evident in the garden)
Gosh, this place is so pretty.
Goodness, look at that. What is this place?
I love these kinds of places.
- That's a restaurant? / - Yes, we went for breakfast.
Only locals frequent the restaurant. I'm serious.
Gosh, it's so pretty. It's right up my alley.
- Right now... / - Yes, I like it.
- Do you like it? Is it fun? / - This is fun.
(The wooden merry-go-round is Eunhye's favorite)
I'm dizzy.
(The wooden see-saw brings back memories)
- Just like that? / - This is fun.
It's been ages since I'd been on a see-saw.
- This is nice. / - Seriously.
I love this place.
Eunhye, this is the famous spot.
- The fluttering laced sheet. / - Okay.
It just started getting popular among the locals.
- If you sit over there... / - It'd look amazing...
No, look over there.
Hey, this is a honeymoon photo for newlyweds.
- That's the best photo. / - I took it.
(Free from kids, no husbands today)
"No husbands today."
Alright. Since we took our photos...
- Let's go eat a tasty breakfast. / - We went to eat.
This place would look beautiful even if it rains here.
It was the monsoon season but it didn't rain.
Oh, no.
What is it? What?
Everything was written in Thai.
- Oh, no! / - It means only Thai people visit.
(The class of a seasoned adventurer)
We're going to have this one, this one...
- Thank you. / - Are we going to have this?
- Are we having this? / - Yes.
That looks really delicious.
Here it is. Here it comes.
Isn't that too much?
I see. This is how it looks like.
(Sausages made of glutinous rice and fermented pork
(Sai krok Isan, about $3)
These are garlic, ginger and chili peppers.
- This is a Thai sausage. / - Okay.
People will either like it or hate it. I've never had it.
I wanted to try it.
They made the sausages from scratch.
That has to be delicious.
- Don't you like Thai sausages? / - They are good.
- Yes, we ate them together before. / - Right.
(She puts it in her mouth first)
Shouldn't you eat the whole thing in one go?
I was going to eat the whole thing at once...
But when I just bit the sausage,
the ginger flavor was overpowering.
First of all, the sausage is good. It's delicious.
- The sausage scent is strong. / - Right, right.
It's good. Eunhye, you must eat it at once.
It tastes like that dish in Korea.
It's like the pork belly wrap.
Let's try it.
(Whatever)
(Isn't it the best-tasting dish in this galaxy?)
(How will she evaluate the Thai sausage?)
It's spicy.
(Screaming)
- Why? / - It got spicier with every bite.
People who love spicy food will love this.
Because it's really good.
It's spicy and my tongue hurts.
But I think I'll miss the dish later.
This is definitely addicting.
Since the chili pepper is strong,
I can't taste garlic and ginger.
And actually, it tastes sour like vinegar.
I don't know where it's from.
Instead of just eating the sausages...
- It's better with the vegetables. / - I agree.
- It's much better that way. / - I want beer.
Why did you make me drive?
(Feeling sorry)
What's this?
We all know this, it's pad thai.
Let's find out how the pad thai tastes
at a local restaurant recommended by the locals.
- My goodness, this is it. / - Pad thai is great.
- That's the best way to go. / - That has to be delicious.
But that pad thai looks different from the ones we know.
- That pad thai doesn't have eggs. / - Right?
It's good.
We eat this a lot in Korea but in Korea...
- They add shrimp and seafood. / - Seafood...
- This one has pork in it. / - I see.
I thought it was beef at first.
It doesn't have that pork smell. And this.
- The mung bean sprout. / - The bean sprout is raw.
It's crispy.
There's a hint of spiciness.
It's the spring onion.
It gets rid of the greasiness.
With the spiciness from the spring onion...
But this is so good.
Yes, it's really good.
Which one is your favorite?
I liked everything.
- The sausage was my favorite. / - Same here.
It was unique too.
The taste keeps coming back to me.
Where are we going after breakfast?
Here's the real reason for coming here.
We're heading to Khao Yai National Park.
Inside the park, we'll meet the wild animals.
Let's see if we can see the elephants.
And the waterfall from hell. Haew Narok Waterfall.
- That was the best. / - That looks amazing.
We'll wrap up with a night safari tour.
With that, we'll end our trip for today.
(An Park Tour)
(Khao Yai National Park)
You'll do the safari tour today.
- It'll take days to see the park. / - I agree.
We didn't get to see the whole place.
(The entrance fee, about $13.50)
(It's additional $1.70 for the vehicle)
Gosh, this place already looks like a dense forest.
It's a jungle.
- It doesn't live at the peak. / - An elephant!
Yes, an elephant.
They told us to watch out for the elephants.
It means that elephants walk around here.
- It's cute. / - How adorable.
You can see that sign only at the park.
You can get the maps.
Show me the place where we're visiting.
This is the observatory for the elephants.
This is Haew Narok Waterfall where we need to visit.
- You need a car to get around. / - Right.
- We're going to the salt lick. / - What's that?
Elephants need to absorb salt.
It's a place where they lick salt.
- Elephants are always seen there. / - Mina...
You really studied a lot.
The elephants come to that place and lick salt.
I heard a herd of elephants visits that place.
- You can just wait there then. / - Right.
- It's literally salt lick? / - Yes, it's called salt lick.
Goodness.
Be careful.
- Oh, no. / - It's so cute. It's looking at us.
Monkey.
- Look. There's another one. / - It's dangerous.
I'm usually scared of monkeys.
But the monkeys there were very clean.
They're not aggressive as long as you
don't touch them and let them be.
- That baby monkey. / - That monkey's so cute.
It was so cute.
They climb up trees just like that.
You can't touch them. Can you feed them?
- No, never. / - They are wild monkeys.
(You can't see wild monkeys at a zoo)
(They are on full alert)
(Let's run away for now)
- That's amazing. / - Let's clap.
- Amazing. / - Gosh, the monkey.
It's fascinating.
It tapped the other one.
(Just lower your head)
How cute.
They were friends.
- You should be careful. / - They're catching lice.
Right, we must drive carefully there.
- It's with a baby monkey too. / - There's another one.
- This is awesome. / - It's with a baby monkey too.
- They're talking. / - There are so many.
You're right.
They're hanging onto the trees like koalas.
Those monkeys...
- Look behind you. / - They're lying on the road.
- They're catching lice in the open. / - My gosh.
The monkey must've said, "Hey, lie down here."
It's so intriguing how they're not dangerous.
Don't you think
they'll come and catch lice if we sit here?
- They're eating. / - Bye.
(We'll catch lice for you next time)
(An Park Tour's animal handbook in Khao Yai)
When you go to tourist attractions
in Japan or Bangkok...
Monkeys usually come at you and look scary.
They're usually scary but those monkeys...
- Were peaceful. / - They were, yes.
- They're going about their day. / - That's right.
They were just spending their time. They're so cute.
The baby monkey was glued to the mother monkey.
- It looked so adorable. / - It was sitting on the lap.
When I saw the monkeys, I got excited.
I really hope we get to see the elephants.
- I think we might be able to. / - Yes, I think so too.
(From the information center to elephant observatory)
Did you arrive at the observatory for elephants?
- I liked this spot the most. / - We got close then...
We walked since we couldn't take the car.
What is that, by the way?
"Deer hit people."
- Oh, that? / - Hey, deer...
- It said so over there. / - They don't hit you.
The deer is giving him a high-five.
It's giving him a high-five?
A deer can give high-fives?
Goodness, Mina. You're quite the joker.
When deer try to high-five you, dodge them.
- What if deer hit me? / - You'll be fine.
Come on.
- Look, Isn't it nice? / - This is nice.
The scenery is out of this world, right?
Yes, it's beautiful indeed.
Gosh, this place...
(The unobstructed scenery comforts them)
It's a music video.
You could hear the grass swaying.
You could hear the bugs and birds chirping too.
You could hear numerous kinds of birds chirping.
The sound of the chirping was enough to comfort me.
Look at the clouds. They're hanging...
- Right next to us, right? / - Yes.
Elephants should be coming from there.
(This meadow calls for a herd of elephants)
- That'd be dangerous. / - You must run if you see them.
That must be the observatory.
- Right? / - Over there.
- But... / - The observatory.
- There's an observatory. / - It's not dangerous.
- But you don't want to startle the elephants.
That could lead to accidents.
Gosh, I love this place.
- Eunhye, come here. / - Yes?
- Where? / - Can you see a red puddle there?
- That? / - Let me explain about that puddle.
Herds of elephants come, eat the salt and leave.
It'd be nice to see the elephants
but we probably won't, right?
I guess they come once in a while.
Apparently you have to be really lucky to see them.
- It must be rare. / - Don't you think we're lucky?
(They wait for the elephants)
- You had to keep waiting? / - Yes.
- It's a sad song. / - The sounds of birds chirping...
(The cruel elephants don't show up)
If the elephants don't come here,
will this get edited out?
- They're not coming. / - The fact that I was first...
To come here and know about this place is my luck.
(We hope that you will be lucky to meet elephants)
- They didn't see elephants. / - You didn't see them?
- You didn't see them. / - We didn't see them there.
- Gosh. / - That lacks the finishing touch.
(An Park Tour)
(Haew Narok Waterfall)
Next up is the Haew Narok Waterfall.
The waterfall from hell, Haew Narok Waterfall.
The water falls from a height of 120m.
- 120m? / - Yes.
- What? / - What is it?
- Where? / - A deer!
- Where? / - A deer! It's on your right.
- The deer is eating grass. / - You're right.
You know, it's not a deer we usually think of.
It's a wild deer.
- It will kick us if we get close. / - Yes.
Will it run at us?
But it looks so pretty.
They preserved nature as much as they can.
- Deer come here and eat grass. / - Precisely.
Are we still watching it because it's a wild deer?
Deer!
Look over here.
- It looked at us. Hi. / - It really looked at us.
- Whenever we met animals... / - Hi.
- It was wonderful. / - Stay healthy.
It was moving too.
(An Park Tour's handbook on animals in Khao Yai)
- This part looks like a real jungle. / - Right?
It's so quiet here.
Since not that many people know about this place...
- It's better because it's quiet. / - I agree.
We get to experience the real nature here.
- We can't with crowds of people. / - Exactly.
We'll only see people here.
Eunhye, I have a confession to make.
I have a confession to make.
The truth is that, to see this waterfall,
we must climb down 190 steps.
- You have to climb back up. / - You must climb up.
- It's called Haew Narok Waterfall. / - 190 steps?
(Is this really happening?)
We're as good as dead.
- It's the steps from hell. / - Exactly.
- The steps are steep too. / - Goodness.
Rather than the waterfall from hell,
the steps are from hell.
Eunhye, since the steps are steep, be careful.
- We might slip. / - Yes.
Eunhye, hold onto the railing. Eunhye?
Are you alright?
Are you alright? You can't do this?
The steps are getting steeper.
I hate this.
(The steps are extremely steep)
- Watch out. / - Focus on you. It's dangerous.
Okay.
(Only those who climb down 190 steps can see)
Amazing.
I felt bad that I hesitated climbing down the steps.
- That looks incredible. / - This looks awesome!
We were so moved when we saw the waterfall.
We realized that the steps were there for a reason.
- It wouldn't be great without them. / - Right.
It must've been so cool there.
There's so much water.
You have to come during the monsoon to see this.
Look over there.
During the monsoon season, the elephants...
Were swept down along this waterfall.
That's why it's called the waterfall from hell.
I can see how an elephant can get swept away.
I've never seen...
- Something huge like this. / - Me too.
This trip is really interesting.
It makes me stare at things for a while.
Usually, I look at things very briefly.
But this makes you want to stay.
The elephant observatory did that to me too.
There's something about this place.
- Right? / - Seriously.
Here, you can feel happiness
when you do nothing.
Let's go.
Not just anyone can see it.
- You have to earn it. / - That's right.
We're crawling.
Goodness, you have to climb up.
(They have to suffer climbing up after the waterfall)
We're crawling.
- Still. You have to see it, right? / - It was so moving.
- Of course. / - You must go.
(Khao Yai National Park)
(They're off to see the night safari)
There must be something over there.
People are taking pictures.
What is it?
(It's out, come here)
- Look over there. / - What is it?
Elephant! That's an elephant!
- It's an elephant. / - It's so cool.
Goodness.
It makes an entrance like
this is a theater or something.
As if it was all planned.
Elephant! That's an elephant!
It's so big. I'm afraid to go out.
- I want to see it up close. / - It's really big.
- It's huge. / - It is.
Don't Thai people love elephants?
It's a symbol of good fortune.
It's really huge.
The elephant moves slower than I thought.
It walks slowly.
She's following the elephant.
She looks really startled.
It's so scary.
Did you see that? The elephant is so charismatic.
Did you see it raise its foot? Unbelievable.
Thank goodness he didn't attack.
The way it threatened her was...
It's leaving.
- You shouldn't leave your car? / - Find your friend.
Of course you shouldn't.
- You saw an elephant. / - Because it's dangerous.
(An Park Tour's handbook on animals in Khao Yai)
This park is so big. The sun is setting already.
I know.
(A new world different from the day opens up at night)
It's really wild.
300 different wild animal species live in that park.
- 300? / - Yes.
I'm unfamiliar with night safari.
The night safari is...
One-hour long.
For an hour, we can explore...
- The wild forest at night. / - You can look through it.
(About $17 per vehicle)
(Something appeared while they were getting ready)
There's a porcupine.
- A porcupine? / - Over there.
Over there.
What is it?
- That thing. / - A porcupine.
- It's cute. / - It's a crested porcupine.
I know that. It's a porcupine, right?
My kid loves that.
- Where? / - It has...
Really long, sharp quills.
- I've never seen them before. / - They're really long.
(An Park Tour's handbook on animals in Khao Yai)
They offer tours at 7 and 8 p.m.
Let's go!
This is kind of...
It's bright here because we have lights.
But look over there. It's scary. It's so dark.
(Night of the wilderness is pitch dark)
- Usually, safari cars have a roof. / - Yes.
But this... There are wild animals...
- Nocturnal animals. / - Right.
This can't be compared with any other night safari.
I'll remember this for a really long time.
We can't experience something like this easily.
We're going deeper into the forest.
Look behind you.
Goodness. It's so scary.
- It's totally dark. / - There's nothing.
- There's nothing. / - It's scary.
Because there is no light.
(Excited and scared)
- It's really scary. / - It's really scary.
(Even the lightning is frightening)
Did you hear that sound?
(She's high-strung)
What's that noise?
What was that sound?
- What is it? / - What's wrong?
(Tap)
(Scared to death)
(Something fell from the tree)
(It's chaos)
What was that? What is it?
That scared me.
What was that?
It's over there. It's fruit.
- That's funny. / - I got so scared.
- It fell on my head. / - It dropped on Mina's head.
- But Eunhye got more scared. / - Exactly.
(Eunhye wins the Best Coward Award)
I was thinking,
"What if a snake falls from the tree?"
And that dropped right onto my head.
I got so scared.
(The vehicles suddenly stop)
There must be something.
What is it?
What's that? There's something small.
I think it's an owl. It's really small.
- It's a wild owl. / - I love owls.
Why is an owl on the ground?
What's funny is that it's right by a lake.
Why is it sitting by a lake
instead of on a tree?
It must be a sad owl.
- It's so cute. / - Maybe it's there to drink water.
I wonder why it's sitting there in the dark.
I think it's amazing
that we get to see an owl in the wilderness.
You never know what animals you'll get to see.
- It's all luck. / - Yes, it is.
I'm not afraid anymore. I want to find something.
It's like finding hidden pictures.
I want to find more
and see more animals.
- You're right. / - Yes.
Animals you see in the wild feel different.
I thought they'd be violent.
- But they're actually gentle. / - Right.
As long as we don't provoke them,
they go about their business.
People shouldn't be locked up in the house.
They should be free and they should go traveling.
- That'll give you peace of mind. / - Yes.
If you're home all day, you become high-strung.
There is...
What is it?
There's something.
- The eyes are shining. / - Is it deer?
- It's a fox. / - What's that?
The eyes were shining bright.
- It's a deer, a male deer. / - It's a stag.
- It's so pretty. / - Amazing.
- Awesome. / - It has antlers.
I've never seen one with antlers.
- It's huge. / - It's so pretty.
- What's that? / - What is that?
- That's fun. / - Isn't it?
- It's fun to look for things. / - Yes.
(A doe is right beside it)
You never get to see animals at night. This is cool.
(The crested porcupines appear again)
What's that? Is that a fox?
- A civet. / - Is civet a wild animal?
- They say seeing a civet is... / - Yes.
As rare as seeing an elephant.
This is awesome.
Amazing.
We saw a civet too.
An hour is too short.
You saw a lot of things in an hour.
But it went by too quickly.
The view is unbelievable.
It's pretty.
Everything is so green.
(This time, they go outside the park)
- It's the oldest and largest... / - Winery?
It's so nice in here.
Ta-da!
Wow, this really feels like Italy.
This is it.
So cute.
You know alpacas.
It's an alpaca.
- I'm hungry. / - That looks good.
I have to take photos.
- That looks good. / - Wow.
- That looks good. / - Goodness.
That was so good.
- What's that? / - You eat so well.
It's so good.
Is it good?
- The pork looks good. / - It's really delicious.
I'd want to come back for this.
(An Park Tour)
Now it's the Park side of the tour.
(Primo Piazza)
This place is so pretty. What is this place?
Aren't you reminded of someplace?
Europe?
Tuscany. Italy!
Look at this. This is a place for me.
A place for you?
- For you. / - Petit Italy in Thailand.
Primo Piazza.
This is it.
Wow, this is so...
This is just like Italy.
- It's pretty. / - This is...
Small towns in Italy have red roofs like this.
Florence is like this too.
Seriously.
Enjoying the scorching sun of Europe,
walking leisurely in the streets...
And drinking tea.
I want to go to a place like Europe, a peaceful place.
(Mina, I want to go to Europe)
Eunhye's husband, please let your wife travel.
The first half of the trip is about adventure.
- Yes, adventure. / - It makes you adventurous.
The last half of the trip is...
- About romance. / - Let's do this.
Romance?
With you?
- No, I mean just the vibe. / - I see.
This is Primo Piazza. Made to look just like Europe.
I love the orange roofs.
It makes me feel at ease.
What do you think? Does it look similar to Italy?
I haven't been to Tuscany, so it's hard to tell
but it's very beautiful and peaceful.
- It feels like we're in a painting. / - It does.
The buildings are orange, so when the sun shines...
You can take great pictures there.
- Asians look nicer in orange color. / - How adorable.
Yesterday, in the national park...
It's hard to believe that it's Thailand.
It is, isn't it?
You can do many things there.
There's a donkey over there. It's so cute.
- Where? / - There's a donkey over there.
- It's like the one from "Shrek." / - I see it.
It's so cute.
- Donkeys are so small. / - It's a donkey.
It's so small.
(What other animals are there?)
(Goats and donkeys)
Alpacas.
- It's so cute. / - Such beautiful eyeliner.
It's very good-looking.
I was so happy because it was so cute.
Alright. I'll feed you soon. Wait there.
(The entrance and the feeding fee, $8.70)
Look at its teeth. They look so funny.
- It's out here. / - It has funny teeth.
Its teeth look like Yu Jaeseok's.
Don't you think so?
It's sticking out.
- It doesn't have upper teeth. / - Really?
- It only has lower teeth. / - Can it chew food?
That's very interesting.
- They want the food. / - They look so nice.
- They are nice. / - They were so cute.
I want to have one.
They're having a hearty meal.
(Mina and Eunhye feed the goats)
This is fascinating. It feels like this is my first time
seeing animals here.
Eunhye, didn't it remind you of your children?
It totally did.
All of a sudden?
There is a photo spot here. Let's take great pictures.
- Pardon? / - Let's take great pictures.
I think we can take a lot of good pictures here.
It's hard to tell who the flower is.
Shall we take a picture?
(It's impossible to take bad pictures here)
- You look so cute. / - It's pretty.
(An Park Tour over flowers)
- You took great pictures. / - Yes.
- It's pretty and nice here. / - The sky looks so nice.
But shouldn't we go eat?
We should. We're going to
a restaurant where you can please all five senses.
If you look, we're not sweating.
It was warm and the sky was clear...
- But we didn't sweat. / - Is it cool there?
(Museum restaurant)
It's convenient to have a rental car.
It is.
(35 minutes from Primo Piazza to museum restaurant)
Aren't you scared?
- Pardon? / - Aren't you scared of these things?
- Are you scared? / - No, I'm fine.
It feels like a whole different country here.
Is this a shopping mall?
Have a look around.
They're selling antique items.
(You'll be fascinated already at the entrance)
(There are various characters and miniatures there)
What is that?
(It's a museum restaurant)
Is it an arcade?
It's a museum and a restaurant at the same time.
That's right.
I'm good at this.
Are you good at this?
I'm good at it on the computer.
- On the computer? / - I have this on my computer.
It's almost antique.
It is. It must be really old.
I wonder where they found it.
These are yo-yos.
- They are yo-yos. / - There are different kinds.
Are those matches?
Children would love this place.
The inside is way bigger than we thought.
They are cars.
Look at this. There is a ski lift as well.
Do they sell those?
No, it's the collection of the owner.
It's an exhibition.
They're so pretty.
No matter how old you are,
there are many things to see for everyone.
Maybe the food was bad?
You'll see. It was delicious.
- It feels like an antique shop. / - It does.
It's like an antique shop.
It feels very exotic to eat in a place like this.
That's why I picked this place.
I like this place.
Khao Yai seems very international.
There are various things here. It's full of colors.
Whenever you take me to a place,
I feel like I'm in a different city.
- You're right. / - Right?
- I'm so hungry. / - I know.
Please get me some food.
Here, we're going to eat what you've been craving...
We'll eat crabs.
- We can eat crabs here? / - Yes.
Please hurry up.
- Hello. / - Hello.
We'd like to order a black pepper crab...
I was too hungry.
She's become sensitive.
- That's famous there. / - What is this?
It's pork skewers.
- Here we are. / - I see.
By the way, where is the black pepper crab?
It's not served yet. Gosh.
We don't have black pepper crab.
What I want to eat is a big crab.
- Let's eat first and then talk. / - I should try it first?
I'm really curious about this.
- How could this... / - That is the dish?
I see crabs.
Isn't it too small?
- It was so delicious. / - My goodness.
(Eunhye starts to look for the crab)
It's a soft-shell crab.
- You can eat the shell too. / - You can eat it whole.
It is a crab.
(The crab's legs are tiny)
It kind of looks like a Chinese dish.
(She can put the whole crab in her mouth)
(It is a crab indeed)
What do you think?
(How does black pepper crab taste?)
Do you like it?
- Do you like it? / - Yes.
This is the soft-shell crab I was looking for.
- Is it? / - Yes.
I'm so relieved now.
This is so delicious.
Soft-shell crabs have very soft shells.
So you can eat the whole crab with the shells.
- It looks delicious. / - It was very delicious.
It'd go well with plain rice.
I tried it with curry before
but with black pepper sauce,
it's salty and spicy.
There's a Chinese dish called stir-fried bok choy.
- I know. / - It tastes similar to that.
This one smells more like seafood.
Is it cooked with oyster sauce?
What is this?
This looks like...
One of the herbal pills that help with digestion.
It's exactly as small as this.
You normally take 30 pieces.
Let me try it.
(Curious)
(What is this?)
Thai...
(Her mouth burns)
As time goes by, it becomes spicier.
It does.
We ate it raw.
These are real peppercorns.
I've never seen peppercorns before.
Should we try it?
(They spat it out right away because it was too spicy)
(They all shared the same experience)
You ate the whole thing?
- No, I had only one piece of it. / - That's a relief.
It's spicier after you eat it.
My tongue starts to burn.
When the peppercorn pops in your mouth and
touches your tongue,
it slowly starts to burn the inside...
- Let's try the green curry. / - Okay.
- It was very delicious. / - This looks delicious.
(What does green curry taste like?)
That should be delicious. Curry with rice.
I put the rice into the curry as we eat rice
and soup in Korea.
- There's red chili pepper. / - It was a hangover relief.
(Thailand is famous for its spicy red chili peppers)
- So it's a bit spicy. / - It's a little spicy.
- It's a little spicy. / - Because of the chili pepper.
It's very spicy.
(If it's spicy, it should be good)
Curry tastes different in every country.
Thai curry has a flavor of
leaves, lime and coconut.
It has such flavors.
- It's different from Korean curry. / - It looks delicious.
- It was delicious. / - If you like these flavors...
You will love this dish.
You should eat the curry with rice
as if you eat instant noodles soup with rice.
- It looks delicious. / - It was very delicious.
(There was much to see and the food was great)
It's very delicious.
(It's delicious)
Sikyung, you can eat that the whole night, right?
I can eat three skewers at once.
What did you like the most?
I can't think of anything but the black peppercorns.
The black peppercorns were shocking.
Peppercorns are more famous in Phu Quoc.
That's right.
Green curry was very delicious
but I would miss black pepper crab more.
I think it'll be hard to forget its taste.
It's probably because of the black peppercorns.
I can still taste it in my throat.
Actually so far, I really like the plan you made.
Will there be more to do here?
- There's something that you like. / - What I like?
It's the biggest winery in Khao Yai.
- Wine? / - Yes.
A winery in Thailand does sound unfamiliar.
- It doesn't fit, does it? / - It doesn't.
(35 minutes by car from restaurant to winery)
(The very first winery in Thailand, founded in 1989)
It was founded in 1989. It's quite old.
Yes.
It started to win international competitions from 2006.
We're going on a winery tour on this car.
- The winery tour only cost $10.70? / - Yes.
You can try wine there as well.
The weather is great today.
- The sky is beautiful. / - It is beautiful.
It's quite cool here.
JR, do you drink alcohol?
Me? I do like drinking.
I like drinking.
I don't drink soju. I like wine.
I like beer.
- You should go there. / - I know.
It's a very hot country.
I didn't know grapes here would taste good.
I didn't think there would be wine here.
Khao Yai is in the north,
so it has a good climate for grape farming.
- That's right. / - What would it taste like?
I wonder.
Is this a vineyard?
You can grow grapes three times a year...
With the climate here but they grow them once a year.
It's because the grapes taste the best between
January and March.
You can grow grapes three times a year?
It's in the north.
They can do it because it's cool there.
(It's the greenhouse where you can see the grapes)
This is beautiful.
The grapes in the greenhouse were not ripe yet.
They were supposed to be sweeter.
But it was still so good.
- It was so delicious. / - Even when it wasn't ripe?
- It was not ripe enough. / - How is this possible?
- It must be delicious. / - It's really...
(Her eyes are wide open)
It's so delicious.
This isn't the taste of grape we know.
Your eyes have become as big as grapes.
(Mina also picks one and tries it)
It was very crunchy.
It's really delicious.
- It tastes like green grapes. / - It does.
It's firm and crunchy.
It's sweet and sour. It's so delicious.
- Do you remember picking cherries as kids? / - Yes.
That's what it felt like.
(Now it's time to taste wine)
It's so...
(Amazed and impressed)
This is...
I already feel tipsy here.
The smell of oak and wine combined...
Smells like whiskey.
It's so pretty.
(Impressed)
(They use air conditioning to keep the cellar cool)
If the temperature is too high, the oak casks explode.
I guess it will inflate inside.
This means they make strong wine.
That's why they have to
keep it cool here.
They have different techniques.
They brew wine in a different way
which makes me wonder how it would taste.
(Today, they will taste 3 kinds of wine)
(Including the winner of 2017 AWC Vienna)
What did the wine taste like?
It was very smooth.
It didn't taste like alcohol at all. It's not sweet either.
Can you have unlimited wine if you pay for the tour?
The tour fee includes wine tasting.
This wine is white wine.
It's made of Chenin blanc grapes.
(What does Thai wine taste like?)
It's tasty.
I actually don't like white wine.
But this one is very delicious.
It's not sour.
It tastes like quality white wine.
This red wine is made of Shiraz grapes.
It's so delicious.
I think this is...
This makes me cast away the prejudice.
I always thought
clear wine doesn't taste good.
(The wine looks light but it has a rich taste)
- It's delicious. / - It smells so good.
This is the last one.
This one is the gold medalist from AWC Vienna.
This is the medalist.
(Mina and Eunhye carefully taste the wine)
(They focus on the wine)
This is a prize winner but...
This is probably how it should taste to win a prize.
- It has a bitter aftertaste. / - Yes, it's bitter.
It clearly has a bitter taste, yet it's not too heavy.
Mina, aren't you drinking too much?
You said you're a problem drinker.
- She just becomes cute. / - She just becomes cute.
That should be alright.
(An Park Tour)
(Restaurant recommended by locals)
(35 minutes by car from the winery to the restaurant)
This looks like a local restaurant.
There are only Thai customers.
- You're right. / - It's where locals eat.
It's a popular restaurant in Thailand.
It's a popular restaurant.
Since we're here,
we should go to a good restaurant.
I asked the locals in the hotel
the restaurants they go to.
And I got some recommendations.
- You asked the hotel staff? / - Yes.
- That's a very nice tip. / - I said I don't want to go...
Anywhere fancy. I asked where he would go eat.
(The kind staff's recommendation)
First, you should try yum woon sen.
I love yum woon sen.
(1. Yum woon sen, 2. Grilled fish)
- Okay, thank you. / - Thank you very much.
I saw something on the way in.
There's something everyone is eating.
- It's pork with bones. / - Pork.
Let's order that and the recommended dish.
When you go to a restaurant,
you should look around first.
You should ask what people are having and order it.
(This will fill Mina and Eunhye's empty stomachs)
The fish was delicious as well.
It does look delicious.
- What is this? / - This is yum woon sen.
(A table full of local Thai food)
Let's try them.
I'm really excited about the fish dish.
(They will try the grilled fish first)
It looks delicious.
- It looks beautiful. / - This was very delicious.
- It's fried. / - Look at the price.
It's $8.70.
(Eunhye tastes it first)
How is it?
Is it good?
The sauce looks good.
(What does it taste like?)
(It's so tasty that it makes you dance and smile)
What are you doing?
It tastes like chicken.
Chicken.
It's like marinated chicken.
The meat is so tender.
Like you said, it's like chicken.
I thought it'd be fishy but it's really delicious.
It's crispy on the outside.
It tastes like filefish jerky.
It's spicy, sweet and salty.
- It's crispy and soft. / - It is.
It smells like a very delicious braised fish dish.
You're right. The sauce tastes just like braised fish.
(It's incredibly delicious)
Look at this.
- This is really... / - Look at this.
You should scrape the fruit inside and eat it.
You're right. There's white fruit inside.
That is so delicious.
(She's busy taking pictures)
This is really tasty.
I usually don't like coconuts.
(Let me try it as well)
- It's so refreshing. / - It's good, isn't it?
It could be a little too milky and sticky,
but this one is refreshing and clear.
It's like a natural sports drink.
I've never had coconut juice like this before.
(Screaming)
(The pork dish many people were eating is served)
I need to take a picture of this.
- This can't be pork. / - She's excited.
I'm suddenly hungry.
- There is a bone as well. / - It's pork rib.
Let's try it.
That!
- It was delicious. / - That's the stuff.
It's deep-fried pork belly.
Everything is delicious once it's deep-fried.
What was interesting was that it was very tender...
- On the inside. / - It has a bone on it.
It was really tender on the inside.
- It looks delicious. / - It's crispy on the outside.
- We can just gnaw it like that? / - It's so delicious.
Okay, let's just gnaw it.
It looks delicious.
- It looks so soft. / - It was really soft.
It's crispy on the outside and soft on the inside?
Yes, it was so moist and soft.
- It must be very delicious. / - We even forgot...
To put the sauce on it because it was so good.
It was like smoked pork belly.
I have never grabbed pork and eaten it like this.
Let's try yum woon sen as well.
Let's try it.
We forgot to order this yesterday.
Let's try it today.
How is it? Let me try it as well.
Okay.
(She tastes it)
The smell of cilantro is not bad.
It smells rather refreshing.
I think I get now why people say cilantro is refreshing.
People who like cilantro say it tastes refreshing.
I think I know what that means.
It cleanses your palate.
Their food is very sweet, salty and sour.
It has strong flavors so cilantro
adds a refreshing taste.
If you add cilantro to a bland dish,
it smells very strong.
But it goes well with Thai food.
(Trying new food is a joy of traveling)
(They enjoy their meal)
At that point, I couldn't taste cilantro in the food.
- It was so good. / - It was so delicious.
Where are we going next?
I'm looking forward to it.
It has been only getting better.
We're going to a night market where you can
feel traditional Thailand.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
(A night market in Pak Chong, Khao Yai)
Pak Chong.
The night market looks fun.
Isn't that 10 cents?
- Yes, it's 10 cents. / - So much good food.
They have various different kinds of market food.
They have so many kinds of food.
- They have fruits. / - The food seems familiar.
Right. It's Southeast Asian food.
- There's even dried squid. / - I can't choose.
It's hard to pick what to eat.
- We felt the same. / - Right?
That's why you have to try everything.
- I don't know which is which. / - So much.
There are waffles as well.
(Let's start the night market of An Park Tour)
What is this? It's juice.
That looks good.
What is that?
What is this?
(She's asking them in Korean)
"What is this?"
- She's speaking Korean. / - That's amazing.
(Will they be able to understand Korean in Thailand?)
- Did you just ask a local? / - "What is this?"
"Is this good?"
We're at the night market in Thailand.
We found a really nice place.
- Yes. / - They have really nice desserts.
It's delicious.
- The juices are $1. / - Is it $1 per drink?
- Yes. / - It's really cheap.
It's really sweet.
The strawberries are kind of sweet.
I like this one.
Let me eat this in our hotel.
Okay, buy this.
Thank you. You're amazing.
She says to buy everything if it looks good.
(Mangosteen, also known as the queen of fruit)
- Mangosteen. / - I really like it.
It's pronounced "lychee" over there.
(1kg of mangosteen, about $1.70)
The good ones might be hidden.
What is this?
Is this potato grape?
It's langsat.
- That's really delicious. / - What is that?
- I was really surprised. / - That's really delicious.
- I was really surprised. / - It's dessert, right?
- It's similar to lychees. / - Yes, that's right.
(The insides are similar to lychees)
It's delicious.
I eat 30 of those at once when I go overseas.
- It's so delicious. / - Really?
It was so delicious.
We bought 2 bags of fruit with only $3.
(I'm so happy)
Are these...
The bananas that they roast in Africa?
I really want to try it but I'm so full. What should I do?
- I'm really full. / - Yes.
(You can't resist the temptation of the night market)
It tastes like waffles with maple syrup.
(Roasted banana, about 20 cents each)
(The night market is big with lots to eat)
(Endless eating show)
(It looks appetizing)
That looks delicious.
The pork ribs were really good.
This is paradise.
- There is so much to eat. / - Isn't that right?
They all look delicious.
What is this?
I can't eat durian.
You can't just walk past all that good food.
- They're durians. / - Durians aren't easy to eat.
You have to try the king of fruits.
I've never tried it before.
(Durians have appeared in the Singapore tour before)
The first taste is okay.
(You either like or hate it because of the smell)
It's also my first time but they say it's delicious.
How delicious is it?
- I've never had durian before. / - Me neither.
- I'm worried about the smell. / - Me too.
How do you eat it?
(The owner peels it for them to eat)
(They naturally take the durian to their nose)
It smells.
I can't eat durian because of the smell.
What does it smell like?
- I can't explain it in words. / - Really?
You can't take durian with you
to your hotels in a lot of Southeast Asian countries.
- You must keep that in mind. / - Is it that bad?
Will Mina try it?
(Mina takes the durian straight to her mouth)
- Is it okay? / - It was delicious for me.
(She has an experimental mind that doesn't hesitate)
Do you know the most tender part of melons?
It's like eating that part.
Really?
(She tries it again after plucking up her courage)
(How is it?)
(This taste is?)
Is it good?
- You should cover your nose. / - She's surprised.
I was really surprised.
(She takes another bite to check again)
- It's like ice cream. / - I'm surprised.
It's like really soft cream.
- What is this? / - It tastes like whipped cream.
The end taste is fresh.
I know why people eat these now.
- It's not unpleasant. It's fresh. / - That's right.
(They got to know a new taste on their Thailand trip)
This is really delicious.
I'm so surprised.
- I had a culture shock. / - She also bought durians.
- I regretted not eating durians. / - Did you buy them?
(The last moment of the trip is sadly here)
(They have a cocktail party to cheer themselves)
(Salmon salad, about $12)
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
This is delicious.
It's sad to think that this is the last night of our trip.
You always wish that you had one more day.
- That's right. / - Yes.
Where do you want to go if you had one more day?
I want to go to the waterfall.
It looks like the Amazon, right?
- I was scared. I was shaking. / - Yes, of course.
The moment we went down,
the waterfall before our eyes was...
So amazing.
They went to a lot of places.
The waterfall was nice.
It was so amazing.
When people say that there is a jungle
and a winery...
It felt like experiencing opposite extremes.
There are so many things to enjoy,
see and eat.
There are so many things.
We came to Thailand for this trip but it feels...
- We've been to five countries. / - You're right.
Thailand and the Philippines,
France, Italy and a mysterious jungle.
- That's right. / - It felt like that.
There were so many things I tried for the first time.
I think I could enjoy all the places again.
(A heart-warming trip with lots of first experiences)
An Park Tour!
(An Park Tour in Khao Yai, Thailand, the end)
Thailand also has...
- Various charms. / - Of course.
JR, what impressed you the most in Khao Yai?
The food was the most impressive for me.
It was really interesting to see elephants
just wandering around.
With a friend...
Just taking a walk that path quietly
and sit in that elephant observatory
without saying a word was very relaxing.
All the bird noises over there...
It really cleared my head.
It's a nice place to relax.
- Okay, let's see the expenses. / - The expenses.
Last week, Song Vacation slept in a pool villa.
So they spent $488.
Will the total expense influence the final decision?
Let's see how much they used.
For 2 nights and 3 days,
the total expense of the An Park Tour...
The total expense is?
- For one person is... / - For one person.
$209.
Wow. It's really cheap.
- Isn't it really cheap? / - It's really cheap.
- It was half the price of Vietnam. / - Yes.
$209.
You slept in a too luxurious place.
But we went to the safari for free
because we slept there.
Was the safari free because you slept there?
It costs $50 per person to go to that safari either wise.
But two people can travel to Khao Yai...
For the price of one person going to Phu Quoc.
- That's nice. / - Even 10 people...
Could sleep in that room.
Okay.
Let's vote.
Would you like to go to Khao Yai, Thailand according
to the design of the An Park Tour?
Please vote.
(An Park Tour planned a trip to Khao Yai, Thailand)
(What will the judges choose?)
They say it's a neck-and-neck match.
Will it be Song Vacation to Phu Quoc, Vietnam?
Or will it be An Park Tour to Khao Yai, Thailand?
- I'm so nervous. / - What will it be?
What will the judges choose?
Since it's neck-and-neck,
the front digit will be the same.
- The front digit might be the same. / - It changes a lot.
I think it will be an 8.
- 8 for both front digits? / - Yes.
- I don't know. / - It was worth a 9.
- I'd say 92 or 93? / - No, no.
- It's an 8. / - An Park Tour.
Song Vacation.
- 1 and 7. / - What's going on?
How did this happen?
- 87? / - We've won.
- What is it? / - We must have won.
- What is the first digit? / - What should I do?
- No? / - Oh my...
(Phu Quoc won with 81 votes)
It was a 4-vote difference.
(Khao Yai with 77 votes vs. Phu Quoc with 81 votes)
- It was pretty close. / - Let's hear their thoughts.
It feels great. Actually,
we introduced Phu Quoc
because we wanted a lot of people to experience it.
We really enjoyed it.
You won't regret
if you go exactly according to our trip.
- You'll go there again, right? / - Yes.
- You're going next week, right? / - Next week.
Okay, JR.
How were the last 2 weeks with us? Did you enjoy it?
I got to learn a lot of good information.
That was nice.
I realized that the most important thing during a trip
is that you have to be satisfied.
I thought it would be nice if people can go
where they can be satisfied.
A preview for next week is that it's our 100th episode.
- That's amazing. / - Please look forward to it.
- Is it the 100th episode already? / - It'll be a special.
Please look forward to our 100th episode special.
We will say good-bye to you here.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle trip!
(Next episode)
I'm going to save everything in my eyes.
I might end up living in Canada.
It's Niagara Falls!
This was all formed naturally!
- I want to live here. / - It's nice, right?
I want to live here, Seulgi.
I think I've seen it in a movie.
This is what Europe is all about.
Wow!
Hey!
Let's go real deep.
Let's ask for a room.
(Battle Trip)
("Semina" by Gugudan SEMINA)