(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Hwijae, special host, Kim Taehoon)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Today's special host is very reliable.
He's a walking encyclopedia.
It's Kim Taehoon.
- Hello. / - Welcome.
He's standing here
and it doesn't feel strange at all.
- It's really reassuring. / - Right.
It's like he's always been here.
I live my life like it's a journey.
- Here we go. / - Being here today...
- I feel very secure. / - Right.
- And I feel whole. / - Right.
You can ask any question you want.
- He can answer anything. / - That's right.
It means he lies a lot.
But he knows a lot of things.
It's fun to know a lot.
It's been 5 minutes since I've been here. What is this?
Can you tell us about Yeouido?
- First of all... / - About Yeouido.
Yeouido has interesting Chinese characters.
It uses the characters for "your" and "island."
So it means "your island."
- It's romantic... / - It's like a lecture.
Yeouido has a special significance in Korean society.
It's a cultural space with broadcasting stations.
It's also a major economic center with
many securities companies.
It's like the Wall Street of Korea.
It's also a place where you can enjoy cultural festivals
like cherry blossom festivals when
the warm weather comes on.
Where should we go after work?
There's a good whelk restaurant in the back alley.
- It stays open late. / - That's true.
- It's really there. / - It is.
Shin Dongyeob is sometimes there.
I feel reassured that he's on my team today.
So where are we going today?
Let's meet our client first.
- Let's meet today's client. / - Okay.
Let's meet him.
Hello, I'm Kim Junseok.
I'm 36 years old and I live in Seoul.
I'm planning a trip to the U.K.
There are many beautiful cities
in the U.K. besides London.
Instead of the obvious stops,
I'd like a really unique city trip.
Please design one for me, Battle Trip.
This is difficult.
- The U.K. / - Wait a minute.
With the U.K...
- Kim Kibang and Lee Kyuhan... / - They went there.
That's right, they've been there.
But London isn't the only city in the U.K.
Where would you go in the U.K.?
I'd like to go to Hogwarts.
- What? / - The school of magic...
- What? / - I'd visit Oxford.
Oxford.
Oxford for me.
I'd go to Tottenham.
- Tottenham? / - Tottenham.
Because Son Heungmin is there.
Ireland for me.
I really want to go there.
- Ireland. / - Why?
It's the home of pop music.
- Right. / - Say something as the pop columnist.
Since the 1960s, following The Beatles...
It's been the Mecca of pop music.
It's the home of musicians
who have inspired countless artists worldwide.
We can't talk about music without mentioning the U.K.
The weather
isn't so good there though, right?
In fact, the gloomy weather
inspired many musicians...
- Of the U.K. / - That's right.
People say that.
That's why many artists
love the U.K.
In that sense, I think it is a charming nation.
For today's episode,
we have four very special guests.
Our trip designers, please come on out.
Welcome.
(Lee Gikwang, Yoon Dujun of Highlight)
(Lee Jonghyuk, Lim Hyungjun)
- Welcome. / - It really is a special.
We have very special
trip designers today.
They are experts on this show.
Lim Hyungjun and Yoon Dujun.
They have both won the battle twice.
They have two wins.
- That means... / - So...
- This year... / - No losses, right?
I was on the very first episode. Founding contributor.
You are a founding contributor.
- I was here with Seol Minseok. / - Founding.
- That's right. / - They won by a landslide then.
- We won by a big margin. / - It was incredible.
And?
From what I have heard, this program...
That Thailand trip with Kim Minkyo...
That caused a boom?
- Yes. That's what I heard. / - It caused a boom.
It kept this show going, so to speak.
Revived a dying show.
That's true to some extent.
- Right? I heard it had great ratings. / - That's right.
- It had great ratings. / - It did provide a boost.
We acknowledge that.
What I'm curious about is...
You must've visited two cities
excluding London.
Could you introduce your cities first?
Yes, we visited...
The U.K.'s heart of soccer.
We visited Manchester.
Hwijae must be so happy.
Manchester!
- The city he wants to really visit. / - Manchester!
- Wow. / - The connection between soccer and...
Manchester is extremely difficult to beat.
It's very difficult to beat.
Which city did you two visit?
- Us? / - Yes.
- We went to a nice city too. / - Where did you go?
- Where? / - A nice city?
- He says a nice city. / - A nice city.
We have to win.
If Manchester
is the heart of soccer,
ours is the liver.
The liver?
The liver is extremely important.
- It is. / - All the guys know, right?
- How important the liver is? / - Of course.
- The heart is more important. / - Liver.
Where is the liver of soccer?
It's the heart of the music scene, Liverpool.
It's the city of The Beatles.
Actually,
these two teams are rivals.
- Liverpool vs. Manchester... / - That's right.
When these two teams go at it, it's the red derby.
- Both teams wear red uniforms. / - Both wear red.
Liverpool vs. Manchester is like Korea vs. Japan.
- Is that so? / - It's a must-win match.
Music vs. soccer.
Hwijae, music or soccer?
- Huh? / - Music or soccer?
- Of course it's music. / - Why must I choose?
Why am I music?
- You were a singer. / - You released an album.
You sang "Say Goodbye."
- "Blessing You." / - You're a former singer.
- You were a singer. / - "Say Goodbye."
How could you compare my album to Liverpool?
- No way. / - But you love music.
It's The Beatles... No way.
I apologize.
I think our trip will be about The Beatles.
Did you see any matches in Manchester?
- Us? / - That's the important part.
- I bet you watched it at a pub. / - We did.
We watched Manchester United vs. Manchester City.
- A derby match. / - A derby match.
A big match.
- The Manchester derby? / - Yes.
Since they watched the match...
I feel slightly worried.
No, no. It's the contrary.
I'm already bored.
- But you like soccer. / - We understand.
You like tennis!
It's only fun for them.
They just watched soccer for themselves.
People only think of Manchester United
when it comes to Manchester.
- That's true. / - With Liverpool...
They only think of soccer.
Don't we want to
go there and see what the city is really like?
Let's look at the map
and see where each city is located.
- Okay. / - Where are they?
It's far.
Goodness, it's so far.
London is beneath there.
- What a shame. / - So that's where they are.
- They're close. / - Right next to each other.
It must've taken about the same time to get there.
Around 2.5 hours by train.
Same for us. 2.5 hours.
- The same. / - It's the same.
2.5 hours by train.
You might as well visit Liverpool and then
drop by Manchester while you're there.
Since they're close by.
- You could do that. / - That's good too.
- Right? / - Anyway for today...
We have our 100 judges who will vote on today's trips.
- Nice to meet you. / - Welcome.
Each trip will have a first half and second half.
They'll be shown in two halves.
- You have to vote 4 times. / - Right.
It's not a total vote.
Only the final vote will determine the winner.
Okay then.
Should we start with our team?
Go to Manchester first?
- Yes. / - Your team name?
To tell you about our team name...
To tell you what it is...
- We took the High from Highlight. / - High.
And the Man from Manchester.
2, 3.
HighMan Tour!
Oh, what a fail.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Hello. / - I'm Yoon Dujun of Highlight.
I'm Lee Gikwang.
- That's right. / - Nice to meet you.
(The idol you want as your boyfriend, Yoon Dujun)
(Thief of girls' hearts with dancing shoes, Lee Gikwang)
Thief of girls' hearts.
(Idols who are known as hardcore soccer fans)
From what I hear...
- This is your third time already. / - That's right.
This is Lim Hyungjun's third time too.
He has won all of his battles too.
- I won all my battles too. / - Really?
This is a death match.
The losing team can't star on Battle Trip after this.
I can see Dujun is getting competitive.
I think we should visit
the birthplace of soccer.
How about we visit Manchester.
- Park Jisung shoots! / - Park Jisung!
- Goal. / - Goal.
- Park Jisung goals! / - I miss that.
- Park Jisung... / - It'll destroy my mind.
My mind is already destroyed.
They're good at soccer.
Lee Gikwang flies down the field.
Yoon Dujun shoots... Goal!
(Idols that love soccer)
Did you really go there?
(From playing soccer to watching the match)
(A to Z about soccer!)
(You thought it was over, right?)
Amazing.
(Activities that will help you de-stress)
Wow. What is that?
This is amazing.
Unbelievable.
That looks like fun.
It's a soccer tour.
But soccer in some ways...
You can love it or hate it.
- There's a division. / - That's right.
We'll divide the trip into two sections.
One day, we'll fill with activities
that suit a holiday trip.
And the rest will be soccer.
They should've gone all in with soccer.
- Then we would've won. / - Right.
They are smarter than they look.
HighMan!
- HighMan! / - They did a lot.
- You went to a lot of places. / - Tour!
Good job.
(HighMan Action Tour)
(HighMan Football Tour)
(Incheon International Airport)
Welcome on board.
- Thank you. / - Lee Gikwang.
- It's your first time on Battle Trip. / - Yeah.
- That's right. / - You must feel unfamiliar.
Very unfamiliar.
It will be.
Actually...
- You look more afraid than excited. / - Right.
Don't worry about it.
If you just trust and follow me,
this will be a valuable trip.
- Yeah? / - Let's go.
Okay.
- Let's go. / - Yes.
Go!
It's so strange to hold this camera.
It would be.
I'll check your reservation.
- Are you checking in any luggage? / - Yes.
Oh, thank you.
- Enjoy your trip. / - Thank you.
(They are departing for the U.K. now)
They're taking off now.
What's the highlight of taking flights?
It's the in-flight meal.
Here's your in-flight meal.
(Dujun likes Korean food so goes with bibimbap)
(Gikwang is on diet so goes with the salad)
The in-flight meal is always good.
This is called manners.
I have to tuck this in my shirt, right?
You have to do this.
I have to tuck my napkin in my shirt.
Thank you for the food.
Enjoy.
I thought Manchester was a rural area but it's not.
It's the second largest city.
- It's equivalent to Busan in Korea. / - Busan.
I'm really looking forward to this.
Manchester and England...
I'll explain more when we land.
I studied quite a lot about this.
I'll explain it later.
(What kind of journey is awaiting them?)
(Incheon)
(London)
(It takes 12 hours and 30 minutes)
They call it the underground.
They also call it the tube.
- Tube or underground. / - Tube or underground.
Family movie?
Korea TV show.
- TV show. / - TV show.
- TV show in Korea. / - Korea.
Hello.
Hi.
This is thanks to K-POP.
- Thanks to BTS. / - Our BTS friends.
(Wow)
- We've been here. / - Really?
- What's going on? / - Where we came for shopping?
Yeah, I came shopping here.
Regent Street.
Oh, this is Regent Street.
Are you in London now?
Yes, we are in London now.
That must be a shopping street.
I think that's probably a department store.
(Regent Street)
(You can experience the London vibes here)
(A popular place among tourists)
We've come above ground from the underground
and it feels so good.
Look at the double-decker bus.
Wow, double-decker bus.
I would think the bus would tip over.
That's really high.
That's the symbol of London.
That's so beautiful.
The thing is...
Europe has a sense of romanticism in the winter.
Yeah, there's something romantic about the cold.
It's cold but still beautiful.
How did they make this look so good.
- It feels like... / - Regent Street.
It doesn't feel like we're shooting.
I feel like I'm on a real trip.
(It's time to depart for Manchester)
(Euston Station)
Finally.
- We are... / - Yes.
About to leave for Manchester.
To Manchester.
But we just arrived in London.
The name of our tour is HighMan.
- Yes, Highlight. / - It's not HighLon.
- Right. / - We'll head to Manchester.
- Are you going straight there? / - How will we go?
We can take the high-speed train.
The distance between is about 300 to 400km.
It's about the same as Seoul to Busan.
It takes about 2 and 30 minutes by train.
- 330km is actually Seoul to Busan. / - Let's go.
I think they probably used Virgin Trains.
From memory, the tickets aren't that cheap.
Transportation does cost a bit.
- Transportation in Europe. / - It's expensive.
It's nice and cozy.
It's nice and warm.
When else would I ride the KTX in England...
- At the age of 29? / - That's right.
This is nice.
Even though it's dark.
It'd be nice to ride this during the day.
(They can't see anything as it's pitch-dark outside)
(This is the view they would've seen in the afternoon)
(The train ride to Manchester on a snowy day)
(That's beautiful)
Let's travel for 2.5 hours on this train.
I want someone to hit me, so I can pass out.
(Dujun and Gikwang fall fast asleep)
The time difference...
- I was so tired. / - The jetlag got to us.
Europe has the time difference that's most difficult...
- To overcome. / - You're right.
(They still look handsome in their sleep)
(The first night of their journey in England passes)
(Manchester)
(What is their first itinerary in Manchester?)
(HighMan Action Tour)
(Museum of Science and Industry)
We are finally...
- Here in Manchester. / - That's right.
- Today is the action day. / - Action Day.
Action.
What do you think of when you think of action?
When it comes to action...
I think of action films.
- Like "Kingsman." / - Right.
When I think of action,
I think of energy,
that's what comes to mind.
This is Manchester, right?
Our Park Jisung of Manchester United.
The oxygen tank of Manchester.
- The oxygen tank. / - Energy.
- Having two hearts. / - Right. Two hearts.
What are they trying to say?
What's going on?
Right. Two hearts.
- The heart is the engine. / - Engine.
Engines are Museum of Science and Industry!
That is where we've invited you.
Great job!
- I knew it. The intro was long. / - Dujun is amazing!
Manchester is
the city where Industrial Revolution kicked off.
I heard there are a lot of great museums
so I thought...
- Sounds good. / - We could visit there.
- We can... / - Yes, good, good.
We could study...
- Fill our heads with knowledge. / - Of course.
Yoon Dujun must've studied a lot.
Yes, he knew a lot.
I only studied lightly.
(Museum of Science and Industry)
(A museum consisting of 5 exhibitions)
(Built on railway and have experience facilities)
The museum has about 5 exhibitions.
- That's big. / - It's really big.
- It's free? / - There's no entrance fee?
- Yes. / - Why is it free?
It showcases England's national power and...
- Scientific technology. / - That's right.
It's a way to show the foreigners their achievements.
- That's why it's for free. / - There's so much to see.
If you look here...
- Air and Space Hall. / - Air and Space Hall.
It's truly energy...
What is that?
This is huge.
(Ta-da)
(All sorts of planes fill the space up)
I really want to visit that museum.
Wright Brothers.
The Wright Brothers made this.
First...
First flight.
Wow, seriously?
This is it.
The way he's carrying that camera...
Dujun loves looking at exhibits.
- It's a suicide plane. / - Yeah, a suicide plane.
In the cockpit.
Where is the other propeller?
Is it in the back?
- Is it on the tail? / - Just one engine?
Light airplane.
That one... Wright Brothers.
We can press it.
- That looks fun too. / - What is that?
- What is this? / - Isn't that a gaming device?
There's an experience space as well.
What is that? You can experience it.
Yeah.
Fly 360 degrees?
- Oh, this. / - Isn't that it?
This is modern VR.
VR is fun.
We become a true pilot.
- There's wind too. / - Yeah.
We get to fly a plane.
It's a 360 degree flight simulator.
Should we try this then?
Let's go then.
- Seriously. / - I can't wait.
Let's try it out.
- Go. / - Let's go.
Have a good trip.
What is this?
It's VR but they're not wearing a headset.
There's a screen inside.
- A whole screen? / - That's from the outside.
We get scared easily.
What if we get sick?
If you look outside...
- You can control it yourself? / - Yes, yes.
Who's that? Who's that?
Pull the stick.
(He's moving the stick)
(Wobbling)
(The machine moves too)
Turn it.
Hey, what's going on?
Wait a minute.
Dujun's eyes look so funny.
Hey, wait a minute.
What is this?
What's this?
- Here we go. / - Pull up.
What is this?
Wait a minute.
- That safety device... / - This is how they edit it?
- You must wear a safety belt. / - The editing...
It actually spins like that.
It spins.
It's not like the flying games
you play at an arcade.
You're right.
Oh, hey, hey, hey!
Wait a minute.
Hey, hey!
- Blood's rushing to my head. / - Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
- Blood's rushing. / - So suddenly...
(Focused)
- Right? / - That's why it's 360 degrees.
You're right.
Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go.
Oh, my goodness!
Hey, hey, hey! Don't do that.
Wait a second.
- That looks fun. / - It's different from regular games.
What? It's over.
It's over.
That was a fun time.
It's not that much but it really looks fun.
I'm dizzy.
We came back alive.
I feel sick.
Thank you.
Did the machine really rotate?
Combat pilots have a hard job.
- It was fun. / - Let's go.
(Indoor action)
- Action enjoyed indoors? / - Here it comes.
Here, here...
Today is the action day.
That's why...
This is for Dujun.
I have prepared a fun, indoor activity we can try.
- For me? / - Of course.
Let's go in first.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
This is bad.
(Dujun is scared of heights)
(Dujun was going to try paragliding in Laos)
- Oh, really? We can't paraglide today? / - No.
♪ Wind, keep blowing ♪
- Dujun, are you scared of heights? / - Yes.
I had no idea.
- How good is it? / - It was scary.
- We have to get on. / - Gikwang enjoys it, right?
He loves it. He's not afraid of anything.
Hey, check that out.
What is it?
The wind is blowing harder.
Look at that. Look.
What is that?
- No way. I can't believe this. / - Is that a person?
- The one flying is a person? / - Yes, it's a person.
Look at that. Look.
What is that?
- No way. I can't believe this. / - Is that a person?
- The one flying is a person? / - Yes, it's a person.
- Dujun... / - His eyes are about to pop out.
Is he an expert?
- Yes. / - Expert of reactions.
No, no.
The man in the tube.
No, before.
Oh, right...
What are you on about?
I thought...
I thought you meant Dujun...
I thought you were asking about him.
This is amazing.
(Indoor skydiving)
(The pan in the bottom blows wind at 50m/s)
(You can enjoy skydiving indoors)
(Indoor skydiving, $76)
(We can almost hear Dujun's eyes rolling)
(Gulp)
This is beyond scary.
You punk. This is so scary.
What is?
You can't do that even if you want to.
Even those who are afraid of heights...
- They can experience it. / - Let's go.
It's that much fun.
Safety comes first
so let's go and get our safety training.
- The safest thing is to not do it. / - There's training.
You must.
It can't be action day without this.
We need to show this level of activity for action day
to the viewers.
- Hey... / - Let's go.
Let's go.
That really looks fun.
Among all the activities so far...
- Yeah. / - It's one of the best ones.
Oh, really?
We can't do that.
(Changing for the skydiving)
We get uniforms.
Can you choose it yourself?
Yes, you can.
- Really? / - They have the Superman costume.
(They receive a safety training beforehand)
This will be fun.
- What's that? / - He looks too sad.
Why is he so depressed?
His eyes...
You have to go one at a time.
Who is first?
Should I go first?
I'll go first.
- You? / - Yeah.
Dujun, let's go!
Is Dujun going first?
I'm a little bit scared.
It's okay.
Hold still.
Hold still please. He...
- Right away? / - Yes, right away.
Let's go Ilsan Spider-Man.
(He can't back out now)
(We trust you, leader)
(Though this isn't real skydiving)
(It's my first skydiving experience!)
(Trembling)
You look more stunned than the girl earlier.
(His body is floating because of the strong wind)
He's good.
He's doing really well.
That's so fascinating.
- Do you float if they crank up the wind? / - Yes, yes.
Depending on how you move your legs and arms...
- You go up higher? / - That's right.
- By yourself... / - You can turn as well.
Shouldn't you close your mouth?
- Your mouth gets dry. / - Right.
You can't close it once you open your mouth.
Dujun!
Close your mouth!
Why are you keeping your mouth open?
Because I'm too excited.
I was so excited. I wanted to scream.
But the wind kept blowing.
The wind is blowing at 250km/hr.
It's blowing.
When you're actually skydiving,
you're attached to an instructor.
- Right. / - But you're doing it alone here.
That's why it's more fun.
- That means he's doing well, right? / - Going up!
He's going up!
Up, up.
- Telling him to go up? / - Going up since he's good?
He's going up.
- That must be scary. / - That's amazing.
That must've been scary.
He looks so jealous.
That must've been a little scary.
- That's so fun. / - You can't feel it going up.
(He flies up to the top)
He should close his mouth.
(Dizzying)
That would be perfect
for skydiving practice.
Gosh, that looks like fun.
That's really awesome.
- He's bringing him out. / - He's out.
- He's wiping his face. / - My nose is running.
Thank you. Thank you.
You have to wipe your nose and mouth.
This is amazing.
It was so much fun.
(Next up is Gikwang)
Gikwang looks like he can do it really well.
That looks like fun.
Yeah, seriously.
(He's flying without any help)
He's cute.
He looks like a flying squirrel.
(Flying squirrel)
He's going up right away.
- Can you grab the wind like this? / - Yes.
- You can. / - Like a ball.
You need quite a bit of muscle strength.
- Like your shoulders. / - Since it goes like this.
You need that support.
(So excited)
(Dizzying height)
You must be thirsty.
That was fun. That was so much fun.
So good! Feeling so good!
It was so much fun.
It's fun.
- It's a lot of fun. / - You must try this.
This is amazing.
Amazing.
Thank you.
How much did it cost?
- How much was it? / - It was $76 per person.
That's worth it.
- It's not cheap. / - For 2 minutes.
You need to eat something.
We're hungry, aren't we?
Very hungry.
So we should try
a traditional English dish.
Soul food.
- Soul food. / - In England...
The food that the English like best...
What is it?
It is...
(A pie shop where you can taste local meat pies)
(They combine traditional pies with a modern touch)
(You can enjoy unique pies with various stuffing)
Pie.
- Meat pie. / - Meat pie.
It's not the pie we know.
What is that?
- I was surprised too. / - It's not a dessert pie.
The pies I know...
- Are like tarts with fruits on top. / - Right.
That's what I thought.
But this restaurant puts meat and this and that,
like ham...
- It's like a meal. / - Yes, a meal.
A pie that's like a meal.
- Hi, guys. / - Hi, guy.
Oh, hi, guys.
Free ranger?
Oh, free ranger?
- Ranger. / - Check this out.
What's this?
(Moodog pie, $11.50)
(Free ranger pie, $11.50)
(Mashed peas, mashed potatoes)
(They look similar on the outside)
English people don't have many soups.
So when it's cold,
they enjoy a warm pie.
Looks tasty.
Let's open it up.
I'm so curious about what's inside.
(Dujun cuts the moodog pie first)
Wow, check this out.
What is it?
It's meat and stuff.
It's a full meal.
(The way he eats makes everyone hungry)
The moodog
has beef inside.
It has beef boiled down in soy sauce. It's not salty.
The pastry is very crispy.
The pastry dough was kneaded with red ale.
That's right. That's what it said on the menu.
You get the whiff of ale as you eat it.
It has that scent.
Chicken gravy...
I'd better pour some.
It's pretty.
The women would like this.
It'd make a great picture to
put up on your SNS.
(Great visuals)
That looks so good.
I haven't eaten yet.
I should've had food first.
- The potato is good. / - I'll open it up.
What does it look like?
It's chicken.
- It looks good. / - It does.
I find this pie fascinating.
(How does the chicken pie taste?)
It has the crunchiness of the crust
and the chicken inside is so tender.
That looks good.
Great with a glass of wine.
It's so good.
It is.
Does it taste like a sandwich?
What does it taste like?
It tastes more like a dumpling
rather than a sandwich.
Dumpling!
That makes sense.
Let's bring in...
The secret weapon.
- Isn't that the all purpose sauce? / - Yes.
They have sauces too.
Oh, sauces.
Fruity brown sauce...
I think they made their own special sauce.
- Spicy. / - I've never seen anything like this.
Once you add this...
It's so good.
Okay.
That must be spicy.
It's not that spicy.
Really?
Spicy for English people
isn't that spicy for Koreans.
(This is good)
For the Korean tourists.
If you want a spicy taste...
Since there are different sauces...
- You'd get a different flavor. / - It's good.
It's really good.
Hey!
Huh?
This is it
- That's the stuff? / - Close the lid.
Why? Why? Is this better?
This is way better.
(Gikwang tries the sauce Dujun recommends)
I want to know what that tastes like.
It's like an all purpose soy sauce.
(In awe)
This makes it refreshing.
It does, right?
The pie can taste a bit heavy...
But because the sauce is fruity...
- Open the lid on this one. / - It's good.
- It looks really good. / - It does look good.
That was really delicious.
It'd be really heavy.
Isn't the pie too heavy for Asians?
- Isn't it too greasy? / - That sauce...
Takes care of the heaviness.
I ate it all.
I ate it all while we were talking.
(HighMan Action Tour)
(Lake District)
(It's day 3's best destination)
- I want to do that thing... / - What?
I like going for walks.
I like walking around.
Walking around slowly
and enjoying the area...
Should I look it up?
A way to enjoy the nature.
Isn't there anything like that?
It's a little further away
from Manchester.
Lake District...
In England,
people call it the heart and soul of walking.
- The heart of walking? / - Heart of walking?
England must like hearts.
- Never heard of that before. / - It's passionate.
Park Jisung is known for having two hearts.
Manchester is the heart of the Industrial Revolution.
(They head somewhere by car for 2 hours)
It takes two hours by car.
(The first time they've seen such a sight)
- It's a refreshing morning. / - It's refreshing.
- It's so... / - The air is so fresh.
Isn't the air already different?
Yes, it's different.
This is Windermere.
- This is Windermere. / - It's called Windermere.
It's the no. 1 place people want to live
after they retire in England.
It must be pretty.
It means it's boring.
A place you don't want to live before retirement.
- A place of healing. / - It's beautiful.
- Chosen by English people. / - It's like a theme park.
That's right, it seemed like a village from a fairy tale.
It looks more like Switzerland than England.
- That's right. / - It's more like that.
(The highlight of Windermere)
Your legs must have hurt.
It looks like Bukhansan.
- We only had to walk for 20 minutes. / - No!
- Your legs must have hurt. / - It was really low.
(Everyone can easily go on this course)
(A panoramic view if you only walk for 20 minutes)
(Lake District)
Let's go for a walk then.
Isn't this a nice walk?
- Are those houses? / - Yes.
That's the true landscape of England.
Outside of the major city.
It feels like you can smell the leaves.
Doesn't it feel like you're chewing xylitol gum?
- Right? / - It's refreshing.
The air is so clean.
It feels cool.
This tree is amazing.
I wonder how old it is.
- It looks at least 100 years old. / - At least 100 years.
This is really amazing.
It doesn't have the full effect on screen.
You have to see it for yourself...
- To get a sense of the beauty. / - Really?
(They meet a bird on the way)
Robin?
Look at him.
It isn't hiding from the camera.
He's knows something.
- It sat there. / - It's so cute.
- It's so cute. / - It's so round.
It looks like a toy.
(Do you have anything to eat?)
- It comes to you? / - It does?
- Oh, my. / - It came to me!
- Oh, my. That's so cute. / - Incredible!
- It doesn't have a natural enemy. / - Must be full.
It's not afraid.
We're near the top.
- Top? / - Top?
Near the top.
We're almost there.
We're almost at the top.
Once we go up here...
How is this possible?
This is awesome.
This is unbelievable.
How is this possible?
This is awesome.
It's pretty.
You can see everything in one glance.
- That's only after 20 minutes? / - For real.
It takes 15 to 20 minutes.
It really is the classic English scene.
I knew why they want to live here after retirement.
I think I know why.
Check this out.
(The view is all around you)
The National Geographic chose this place among
50 places you have to see before you die.
It's on that list?
It looks so nice.
(Lake District)
This is so interesting.
It's not that high.
- It's like a neighborhood hill. / - I know.
Jeongbalsan in Ilsan seems higher.
Right.
- Seriously... / - But the view...
- It's so low... / - How is this possible?
Being able to see a
360 degree view...
Have you heard about Wordsworth?
- No, I haven't heard about him. / - He's a poet.
I haven't either.
There's a poet named William Wordsworth
and he's from this neighborhood.
I think he saw this view when...
- He wrote the poem, "Daffodils." / - He must have.
Let's project ourselves like the poet...
I'll recite the poem.
What are they doing suddenly?
He wanted to read it there.
"I wandered lonely as a cloud..."
- "That floats on high o'er vales and hills." / - Dujun...
- He's so sentimental. / - "When all at once..."
"I saw a crowd,
A host, of golden daffodils."
"Ten thousand saw I at a glance,
Tossing their heads in sprightly dance."
"The waves beside them danced but they
Out-did the sparkling waves in glee.
For oft, when on my couch I lie
In vacant or in pensive mood,
They flash upon that inward eye
Which is the bliss of solitude."
"The bliss of solitude."
He wrote this when he was alone.
"For oft, when on my couch I lie
In vacant or in pensive mood..."
Isn't it over yet?
Dujun!
I love this part.
"Which is the bliss of solitude."
When he says "the bliss of solitude," it's a paradox.
Like the silent scream.
Just as we learned...
The bliss of solitude.
You can really feel the bliss of solitude.
To be honest, if I go to England,
I want to rent a place and stay overnight there.
It's really worth it there.
It went by so fast.
I was worried they would only show soccer stuff.
There was a lot to see.
- Not at all. / - There were lots of surprises.
I thought the pie would be like a walnut pie.
But it was a meal.
Your activity was amazing too.
The activity was awesome.
- How was it really? / - I wanted to try it.
From what I know, actual skydiving...
- Lasts about a minute. / - Less than a minute.
It lasts only that long.
But for $76...
- It's affordable too. / - For that cost...
- You can fly for 2 minutes. / - 2 minutes.
- It's double. / - You can fly indoors.
- With your mouth wide open. / - Yes.
The lower part looks okay but isn't it scary...
- When you went up? / - Not at all.
The Lake District...
- We have to point some things out. / - What?
It's 1 of the 50 places you must see before you die.
Before the apartments were built in Dongtan...
It used to look like that.
- The new city of Dongtan. / - Right.
- Hey, come on. / - Before the new apartments.
- Dongtan... / - From what we saw...
We just felt the air was clean.
What was it actually like?
It felt like I went inside a movie scene.
There were trees...
- And the sky. / - There were birds.
- The bird came to you. / - The bird was cute.
- The bird was incredible. / - Right.
That bird was really cute.
It played a huge role.
The first half of the Manchester HighMan Tour.
Would you visit Manchester or not?
Please vote!
(HighMan Tour planned a trip to Manchester)
(What will the judges choose?)
It's only the first vote so let's take it lightly.
What do you think your score is?
- Out of 100. / - It'll be over 80.
- Over 80. / - It's my third time.
Yes.
- The look on their faces... / - You can see it?
It's the worst I've seen in the 3 times I was here.
I'm worried right now.
It looks like he's enjoying it.
- Because... / - It's only the first half.
A great victory to us...
I don't want to hurt Dujun.
But...
It's high, right? Jonghyuk is shocked.
This is your doing.
It's high.
Is that high?
- It's high. / - Dujun.
- It's high. / - It's your third time.
So you know just by seeing them.
I think the score is either really high or really low.
The first half score is
just to test whether your buttons are working.
It doesn't mean much.
After seeing Lake District...
It's the score I thought it deserved.
Out of 100. Fine.
Anyway, it's the first half.
- It's just a teaser. / - The highlight is the second half.
We need to rush it here.
We have to watch the second half.
Soccer.
It's soccer...
- With soccer... / - What else is there?
Dujun is a little shocked.
- What else? / - Is it all soccer?
I'm a little worried.
There are a lot of female judges today.
If you continue to talk about soccer here,
the votes might decrease.
Female judges,
please open your minds a little towards soccer.
Put away your prejudice against soccer.
Think of 2002.
- Everyone. / - Imagine how fun it'd be.
Everyone! In just 3 months, it's the World Cup.
Don't forget that.
Picture that passion and let's watch
the second half.
First of all, we must watch soccer.
We must watch soccer.
- It's a life dream. / - Of course.
It's a dream so we'll watch it.
There's that thing...
- What? / - The Manchester derby.
It's next week.
- You're right. / - Yeah, it's next week.
(It's the biggest soccer league in the world)
- I really want to go there. / - One must go there.
(40 home matches without a loss)
(The invincible Manchester United)
(The only undefeated team in the 2018 season)
(And the strongest club in the European League)
(Going for their 13th win in a row, Manchester City)
We'll get real reactions here.
Serious, I was so happy.
(However)
- But then... / - Because of the snow?
- Canceled? / - If the weather is too bad...
- Is the game... / - Yes, if it's really bad...
The game could get canceled.
What's going on?
This is just the start.
- It's just the start? / - Yes.
My goodness. I thought the soccer was over.
- This is football day. / - Is action day over?
- Action day was over long ago. / - I see.
Before we start football day...
When it comes to the U.K., it's the home of soccer...
- Gikwang. / - Yes?
What's with the bag?
It's just a bag.
- If you carry it on your back... / - They'll steal it.
They can steal everything.
- You can be pick-pocketed. / - Must wear it forward.
Before we start football day...
When it comes to the U.K., it's the home of soccer...
They really live a life of soccer here.
We'll take a time of learning.
- Let's go. / - Let's head inside.
- Goodness. / - It's a soccer shrine.
- What is this? / - They're playing this.
- What is that? / - Is it pool?
They play pool with soccer?
It's pool with your feet.
It really is the city of soccer.
- Foot pool? / - I want to try that.
Foot pool.
(Foot pool, $11.50 for 45 minutes)
- Join? / - Yeah.
- Really? / - Yeah.
Where are you guys from?
- Korea. / - South Korea.
Korea.
(They start with greetings)
- You're playing 2 on 2? / - Yes.
(Korea vs. England, a battle of pride)
(The match begins)
Is that bad?
I tried a fake.
(They score one point each)
Nice shot. Nice shot, boss.
They're pros.
- Okay? / - They're going easy on us.
- I don't have an angle. / - Just tap it.
It's not easy to hit that.
Just push it with your sole.
Is it okay to hit the black ball?
You can hit it.
- So long as you don't put it in. / - Just hit it, right?
Try it.
- That won't do. / - It's going in. It went in.
It went in.
It's in.
- Did they score the wrong ball? / - It was a mistake.
- You lose if the black ball goes in, right? / - Right.
We win.
Is it over?
- Is it over? / - That's how it ended.
What the?
- You failed. / - They failed.
That black ball...
- Is the same black ball in pool. / - It's the 8 ball.
What's the most important thing here?
What is it?
It's the gear. We don't have the right gear.
We have the wrong shoes.
(He blames the shoes)
- One more game. / - One more time.
We should've worn sneakers at least.
Okay.
Nice shot.
The wind is in the opposite direction.
(A precise shot)
Nice shot.
Wow, Dujun.
Very nice.
Professional.
Nice shot, boss.
Since we can't score...
- We'll disrupt them. / - Interfere.
Okay.
(Gives it a light tap)
- We disrupt them. / - No, no?
You have to hit the ball.
- You have to hit the ball. / - Really?
Go again, go on.
- Go again? / - Try again.
Try again?
Darn it.
Okay.
(The U.K. team fails to score)
He did that on purpose. Let's give them a chance.
We have our pride.
- He'll score it. / - They're doing it on purpose.
- Go easy on them. / - I'll show them a performance.
(Relaxed)
(Might as well do it right)
They might win.
That was fun.
(Score the black ball last to win)
(U.K. team continues to fail)
This isn't easy.
- I think this would be easy. / - Like this?
We have to do this here.
I'll measure it for you.
(Measuring the angle)
- Here? / - Okay. I'll hold it here.
I think it's about here.
- The 8 ball. / - Yeah, about here.
(Here I go)
That looks really difficult.
Using the cushion.
No, no.
(Close)
It's blocked.
(U.K. team tries a teamwork shot too)
(It heads towards the orange ball)
They lost.
- It might go in. / - The black ball.
Nice shot!
(It keeps going towards the black ball)
(Please, no...)
Nice shot!
(Proud to watch it again)
- Thank you. / - Good game.
- Good game. / - Good game.
Is that the trend in the U.K.?
Or is that the only place with foot pool?
- Is it popular? / - Yes, it's even in Korea.
- What? / - It's in Korea too.
They have those in Futsal stadiums.
Why did you pack your bags?
What was our tour again?
- The HighMan Tour. / - HighMan Tour.
Highlight in Manchester.
This is the place we've been waiting for.
We've only ever seen it on TV.
Where Park Jisung used to play...
It's the Old Trafford...
We're at the hotel right in front.
- There's a hotel there? / - Yes, there is.
- Really? / - It's for the true fans.
Sleep right in front.
That hotel must've been built for the stadium?
For the true fans...
Do you know Ryan Giggs and Gary Neville?
- Legends of Manchester United. / - Right.
They invested money to build that hotel.
- It must not be that old. / - Not that old.
- Let's go in. / - Yes.
How is there a hotel
right next to the stadium?
It's right next to it.
Don't the numbers look like the uniform numbers?
It's like that font.
Goodness. We're right in front of Old Trafford.
- Seriously. / - This is amazing.
- Wow. / - Shouldn't we take a photo of this?
- The view... / - I'm curious about the view.
- The stadium was right in front. / - The view!
What is this?
(You can see the Old Trafford right out the window)
It's clean.
The wallpaper is like a soccer ball.
It's even called Hotel Football.
I can't believe Old Trafford is right before my eyes.
They gave us a very nice room.
- That's amazing. / - This is the best spot.
- Soccer fans would be so excited to be there. / - Yes.
It'd be like a shrine.
I've never heard that there was a hotel there.
(The morning begins with the tour of Manchester)
Manchester. Must-see location...
- There's one here too. / - What is that?
National Football Museum
in Manchester.
A place of excitement for all EPL fans.
It was made with cutting edge technology.
- Let's check this place out. / - It's not bad.
Since we love soccer.
(HighMan Football Tour)
(Football Museum)
(15 minutes from hotel to the museum)
- It's the soccer tour today. / - Right.
What's the most important thing about soccer?
What is it?
- What do you think it is? Guess. / - What is it?
I don't know either.
That's why we're at the museum today.
- Really? / - So let's...
It seems like they're welcoming us
with a very loud announcement.
"Welcome, Dujun and Gikwang of Highlight.
Thank you for visiting Manchester."
This is a national museum.
- Is it? / - It's the National Football Museum.
- And there's no entrance fee. / - Is it free again?
- Yes. / - Goodness.
The pound is expensive.
It's expensive so to those watching this tour...
We want to show you ways to enjoy it for cheap.
- It's our duty... / - Sounds good.
- We're not here to have fun. / - That's right.
We're not... Are we here to have fun?
It's to have fun and...
- To inform the viewers... / - Is that it?
We have to inform the viewers so...
We'll explore the Football Museum.
- Let's head out. / - Let's go.
It's Pele.
- The soccer museum is a risk. / - No, it's not.
(National Football Museum)
(Exhibits 140,000 displays of soccer history from 1872)
What's that? Are they souvenirs?
You must go there if you like soccer.
You'll go crazy.
(The highlight of the Football Museum)
(You can experience soccer related games upstairs)
(Day pass is $36, 10 games are $14.40)
It's the penalty shootout game.
You tally the score through penalty kicks.
- Should we play on a bet? / - Like what?
Play for pride.
- What else is there to play for? / - Right.
(He's played soccer from a very young age)
It's a friendly competition.
(Ronaldo Jun)
When did they shoot that?
(The captain of the celebrity soccer team)
(Captain Gikwang)
(Embarrassed)
Cute.
- When did they shoot that? / - My goodness.
I laughed because he was funny...
(Let's enjoy that cuteness again)
(Ronaldo Jun vs. Captain Gikwang)
Three shots each.
- Whoever scores the most. / - The total score.
Yoon Dujun's first kick.
We were wearing dress shoes...
(Flies towards the goal)
(Flies above the goal post)
- No goal. / - I relied too much on power.
He missed his first kick. The second shot.
He's good.
We can expect a high score for this one.
- It was a good kick. / - he's good.
940 points. The last...
(He can't just let it end like this)
(I'm Yoon Dujun)
(My soccer skills have always been praised)
(I need to show them)
The last kick.
- I went too much for the corner. / - It's too high.
That's no good.
- What the? / - It registered as a goal!
It's worth 1,000 points.
It really is 1,000 points.
The last kick.
I went too much for the corner.
- It didn't go in. / - It registered as a goal!
- That's not fair. / - The ball dropped in.
Stop talking nonsense. I heard it go out.
You heard it, right? That's a goal.
You heard the net.
- What a shame. / - 2,085 points.
- You got over 2,000 points despite a miss? / - Yes.
I will show you the pride of Korean soccer.
You're wearing a red shirt as well.
(It's finally my turn)
(With the pride of the celebrity soccer captain on the line)
Here I go.
- That was a good kick. / - Good kick, right?
That was a really good kick.
- This is... / - The goalkeeper would stop that, right?
No way.
1,000 points. Nice and neat.
This machine makes errors.
Gikwang is really...
They're on the same team and they're fighting.
This time I will shoot the ball that way.
Give it a try.
That was a good shot.
That was a good shot. Good shot.
That's how you kick a ball.
- This is the pride of Korean soccer. / - Good work.
Good job. It's slow but good.
Of course.
Here goes.
(Will he win?)
(Who will win this match?)
- Good kick. Not bad. / - Good kick.
I won?
You win.
- I won? / - You win.
Congrats.
It doesn't look good right now.
- Only for those who like soccer. / - Look at their faces.
- What do you think? / - Playing for lunch.
The audience doesn't look happy at all.
This is bad.
(China Town)
(There's a restaurant that Coach Ferguson loves)
China Town is well developed in any city.
It's like a movie set.
(They arrive at the place full of Chinese characters)
(It's the China Town in Manchester)
As you see, we're in China Town.
If you look over there, you can see
the symbol of China Town, the Paifang.
It's the first Paifang built in all of Europe.
It's very well-preserved.
This China Town has a long history.
Why are we in China Town?
What do you think?
We're hungry, so to eat.
Correct!
There's a very famous Chinese restaurant here.
It's loved by Coach Ferguson and
other famous soccer players.
They're regulars here.
Looks delicious.
- I'm sure Park Jisung visited here. / - Right.
I dare to assume that.
- Let's check it out. / - Let's go.
As you can see, doesn't it look very traditional?
- It looks very traditional. / - It has a 40-year history.
- It's a fancy restaurant. 40 years? / - 40 years.
It's a Chinese restaurant.
I wonder where they sat.
- Coach Ferguson... / - The famous guests.
Since the bird is pointing with its beak...
I think that symbolizes it.
So this seat is where Coach Ferguson sat?
Where I'm seated right now...
Since these two are pointing to this same seat...
According to feng shui...
- This looks like the best seat. / - You're right.
As we're talking, what is that?
Thank you.
This is the dish Coach Ferguson loved.
- Lobster? / - Cantonese style lobster.
- It's cooked with garlic. / - Looks good.
That has to taste good no matter what.
(Cantonese style lobster, $112)
This is a Cantonese dish.
It has a familiar smell.
It smells very good.
- It reminds me of chili crab. / - Right.
It reminds me of that too.
- Then let's... / - Let's try it.
- I have a shellfish allergy... / - You can't eat it!
He can't eat then?
- You're allergic to shellfish? / - Yes, he is.
My goodness.
How happy would you be if your friend has that allergy?
Yeah, it could be annoying to share.
- It's lobster. / - You'll eat that all on your own?
Thanks.
Just by seeing it and smelling it...
- Goodness. / - It's going crazy right now.
The set here is so...
You barely eat one lobster a year.
Will it make Dujun show
a genuine smile?
Will it?
(I want to eat it too)
Is it delicious?
For real? Honestly?
Do you want to forget your allergy and try a bite?
- Is it that good? / - For real.
It's the best dish I've had in England.
The food in England sets a new record every time.
It's here.
Oh...
This is for the shell.
(So long as it isn't me)
Is it that good?
- It's... / - Does it melt in your mouth?
Rather than it melts in your mouth,
it's very plump.
- But it's not tough though. / - Like steamed monkfish?
It's just a luxurious texture.
When I visit Europe,
I always go to Chinese restaurants.
- It's different to the ones in Korea. / - It's different.
- It's very different. / - It has its charms.
The seasoning is made in a Chinese way.
It's something you can't easily find in Korea.
Yet, it tastes familiar. I think they made the sauce
using chili peppers.
It tastes very familiar.
- Korean people would love this. / - I think I got it.
Chinese food... Wow, it's here!
- What is this? / - It's Chinese steak.
Chinese steak.
- Wow. / - Chinese steak?
Check out the sound.
What is that? You can just eat it like that?
(Chinese steak with spring onion and ginger)
- It was tender like braised ribs. / - It's beef.
It tasted like oyster sauce or soy sauce.
It was a delicious salty marinade.
You have to eat it with rice.
So even in China Town...
- This was a famous place? / - Yes, even there.
- I'll have a taste. / - Can't we quickly eat it?
(They finally take a bite)
Why?
That face means it's really delicious.
(No words are needed)
You don't like it?
Oh, you want me to try it.
It's perfectly seasoned.
The meat is so tender.
It's seasoned very well.
(This restaurant serves nice steak)
It's delicious.
This is the best restaurant in England.
- This is the place. / - This is it.
It's not like steak actually.
It's tender like braised pork ribs.
The sauce is savory and sweet.
- It's well seasoned. / - It feels like bulgogi too.
Whoever tastes it will
be able to enjoy it.
It's so good. I'm really happy.
Wow, this is so delicious.
What is this?
It's egg fried rice!
(He overdid it)
That's funny.
I can't believe how luxurious this lunch is.
I'm crying tears of joy.
It's really delicious.
- You can eat that rice with meat. / - The sauce...
- Mix it together. / - It'd be so good with the sauce.
He's eating that lobster alone.
Since English people come here,
I can see that they put in an effort
to cater for their tastes.
It's a slightly salty flavor.
But it's not too strong.
Compared to other Chinese cooking.
I think this might be the best day of my life.
- Having this great food. / - Yes, great food.
- And watching a historic game. / - Historic.
(Finally, the highlight of Manchester)
- Is it finally time? / - Finally.
Finally the highlight.
I've been hosting Battle Trip for 2 years,
I've never seen the audience this quiet before.
Because it's their first time
witnessing Manchester derby in 2 years.
You may not be able to relate.
But watching a Manchester United match
is the no. 1 thing on their bucket list
for true soccer fans.
It's like a Highlight fan listening to their album
and then going to their concert for the first time.
- Right. / - That's how it feels.
I think I understand.
(They will go to the stadium by the tram)
The tram we will take is coming in.
(20 minutes by tram)
Riding in a tram like this...
It's nice. We can enjoy the scenery as well.
The view outside is beautiful.
- It's slow but it feels nice. / - Yes, it's a nice vibe.
We could use it.
A shot outside the tram.
The viewpoint is too high.
You're right.
This is precise, right?
(This is the right viewing height)
(You can see his eye)
This is the viewpoint.
Let's go with VR.
VR.
(This is what they're actually doing)
Big eyes.
It's nice.
(They arrived after 20 minutes)
I saw that on the news.
How many hours is that before kick off?
- 3 hours before. / - 3 hours?
(So different to when they left the hotel)
The crowd is going wild here.
- It's so... / - It's going off and we're right in the middle.
When we stayed at that hotel,
we didn't think so many people would gather
at the plaza like this.
If you take a look...
- It's 3 hours before the match right now. / - Right.
But all these people here show how passionate it is.
Even now my heart...
- It's starting to race. / - Is it?
This is the most historical moment of my life.
- The security is intense. / - That's right.
Let's head in as we hope
that the players will have a safe match.
Let's go.
I can't believe this.
Old Trafford can seat
around 75,000 as far as I know.
I really want to go there.
- If it's 75,000... / - It's incredibly large.
This makes no sense.
This is Old Trafford.
We're heading in.
(They can't help but exclaim)
It's like art.
I really can't believe this.
I'm getting goose bumps.
- That's amazing. / - I'm getting goose bumps too.
- You have to see it in person. / - Of course.
If you like soccer, you'd love it.
This is ridiculous.
(It's almost game time, the players are warming up)
Unbelievable. No way.
(The players are right in front of their eyes)
Have you seen a Korean soccer stadium?
- There's a running track around the field. / - It's far.
You're far from the field. That's a soccer only stadium.
The seats are right behind the goals.
You're right. It's right in front.
Unbelievable. No way.
(The players are right in front of their eyes)
No way!
(Gikwang can't close his mouth)
This is my happiest moment of 2017.
As a person who loves soccer,
I can't believe that such a glorious day would come.
(However)
What's wrong? No, no.
Snow, snow.
- Since it's winter. / - Why is it snowing so much?
(Serious)
(Fortunately, the weather got better so the game began)
Amazing.
Here we go.
I've always only heard this sound on TV.
I never thought I'd hear it in person.
(We apologize that due to copyright laws)
(We cannot show any footage of the soccer match)
(Please enjoy the match through idol reactions)
- Reactions. / - Reactions...
(Manchester City is about to score)
(Manchester United player is tackled)
(They miss the ball)
(They get close to the goal)
(This isn't copy and paste)
(They look like meerkats)
- What happened? / - They must've scored.
Manchester is really quiet.
It doesn't look good.
The viewers can't see well.
On TV, they show replays.
- I saw it. / - I missed it.
(Manchester United continues to make mistakes)
That man behind doesn't look happy.
(Wow)
They must've scored.
They scored.
The first half just ended.
It's really hot in here.
- Beyond expectations. / - That's right.
They're playing really well.
- Seriously. / - It's a lot of fun.
I'm expecting more for the second half.
(They seem to be very excited)
(The lively and captivating match continues)
(Just then)
They score again.
- How was it? Are they good? / - You can tell.
They were incredible.
(Manchester City wins by 2:1)
(Historic moment, is this for real?)
How good must it have been?
(After the soccer match)
The sense of realism was amazing.
Manchester City set a new record.
The first time they've had 14 consecutive wins.
- We were part of that historic moment. / - Right.
That was very meaningful.
My excitement hasn't calmed down yet.
- Let's continue the talk over a beer. / - Sounds good.
We can't calm down our excitement right now.
- We must visit an English pub. / - That's right.
- Let's enjoy it. Let's go. / - Let's go.
(It's already the last night of the trip)
It's a traditional English pub.
There are 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 monitors...
It's amazing.
- Every monitor is playing soccer. / - I love it.
There are lots of sports pubs in England.
- That's right. / - What a sports pub is...
- Those who couldn't get tickets... / - They gather.
They drink there as if they're at the match.
Great work today.
The symbol of England.
- Let's end the tour... / - With ale.
With a glass of beer.
- There are so many monitors. / - HighMan Tour!
- I feel like beer now. / - Oh, beer...
It might be more fun to watch...
- The game here and drink beer. / - That's right.
Dark beer usually is less carbonated...
- Than other beers. / - Right.
This isn't carbonated at all.
Try some.
There are a lot of people who can't drink
carbonated beverages.
This is good for those people.
I thought it would be similar
to the "G" brand beer.
- It's good. Nice and smooth. / - It's really tasty.
We'll drink more next time.
In England, even if you watch on TV,
the money...
- Since it's not a free channel. / - Really?
It's the first time I've watched EPL in person.
This was something I only dreamed of.
I watched these games at home...
- While sleeping. / - Right.
We actually saw this with our own eyes.
I was so happy to see the players 20m in front of us.
- It was a dream come true for them. / - That's right.
That's one tick off the bucket list.
Let's pick the best moment of this England trip.
I wanted to try skydiving once before I die.
I think it was really nice to experience
indoor skydiving.
It felt like I was riding a strong wind
for those short 2 minutes.
- It felt like flying. / - Exactly.
I'll never try skydiving for the rest of my life.
I'll never do it.
But all my curiosity about skydiving
is completely satisfied.
I don't need to try skydiving ever again.
I think that's a good thing
about the indoor skydiving.
And I liked the whole view of the Lake District.
It was the best moment for me.
I'm sad that we couldn't get the whole thing
on camera.
It's such a shame.
Because it was a 360-degree surround view.
The camera can't capture the beauty of the sky
but it can capture the beauty of beer.
It's really strange.
I liked the poem I read up there.
- I liked the process of going up. / - Right.
Just like the view, it opened up my heart.
It was the best moment. That magnificent view.
I hope HighMan Tour will win this battle.
- For a successful finish. / - I want my third win.
Great work.
HighMan Tour!
Where are you looking?
(HighMan Tour, the end)
I always say that
I want to go on a trip with a girlfriend.
But this trip was good enough to go with a friend.
It's good that they went there together.
Gikwang and I are the two members
who love soccer in our group.
- You love sports. / - Yes.
So how did it feel to have the players right before you.
It still feels like...
- Your heart races? / - I was dreaming.
I think you'd be more nervous
3 hours before the match when...
- The people start to gather. / - Right.
Please tell us how it felt then.
When we have a concert,
our fans wait for several hours there.
It felt like we could experience
the same thing indirectly.
Above all things, I was honored
to watch the best soccer teams play
in the best league. As a fan of soccer...
- That's just... / - I understand.
Now, it's time to check their traveling expenses
excluding the airfares.
- How much did you spend? / - Dujun.
Excluding airfares,
during the 3 days, HighMan Tour in England spent...
- Per person... / - How much?
It's quite costly over there.
$660.90.
$660?
It's cheaper than what you expected, right?
That's because the museums are free.
- Since they're public. / - The judges are stirred up.
Let's cast the final vote.
This is my third time to be here.
The audience looks more displeased...
- Than ever. / - No, we can still win.
It's because they were too focused.
Dujun must have a feeling...
If the other team went to France or Italy, then I'd worry
but they went to England as well.
- You never know. / - Right.
Just how much better could it be?
Or how much worse?
- Please be understanding. / - What's in Liverpool?
I believe it'd be good to visit at least once.
If you end up going,
I hope our plan helps even just a little bit.
Are you ready?
Will you go on a trip to Manchester according to
the HighMan Tour? Yes or no?
Please vote!
(HighMan Tour showed the best trip for soccer fans)
(What will the judges choose?)
We went to Manchester today.
- And we'll go to Liverpool next week. / - Yes.
Are you confident? You guys look so tired.
If we knew the audience would respond like this...
- We should've gone first. / - Why?
To change this mood...
We need a considerable amount of energy.
However...
When I went to London,
I didn't see a reason to fly for 12 hours to get there.
But when I went to Liverpool, I was glad that I went.
We always think that too.
He said something hopeful for the first time.
- Next week, you'll see... / - You'll see.
We will leave for the romantic city, Liverpool.
Please join us again next week.
Thank you.
(Next episode)
So this is what England is like.
It's great.
This is totally me.
There's something new.
Liverpool is cool.
Finally, The Beatles...
It's love for The Beatles.
So cool.
I feel emotional.
(Battle Trip)
("True Love" by Kim Sungkyu)