I think I know why people say this is the best.
This is fun.
Is this what it was?
Let's find some inner peace here.
It's a UNESCO World Heritage Site.
This is the best.
This is so delicious.
(Handle with care)
It looks like a city of the future.
I didn't know it would be so good.
(Who will be the winning team?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Park Sohyun, Hong Hyunhee)
(Mimi of OH MY GIRL, Kim Shinyoung)
(Special host, Kim Minkyoung)
Travel is war!
Battle Trip!
Continuing on from last week...
Counterattack of secondary travel destinations part 2.
And we're with our planners.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
Nice to meet you.
- Shinyoung. / - Yes.
You look excited today.
I'm so excited.
Because we're finally watching their trip.
Right.
You look a little intimidated...
- After watching our trip. / - Let's be honest.
How did you like Hangzhou?
Hangzhou? I was impressed by its scale.
But Kyoto has its own sensitivity.
Sensitivity.
- Sensitive Kyoto. / - Sensitivity.
- Sensitivity? / - Sensitivity is important.
Our trip is designed to cater to Mimi.
Because it's her first trip.
- Right. / - We planned the trip...
For beginners, intermediate and advanced travelers.
We went to a place that even Japanese don't know.
For the first time in this show,
we show you 1 of the top 3 best views in Japan.
- One of the best 3? / - It's a first.
You've been to Japan so many times,
but it'll be your first time to see one of those views.
- Mimi. / - Yes.
Was it really the first trip of your whole life?
I've never been to other countries
unless it was for work.
It was my first trip to an overseas country.
And Shinyoung is very busy...
- With Celeb Five these days. / - She's very busy.
- She took some time off for me. / - Two idols.
That's right. We're idols. Both girl groups.
- They are two idol artists. / - But they're different.
You look cool.
Actually,
here I call her Mimi.
But I address her as "senior" on music shows.
She says, "Found you! OH MY GIRL."
And we say, "Please raise us up."
We each have our greetings.
That's lovely.
How many times have you been to Kyoto?
I've been around 30 times.
- To Japan. / - You've been so many times.
- She's an expert. / - She's been heaps of times.
- She goes real often. / - You look confident.
She keeps smiling.
That's because...
- She's been there 30 times. / - It's been 30 times.
When comedians like me, plan a trip to Japan,
we ask Shinyoung where to go.
She's that much of an expert.
So today's battle is Kyoto vs. Hangzhou.
Let's find out where it's located.
- It's Japan. / - Kyoto.
- Japan... / - It's really close.
- It's Osaka. / - It's close.
It takes about 1.5 hours by car with traffic.
If you take the subway...
- There's a subway? / - Yes.
- Yes, they do. / - Around 40 minutes.
- So it's like going to Gyeongju. / - It's really close.
- Gyeongju. / - Since it's the old capital.
When we go to Kyoto...
- We visit Kiyomizu Temple. / - Right.
Ninenzaka and Sannenzaka are common places.
We didn't go there.
- You didn't? / - No?
It's so fun to go on a trip with Shinyoung.
She also went on trips with a lot of idols.
- I mostly go... / - You sent with Seolhyun.
- With Seolhyun... / - Seolhyun of AOA...
- You've traveled with Jimin. / - Jimin.
Do you have some criteria for choosing your partner?
People who are going for the first time.
First trips.
- Joining them on their first trip. / - Our job...
Is to give people laughter.
I wanted to give Mimi another form of joy.
I mean it.
When Shinyoung goes on a trip,
there are things she does
to have a good time on a trip.
- Give us some tips. / - In the past...
It was getting blind drunk.
- Really? / - That's right.
I don't search for
good restaurants beforehand.
I just take a cab.
I get in a cab and...
I ask the driver to take me to a good restaurant.
- That's right. / - Cab driver favorites.
I have no clue about the place
but he just takes me there.
- And the food's really good. / - In Japan?
- Yes, in Japan. / - You can do that?
- In any country. / - You need to speak the language.
- This is a great tip. / - No, wait.
If the driver asks questions,
we have those apps nowadays.
If you don't speak the language, use the app.
- Then... / - They'll really make the effort to tell you.
They will recommend a restaurant for you.
I get off the cab and take a selfie with him.
- How nice of them. / - It's a really good place.
They help you to the end.
Right to the end.
That's really fun.
- But the cab fare will be $10. / - No, no.
It won't be $150.
We only traveled within Kyoto.
We walked around on foot.
You two wouldn't need an interpreter in Japan.
- That's right. / - We didn't need an interpreter.
We really didn't need one.
I studied Japanese since I was a trainee.
She's really fluent.
- I can communicate in Japanese. / - Yes.
Teach us some words we need to say in Japanese.
First, there are some easy ones.
It's one or two when you order food.
- It's really simple. / - Hitotsu.
Hitotsu.
Futatsu.
- Hitotsu. Futatsu. / - You don't need more than that.
- Says who? / - What about three?
Three?
Three.
- One, two, three. / - Three.
Shinyoung speaks Cantonese.
She can sing in Cantonese.
Of course.
Holding hands?
What is this?
"Smiling Angel."
No.
♪ It'd be nice ♪
♪ Holding your hands tight ♪
I can hear it.
I heard it.
You can hear it.
- Excuse me. / - ♪ Say good-bye ♪
- ♪ Say good-bye ♪ / - Shinyoung.
We have to check out your video.
Okay.
We'll be heading to Kyoto now.
Kyoto was Japan's capital for 1,000 years.
Kyoto is rich in history.
There are 17 World Heritage Sites.
World Heritage...
You walk around and it's UNESCO.
That's amazing. 17 World Heritage Sites.
Also, don't you remember?
In Taiwan, my eyebrows of truth.
- You remember, right? / - When you eat...
Something delicious.
- Your eyebrows react. / - Seriously, people...
You just need to know one thing.
Whether my eyebrows move or not.
Just think about that.
Okay.
Tell us the tour name, and we'll start.
You'll probably remember this.
We made a remake.
- Whether you go... / - Kyoto!
- Whether you don't... / - Kyoto!
- If you'll regret it... / - Go to Kyoto!
Let's begin.
I really know my way around Tokyo.
You can walk around even without a car.
I've been to Kyoto two times.
Once I went with a friend.
Last year, I went with just Seolhyun.
She still wants to go back.
I take so many people on trips.
We buy each other's clothes.
I remember that street I walked on for 30 minutes.
- She's been a lot. / - A lot.
Last time, on Battle Trip,
I went with Shindong.
- It was a co-ed episode. / - That was so fun.
This time it's like going with the youngest.
I've been in a girl group now, so I know.
Of course.
You have no free time.
Your 20s is the best time of your life.
It's when you should have the most fun.
But she's never been on a trip before.
So I said, "Let's go together."
But I didn't want to pay.
That's why I asked Battle Trip.
I'm just kidding.
I have so many good memories
of having a fun on Battle Trip.
It got rid of all my prejudice against Taiwan.
So I hope she has fun too.
Come in already.
Hello.
You really dressed up.
She's so pretty.
Pretty.
(She's actually a charismatic rapper)
Five, five, five, five, five. Celeb Five.
I'm the leader, Kim Shinyoung.
Found you! OH MY GIRL.
I'm Mimi of OH MY GIRL.
That's us.
Yay!
It's a meeting between girl groups.
We got close when
I hosted OH MY GIRL's showcases.
Three of them now.
So many...
We only met for business.
But she's really country
and innocent.
She takes such good care of me.
She really does.
She always buys me good food.
We talk at least once a day on the phone.
Really?
One call per day.
You're really close.
That's not easy to do.
We always do video calls.
I always see her updates on Instagram.
She posts a lot.
Please say, "SNS."
I see her updates on SNS.
I have to teach her a lot of things like this.
I need to teach her since I am a senior.
- SNS, okay? / - Understood.
You're like a mom.
Okay, okay.
We hold hands.
We're really affectionate with each other.
We even kiss.
Yes, we kiss...
What's wrong with you?
You're thinking naughty thoughts.
- I just like you, is all. / - Alright, alright.
- They seem really different to us. / - Yes.
They actually look like close friends.
- We're close. / - We are.
What do you want to do on a trip?
What comes to mind?
We have to eat.
Food.
Eating, and bike riding.
In those romantic mangas.
You always see...
The heroine in a school uniform.
Hurry.
You want to do that?
Bike riding, and?
Admiring the trains passing by.
Like in "Slam Dunk?"
♪ Running up and down the court ♪
And you see Hanamichi on the train.
I'll try to do whatever you want.
In order to get an authentic experience of Japan...
Let's go to Kyoto.
- Kyoto. / - Sure.
When you go to Kyoto, you remember Kyoto for itself.
I'll take you to places where
Japanese don't even know.
I'll try not to do things I want to do.
I'm sacrificing for you.
What is it you want to do? Clubbing?
I want to go clubbing or shopping.
I want to go to the mall
and buy all the figurines.
Sook knows what I'm talking about.
- You must go there. / - You must buy it.
That's a must-visit spot for comedians.
When the sea comes within view...
That's my fantasy!
It feels like a movie.
Seriously.
(Shinyoung's Kyoto Level Up Tour)
(From the beginner course in the city)
(Intermediate course that satisfies all five senses)
(To the advanced course with secret views)
That's so pretty.
(Incheon International Airport)
(Kansai Airport)
(1 hour 40 minutes)
Let's go.
(Yeah!)
I get so excited exiting the airport.
Just enjoy it.
That's the first thing to do.
First, we have to go to Kyoto Station.
For beginners who are on a trip
for the first time like you,
go to the side as soon as you come out.
You see that on the side?
- Buses are the most convenient. / - Right.
Just take the bus.
What do you normally take?
To be honest, I take the cab.
- You can't be frugal on trips. / - That's right.
Isn't that right, Sook?
She doesn't walk more than 100 steps.
(Hahaha)
I'm just going to trust you on this trip.
Just trust me.
I'm going to trust you.
(She looks more excited than Mimi)
Heading off.
She's so cute.
(Kyoto Level Up Tour, beginner course)
(Walk into Kyoto)
(Nishiki Market)
(Gion Street and Kamo River)
(Food Stall)
(Kyoto)
(Capital of Japan from Heian period till mid 19th century)
(The center of Japanese culture and tradition)
(Kyoto Station)
If you're a beginner,
you must come here. Kyoto Tower.
Amazing.
The best, right?
It's really high.
When you collect snow globes,
they have the Kyoto Tower for Kyoto.
- Really? / - Yeah.
- Amazing. What's inside? / - It's the symbol of Kyoto.
I've never been inside.
You said you went there over 30 times.
I just walked around.
It's enough to pretend I know.
I've been there once.
Okay.
It's like the Japanese version of Gyeongju.
- Gyeongju. / - Yeah.
That's what it's like here.
There must be a lot of good food.
There's lot of good food and lots of cool stuff to see.
- First... / - Where are we going?
There's a place that really stands out.
Where?
We'll go there first.
It's called Higashi Honganji.
It's a historical site in Kyoto.
- This place here. / - It's really natural.
This place is so cool.
We walked about 10 minutes from the station.
It's just on the way.
Things like this...
On this street,
they sell heaps of mochi.
- There's a lot of street food. / - Yes.
These are crepes.
You have to eat crepes when you're in Japan.
This is amazing.
(Oh, my)
Look at this. It's a carp.
It's a fish.
- Isn't this so nice? / - That is so interesting.
His face is green.
The streets are so pretty.
I'm so happy.
Both of you look so happy.
- Of course. / - That's right.
- Don't we look happy? / - Yes.
You'll walk a lot when you travel with me.
That's good.
It's different
when you walk around on a trip
and when you ride a car.
- They're totally different. / - Yes.
That's why I walk.
This is Higashi Honganji.
It's really big.
It's one of the three famous gates.
Like Dongdaemun and Namdaemun.
Let's go.
- I gave her a simple explanation. / - Let's go.
It's all catered to her.
- It really was. / - It was all catered.
- It's so big. / - Right?
This is a historical site of Kyoto.
It doesn't matter which country it is,
these majestic sites are always cool.
They have this sense of dignity.
- That's right. / - Dignity.
So it's like this...
- It's really grand. / - You don't have to know too much.
This is Higashi Honganji
and it's a wooden structure.
That's all you need to know.
Just have a look around.
Let's just have a look around.
You can come here again when you have time.
That's what it's like.
We still have lots of places to go.
It's like...
Wherever you walk...
Look, everyone's walking on foot.
Everything is close by in Kyoto.
It's really pretty.
- It is, right? / - Yeah.
That hotel is where Seolhyun and I stayed together.
- Really? / - Yes.
Whenever it's someone's first trip, I go to Kyoto.
You present them a great trip.
Kyoto is the first destination that comes to my mind.
I have good memories here.
I get reminded of the city.
I walked around a lot with Seolhyun.
My Japanese teacher also said...
- You can never see enough of Kyoto. / - She's right.
Even if you get lost, it's fun.
That's what traveling is like.
Even if we get lost, I think it'd be nice.
It doesn't upset you.
I'm glad I put sneakers on.
I think one should wear sneakers here.
You're right.
Because you have to walk.
Of course.
You're truly free to go where you please.
I really planned it like that.
That's a common street.
- With lots of good eats. / - Right.
You have to take photos there.
- It's just... / - The street itself.
Anywhere you go is a magazine cover.
You can comfortably walk the streets.
- It looks like a movie. / - It's her first trip abroad.
- Just walking made her happy. / - Let's go in.
- It's Nishiki Market. / - Nishiki Market.
It's Nishiki Market.
It's a market.
It's the kitchen of Kyoto.
It has 400 years of history.
- Is this also 400 years old? / - Yes.
There are over 1,400 stores in the market.
- It looks amazing. / - This is the stuff.
(It's amazing)
It's incredibly old.
It'll be very crowded.
But all the food is delicious.
- There are so many people. / - Let's go.
- Let's buy everything. / - Okay.
You're hungry, aren't you?
That was the plan all along
Really?
Everything's good once you work up a sweat.
Let's try different foods...
And choose the best ones?
We'll choose the best ones for gifts.
Sounds good, sounds good.
That's fascinating.
What is?
Look at the octopus.
- That's so cute. / - They were really good.
It's so cute, I want to eat it right now.
Pocket octopus.
That's cruel.
- Everyone's looking. / - That was delicious.
Two.
Want to try this one?
- One. / - One, please.
It's good.
- Is it? / - Yeah.
It's slightly...
That was so good.
(So nice)
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's so sweet.
Want another one?
- Eat another one? / - Eat another one.
One more please.
Shinyoung's let go.
We bought another skewer.
You have to.
You have to eat one each.
You shouldn't miss scallops.
Welcome to the world of scallops.
It's so delicious.
We tried that one.
- It's just a beginning. / - Shall we begin?
- You must try parboiled octopus. / - Looks delicious.
There's eel inside.
- Octopus. / - Egg rolls.
You must eat that.
You must.
- Let's eat eel. / - The good thing about this place...
You don't just buy it and leave.
There are places you can eat.
- Next door, like that. / - Separately.
It's just one bite.
Just a single bite.
(Chomp)
Do you like it?
I love eel.
It was so delicious.
It looks delicious.
Everything tastes good.
That one looks so good.
- Eel egg roll is delicious. / - Seriously.
It's insanely good.
It's good.
Is it good?
I want to eat it again.
- They look so pretty. / - This is interesting.
How could fish cakes be so pretty?
Yeah.
The fish cakes are so pretty.
You must not miss
this kind of food in Japan.
It's the Eyebrow Tour.
Seriously, my eyebrows...
It's really sweet.
Is it sweet?
- So cute. / - They're so plump.
It's so chewy.
- It's so good. / - So much stuffing.
- You must try the fish cakes. / - That's bacon.
Because it's all handmade.
Everything's handmade.
- That was good too. / - They cook it right before you.
- Mimi! / - It's so good!
Minkyoung is having a hard time.
- Mimi! / - That was so good!
- It's so good. / - Just one bite!
It's a pollack roe egg roll!
It's so good.
Excuse me.
One pineapple juice please.
They juice it just like that.
- They juice it whole. / - Just like that.
Don't you drink that in Southeast Asia?
It's worth $10.
- Really? / - Yeah.
(Slurp)
This is madness.
Isn't it amazing?
- It's so good. / - It's so good, right?
We should've asked him to juice some more.
I really want to eat the fish cake and pineapple.
We ate a lot.
Wait a minute.
Didn't you guys just arrive there?
You have to eat like that.
You have to eat like that on trips.
$40.
- $40 worth. / - You can't help it.
$50.
Mochi, mochi.
- We're not eating too much. / - Right.
We're just excited about the taste and the vibe.
They're cherries.
One, please.
This is just a snack, right?
- It's just a snack. / - Just a snack.
Would Japanese people feel like us
at Mangwon Market?
Right?
- Right now... / - Mangwon Market.
We're walking around the Japanese Mangwon Market.
(Nishiki Market is the kitchen of Kyoto)
Egg roll.
I love these.
What is this?
Pickled dishes.
- It tastes great with rice in water. / - Right.
You can buy it in Korea too,
but you must try the local one.
Looks like you're on our side, Sohyun.
She's on the Kyoto team already.
(Popcorn)
(The eyebrows of truth react)
I'll buy you some.
This is why you travel with your seniors.
A bigger one please.
Look at those roasted chestnuts.
- Aren't roasted chestnuts just for winter? / - No.
Thank you.
Careful it's hot.
You're indeed an idol.
Idol?
Idol.
Korean idol.
I'm the Nishiki idol.
- Nishiki idol. / - Nishiki idol.
I see.
Thank you.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
They're so nice.
They give you 5 to 6 samples.
- You must be full. / - They're really nice.
Ice cream.
Shinyoung, Shinyoung.
This is too much.
The 2nd best dish? 1, 2, 3.
Scallops.
Scallops were so good.
Best dish. 1, 2, 3.
- Pineapple. / - Pineapple.
- What? / - It wasn't the pineapple.
To be honest, it was the fish cakes.
- Fish cakes? / - The fish cakes were so good.
- I want to try the pineapple. / - Ginger!
It wasn't too strong and the texture was nice.
- Pineapple for you? / - Yes.
- The pineapple was insane. / - It was so good.
I gulped it down.
- But it made me angry. / - Why?
- He should've juiced up more. / - Right.
When you go there, ask them to juice up more.
- Our second stop is... / - Vintage shop?
- It's a vintage shop. / - Okay.
- We're on a trip. / - We have to get some.
- Let's make it hip. / - Okay, let's go.
Isn't this a Celeb Five outfit?
This is Celeb Five.
- It was really pretty. / - So many pretty clothes.
So many.
- This place is amazing. / - Hey, Mimi.
- Yes? / - That guy's my type.
- He's totally my type. / - You have matching beanies.
Is this fate?
Isn't he really handsome?
- He's so handsome. / - Isn't he really handsome?
He's my type.
- Totally agree. / - He's handsome.
- My type. / - What if he recognizes you?
(Prettying herself up)
- Director, do I look okay? / - What are you doing?
That was you prettying up?
He's so handsome.
- The workers here dress so well. / - I know.
A short passionate romance.
- I imagine it sometimes. / - Imagine what?
Shinyoung's imagination becomes reality.
Isn't he really handsome?
He's even better in person.
- He's even better-looking in real life. / - He's handsome.
- With thick eyebrows. / - What a handsome face.
I can't see the clothes.
- Oh, no. / - I can't see the clothes.
- Her heart's fluttering. / - He's so handsome.
- No. / - Your eyes.
- Let's choose an outfit for each other. / - Okay.
- Okay? / - Got it.
Is there a smallest size of this?
This is the smallest size.
Shinyoung likes red and yellow.
We picked clothes for each other.
- I'll turn you into a celeb... / - Since you're close.
In anyone's eyes here in Kyoto.
Nice.
I chose that.
Kim Mimi...
I chose that outfit.
Good choice.
(This is a celeb)
- Anyone can tell... / - That's the celeb style.
So out there.
So pretty.
- Mimi did it. / - Celeb.
Someone took my photo.
A Westerner took a photo of her.
- For real? / - She really liked her look.
My goal was right.
I told you I'd turn her into a Kyoto celeb.
They're taking photos of her. It's going off.
I did it. My styling is a success.
(Hiding)
Wasn't that a Japanese kid?
Is that kindergartener going home?
Waiting for her big sister.
- This street is nice, right? / - I love it.
Can you think of the equivalent in Korea?
- Hanok Village. / - That's right.
If Jeonju has the Hanok Village,
Kyoto has this traditional area.
So pretty, right? This is Gion Street.
You can just walk around everywhere.
This is the spot. Check this out.
That's amazing.
You can see the river flowing.
So pretty, right?
This is amazing. Why is the water so clean?
- Right? / - I wanted to keep showing her nice things.
As much as I could.
- That's how you feel. / - I want to get coffee here.
- Incredible. / - Though I don't drink coffee.
Here... But you don't drink coffee.
I don't drink coffee...
- You can drink something else then. / - You're right.
The streets are so beautiful. It's crazy.
- How happy would she be? / - I remember.
I don't think I'll ever forget this.
Keep treasuring this with your eyes.
- Look at this. / - Kyoto is so nice.
Isn't this amazing?
- How is it? / - I love it.
- Do you love it? / - Yes.
Mimi, go.
You need to take photos here.
You must when it comes to wings.
- Isn't it so pretty? / - I look like I have long legs.
Mimi, you're enjoying Kyoto thoroughly.
But this is the beginner course.
- Is this the beginner course? / - Yes, it's level 1.
Oh, that's right.
- Whether you go to Kyoto... / - Or don't go to Kyoto...
If you'll regret it, go to Kyoto!
Good job.
You'll seriously regret it if you don't go to Kyoto.
You will.
This is the riverside I really like.
- Is this the street you like? / - Yes.
- Like it? / - The view...
This is the perfect hour at this river.
You can't see when it's too dark.
This season is perfect.
They open the terrace starting from May.
- They open the terrace. / - You need to come here.
You need to feel this.
I really wanted to go there.
The plane time wasn't right.
That place is hard to go because of that.
- That... / - We only ever walk there.
- That river... / - If you walk down, it's amazing.
Even the poet Yun Dongju walked along this river.
This place is really nice.
When I was leaving for work in the morning,
I saw people jogging.
It was outside my house.
I didn't sleep for two days.
I thought, "How different can our lives be?"
But we're the same right now.
I'm just happy that I'm part of this group.
See as much as you can of this river at this time.
I'm speechless.
- I know what it feels like. / - Me too.
It makes you choke up.
Your happy hormones gush out.
I think Shinyoung might cry.
I shouldn't be so moved like this on the first day.
Why is the beginner course so nice?
I found a really trendy place.
- Okay. Let's go. / - Let's go.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
- Brush away the dirt. / - Let's go.
- It's this way. / - Is it this way?
- Don't pretend you know the way. / - Okay.
(Relaxing in the city beside Kamo River)
- I think they walked 10,000 steps. / - That's amazing.
- Oh! / - Isn't this incredible?
- There's the moon over there. / - And look left.
There's the Kyoto Tower.
It looks different at night.
It's totally hip here.
The owners made all this.
Students of the Kyoto University of Art and Design.
They made all of this.
This place is really trendy.
- Isn't it really trendy? / - It's so hip.
- Doesn't it feel like Hongdae? / - Yes.
- It's like Hongdae or Yeonnam. / - It feels young.
There are a lot of things to eat.
You can choose according to your preference.
- It feels young. / - Of course.
There's a campfire there.
This place is also different.
(You can roast marshmallows here)
(What will they eat?)
- Amazing. / - What is this?
Grilled foods. Should we get one?
- Skewers! / - They were so good.
(2 chicken skewers for $4.90)
- Should we try Kyoto beef? / - Yes, yes.
Kyoto beef...
This is it.
- That was so good. / - Kyoto beef.
- You must try it. / - Highly recommended.
Number one.
Yakisoba.
This feels like a pub at a university festival.
(They're done setting up)
- Thank you. / - It was really good.
This is Kyoto beef.
Thank you for the food.
Let's have one each. One chicken a day.
- One chicken a day. / - This is like a food show.
- Wow. / - It's so good.
It's really tender.
- It looked dry but it's not. / - Not at all.
It's not salty. I thought it would be
but it's not salty at all.
Mmm.
I can taste the charcoal.
It looks so good.
(Frown)
Hip!
This was so good.
You must eat this.
- This... / - Kyoto beef.
It's insane.
Why is it so tender?
- My eyebrows are angry, right? / - Yeah.
Wow.
It tastes like milk.
Really good beef tastes like milk.
- Beef tastes like milk. / - It tastes like milk?
(Special sauce with butter and garlic oil)
(It's popular because they use high-quality beef)
- Look at that meat. / - I want to eat it again.
- Like they're frying the meat. / - That was so good.
- This is the best steak. / - The best?
- It's so good. / - It's really good.
You have to try this.
It's so good.
Try some. Eat up.
This is amazing.
This isn't like the one we ate in our room.
- Here, cheers. / - Cheers.
Wow.
- It's spicy. / - It's different.
- It's different to the ones I've had before. / - Right?
- It's a fusion dish. / - A fusion dish.
Is this tripe?
- Isn't it pork? / - No.
- I think it's tripe. / - It's tripe. I'm sure.
I'm sure of it. This is a Japanese style fried tripe.
It's not like yakisoba.
It is Japanese style fried tripe, with a spicy aftertaste.
This would be a huge hit in Hongdae.
(It's perfect for the taste of Koreans)
- I'll eat the rest. / - Okay.
(Shinyoung eats so well)
We ate everything. It's so good.
We're really picky.
You know how sensitive my tastes are.
- Very sensitive. / - She's a gourmet.
You get tired of eating Japanese food after 2 days.
You want to eat spicy food.
You should eat this. It's spicy in the end.
Let's go to the campfire.
To be honest, I was jealous.
I want to roast marshmallows.
- Like a hippie. / - Like hippies.
You can roast marshmallows at the campfire.
- That's romantic. / - Yes, that's romantic.
It's $5 for this box?
- It's for the vibe. / - Yeah, don't save on food.
That's right.
This was my first time roasting marshmallows.
It's so good.
- Isn't it good? / - Yes.
This is so delicious.
This tastes like toffee.
It's like toffee and also choco pie.
- You're right. / - The marshmallow in the choco pie.
(Yum)
It felt so warm.
I can't forget this day.
That looks so good.
I love it.
My legs are about to burst.
It hurts but it feels good.
Pervert.
It hurts but feels good.
It's been a while since I ate without stress.
Right?
Tomorrow, we'll make your fantasies come true.
- My fantasies... / - Tomorrow is level 2.
(The day of the intermediate course is dawning)
This was amazing.
What is that?
- Bamboo forest. / - You have to walk hand in hand here.
(Kyoto Station to Saga-Arashiyama Station, 15 mins)
I really wanted to come here. The best of nature.
This is our intermediate course.
There are things that you may have seen on blogs.
And there are surprises.
- There are also surprises? / - Of course.
The place we're going... Kyoto nobility.
- Nobility? / - It was their holiday destination.
They say to go to the bamboo forest early...
- Because there are so many people. / - We're here.
This is the bamboo forest.
Why is it so pretty.
Listen to the sounds.
This is amazing.
- It's like a scene from a commercial. / - It's so nice.
- This is the intermediate course, right? / - Yeah.
- Level 2. / - Yeah.
When people come here, they all go left.
- You're right. / - They go left.
We'll go straight.
- This way? / - Yes.
When you go straight from the bamboo grove,
you can take photos inside the bamboo grove.
Not that many people go there.
I'll introduce you a completely secret photo zone.
- Okay, okay. / - Just go straight.
Follow me quietly.
I love things like this.
It's so pretty.
Album cover photos would be amazing here.
- There's no one, right? / - Right.
It's really secluded.
- It's so pretty. / - Look at that.
- This is it. / - Look up.
It's so pretty.
How can it be so nice?
I don't believe this.
Bamboo...
I'm scared that I might forget this sight.
- What? / - I'm scared I might forget this.
It has a cool vibe.
- You need to shoot a movie there. / - That's not CG?
Mimi's expression was beautiful.
She's scared she might forget this sight.
It's poetic.
I want to remember this.
- I still look at those photos. / - Wow.
- You must've really enjoyed it. / - It's beautiful.
Just come here a bit early.
- Don't take photo with the crowd. / - Right.
You can enjoy the bamboos at ease.
And take all the photos you want.
- You still won't come? / - You won't?
- Whether you go to Kyoto... / - Or don't go to Kyoto...
If you'll regret it, go to Kyoto!
You must come here.
- Even when you see this? / - You won't come?
(Second course of enjoying Arashiyama)
So cute.
This is the start.
Open car.
There's Sagano Romantic Train.
It costs $6.10 per person.
Let's check it out.
- You took the train? / - It goes then comes back.
- You took that? / - You can enjoy the view.
Right and left view are different.
(It's an open roof)
- It's all open. / - That's nice.
(Here, the scenery looks nicer on the right)
- Doesn't that mean "right?" / - Yes, right.
You can see cherry blossoms in March and April.
- Cherry blossoms? / - It'd be so pretty to come then.
So pretty.
Wow, it's so pretty.
In autumn, you get foliage.
(Romantic train in the autumn)
We're going to Hogwarts. To Hogwarts.
I feel like I'm transporting to a magical world.
Here it comes. We need to film this.
(Screaming)
It's so picturesque.
It's so cool.
It's a sight everyone must see.
- The air is so clean. / - I love this.
- The train itself looks beautiful. / - Isn't it beautiful?
(So nice)
- Mimi, you look happy. / - I was so happy.
Wow. Look at that.
We're here.
- Are you happy? / - I'm happy!
Here comes the hard carry.
Goblin.
- What's that? / - Goblin.
Is that a real goblin?
World champion?
Oh, Kim Yuna!
Oh, Bae Yongjoon.
Korea baseball, number one.
Soccer, number one.
He's there to brighten the mood.
To make the trip more memorable.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Be happy.
Mr. Goblin!
Hi, vintage shop hottie!
- I was so into him. / - He came to mind.
I honestly fell for him.
- It's a face you can't forget. / - He was so hot.
We can do a flower cookie class in Japan.
You know what that is, right?
They're shaped like flowers.
You don't know?
You've never seen them, right?
- Something like this. / - They look pretty.
It'd be good to make...
And give out to your members.
- That'd be nice. / - Mimi has the Midas Touch.
Mimi has the Midas Touch and so do I.
- You make them yourselves? / - Yes, you do.
- You can experience it for yourselves. / - You do.
Traditional Japanese sweets originate from Kyoto.
- Kyoto. / - This place has been running...
For about 150 years.
- 150 years? / - Yes.
(They will make these sweets today)
- How pretty. / - It's so pretty.
I've tasted them with my eyes already.
(The instructor shows up)
Hello. Nice to meet you.
That master has been making sweets for 50 years.
He'll give us a brief explanation.
Everything is in Korean too.
You think you can do this?
- I'm good at assembling things. / - Right?
You're good at making stuff.
I like crafting by nature.
You sound pretty confident.
(A red bean sweet made with sugar, flour, rice flour)
- Take one each. / - I see.
I've only seen those sweets.
- I've never made one myself. / - Exactly.
- Make it 4cm in diameter. / - Press it like this?
Yes, press it like this.
- Like this? / - Yeah.
Put this in the groove.
Press it.
Put the white one in the center.
- In the center. / - Okay.
Flip it over.
(They slowly enter a difficult stage)
Turn it over.
(You have to turn it inside out)
Now, keep watching.
(She gives up on interpreting)
Interpret for me.
You can't just sit there doing your own thing.
Why am I learning over your shoulders?
I'm sorry.
Do it like this.
- Interpret. Don't just do it alone. / - I was too focused.
I understood it but I couldn't interpret right away.
- I had to make mine too. / - Over the shoulder...
(She learned faster by just watching Mimi)
Put it inside. Just like that. Yes, you're good.
- You're good. / - I think I'm getting close.
She's good.
Show it to him.
Shinyoung is good at making that.
- Look at her fingertips. / - She was really good.
Her hands are cute.
(Mimi doesn't get what to do)
(Only hers is perfect)
When you turn it, use your thumb.
Look. Turn it like this.
- She's a lady. / - She's so good. My gosh.
- She's good at that. / - How could she make that?
I'm good at making stuff.
(Stamp the mold and it's done)
This is so cute.
- Your sweet looks so pretty. / - Now, we're done.
- Shinyoung's looks much better. / - That's right.
- My hands are rough. / - Shinyoung's sweet is pretty.
- He gave us tea too. / - That was really delicious.
- My gosh, that tea. / - It smells really good.
It's rich.
Given its bitterness, I would've spat it out.
- It'd go well with the sweets. / - But it's smooth.
- They'd taste good together. / - It must be sweet.
- It was good. It was really tasty. / - Right.
- It's good. / - It's good.
(A bite of sweetness and a sip of matcha tea)
They go well together.
Mimi is fluent in Japanese.
I don't speak Japanese but I can follow instructions.
The class costs $19.60 cents per person.
- The sweets are included too? / - That's reasonable.
He's showing them something.
- It's a technique. / - He showed us something else.
He showed it to us because Mimi worked so hard.
- Is that a Pokemon? / - He was excited.
He can create whatever he wants.
- You can even make that. / - The maneki-neko!
- It has paws too. / - Seriously.
- The cat waves its paws. / - That's right.
- The fortune cat. / - I know that cat.
- The one that says hello? / - Yes.
The cat that goes like this.
- We made the sweets, right? / - Yes.
The dinner will make you slap your knees.
You'll slap your knees out of amazement.
We just took a class to make the sweets.
- Yes, we did. / - This is the next place!
They're going there at last.
Can I share this with you now?
It's been running for 140 years.
- The restaurant? / - Yes.
This is a sukiyaki restaurant.
- Sukiyaki? / - Yes. History.
- It's 140 years old? / - On Teramachi Street...
This is the only original building.
- This is amazing. / - This is the butcher shop.
- This is the butcher shop? / - Yes.
This is the butcher shop and a restaurant is upstairs.
- We can trust the meat quality. / - We can?
- We'll have the sukiyaki meal. / - The sukiyaki meal.
$150?
- It does look delicious. / - That tasted amazing.
- It's quite pricey but... / - Wow.
If we're going to have sukiyaki,
we should have the best sukiyaki from this region.
Would you look at that.
- It's worth the expense. / - It really is.
It has a rich flavor.
- Level three. / - Three.
Three.
(The sukiyaki makes her eyebrows squirm)
(They learn how delicious sukiyaki is)
- Hello. / - Hello.
Look at this. Do you see the street?
It's Teramachi Street.
That's this street 140 years ago.
- The building's the same? / - Exactly the same.
It's amazing that a restaurant is
more than 100 years old.
Look at this. They painted the staircase over and over.
But you can see the traces of time on it.
- It's amazing. / - This is amazing.
This is a typical traditional Japanese tatami room.
- You can hear the water flowing. / - I hear water.
That place tastes good before you even try the food.
What do you think of when you think of sukiyaki?
- I have never tried it yet. / - Really?
The most popular form of sukiyaki is from Kanto.
You eat it boiled or steamed.
The one we most commonly eat is the Kanto style.
- Here, it's the Kansai style. / - Kansai?
They grill it, which is the Kansai style.
It's different. They eat it in different ways.
- It is? / - Yes.
- Here we go. / - It's so...
It seems so traditional.
- It's cute. / - I can't wait to see it.
I wanted to treat her a proper meal at least once...
In a great restaurant.
- Despite the costs. / - Right. Just for me.
She's breaking the egg...
One each. She's removing all the unsightly parts.
The meat!
Unbelievable!
(Today's menu, beef appears)
This is awesome.
- This is awesome. / - Hey, this looks like some...
- It looks so good. / - That meat...
They get the best parts from various regions each day.
Look. Kanto-style sukiyaki is served in a saucepan.
It looks like a pan for okonomiyaki.
Wow.
I can't help getting impressed by every single thing.
That's a bit embarrassing.
Okay.
(So this is how you look unclassy and embarrassing)
You should be like this.
Try to look cool with it. Your face tells you're excited.
- Does it? / - You look so excited.
It's so obvious.
(Finally, the iron plate gets heated)
This is insane.
This is how they cook in Kansai.
They do that in Kansai.
- They add sugar? / - It coats the meat.
They melt the sugar!
That makes it really delicious.
It sounds like rain.
- This is the same from the mangas. / - That's right.
You hear this in manga.
Oh, I hear the rain!
(A sudden shower on a hot day)
- Oh, I hear the rain! / - We both love animations.
Then you see the lightning.
It's cooking so well.
(The sizzling sound comforts you)
(Mimi is surprised again)
What is this sauce?
- It's soy sauce. / - They pour it on the meat.
(I want to eat that)
I asked what kind of sauce it was
and she doesn't know because the owner made it.
Of course. It's the secret sauce.
- Passed on for generations. / - It's their secret.
Telling us to do this?
- Like this? / - Yeah.
I'd like it to be well-mixed.
I like it half-mixed.
Gosh, it looks so glossy.
(Sugar and soy sauce add gloss to the meat)
Can we eat it just like this?
- Do you dip it? / - This is the Kansai...
Oh, my goodness!
We're going to eat it now!
Rinse out my mouth.
- Thank you for the food. / - Thank you.
Let me try it.
Isn't the meat tough?
- It has to melt. / - Of course it's not tough.
It's not tough.
If you say it's tough, you're lying.
- Really? / - Of course.
(She dips the meat in the egg wash)
What will we do about this?
(I can't help laughing)
Excuse me.
She's so happy.
- It's instinctive for me. / - This is incredible.
(She finally tastes it)
(They're reminded of how it was)
You're going to eat it in a single bite?
You need to eat that in big bites.
(She finally gets to taste it)
(They take the very first bite of traditional sukiyaki)
Amazing. It just hit her.
- There you go. / - There it is.
(It's amazing)
It must be so good.
I see "delicious" all over the screen.
- All over the screen... / - Wow...
This is so good.
What will I do when my first sukiyaki is this good?
This is how you become a terribly picky eater.
"This isn't right."
"This isn't how it's supposed to taste."
She added the sugar...
What about the sugar?
I've never seen sugar used like that before.
If you taste the sugar, it's not that sweet.
- It's not sweet? / - It's less sweet.
- Not too sweet. / - It's like a coating.
It's a flavor enhancer.
It's not that strongly seasoned.
(She pours some soy sauce on the iron plate again)
It's time to cook vegetables.
- They grill it? / - Yes.
Kyoto is well-known for good vegetables.
- She sprinkled the sugar again. / - She did.
So pretty.
She keeps adding the sugar.
(Now the soy sauce)
Do we dip it all in the egg wash?
- Do it as you like. / - This is amazing.
(She dips it in the egg wash)
This is just so...
This is amazing.
(This is it!)
(Deliciousness)
(They're surrounded by deliciousness)
(Shiitake mushroom)
It tastes like meat.
(What?)
Am I wrong?
- You're right. / - Right?
The texture is...
I don't like tofu so much.
Me neither.
(Amazed)
This is not tofu.
(No, no)
It's so delicious.
(Flavors enhanced by the sugar and soy sauce)
(She keeps eating the vegetables)
Why are you eating so much onion?
I don't know. When my mom sees this,
she'll be shocked that her daughter eats onions.
- Exactly. / - And I eat green onions.
I'm eating it like it's meat.
To be honest, I can eat 3 bowls of rice with this.
It'd be so good with rice.
- I want to eat rice with this. / - Here comes the rice.
- The rice here is so delicious. / - In Japan...
(The meat is ready as well)
- Thank you for the food. / - Dig in.
That's right, the egg at the end...
You add the egg with sauce on your rice...
- Eat it together. / - You have to eat it up.
- That's it. Way to go. / - Just like that.
Put white rice in your body.
(There you go!)
- That's how you gain weight. Yes! / - Well done!
Great job!
Amazing.
Why do we always eat rice after eating meat?
(Perfect combo of meat and rice)
- It looks so delicious. / - I want to eat it like that too.
(This is what I wanted!)
I wonder how it'd taste.
- Ah, it's the next course. / - Oh, it's not over yet.
Because this is a course meal...
- She grills the food slowly. / - Cooked nice and slow.
(A big bite)
- Dig in. / - That was so good.
- Eat it now? / - You have to eat it now.
(Once it gets cold, it won't taste the same)
(They're both impressed)
Deliciousness.
It's floating around the room.
That was the best.
This is the best sukiyaki I've ever had in Japan.
- Is this the best? / - Yes, this is the best.
- Mimi. / - Yes.
Would you order one more bowl of rice for me?
The servings are small despite the great taste.
Then I don't have to save the rice.
You need two bowls of rice.
- You must eat two bowls of rice. / - Of course.
- Are you done with your rice? / - You can have it.
I ordered another as well.
- You ordered one too? / - Yes, I did.
(Mimi's stomach has become bigger now)
(Mimi ordered two bowls of rice)
She doesn't leave a single grain of rice.
(They give the clean bowls back to her)
(They welcome new bowls of rice)
Welcoming the new bowl of rice.
Is this the last bite?
What a shame.
- I can imagine. / - Check that out.
(I will enjoy to the very last piece of meat)
(She savors the flavor for a long time)
My mouth is watering.
I have a huge mouth cavity.
- Minkyoung... / - Minkyoung, you can't leave.
- Grab her. / - No, no.
- That's a television screen. / - No, no.
- That's just a screen. / - Is it?
- Is it just a screen? / - It's just a screen.
- My goodness. / - This won't do.
Now you must know why I spent money on this.
(Shinyoung's love spreads in her mouth)
- Could you pour it here? / - Now?
That's amazing.
I know what that is.
- It's ochazuke. / - That's delicious.
- It's good like that. / - No more meat.
We finished the meat. We have pickled radish left.
- It was so delicious. / - This meal is worth $150.
She keeps lifting her arms.
Everyone, $150 dollars is so worth it.
I'm finished.
That was one of the top 3 meals of my life.
- It was really delicious. / - It was that good?
It was to die for.
I had two bowls of rice.
I've never had two bowls of rice before.
My eyebrows tell the truth.
They frown like this.
They tell the truth.
If I ever find myself in Kyoto, I'll definitely go again.
This is our second day.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
- Can I look forward to it? / - I'll fulfill all your dreams.
- My dreams? / - Yes.
An unbelievable itinerary that will
fulfill all of your dreams.
- It was so good. / - This is our last itinerary.
It's the advanced course.
I loved it there.
I don't think a lot of people know this destination.
Look at the color of the water.
- I love it here. / - Riding our bikes...
Today's itinerary is for the advanced level in Kyoto.
- It's the ultimatum. / - Okay.
- It's the last level. / - It's our last.
We can visit 2 places. We'll go to 2 places today.
As for the first destination,
not even the locals know about this.
- Have you heard of Amanohashidate? / - What?
- Amanohashidate. / - No, no.
- You've never heard of it, right? / - No.
I prepared my courses by stage.
You'll be surprised to find out about the last course.
That's what I intended our trip to be.
- Here's the scenic view. / - 1 of the 3 best views.
There are Japanese floating homes.
- Japan has floating homes? / - Yes, they do.
You need to go north from Kyoto
toward the East Sea of Korea.
We can take the train there.
We'll ride the express train.
- In Korean. / - Welcome.
(They buy the express train ticket to Amanohashidate)
Oh, "A."
Hashidate.
Okay.
I haven't been on a train in ages.
- Really? / - Yeah.
- That's right. / - It takes about 2 hours.
When you're busy talking...
- Time flies. / - It goes by so fast.
- Welcome. / - The weather is amazing.
Amanohashidate.
- The weather's so nice. / - The weather was amazing.
The weather is excellent.
We're right here.
We're here.
- Let's go to View Land first. / - Okay.
Wait. That's how we're supposed to look.
- Must we look at it like that? / - Of course.
There's a view you must look upside down.
Amanohashidate View Land.
(It's located at the top of the mountain)
You have to climb the mountain?
This place is...
On top, there's the monorail and below,
there's a one-person lift.
- Is that how you'll get there? / - Yes, that's right.
- That looks fun. / - That was fun. It was.
What do you mean it was fun?
You were like this the whole time.
You'll see that soon.
(They choose the one-person lift)
- There are so many people here. / - This is nice.
- That's how they ride it. / - It's $8.30 for entry.
You have to be careful.
This doesn't scare me. I'm not afraid of heights.
But you are, aren't you?
- No. / - Your face looks a bit stiff.
Your eyes tell me you're lying.
It'd be great to travel up in the open air...
But there's no seatbelt.
(See? Aren't you scared?)
I'm not that scared of it. I was just joking.
But I think this is scaring you.
Even an old man is riding this.
- He rides it very comfortably. / - He seems relaxed.
Even little kids.
She just held the baby.
- I'm not scared. / - Sit on my lap.
Be careful. Watch out.
- She seems really nervous. / - She was so nervous.
She couldn't let go of the pole.
(Scared noises)
Shinyoung.
- You pretended to be unafraid. / - My goodness.
(She quickly grabs the pole)
It's high. It's high.
Wow.
She had so much fun.
- Shinyoung! / - My gosh.
- Shinyoung. / - Try to enjoy it.
- Why do you look so stiff? / - I was enjoying it.
Try to enjoy it.
(She's frozen)
- It's a still photo. / - She froze.
No. Right now, I'm so...
Comfortable...
(The lift is climbing up)
Mimi, doesn't the air smell nice?
Shinyoung, this is awesome.
Look behind me.
(A wonderful view as they climb up)
We're climbing up.
This is the best view.
Everyone must visit.
(You get to witness it on the way down)
That's the dragon... The dragon...
- Like a dragon's tail. / - You see that coming down.
- You did see the view, right? / - Yes, I saw it all.
Her hand has been in that one spot the whole ride.
It was the same when she came down.
(Hasn't moved an inch)
What are you mumbling about?
That's the quietest I've ever seen Shinyoung.
This is amazing.
I love it here.
- This place was so pretty. / - Amanohashidate.
One of the top 3 views.
- This view here? / - Right there.
Shaped like a dragon tail.
This looks like an amusement park.
- Everything looks pretty. / - It's a theme park for kids.
Don't look. Don't look yet.
- I shouldn't look now? / - Don't look yet.
- Don't look. Not just yet. / - Okay, okay.
- Don't look yet. / - It's like her boyfriend.
They look romantic.
"Don't look."
It's like a surprise.
Ta-da.
The view!
(They can't believe their own eyes)
That's the pine forest?
- The whole path is the pine forest. / - Oh, my.
It's 1 of Japan's 3 best scenic views.
- One of the best... / - Yes.
- This is insane. / - This is amazing.
Isn't this incredible?
This is amazing.
You can see the sand through the clear water.
Where do we look upside down?
- She'll take photos for us. / - Really?
Hey, let's print our photo.
(She takes the photo with a camera)
(And they can print the photo on the spot)
- This is our photo. / - It's on the spot.
- I still have it. I'm so happy. / - It's me.
You can't miss out on that.
- This will last forever. / - Right.
Hey, let's try this too.
- Looking upside down? / - Let's go for it.
There's a specific spot where you look upside down.
What's that? You look like that?
This is it, right?
Wow, it looks different.
- It looks different. / - How does it look?
- The view is different. / - You see the tail the other way.
- It's different? / - Yes, it's different.
1, 2, 3.
(They try it together this time)
It looks different.
You should look at it upside down now.
It looks like it's coming towards you.
Oh, like this.
- A dragon... / - It's like the head of the dragon now.
We should buy some souvenirs.
They sell postcards.
A snowy day.
It looks like this on a snowy day.
They have different seasons.
- It was formed 8,000 years ago. / - Winter looks nice.
Winter is really pretty.
- Are you buying another key chain? / - Yes.
- My keychains. / - What is this?
(My goodness, Shinyoung)
- You have too many. / - You collect those.
I always buy anything that begins with, "I Love."
You have to buy these. These will last forever.
Nothing will last from your trip but souvenirs.
You buy it if it has "I Love?"
No matter what.
"I Love Vietnam," I buy it.
"I Love Singapore." Mine.
I should buy one for Jiho.
Why are you buying so many?
Only souvenirs last from trips.
What's this? A postcard for each season?
(She's sweeping the shelf)
You're going to empty this place.
Shinyoung is shopping here.
She's spending too much money.
I don't buy a lot of souvenirs.
But Shinyoung...
She seriously bought every kind of souvenir.
It's the same for every trip.
Money can burn since it's paper.
But memories can't burn.
So I never save money on trips.
I think that's great. Shinyoung told me
she buys the souvenirs because the memories
she has with the souvenirs are important to her.
I could relate to what she said.
So I realized that if I ever go on trips,
I should buy the souvenirs from that region.
This place... The way up and
the view from up here...
Make this a must-visit location.
- Isn't it the best? / - Everyone should come here.
Best destination for our last day.
However, I have another great spot.
You have another one?
- You have more? / - Of course.
That has to be the best spot.
It's a Japanese version of Hallstatt.
- Hallstatt in Austria? / - The floating village.
(Like the fairytale-like, floating village in Austria)
(Where is the Japanese Hallstatt?)
- Is that really in Japan? / - That's in Japan.
That's in Japan.
You can say that they're floating homes in Japan.
We go back to the station and take the bus,
and travel for around an hour.
- An hour? / - Yes.
- We took the bus. / - Bus? That's great.
(59 minutes from Amanohashidate to Ine Village)
This is Ine no Funaya Houses.
This village is originally called Ine.
The area with the floating houses is called Funaya.
But tourists just call the entire place
Ine no Funaya Houses.
- Ine Floating Village. / - Right.
I'd love to live there for like a month.
Right?
I see bicycles!
What was your fantasy?
Riding a bicycle.
What do you want to do on a trip?
Bike riding.
- You want to go bike riding? / - Yes.
When you see in those romance movies...
- Actresses always ride a bicycle. / - That's right.
- Let's go. / - She likes romance cartoons.
- Romance dramas. / - She wanted to ride a bike.
- I love that. / - You can borrow it for free.
All we have to do is return the bicycle. That's it.
This has been my fantasy. I'm excited.
I'm so excited.
(Her laugh is high-pitched)
- This is no joke. / - That was your first scream.
(Here we go!)
I'm sorry to choose this song,
but please play "To Me Again" by THETHE.
You can't sing it wrong.
(Getting ready to sing)
♪ One day ♪
The song is perfect.
♪ As I walk down the street ♪
This is awesome. Mimi!
Mimi!
- This is great. / - I'm going crazy.
- Shinyoung. / - This is crazy.
Look at the wildflowers. They're beautiful.
This place and the bicycles are perfect together.
It's so pretty.
I feel like I'm the heroine of a movie.
- Really? / - I understand that feeling.
We're filming a movie.
She said she wanted to film a movie.
Like in a drama.
(A brief encounter)
The vintage shop hottie.
I actually liked you.
(She couldn't confess it back then)
I remember him.
The vintage shop guy?
I couldn't say it because of my position.
(A love story that transcends class)
What do you mean by position?
The heroine changed.
A girl has to ride in the back.
- What? / - She would stretch her arms out...
- And feel the wind. / - Like "Love Letter."
We're going to see it now.
Look to your left. It's so pretty.
- That's the sea! / - Amazing.
- This was my fantasy! / - The sea!
(The sea appears)
- Unbelievable. / - Hey.
(Admiring)
- Shinyoung, I'm the heroine. / - It's beautiful.
- Hey, I'm the heroine. / - The heroine.
I'm happy.
(A peaceful and beautiful landscape)
This is it.
Wow, this is insane.
This is the photo zone.
- This is the photo zone. / - It's like a painting.
This will be legendary. Stay right there.
In front of there?
- So pretty. / - This is the best girlfriend picture.
- It's like shooting a commercial. / - So pretty.
(Shinyoung takes cute pictures too)
Oh, you look cool.
"The Fishermen and the City."
- What are you doing? / - Come on.
- It suits you. / - Don't male idols usually do that?
- That suits you. / - I love doing stuff like this.
- How cute. / - That looks great.
That's cute.
(Evolution of funny pictures in 3 stages)
- This is great. / - That's so pretty.
Picture of a lifetime.
There's a famous SNS photo spot.
- It's a photo spot. / - There's a cafe with a view.
- It's a floating cafe. / - That cafe's so nice.
This is great.
- The view. / - Japan has good coffee.
- There's a place where you take photos. / - A given.
- They set a stop for photos. / - Look at my stance.
Busy taking each other's photos.
I updated my SNS so often.
That photo spot is reserved for photos.
You can sit there and drink coffee.
You can only take photos there.
- So it's just for photos. / - There's more upstairs.
If we go upstairs...
Unbelievable.
Wow, look at that.
This seat.
I can see under the water.
Look below. You can see everything.
I'm about to cry.
The view was so...
It's so beautiful.
To die for.
- It felt like we were resting. / - What's that?
- Dessert. / - Cake.
I want to live here.
- I really want to live here. / - I do too.
I understand what you mean.
(A peaceful break time)
(This is inner healing)
When we were riding bicycles we said,
"It smells like liquor."
- "It smells like rice wine." / - That's right.
There's a distillery.
It looks like a distillery, right?
- It smells like rice wine. / - It does.
I don't know any Chinese characters,
but I know the character for "alcohol."
The place is over 260 years old.
You must go inside.
What's this?
- I think it's squid. / - Right?
I'm so curious about this.
There are so many people in here.
This is it. Check this out.
Is that it? Here it is.
- You'll be shocked. / - It's squid.
- It's a bottle. / - Squid bottle?
It's a squid liquor bottle.
Won't it get soggy if you drink from this?
- It could... / - That's an actual squid!
You break it off and eat it with your drinks.
After you drink everything, you can eat it.
When it becomes soft, you can eat it then.
- People who drink will love it. / - Are you buying gifts?
- An Youngmi, Shin Bongseon. / - Like a fruit cup.
- You have to get one for Youngmi. / - Of course.
I should get one for my dad.
My dad, too.
- One for your dad. / - Yes.
- Sake. / - Ice.
It's sake ice cream.
- Sake ice cream? / - Yes.
- Do you get drunk if you eat it? / - No, no.
- No? / - It's really delicious.
They give you samples.
- Black rice. / - That was incredible. So good.
- Cheers. / - Our first drink.
It's our first drink.
(They drink together for the first time)
It's clean.
- It wasn't too strong. / - "Clean."
You buy so much every time.
- That squid bottle is interesting. / - You buy a lot.
We bought a lot.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Also, there's one more thing.
More?
- There's more? / - She's buying too much.
- There's more? / - Not that way.
- Today's our last day. / - We've bought these...
We've been to a distillery.
It's similar to the place we went on the first night.
- That's right. / - The cart bar?
- Yes. / - That's it.
This is like that place.
- Here. / - It feels like we're eating on a boat.
It's floating. It moves around.
- Just like a boat. / - I love things like this.
- I love it. / - You'd get drunk.
The breeze is so nice.
The wind feels really clean.
- The waves are gentle. / - It's so nice.
- Because of the island. / - It's blocking the wind.
- This is the black rice. / - Is this it?
- It's made with black rice sake. / - Black rice sake.
- Can you drunk off that? / - No.
- You can't taste the alcohol. / - Can't taste it at all.
You can smell it a little bit.
That looks so good.
It's so good.
The ice cream has texture like sorbet.
You're right.
This ice cream has a stronger sake flavor.
The waffle hardly had any alcohol scent.
I love this.
Hey, I love this squid bottle.
It's such a good idea.
The squid bottle is $8.50.
- Is this it? / - This, this.
You'll break your teeth.
- That's really tasty. / - What?
It must be completely dried squid.
Yes, it's dried and it's very thin.
- It expires... / - 3 months...
It'll become soft when you drink from it.
This way you won't have bottle and cup waste.
You can eat it right away.
Is this the end?
- I don't want to go home. / - This is our last stop.
We're going back on the evening flight.
- I got something for you. / - What is it?
She's a very pretty person. Really.
Her existence itself is just lovely.
I wanted to make her something...
(Don't look)
- Why? / - I'm embarrassed.
What is it?
But I don't know if she'll accept it.
(After a long deliberation)
I'm going to write lyrics for Shinyoung.
Goodness.
- It's a song. / - A song as a gift.
- That's the best gift. / - I'll write it at home.
- Rap. / - I should've done that.
Yes. The words are all in here.
I'm going to record it.
I wrote them before the trip. That's before the trip.
(Embarrassed)
Because you prepared such a great trip...
Even before the trip and during the trip,
I wrote some lyrics.
Oh, cringe. You're making me cringe!
- Cringe. / - I was embarrassed.
- Go ahead. / - I'm ready.
- Please look the other way. / - Okay.
Here goes.
- "To the Beautiful You." / - It's to "B612."
♪ Honestly, it's a bit awkward ♪
♪ If it's a no, it's a no from the start ♪
(Shinyoung hears it for the first time)
(If it's a no, it's a no from the start)
- Did you actually record this? / - Yeah.
I recorded it.
The song that's playing now, is the song you wrote?
Yes.
Wow, this is the best.
So it's this song.
(You are so pretty in my eyes)
I almost cried.
I don't think she wrote the lyrics...
Just because we had this trip.
She must've thought about me a lot...
- In order to complete the lyrics. / - That's right.
(I hope you keep smiling like a kid)
(You'll be by my side, and I'll be by your side)
- Shinyoung, you're a lucky person. / - She is.
Shinyoung, be good to Mimi.
- I'll be good. / - What about me?
She's good to me.
- What about me? / - Be good to her.
What about me?
- It's sincere. / - It is.
I wrote it while thinking about you.
I liked it because of you.
- "I liked it because of you." / - Shinyoung's trip...
Gets your money's worth.
I got my money's worth until the end.
We went on a trip together but
she bought my gifts too.
Even though I was right there.
That's so precious.
I think I bought a lot of gifts.
It wasn't over until it was over.
Isn't this a new flavor?
- You don't stop. / - Scorched rice flavor?
- It's a sample. / - Samples.
It has a slight scorched rice flavor.
- For the members. / - We have members.
I had to buy for the members.
Shinyoung is warm-hearted,
so she takes care of others wherever she goes.
I'll buy it.
The happiest moment during the trip?
- When we went to Ine. / - When we went to Ine.
See?
We both said the same thing.
When we just sat there.
I love Ine Village.
We just sat around. We didn't do anything.
Don't. Don't do anything.
- Whether you go to Kyoto... / - Or don't go to Kyoto...
If you'll regret it, go to Kyoto!
- You must come! / - Come to Kyoto.
That was so nice.
I just stood up without realizing.
How did you like your first sukiyaki, Mimi?
My first sukiyaki...
- It was so good... / - Are you salivating?
Yes, even now. I really want to go.
Someday, just like Shinyoung says...
I'll take a junior there and
share that taste with them.
- A male junior? / - Yes, yes.
Male? He baited you.
He got you good.
I heard wrong.
She means boyfriend.
She'll take a male junior and say,
"You write the melody, I'll write the lyrics."
That's not it. I always tell her
that she doesn't need to be nice to me.
Take what she experienced with me
and share it with someone else traveling
for the first time.
That's because someone did that for you.
That's right. I got a lot from my seniors.
It was Mimi's first trip.
What was the most memorable thing?
It was Ine no Funaya Houses.
If you're there...
- It's just quiet. / - Peaceful and beautiful.
But she's only 24 years old.
She'd prefer clubs in a city to a rural town.
- She's not like that. / - She likes this stuff.
I've never been clubbing before.
Let's check the costs now.
The Hangzhou team spent $289.90 per person
for 3 days.
We had a lot of good food with it.
That's right. Then...
- Whether you go to Kyoto... / - Or don't go to Kyoto...
If you'll regret it, go to Kyoto!
- Your total expense was... / - I can't wait.
For 3 days...
- Per person. / - Per person.
$560.20.
- That's not a lot. / - It's not that much.
That's for 3 days.
I thought it'd be over $1,000.
It's not as expensive as you think.
It's because they didn't eat anything
that expensive after the sukiyaki meal.
That includes the $150 sukiyaki meal.
Yes, yes.
Please get ready to vote.
Whether you go to Kyoto. Or don't go to Kyoto.
If you'll regret it, go to Kyoto!
Will you follow their Kyoto itinerary and travel to Kyoto?
Please vote.
(They chose Kyoto as their location)
(What will the judges choose?)
Toad Tour's trip to Hangzhou?
Or the Kyoto trip?
- It is neck and neck. / - You never know.
What did the judges choose?
Toad Tour. Kyoto Tour.
Goodness...
- What is it? / - I'm nervous.
It's the first digit.
I really worked hard.
- It's the same! / - No!
- No! / - What's happening?
- Come on, Kyoto! / - Let's all go to Kyoto!
(Kyoto Tour wins with 85 votes)
This is amazing.
Minkyoung, how did you enjoy the show?
- Wasn't it great? / - I love traveling alone.
But after seeing two trips with great people...
- I was really happy. / - How hungry are you?
My skirt got loose.
She can fit her fist in there.
Next week, we'll bring you some domestic trips.
Korea is filled with beautiful islands.
- So many. / - It'll be an island trip battle.
Please look forward to it.
It's the perfect time.
Please tune in and make holiday plans with us.
We'll see you again next week.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
(Next episode)
Domestic islands...
Let's go!
I can see the ocean.
It's so green on this side.
Three Meals a Day Tour!
Why Are We Going Together?
(A place of healing)
(A Jeolla-do food trip)
Boiling hot. Boiling hot.
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
(Returning to their childhoods)
Hey, this is fun.
(Gyeongsang-do food trip)
- Let's go! / - Let's go.
(Battle Trip)
("Umbrella" by Jisook)