Now, this is Canada!
I want to live here, Seulgi!
Niagara!
(Canada has amazing nature)
So pretty.
This is made naturally.
Wow!
Here we go, here we go.
Now, this is Europe.
So pretty!
Even this looks so pretty.
You can't capture this beauty with a camera.
No, you can't.
I feel like I'm in a fairy tale.
Yes, I'm a princess.
There's nothing much
in making a good country to live in.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Seo Hyorim, Lee Hongki of FTISLAND)
(Wendy and Seulgi of Red Velvet)
(Special host, Lee Teuk)
Traveling is war!
Battle Trip!
Continuing from last week, this is the third week.
We have our travelers who went on trips to
the countries we'd want to live in.
Welcome.
- Welcome. / - Good to see you.
Different outfits for this episode.
Hongki's such a fashionista.
- This? / - What is that?
Not anyone can pull that off.
Is that Choi Hongman's shirt?
What was that?
Is it a hospital gown?
Are you a doctor?
He looks like either a doctor or a patient.
One of those two.
I felt a bit sad going home last episode.
My heart needs healing.
- Right, last episode... / - Right.
We lost 67 to 72. Just by 5 votes.
- But it's not over yet. / - That's right.
We have another battle left.
And we're with our 100 judges in the audience
that will be casting these votes.
- Welcome. / - Hello.
(100 judges in the audience)
So, where will we go today?
- A new battle will start. / - That's what's important.
Where is it this time?
- If you go to many big cities... / - Right.
You might want to live in one of the smaller cities.
So we'll check out some small cities.
Small cities.
This is a new term.
It's related to traveling.
- A staycation. / - Staycation.
It means to stay in one place for a long time...
- To relax and unwind. / - I love that.
It's a combination of the words
stay and vacation.
- Vacation... / - Vacation...
- Vacation? / - Vacation.
Was that a German accent?
Don't make me speak English.
It's too hard.
As long as you have time,
who wouldn't want a staycation?
- Of course. / - Sure.
- Everyone would. / - For like a month or two.
There are many small towns in Korea
to travel to as well.
We've introduced many places on this show.
We went to the historical city of Gunsan.
- Gunsan. / - Can't miss that out.
- Next is Jinju and Hadong. / - Jinju and Hadong.
That place is so popular these days.
- Remember the camp site they went to? / - Yes.
It's all booked up until the end of the year.
Until the end of the year?
I went to southern Italy
on Battle Trip 2 years ago.
Amalfi, Positano,
Ravello and Capri are all small cities.
That's when I started
getting into visiting small cities.
So last year around this time,
I traveled to small cities in Germany.
I started at Wurzburg
and went all the way to Fussen
like it was a road trip.
I checked out each village along the way.
- She memorized all the names. / - I have a question.
How do you memorize all the places?
- When do you work? / - Seriously.
I take a trip the day after I finish my dramas.
She didn't work for some time and just traveled.
You spend more time abroad than in Seoul.
Do you hate Seoul that much?
No, I love it.
Wendy said last episode that Seoul's the best.
That Cheongdam is the best.
Wendy said that.
Wendy, you lived in Canada.
Can you tell us about
the small cities around where you lived?
I lived in Toronto and it was nice there.
But I really liked Quebec and Montreal.
- Quebec... / - They have a lot of festivals.
- It's nice there. / - I haven't been there.
- It was so nice. / - Quebec.
It's a bit different from Canada.
It's like Europe in Canada.
- France. / - Yes.
- Right. / - That's right.
- They speak in French there too. / - Right.
So it's a bit different.
- The place we went to... / - You'll see.
It's like that too.
We're good then.
It's a place that isn't well-known in Korea.
There isn't a lot of information about this place...
- On Korean blogs either. / - We won this one.
Let's see where it is on the map.
Small cities in Canada.
Where?
We stayed at Niagara Falls.
Across that is Niagara-on-the-Lake.
That village is so pretty.
- Canada is known for icewine. / - Right.
It gets really cold there in the winter.
There's this one winery where the wine...
- Keeps freezing and thawing. / - A winery.
If that process keeps repeating...
- It makes the wine sweeter. / - Right.
- Great for grape farms. / - Yes.
So we went to that winery.
- BoA likes wineries. / - BoA's song.
♪ Winery ♪
(Why, Lee Teuk? Why?)
Why'd you make me do that?
I saw on the map that the 3 cities...
- Are a bit spaced out. / - They're far apart.
We didn't use a car.
We used an amazing mode of transportation.
- Magnetic levitation train? / - Amazing?
The ground...
- It's off the ground? / - Yes.
- It flew. / - Like Iron Man.
- Like Iron Man. / - It floats off the ground?
Are you going to reveal that
you spent like $8,400 on this trip later on?
- No. / - Did you take a helicopter?
I looked into this already.
We had one in the U.S.
Once in the U.S. over the Rocky Mountains.
- I bet it costs a ton. / - It's a lot cheaper.
- Really? / - So around $3,800?
No, no.
You don't get to ride a helicopter every day.
But if you ride one when you're traveling,
you'll remember it forever.
It'll be a memory.
You always want to splurge a little when traveling.
And for me, it was the helicopter ride.
Wasn't everything like that?
Hongki, tell us what we should watch out for.
We went to Canada to travel.
Since it's close to Canada,
we crossed the border to the U.S.
It's like this.
You're in Canada and you want to check out the U.S.,
you can go and come right back.
That's how it was like.
- But isn't that cheating? / - Why?
It's Canada versus Austria.
But if you go to the U.S.,
that's a different country.
If we knew that ahead of time, we would've...
Our team could've been all over the map.
They were in the center of Europe.
They could've gone to Germany, Hungary...
Switzerland, Italy...
Our team went to the U.S.
because we just wanted to get
the most out of our trip.
That's how it is.
Let's see Realistic Sibling Tour to
some small cities in Canada!
(Canada is where nature lives and breathes)
I feel like I'm getting sucked in.
(Voted second best country to live in)
Last episode was amazing.
(Realistic Sibling Tour to Canada)
Do you all see the view?
(The nature is truly amazing)
Niagara mist.
I have to take that boat ride.
This is made naturally.
Wow, it's so pretty.
A lake.
(Sault Ste. Marie is famous for their maple trees)
This really feels like Canada!
It's so pretty.
(People want to live in Canada for the nature)
Did you see the nature?
Let's go.
Let's go!
(Let's check out the small cities of Canada!)
This will be our first time in Canada.
I don't know much about traveling.
It's best to find a center place to stay
so the distance we travel is minimized.
It's too far to travel to each city.
- So... / - We're not going to rent a car, are we?
We are.
I rented a car on my trip to London...
- And drove for 3 to 4 hours at a time. / - Really?
- Yeah. / - Really?
Yes.
That's so cool.
- So cool. / - She's like a foreigner.
I think I rent a car
whenever I go abroad.
- I think I saw it on your social media page. / - Right?
That's good then. You can drive.
(Flustered)
- I don't get to travel that often. / - Right.
I get to visit countries to perform...
- But not really for traveling. / - Right.
I always end up in the biggest city of that country.
Like Paris in France.
That's all I get to do.
I'll leave this trip up to you, Hyorim.
I'm not good with this stuff.
You mostly travel to the big cities.
Right.
That's why...
I think we should check out the small cities
for this trip.
Places people wouldn't go to.
So, there's Kingston.
As well as Niagara-on-the-Lake.
It's just 30 minutes away from Niagara Falls.
There's a village straight out of a fairy tale.
I want to go now.
We'll be leaving soon.
Yeah.
The small cities...
- Where Koreans... / - It was so nice.
- For me... / - Amazing.
It's called the Thousand Islands.
But there are actually 1,856 islands.
Wow, what is that?
This is awesome, Hyorim.
Isn't it?
(A special helicopter)
It's all frozen inside.
This is the stuff I like.
Ring, ring.
♪ It's American rain ♪
- ♪ Please open up ♪ / - Hongki is finally excited.
(Chaotic)
(Noisy)
(Lively)
Wow!
(Their trip to the small cities of Canada starts now)
(It's day 4 of their trip in Canada)
(The weather is nice again)
(Niagara Falls, 7:00 a.m.)
Let's go!
For today's schedule...
- Kingston. / - Why did we wake up so early?
We're going a bit far today.
We're going to Kingston.
(Kingston)
(Called the living history of Canada)
(The first capital of Canada)
(European-style buildings from British colonization).
(Kingston is a great place to travel to)
(Because you can see the Thousand Islands)
What's that?
That's so cool!
There were flags.
Of other countries.
The owner's country.
(A famous place to travel to for the rich)
(It's popular to take a tour of Heart Island)
Check this out.
Ta-da!
- What the... / - I got this for you.
It's even blue.
Oh, my God!
Wow, that's so cool.
A convertible?
- That's the car? / - Right.
This is ours?
(You need one to tour small cities)
It would be great to ride a convertible there.
Right.
I almost always rent a car when I travel abroad.
Especially for small cities.
You need an international license, right?
You need an international license
and your Korean license.
Right.
Let's go!
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ Just us two ♪
(Small cities are a treat for the eyes and mouth)
(Touring day)
(Eating day)
(Niagara Falls is their base camp)
(Kingston is a 4-hour drive away)
It must be nice to drive in a place like that.
A 4-hour drive?
It's not tiring to drive abroad
in a place like that for 4 hours.
I love how I can just drive without thinking.
Not many traffic lights.
Isn't this nice?
Perfect for driving.
(They can't help singing on their way to Kingston)
♪ And I try, even though I don't know where to ♪
♪ I drive and drive ♪
He drove and sang for you! How nice!
(A drive with a live performance)
♪ And I try, even though I don't know where to ♪
♪ I drive and drive and it's still fine ♪
(They've been driving for an hour)
He's tired now.
This road won't end!
He started complaining.
I was excited at first that
there's no traffic and there's all this nature.
But everything looks the same!
4 hours might seem long to us...
But it's not considered long in other countries.
For Canada, "nearby" is 3 hours away.
4 hours is like us going to Bundang from Seoul.
- The next town over. / - Right.
- It's the next town. / - 5 to 6 hours and you're there.
Right, that's how it is.
That's why you need cruise control in the U.S.
Just leave it on.
- It's tiring for us. / - Can't keep your foot on the pedal.
This is insane!
This is what road trips are like.
This is Battle Trip.
(Ontario, Canada is 10 times the size of Korea)
Just what is in Kingston?
There's a heart-shaped island
you can see from the sky.
And the guy that owned it is named Boldt.
His beloved wife fell ill.
So he built a castle for her.
(The secret behind Heart Island)
(Hotelier Boldt started building a castle)
(On a heart-shaped island for his wife)
(She died of illness right before completion)
(He stopped construction and never returned again)
(The castle was sold for $1 by the descendants)
(A U.S. company completed the construction)
It was sold for $1.
Then they finished the castle.
Now it's a tourist attraction.
For $1?
- $1. / - I should've bought it back then.
- I have a question. / - What?
Do girls want to go to places
with romantic stories like that?
Yeah!
A place with history.
And it's romantic too.
I find it interesting that
girls go to see this stuff.
We travel far to see things like that.
It really is heart-shaped.
(Trip to the small cities in Canada)
(A cruise around the Thousand Islands)
(The dock for the Thousand Islands cruise)
(It rains as soon as they get there)
It's not so nice out today.
Let's go!
Do we have to go when it's raining?
He doesn't want to go.
He kept complaining.
He yelled at me a lot.
I didn't know it would rain.
It started raining on the way here.
Let's cancel this plan today, Hyorim.
But we drove all the way here...
I can't help that it started raining.
It was raining when we left.
He keeps complaining.
Hongki's concept for this trip is the complainer.
(The Thousand Islands cruise, $37.50)
That's the Saint Lawrence River.
It leads all the way to sea.
(The Thousand Islands cruise)
(From 30-minute cruises to one that serves dinner)
What's that house?
- Is that really an island? / - That's an island too.
- That's an island? / - Didn't it float to there?
It's an island.
- It's like a bathroom. / - Isn't that still moving?
(Some islands are natural and some are man-made)
At least we have a roof.
It's fine even though it's raining.
This place is called the Thousand Islands.
But there are actually around 1,856 islands.
Wow, 1,865...
Most of them are vacation homes.
Most people own a yacht.
(Various islands can be seen on the cruise)
Look at that vacation home.
- You could fish from your house. / - Right.
Each island belongs to someone.
You'll see flags on each island.
Flags of Japan, America, France...
That's where the island owner is from.
But not a single Korean flag yet.
Prepare your cameras. A nice island is coming up.
Where? Where?
Where do I point my camera?
This one?
- Oh, this... / - Those islands are very unique.
The left island belongs to America
and the right one belongs to Canada.
- With a bridge connects them. / - Two islands.
Two different islands.
I guess they're named differently too.
It's nice to check out the different islands.
This is so nice.
(Hongki was indoors to avoid the rain)
(Now he's enjoying the cruise)
With some coffee...
I get to relax and check out the islands.
(This is what true siblings look like)
I see another boat.
The islands...
(They sit separately but they don't miss a thing)
They're designed according to personal preference.
We are now passing through the U.S.
- We're passing the U.S. / - We're in the U.S.
The U.S.
That's the U.S.
(They're sitting apart but they think alike)
I can just hear him complaining now.
Oh, whatever.
I don't want to hear it.
Man! Who said it wasn't cold out here? Geez!
So many complaints.
So funny.
Do you know why there are no people up here?
I know.
Because it's rainy and cold.
They're just giving us some space.
Then you stay here alone.
Why is there a home there?
These islands are all owned by people.
Really?
Yeah, so that's why...
Soyou bought property here?
There he goes again.
Sorry about that.
I want to get off now.
I want to go back!
- ♪ Please open up ♪ / - Please listen to me!
He really never listens.
Why was I acting like that?
Did you bring your passport?
Your passport.
- Why? / - Your passport.
We're going to the U.S.
(The U.S.? Isn't this Canada?)
The island we're going to is in the U.S.
You need a passport and visa to go.
So you have to apply for a visa.
This is the U.S.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
(They arrive at the romantic Heart Island)
Let's go.
You've arrived in the U.S.?
- Yes. / - Yes.
Wow, awesome.
It's this way.
So, you use different money here?
- Only U.S. dollars. / - Dollars.
That looks like a church.
(Boldt Castle entrance fee, $19.50)
Do those small things count as islands too?
If it is, I'll buy it.
It's an island if there are at least 2 trees?
Is this American rain?
Yeah, this is American rain.
♪ American rain is falling ♪
(Disbelief)
Play my song, "In the Rain" as the background song.
You have a song called "In the Rain?"
♪ I hope that rain washes away our memories ♪
(They're about to enter Boldt Castle)
(It's like something you'd see in your fantasy)
So nice.
It doesn't seem American or Canadian.
It seems European.
What is this castle? Just for looking around in?
It's open to the public like a museum.
It's like a memorial hall.
So cool.
I bet it has some elements of the U.S. and Canada.
The person, Boldt...
- For his wife. / - He built this for his wife.
That story...
- It strikes a chord for women. / - It's romantic.
- Yes, it's romantic. / - That's so cool.
- Family... / - Boldt.
- Family suite. / - Entrance.
Oh, the family's suite.
So, this is how it used to be.
You're right.
George Boldt.
This is...
Where he slept.
They stopped construction here too.
It was like this.
- It's so pretty. / - So pretty.
So, this is...
Like the living room where the family gets together.
Where they can have coffee or tea.
This place wasn't finished either.
- There's a sad story here. / - Yeah.
It was so sad that it was sold for a dollar.
- No, it's not like that. / - His loved one died.
- So it was pointless. / - He didn't bother finishing it.
It lost its commercial value.
Wendy, do you want to go?
I feel sad.
- Where they can have coffee or tea. / - So pretty.
This place wasn't finished either.
They finished it so it looks how it would've.
They restored the 2nd floor for tourists.
And the rest of it is still unfinished.
So cool.
They didn't bother finishing this area.
It's a shame.
He never came back to this castle again.
- Boldt? / - Yes.
I passed by it before but never went inside.
They have a pool too?
Yes, there's a pool.
It says there's a pool.
They have everything.
Here it is.
They made this area into a pool.
Hey, a toad.
There's money on it.
I'll give you a coin. Give it a shot.
I'm great at stuff like this!
- Really? / - Yeah.
Give me a few more. You never know.
- You said you could do it in one try. / - Give me.
Throw it.
Oh, come on!
That isn't easy.
We spent a lot of money here.
Come on! Geez...
Come on!
- I'm getting the hang of it. / - Hey.
We definitely spent a few bucks there.
That isn't easy.
Coins.
One coin please.
This is making me mad.
He even used my money.
(His final effort)
Last one.
Good luck for Hongki!
He might end up swimming in there.
Did he get it?
It bounced out.
I guess that's a no for Hongki.
It fell in.
Move. Let me try.
I think she'll get it.
Is it that hard?
Toss it a bit far.
Good luck for Hongki.
Good luck for Hyorim.
- In one try? / - I think she'll get it.
No way.
Unbelievable.
How does that make Hongki look?
She made Hongki look silly.
She did it in one try.
I didn't expect that either.
(In one try)
Looks like I'll have good luck!
I'm so happy.
Look at Hongki!
How embarrassing!
You know what's good though?
I wished myself luck too before she threw it.
- But I threw it. / - Thanks.
How did that happen?
I'm so happy!
It's a good thing that
I said my name too before you threw it.
Don't include yourself.
I'm not.
Fine, we'll both have good luck.
- Yeah. / - Yeah.
As soon as my coin landed...
I became the queen of weather.
I still can't believe it.
I'm really lucky when it comes to weather.
So pretty!
- We should take a photo here. / - Yeah.
I'll take one.
1, 2, 3.
(Beautiful Boldt Castle)
(Goofy poses)
(The realistic siblings)
A couple shot.
Shall we stop at the gift shop?
Shall we?
All he looks at are cups.
He's obsessed with cups.
Isn't this one nice?
I'm moving house soon.
He bought a lot of cups.
Buy one as a souvenir.
They had so many pretty ones.
(Boldt Castle has a lot of nice souvenirs)
The cups all said Canada on them yesterday.
But here, they all say Boldt Castle.
Or New York.
Since you're in the U.S.
(I only have eyes for you)
A beer mug?
He seems the happiest when buying stuff.
I bought a few as gifts.
- As gifts. / - Yes.
Refrigerator magnets.
I collect those.
And international post cards.
Or if I go to museums,
I usually get a post card
of the most memorable painting.
Since you can't buy the painting.
So I always buy post cards.
I have a big stack at home.
This one's the best.
You can see the heart-shaped island.
(She picks a post card of Heart Island)
Heart-shaped.
When would we ever go to Boldt Castle.
Right.
(Bye, Heart Island)
Let's go!
(They head back to Niagara Falls)
- You're going back? / - Yes.
For 4 hours?
On the way back, the trip will seem shorter.
That's true.
- We were talking the entire way. / - Right.
Time really flew by.
I'd drive for 4 hours to go see that.
- Right. / - It's worth going to.
- I'd go there. / - You have to go.
(It's day 5 of their trip in Canada)
(The sun is still warm)
(And Niagara Falls still looks amazing)
(The current time is 8 a.m.)
Now where to?
We're going to a market.
It's Canada's biggest and oldest market.
We'll get some food...
Allow me to escort you!
Of course.
He's in a good mood again.
Drive!
- My goodness! / - Drive.
Oh, boy! Goodness!
Let's put on our seat belts.
- Let's go! / - Let's go!
(Glances)
We should've rented a supercar like those.
Are they for rent?
This is a supercar too.
Since we're going to a super market.
If you drive to the super market, it's a supercar.
They have the same sense of humor.
Supercar...
Oh, my God!
(Farmers' market)
- You're going to a market now? / - Yes.
Is it open every day like a super market?
No, it's not like that.
It's only open on Thursdays and Saturdays.
And it starts at 7 a.m. and closes at 3 p.m.
- It closes early. / - Yes.
- It closes at 3 p.m.? / - That's what made it tough.
It all closes so early, so we had to wake up early.
- Since it opens early. / - Yes.
(The market is an hour and 40 minutes away)
We're here!
Is this it?
That way.
All the specialties that can be found in this area...
It's a huge market that sells all that.
We can pick out street food...
- And sit over there. / - Whenever I travel...
- I always go to the market. / - Right.
- It's so much fun. / - Yes.
- This is... / - It's like Moran Market.
It's like Moran Market.
It is not.
I go to markets like this often when I travel.
I hear there's a lot of good stuff to eat.
What's that? Clothes hangers?
Yeah.
And they have guitars, Hongki.
Oh, they have stuff like this too.
These are handmade.
Yeah, they're all handmade.
People made them at home and brought them.
Right.
- Let's get some food. I'm hungry. / - Alright.
It's your favorite. Syrup.
- Where? / - There.
Where?
I was saving that to have with meat.
- Drink it all in one shot. / - Canadian whiskey?
Yeah, Canadian whiskey.
Gosh, it's sweet!
- Whiskey for Hongki. / - I have to buy a bottle.
- This will make a great gift. / - Maple syrup.
Let's pick out some food first.
Then we'll get your whiskey.
- It's so pretty and nice in here. / - Yeah.
There was so much good food there.
(Food that you can see in any other countries)
Pizza.
(As well as unique dishes you've never heard of)
- I'm hungry. / - Let's pick what we want to eat.
So much food.
- Look at those sausages. / - Should I get chicken?
- Chicken? / - Yeah
How's that sound?
You get what you want.
- I'm getting chicken. / - Alright.
It's chicken.
Is it not?
Fried apples.
(Fried apples!)
That's really famous.
- They fry apples? / - What is that?
- And it's eaten with ice cream. / - This is a first.
It's so delicious.
I kept thinking of it when I got back to Korea.
(Apple fritter with ice cream, $5.40)
I want that for dessert.
I'll go get something else.
- We split up. / - Stay here.
She went to get that apple fritter
and he went for chicken.
- There has to be chicken in that big place. / - Yes.
Why isn't there any chicken?
I don't see what I want to buy.
He really likes chicken.
Man, I'm hungry.
(Staring)
Oh, that's chicken.
(And there are two different kinds)
Spicy chicken.
(Fried chicken and two sides!)
(He does a happy chicken dance)
(Pleased)
(He successfully gets some chicken)
Another mood swing.
There he goes again.
- He's happy again. / - He's happy again.
One dozen please.
- How cute! / - Donuts.
- And I got pizza. / - That pizza looks good.
The pizza was delicious.
(Huh? Why flowers?)
I got flowers!
- You can't bring that back. / - Did you eat them?
No, when you stay in the hotel...
- The scent? / - If you have flowers...
It feels like a cozy home.
She's a romantist.
(They have a nice brunch in the nice weather)
- That looks so good! / - It was delicious.
I want to try that.
I found the chicken.
I like having a lot of different dishes.
But we already have so much food.
Did I buy too much?
All I bought was one thing.
Gosh...
She bought way too much food.
- You have to taste each one. / - No.
- Right. / - You did a good job.
You want to try a bunch of stuff.
You have to taste everything.
Sure!
Hongki's getting yelled at.
(Chicken noodles and rice, $6.70)
(The familiar smell of chicken)
This is a great idea.
These 3 dishes come with rice.
From before...
Look how much he's eating.
He likes it.
(Chicken has never let him down)
You have to try this.
- This is... / - It's Thai food.
It's not Thai. It's Chinese.
It's kind of like Chinese food.
- Chinese food in Canada? / - Right.
It's perfect!
(Perfect for his immature taste buds)
- I found this for you. / - Smoked chicken.
(Hyorim bought some chicken for picky Hongki)
- That looks good. / - That's the real deal...
- That's what you should've gotten. / - Looks great.
(Smoked chicken)
They asked how spicy I want it.
I bet that's delicious.
I bet it is.
- This is good. / - The sauce is really good.
The sauce has some heat to it.
It's something I've never tried in Korea.
- This? / - Yeah.
BBQ Chicken has this flavor!
No, it's a bit different.
The spicy smoked chicken from BBQ Chicken
tastes just like this.
He hates losing arguments.
They serve their drumsticks like this?
- Yeah, just like this. / - Not the fried kind?
They have smog chicken too.
Oh, really?
This is smog chicken.
Smoked.
It's smoked. Not smog.
- Smog is something different. / - Right.
This is really famous.
- The line was really long. / - Yeah, I saw.
It's a fried apple,
drizzled with maple syrup.
That's a fried apple?
- I want to try that! / - I want to try that too.
- I want that. / - With some ice cream.
- I really want to try that. / - The fried apple...
That was a great combination.
- That looks so good. / - It was delicious...
- That I ate another one. / - That looks great.
- It's kind of unique. / - Yeah.
I've never seen this before.
Gosh, I think it'll be too sweet.
I love sweets.
It's not that sweet.
- Not as sweet as it looks. / - It's really crispy too.
(I'm not a big fan)
The ice cream and maple syrup are sweet...
But the apple inside tastes fresh.
Totally different from an apple pie.
(So, Hyorim)
Isn't that dessert though?
I don't care about that stuff.
I'll eat everything.
- I bet it's good. / - I don't understand that either.
This is how I am.
I have trouble understanding
unimaginable combinations.
That's why I'm not too big on sushi.
- What? / - Why not?
Really?
I love eating just raw fish,
but when you combine that with rice...
I just don't understand that union.
Just like that, I don't understand this union.
The apple has been fried
and you're eating it with ice cream.
I don't get why Hongki doesn't like that stuff.
There's nothing I can't eat.
You two seem like siblings.
What are we doing after we eat?
Something you'll like.
We're going to a winery.
Canada is known for icewine.
I shouldn't get drunk on TV.
- Let's go! / - Let's go!
You can do wine tasting there.
- Right. / - Yes, you can.
(An hour and 40 minutes back to Niagara Falls)
I prepared a private and special event
just for you.
We're not just going on the Niagara tour.
If you spend a bit more...
This is a tour that even locals don't know about.
We're going to the winery.
Yeah.
So to make it private...
(What's that?)
We're taking that helicopter?
Yeah, we're taking a helicopter to the winery.
We took a helicopter tour
over Niagara Falls.
But if you spend a bit more,
it'll drop you off in front of the winery.
- Really? / - Yes.
- The helicopter? / - Yes.
We got ourselves a private helicopter.
The private helicopter tour costs $280 per person.
(Starting point, Niagara Falls, winery)
This should be fun.
Wow, the wind...
I've never been this close to a helicopter.
Let's go!
(Bet you've never taken a helicopter to a winery)
(Wow, exciting)
Whoa!
Wow!
It's not that noisy.
You don't have to wear headsets?
It's a new model, so it's not that loud.
You don't have to cover your ears.
- Yet you can hear everything. / - That's awesome.
- So that's a nice helicopter. / - Yes.
(Excited)
That's really scary.
It feels great to fly.
(Wow)
(To icewine)
(They can see Niagara Falls out the window)
Wow, amazing!
That's so nice.
The view from above is way different.
Of course.
You can take in the entire view.
We saw it from every angle.
Wow, that's so nice.
Now we'll tour the falls
and then head to the winery.
- Oh, really? / - Yeah.
What a special course.
Right.
Look, that's the U.S.
- That's the U.S.? / - Yeah.
(Canada, U.S.)
- That's the U.S. / - We were in American sky.
Look at that. That river is so windy.
- Right? / - Yeah.
Amazing...
And crossing the border by bridge
is kind of amazing to us Koreans.
This looks amazing.
Wow! There's the waterfall.
(How will Niagara Falls look from the helicopter?)
(They saw the Niagara Falls by boat last time)
- Now you'll see it from above. / - Yes.
We'll see it again from above.
This is amazing.
I can't see in front of me!
Wow...
So pretty.
Gosh, this is so pretty!
The mist...
Wow, amazing.
This is made naturally.
Here we go, here we go.
(Time to enjoy the view of Niagara Falls from the sky)
Now from the sky.
What a sight.
It was like a painting.
An amazing sight.
Isn't that the U.S.?
Yes, that's Bridal Falls.
And that's Canada.
Canada's waterfall is bigger.
- And the shape is pretty too. / - You're right.
(Her heart races at the new sights)
(He makes a big deal over nothing)
(As we whistle over Niagara Falls)
It's so different seeing it from above.
The river flows down there.
That's right before the waterfall.
Wow, amazing!
(They fly towards the endless flowing water)
Hey, we were on that boat last time.
Everything I look at is so refreshing! This is great.
This is great, Hyorim.
- Right? / - Yeah.
- Now he finally admits it. / - For the first time.
Now we're going to the winery.
You take the tour and go right to the winery?
- It drops you off there like a taxi. / - Awesome.
- Such a great course. / - Like a taxi.
How long does it take to get to the winery?
- Around 20 minutes. / - 20 to 30 minutes.
It looks like a separate house or a farm.
(Where they'll get off)
Oh, so here it is.
- How do you get off? / - Where will you land?
I don't see anywhere to land.
- Just on the grass? / - Just on the grass.
(The helicopter landed right in front of the winery)
So cool.
Not a lot of people come by helicopter.
So everyone comes out of the winery to see it.
- It's like special treatment. / - You feel like a big shot.
Right.
I want to take a helicopter to go drinking too.
"What did you do yesterday?"
I just took a helicopter to get some wine.
You need a helicopter to get some wine.
Wow!
(Feeling great)
Wow, this is great!
Hongki's happy.
(Another person is excited)
Hurry up!
(That's enough of that)
Geez, you're so silly.
(Hahaha)
I love this.
- This is it? / - Yeah.
(Trip to the small cities in Canada)
(Icewine winery)
- It's a luxurious trip with the helicopter. / - Right.
This was unexpected.
(Niagara-on-the-Lake)
(A quiet and small city by the lake)
(A big vineyard near Lake Ontario)
(A beautiful village with nature and wine)
- It's real ice. / - Wow, look at that ice.
They have an ice room.
(Niagara-on-the-Lake)
There's a special place where you can sample wine.
- What is it? / - You'll see.
- I'll see? / - Yeah, you'll see.
Don't be shocked.
I've never been to an icewine winery like that.
- I'm Dylan. / - Dylan!
- Nice to meet you. / - Nice to meet you too.
- Already? / - Thank you.
Our Vidal Icewine infused into the bottle.
(He pops the cork like magic)
It's rose.
We used 100% of the grapes from Ontario.
Cheers.
It smells like champagne.
(Hey! Hey!)
- What? / - She can't stop!
She likes it.
I turn red even after one drink.
- So I shouldn't drink. / - Yeah, you don't drink.
But the wine was so good, I kept drinking.
(So delicious that she chugs it down)
You don't need a straw?
It's so good!
This is so good!
- This is good. / - I like it.
(Now it's time to tour the winery)
(Roses at the entrance of the vineyard)
Roses.
They're bigger than my fist.
There's a reason why that rose bush is there.
Rose bushes are really important to a vineyard.
- Oh... / - Because...
A rose is susceptible to disease
and insects very easily.
So if there's anything wrong
with the rose bush...
Questions 1 through 17 are English listening.
Listen carefully and answer the questions.
It really felt like an English exam.
Workers know that there's a risk to the vines
and can take action quickly
before the grapes are damaged.
These are pretty...
It's the Canadian mentality.
(He can't believe he just said that)
- The roses are weak... / - Easily.
But they plant roses here because
the roses are the first to react if there are any pests.
So this shows the condition of the vineyard.
Workers know that there’s a risk to the vines...
The roses are the first to react if there are any pests.
And can take action quickly
before the grapes are damaged.
So this shows the condition of the vineyard.
They look very healthy.
So the vineyard must be healthy too.
So everything here should be healthy.
Yeah, that's right. No pests.
Say it in English.
Let's go!
Don't make me speak English.
My mind goes blank when I try to speak English.
- Grape? / - Yes.
It's growing.
- Those are grapes. / - Still babies.
I had no idea that wine was famous in Canada
before I did research for this trip.
I heard that icewine was famous here.
Icewine...
- It looks like "Frozen." / - Right?
So it keeps freezing and thawing.
Wow, I bet it's delicious.
So, for icewine...
You drink it with ice in them like iced Americano.
So, is icewine cold wine?
No, it's not like that.
Icewine can be drank cold.
But the best temperature is 7 to 8 degrees.
- So that it's chilled. / - Chilled.
All these barrels are filled with wine?
A little wine in here?
Actually, the equivalent of 300 bottles of wine in each.
Wow, there is wine in these barrels.
We have to wear this.
- Isn't this a Canadian brand? / - Yeah.
You have to put on a coat to try the wine.
Is this a gift?
In a way.
Because you're going to want to be wearing that.
We're going into our 10 below icewine lounge.
And it is -10℃ in there.
- Ice room? / - Yeah, an ice room.
It's -10℃ in there.
You have to wear one then. Wow, this is crazy.
So this is why you said this was special.
-10℃ since it's icewine.
(Where will they taste icewine?)
Look at her face. Great reaction from both of them.
- I didn't want to come out. / - So nice.
Yeah! This is what I said was famous!
They're frozen in ice.
- They're in the ice. / - Yes.
Is that real ice?
I'm starting to sober up.
It's really cold.
(Everything is ice)
We carved it out of 30,000 pounds of ice.
We have to rebuild it about every 2 years.
Cold!
Very cold.
But the perfect spot to try...
- Our signature series Vidal Icewine. / - I like this!
(How would it taste?)
- So, because it taste sweet... / - More, more.
- That's the famous one, right? / - Yes.
More, more, more.
Let's start with one and go from there.
So...
- Cheers. / - When you drink this...
Because you taste sweetness...
This is what I'm talking about! I love this stuff!
He's excited now.
Hongki is finally happy after 3 episodes.
Don't drink it all at once. Sip it.
From your tongue.
He's good at doing what he's told.
He likes it.
That's what I'm talking about!
- This is it! / - You said you don't like sweets.
But this is wine.
- Is it different? / - Of course.
There's honey in alcohol!
It's not honey.
The grapes are just really sweet.
(I love wine)
Hongki's finally showing some reactions.
- Like a baby that was just fed. / - That stuff...
It's the best wine.
The sweetness differs depending on the vintage.
The one on the wall over there.
During winter 2013, it was so cold
that we measured the highest possible sugar content
in grapes.
From 2013?
They were able to make 1,500 bottles.
- It's incredible... / - It must be really expensive.
It's very difficult to turn it into wine.
(Limited edition icewine)
- 1,500 bottles. / - You can try that too?
- Limited edition. / - No, not that one.
You have to buy a bottle.
- Can I buy? / - Yes.
- How much? How much? / - Really?
$500.
- Around $500. / - $500? Are you serious?
If they sold that in Korea, they'd charge like $1,000.
Of course.
It's good.
It's really good.
(He has another glass)
Thank you.
Man, it's cold.
- This is so nice. / - Let's get out of here.
Just wait. Let me taste my wine.
Then I'm leaving first.
It's cold!
- I can't take this anymore. / - He's not happy anymore.
Fine, I'll join you after I finish mine.
- You should keep drinking. / - You should've waited!
- No, it was nice and quiet. / - He should've stayed.
It was nice to get some alone time.
It's so nice and quiet without Hongki.
My gosh, it's raining.
See? I told you so.
- Call a cab. / - Yeah, we should.
Old Town...
Done.
Hello.
(Going to downtown Niagara-on-the-Lake)
(It looks like old England)
So pretty.
Where is this place?
This is Niagara-on-the-Lake.
- It was the former capital of Canada. / - It was?
If you go there,
you can experience Canada and Europe.
You can experience the UK.
- And you can go to the U.S. / - That's great.
(Very European due to British colonization)
There are many British-style buildings here.
I heard this hotel is really famous.
(They see an old hotel along the path)
- That's a hotel? / - Yes.
Queen Elizabeth II visited here during Victorian era.
Let's check out this pretty hotel.
(Victorian style interior from 18th century England)
Very antique looking.
It's really like England.
I feel like I'm in England.
(They'll enjoy some afternoon tea)
I went to London recently.
This is kind of like that.
This place... Is so...
I feel like we shouldn't be noisy here.
I feel like we have to sit here quietly.
In the UK, they have afternoon tea
for 3 hours after their meal.
I first learned about afternoon tea here.
- What? / - Afternoon tea.
Afternoon tea...
- Is very old tea drinking custom in England. / - Right.
Korea is too used to doing everything fast.
So we eat and go...
- But they take their time abroad. / - Right.
They chat for 2 hours. So they keep giving you tea.
- You get tea refills. / - Like pouring you booze.
The teapot is this big.
(Relaxing on a lazy afternoon with a cup of tea)
You drink that tea after lunch...
- And drink slowly for 3 hours... / - Look at that.
As you talk and enjoy yourselves.
- With scones. / - Scones.
Gosh, look at that.
(The food is a treat for the eyes)
They do it just like they do in England...
- Because of British colonization. / - Eating all of that?
- All 3 tiers? / - Right.
- You have to eat that. / - Of course.
People that enjoy that practice
tend to eat light lunch like a salad...
- To save room for that. / - For that.
(How will afternoon tea in Canada be?)
This is the signature tea of this hotel.
Afternoon tea is usually enjoyed
with tea and champagne.
- This is black tea. / - Yeah.
- Look how big the teapot is. / - You're right.
When you first taste it, it tastes like red chili paste.
- Chili paste? / - It tastes like chili paste to me.
It does kind of smell like that.
It was a bit spicy.
Slightly spicy.
With afternoon tea, you start from the bottom.
1, 2, 3. That's the order.
She sounds cute when she talks,
but she's scary when she eats.
Is this apple pie?
No, they're also sandwiches.
It's a sandwich made with pie crust.
They don't usually do this.
What a devious sandwich.
- Why? / - It's dressed like a pie.
Geez...
Hongki loves lame dad jokes now.
It's dressed like a pie.
(She hates it)
This sandwich is dressed like a pie.
Oh, brother...
- Should we try some? / - Start from the bottom.
(Time to really enjoy their afternoon tea)
That sure looks good.
The ones on top look the best.
Yes, so you start with the savory ones.
I always have afternoon tea
at least twice when I travel.
They usually use plain bread to make sandwiches.
- But they used pie crusts here. / - Just this place?
Yeah, I've never seen this before.
(Nom)
What's this?
I've never tried this before.
- What's that inside? / - What's that filling?
- I see something inside. / - Cream?
- It's tuna... / - Tuna salad?
They're stuffed with tuna salad.
They mixed up some tuna
with mayo and vegetables.
This is good.
(She moves onto the next sandwich!)
(She really starts chowing down)
(Killing the first tier all by herself)
Do you do 1,000 push-ups in your hotel room
after finishing that?
I love bread.
How do you not gain weight?
Bread really suits me.
(Tier 2, scones)
Scones are delicious!
Seulgi is already on our side.
I'm really tempted.
(Tier 2, scones)
You can judge a place on
their afternoon tea by how good their scones are.
We can't stop eating.
The scones were delicious.
- Afternoon tea... / - Wow, that butter...
- Is all about scones. / - For real.
Scones determine whether that place
does good afternoon tea or not.
- Scones are very high in calories. / - Yes.
But they're so delicious.
- You tend to eat more with tea. / - Right.
- Take a bite and take a sip. / - Right.
(A scone with plenty of butter, jam and cream)
That looks good though.
This scone is delicious.
The scone is so soft.
It only shows Hyorim eating.
I think Hongki is already full.
- Was he even there next to you? / - Back then...
I was just waiting for her to finish eating.
I get to experience all sorts of stuff thanks to you.
When guys travel together...
You'd never do this.
It's not even that.
We wouldn't know a place like this even exists.
For real.
- True, guys don't really know. / - That's true.
- Guys don't know. / - We don't.
Because I'm with you,
I know about this 3-story building...
Oops...
These 3 levels of food.
Right.
(This sure tastes yummy)
(Tier 3, sweets and desserts)
- Let's hurry up and finish this. / - Alright.
Man, I feel like you've been eating for 3 hours.
(Disbelief)
You shouldn't lie on TV.
He kept complaining that I took 3 hours.
It felt like 3 hours to me.
She made it to the top all by herself.
She made it to the third floor.
This place sure is cute though.
Even that street was so pretty.
- There aren't that many people. / - Yes.
I want to buy a cup like this.
Wow, what a pretty hat.
This place is packed.
- Let's go inside. / - I love hat shops like this.
(Hyorim loves hats)
This place is great!
You might be stuck in there forever.
- You'll ruin your schedule. / - I love hats.
They had hats that English nobility would wear.
When Prince Harry got married recently,
the guests wore hats that went like this.
Hats like that.
- Like the ones with veils? / - Right.
This hat is so comfortable.
Where did Hongki go?
Huh?
Wow, I love visors like this.
Gosh, where is that hat?
The one the model is wearing...
Wow!
So many different hats.
- It looks nice. / - You look good in anything.
- They suit you. / - You look good in hats.
Goodness...
- This one's so pretty. / - This one is pretty.
Right? I'm getting this.
- This is nice. / - Yeah.
(How long are we going to look at hats?)
- This one's nice. / - Yeah.
Hongki is starting to get impatient.
Men just wear baseball caps...
I'm going to check out some plates
at a different shop.
Alright.
He's going on his own.
- This is when you should split up. / - Right.
I need to look around more.
I want plates.
I saw some earlier.
I should've came here sooner.
- It's closed. / - Yes.
Did you say it closes at 3?
Too bad.
(He looks sad from behind)
This place closes early.
We took too long for afternoon tea.
- You spent the entire afternoon. / - For real.
It's so sad when you want to buy something
but the place is closed.
And you have to leave the next day.
All they sell is alcohol.
(Any cups in there?)
I know that feeling.
(He can't seem to walk away)
(He goes back to the hat shop after looking around)
- I went back. / - Poor guy.
What is it?
She's still in there?
Oh, me?
(She's still checking out hats)
I need to buy something special.
Geez...
I was in there for about an hour.
- I got one. / - That one?
- Yeah, this one. / - Oh!
- How cute! / - That's a case?
It looks nice.
- You're lying. / - No, it looks nice.
- It does? / - Yeah. It's nice.
A waste of money though.
Let's go.
Did you wait long?
- Sorry. / - I was going to buy one too...
But I have a lot of similar ones.
Really?
(Trip to the small cities in Canada)
(Famous local restaurant)
A friend of mine in Canada
recommended this restaurant.
- It looks like Japan. / - We're here to eat.
It really does look like Japan.
It was very unfamiliar for us too.
(Looking around)
I think this is the entrance.
- There's no entrance. / - For real.
- Where's the entrance? / - What is this?
- That's a restaurant? / - Yes.
We used the GPS to find it.
There's nobody there.
- We found it on the map. / - We kept looking.
- Isn't that it? / - I think it's here.
Isn't that a door?
I think this is it.
Someone came out.
(The door opens)
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Fine, how are you? / - Good, thanks.
- This is nice. / - How are you doing?
Good.
- It looks empty. / - I was shocked.
What is it?
- Wow. / - Wow, what is this?
(A place loved by locals and tourists)
You will be shocked.
They raise the animals very ethically
for their dishes.
That's what it said there.
They grow their own vegetables...
- They grow everything? / - It was organic.
This is pretty cool.
- It's pretty. / - That's what it looks like inside.
This is cool.
It was so quiet outside, but it's packed inside.
- The door was hard to find. / - What is this?
I bet it was very new.
So many people here.
This place has a twist.
When you're outside...
It's so different from outside.
How is this possible?
Did they open this place secretly?
Secretly...
From the outside...
- It didn't look like a restaurant. / - Right.
- This is cool. / - Yeah.
(Time to pick something from the menu!)
Look at this.
This place is hot these days.
(Even the menu looks cool)
This is so funny. This dish is called Dip-dip Egg.
Oh, I heard this is really good.
Dip-dip Egg.
Let's order something new.
No chicken this time?
(Deliberating)
Don't order chicken, Hongki.
I want the chicken.
(Chicken again?)
- Please... / - Geez...
Oh, my God.
- I want the chicken. / - Chicken...
(Pleased)
Don't they have any chicken?
(Hongki's love of chicken was seen last time)
(Chicken makes Hongki happy)
What's wrong with me? Geez...
Try some other stuff, Hongki. Please...
I even had spicy chicken stew today.
He really loves chicken.
(The first dish comes out)
(He brought a wine glass)
(Fills up the glass)
- That was delicious. / - What is that?
It was a drink before the meal.
It's an alcoholic beverage that piques the appetite.
This is so neat.
This is icewine.
- It's alcohol? / - Yes...
- A cocktail? / - It's wine.
- It's wine? / - Icewine?
Yes.
That looks so good!
- Isn't this... / - Raspberry sorbet.
That's raspberry sorbet.
This is icewine?
But it wasn't too strong. It was delicious.
It was so good.
I could've kept drinking that if it wasn't for the shoot.
(Mm)
Mix it up?
Do you mix it up or just drink it?
- I wasn't sure either. / - Mix it up?
This comes with a spoon.
Oh, you're supposed to mix it up?
I have no idea either. It's my first time here.
I'm not sure.
Icewine is supposed to be a dessert wine.
But since we already had wine,
this will be a drink before our meal.
(That's the stuff)
In one gulp.
(Delicious)
This is what this tastes like.
It tastes like they melted frozen icewine.
- It's like a slushy. / - Yeah.
It's different from the icewine we had earlier.
That's so unique.
I got really into wine on this trip.
This is good.
What is this?
(Their appetizers come out)
- That. / - What is this?
(A nest?)
- What's that? / - Dip-dip Egg.
- What's that? / - This is?
It's Dip-dip Egg.
- This is Dip-dip Egg? / - Dip-dip Egg.
Gosh!
So, you dip something in there?
It has dipping sauce in it.
You dip your bread into that.
(Dip the bread into the egg)
- That brioche looks great. / - It's a sauce?
- It was delicious. / - So good.
What's in that egg?
- It's egg. / - They mixed something with runny yolk.
(Amazing)
It doesn't seem like egg,
but it tastes like egg.
I don't think anyone that tries this
will say it tastes bad.
Definitely.
So thoughtful.
Such pretty plating.
- It was so good. / - Truly.
Whoever says this tastes bad is an idiot.
It has to be good if Hongki says it is.
(Off to a great start so far)
This is good.
(The meal is just beginning)
If the appetizer is good...
- The expectation for the main dish rises. / - Right.
(Fish steak)
They were all good.
(Chicken steak)
(Beef steak)
Wow, they're here.
Fish.
That fish looks delicious.
Such clean plating.
(A white fish fillet is first fried in oil)
- What's that? / - All their food...
- Is cooked in a brick oven. / - A brick oven?
- Then it's grilled in the pan again? / - Yes, again.
That looks so good.
That looks good.
(Seared twice in the pan, baked once in the oven)
(To make the fish more firm)
(The fish steak is moist and firm)
- That looks delicious. / - It's a bit rare.
I don't think we'll need a knife.
I ordered this fish.
This is like one bite.
I was a bit surprised.
- That's so small. / - It's too small.
(Watch)
One bite.
Done.
That's pretty pricy then.
That's not a big portion.
- But the thing is... / - It turns out...
They gave us half portions of each...
- Thinking that we'd share. / - They split it up.
(That's why)
No wonder it looked so small.
I thought something went wrong,
but they split up the portions.
- Yum, this is delicious. / - It really is.
- So good. / - This is good.
Here it comes.
- That one was great too. / - It was so good!
- That's chicken? / - But it was stuffed...
- That's new. / - Yes.
- What is it? / - It was stuffed chicken.
(Nom)
This smells great.
I like how the outside is crispy.
They stuffed this chicken breast with tender meat.
The chicken was rolled up.
You know the tender part? That was on the outside
and the dry meat was stuffed in the inside.
So they wrapped the chicken breast.
- So that entire thing is chicken? / - Yes.
That looks so good.
Seulgi's so cute. She keeps saying "I want to try that."
- "That looks good." / - It looks so good...
"I want to try that."
I love the sauce. It's like peanut sauce.
I don't really like chicken...
I prefer the veggies served on the side
over this chicken.
The vegetables are cooked so nicely.
You should like this one.
(Sirloin steak, $40.80)
Sirloin?
(Sauce to make it taste better)
What sauce is this?
The sauce is bearnaise sauce.
(Made of egg, butter and herbs like hollandaise)
(This sauce goes great with meat)
It looks fattening.
The sauce looks delicious.
(Yum)
Thank you.
(She cuts a piece and tries a bite)
This meat is so tender.
It's not tough at all.
(The steak is delicious because it's been aged)
I love when meat is this texture.
This is a unique sauce.
The sauce is the color of mustard.
- All those food go well with wine, right? / - Yes.
It's near a winery.
That's why a lot of places around there...
There are a lot of restaurants that sell
dishes that go great with wine.
I don't really like steak that much.
But this steak is so tender.
For real.
- More than Korea. / - I really enjoyed this steak...
But it seemed more like smoked meat.
I don't know if I should even call this a steak.
Steak has that slightly charred taste.
But this meat is really tender.
- So it's like ham? / - Yes, like it was smoked.
Since we're full from eating, how about a walk?
You need to digest.
I heard this neighborhood
has a lot of cute shops, so let's check them out.
Alright.
This is almost like a date.
If you cut off the audio, you two seem like a couple.
But all you two do is fight.
- Fighting and complaining. / - Right.
If you cut off the audio, you two seem like a couple.
(The highlight of their trip)
(Enjoying some cold beer outdoors at a brewery)
This is a brewery.
Yeah, they make beer here.
(This pub is already pretty packed at 9 p.m.)
This is so nice.
(Enjoying a live performance on their last night)
I love that we're out in nature like this.
- Being outdoors like this? / - Yeah.
- I love this. / - This is nice.
I want to build a place like this too.
(A brewery with a vineyard nearby)
Wendy, stop scowling. Are you okay?
She's just really impressed.
I want to go too.
I love that atmosphere.
A vineyard right behind you as you have beer?
- With a performance. / - They kept performing.
- It was wonderful. / - That look so nice.
It's so pretty.
- I want to build a place like this too. / - It's so nice.
I like this.
I love this sort of thing.
(Getting into it)
(This is so nice)
(Time for some cold beer)
(There's something unique about this brewery)
They make their own beer here.
Did you see the tank earlier?
That's where they make the beer.
(They make beer in barrels from wineries)
It's craft beer.
(Special beer you can try at a winery)
($5.60, $3.80, $5.60, $5,60)
How strong are they?
- Well... / - They're a bit strong.
Which one was the best?
I liked one of the dark one.
I'd get the IPA.
One of the dark was strong.
The dark one was strong.
Man, I want beer now.
This one is dark in color, but it's sour like a candy.
- Really? / - It's sour.
The flavor is...
(Hongki is the first one to try it)
- What's with the face? / - Is it good?
No, there are two dark ones.
There were two?
(Tart)
How is it?
- How is it? / - What was that?
- What? / - Try it!
It tastes very unique.
- You're downing it all again? / - Look at her eyes!
She looks scary with her eyes like that!
It's like lemon soda.
It's very tart.
This one's really interesting.
The carbonation really has some bite to it.
- I feel like this will aid digestion. / - Yeah.
This doesn't seem like beer.
This one's really different.
(They try the other beers)
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
(Hongki loves this sweet and bitter ale)
It's good because it's craft beer and it's draft beer.
(Draft beer is always the best)
(Delicious)
It's over now.
Yeah.
(Pouting out of sorrow)
I had a great trip thanks to you.
Of course, we mostly did stuff that you like.
But it wasn't so bad!
I got to learn a lot about Canada.
This place is very different
from the Canada I had in mind.
Especially this neighborhood.
I felt two things on this trip to Canada.
First, it was the nature.
Canada's nature is amazing.
And the feeling that everyone is so respectful.
Even if you speak a different language,
everyone seemed very friendly.
The only thing I knew about Canada
before coming here was the Niagara Falls.
And this is eastern Canada.
All the small cities and towns
were so charming.
I was jealous of that helicopter ride.
- A trip like this... / - Great work.
- Thanks! / - It must've been tough following me.
How nice.
(Realistic Sibling Tour ends here!)
(Totally satisfied)
- I was amazed by the helicopter scene. / - Me too.
Some people might be nervous about a helicopter,
but they have the latest model, so it's a comfy ride.
That feeling when you get off...
- Like you're royalty. / - How much was it?
6 people is the fixed number.
We did a lap around Niagara Falls
and then it dropped us off in front of the winery.
That's $280 per person.
What costs $120?
- Just touring the Niagara Falls. / - So that's $120?
- But it doesn't fly you back. / - It's one-way.
A helicopter tour of the Grand Canyon
was $500 per person.
The helicopter tour of the Rocky Mountains
was $900 per person.
The winery tour is one-way...
- And it's not as far. / - Right.
You won't get bored.
So it's between $120 to $280.
- It seems worth the investment. / - Of course.
- You might as well. / - When else would you go?
Time for us to find out the total cost.
Let's see how much they spent.
Canada is a bit pricy, isn't it?
- No. / - Really?
- Not as much as you'd think. / - Not like Austria.
You rented a car, went on a helicopter ride...
I don't think it'll be a low cost.
Let's see it.
- We were there for 6 days... / - 6 days.
- And we spent a total of... / - How much?
For 6 days?
$1,315.30.
$1,300?
$1,300.
- Including the helicopter ride? / - Yes.
- So in a day... / - Including the hotel rooms.
- So you spent $300 a day. / - Including the hotel?
The hotel wasn't that expensive.
I think we can win with this.
If you don't do this stuff when you're in Canada...
- You're going to regret it. / - Right.
Let's see the final votes.
- Please be good to us. / - Please help us out.
Realistic Sibling Tour...
Would you go to Canada or not? Cast your votes!
(They designed a trip to a country they'd want to live in)
(What will the judges think?)
Do we have the result?
Don't show us yet!
You should show us.
No...
Can you just show me?
The number should be high.
I can't tell by Sikyung's reaction.
I think they got a lot of votes.
I'm on his team and I can't even tell.
- I can't tell. / - He seems flustered.
- His acting really improved. / - No.
We got a lot of votes this time.
We got a lot more than he expected.
They look worried.
Such poor acting.
- We have your votes... / - I'm worried.
We got a lot.
- And this is the total. / - A lot of people didn't move.
You didn't get many last time.
See? We got a lot.
- We got a lot. / - We got this!
But this...
Just how many votes will you give us then?
With this many votes...
- I have no idea what will happen. / - I'm worried.
(Next episode)
(Trip to the small cities in Austria)
It's like I'm in a fairy tale.
- I love just walking here. / - Yeah.
It reminds me of the scenes from the movie.
- Wendy... / - And Seulgi!
Digidigidip Tour!
(They'll try the sweets of Austria)
It's so pretty.
You have to try this.
(Flying through the skies of Salzburg)
This is so much fun!
I'm flying!
Oh, my.
(Battle Trip)
("Touch &amp; Sketch" by Leo)