(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Hwijae, special guest, Lee Teuk)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Look who's here.
Today, we have a special host,
Lee Teuk of Super Junior.
Hello, I'm Lee Teuk.
We've been waiting for you.
I'm so excited to see you guys again.
I was in the first episode of Battle Trip.
- You appeared on our first episode. / - Yes.
- The first episode was disastrous. / - It was.
- I went on a one-day trip... / - It was a long time ago.
With Henry.
- And it was literally disastrous. / - It really was.
They restored the drama set.
There was nothing when I went there
but it is a famous tourist attraction now.
- You should go to Taebaek again. / - With Kyuhyun.
I've been to Taebaek, so I'll go somewhere else.
(Please send me somewhere else)
- Alright then. / - And I'm glad to be here...
- Again on the 100th episode. / - That's right.
So this is our 100th episode.
This is the 100th episode special.
(Battle Trip's 100th episode)
Thank you.
- We should thank our viewers. / - We're very grateful.
Thank you so much.
So, we have the theme
for the 100th episode of Battle Trip.
I think people say this a lot when they're on a trip.
- What is it? / - We mostly go on short trips.
- Yes. It's short. / - That's right.
We usually feel that we want to live there for a bit.
You must've thought that at least once.
So here's today's theme.
It's the countries we'd want to live in.
That sounds great.
This is the new travel trend.
People go on a trip to a country they'd want to live in.
Many European tourists go to Southeast Asia
to live there for a couple of months.
Yeah, they do that.
- 6 to 7 weeks. / - I was surprised to hear that.
I couldn't believe they could take 2 months off.
But now, it is something we can do.
Living overseas for a month.
- That's the trend these days. / - That sounds great.
I'm so envious. I wonder who went on this trip?
We should be going to these sort of trips.
I know.
So, today's trip designers
went there for months?
They just had the experience.
- Right. / - They just experienced it.
So, today's theme is the countries we'd want to live in.
I wonder which countries we're going to today.
Here come the four trip designers for today.
(Who are the trip designers?)
(Seulgi and Wendy of Red Velvet)
(Seo Hyorim, Lee Honggi of FTISLAND)
Hello.
I know Wendy and Seulgi are good
but Hyorim is the best.
- She loves traveling. / - She's an expert.
She's a travel expert.
And she eats a lot.
She does eat a lot.
- I'm actually... / - Really?
Thinking about becoming a real trip designer
for a living.
- What's wrong, Honggi? / - He doesn't agree.
- I think... / - I'm just thinking.
Some people might have the same taste as her,
and some people don't.
You can't do this from the beginning.
So, what's your team name?
It's the Realistic Sibling Tour.
- Realistic Sibling Tour? / - Real siblings?
- It means they fight a lot. / - Right.
I put up with her so much.
You did?
I did the same thing.
Alright then.
Meanwhile, Seulgi and Wendy are of the same age.
They were both born in 1994.
- Right. / - 1994.
We were born in 1994.
We traveled
with our members a few times before.
We've always wanted to travel just us.
But it was our first time.
It was very fun.
- Did you like it? / - Yes.
Do you think you'll win?
- We're very confident. / - I'm sure we will win.
Besides winning or losing,
our trip will be very fun.
- That's it. / - That's what we need, Honggi.
It has to be fun.
- That's all we need. / - You'll see...
What happens
when a sibling goes on a trip together.
- That's right. / - It's a real trip.
We hit the ceiling there.
Red Velvet is good at everything for sure,
except for this.
They aren't funny.
- Oh, no. / - But...
- That's a dangerous comment. / - That's not true.
We had a lot of fun
when we went on the trip.
Since we had fun,
the viewers will have fun watching it.
- That's right. / - How could he say that to them?
We're going to watch these clips soon.
I wonder which country they'd want to live in.
- I'm curious. / - Which country did you travel to?
It's the country I'd want to live in as
I breathe in clean air in Mother Nature's bosom.
Canada!
- I hear it's a good country. / - Good choice.
It's the country of Mother Nature
with the Rocky Mountains.
A country that doesn't have to worry about fine dust.
- It's free of fine dust. / - That's true.
Can you give us more hints?
- Canada reminds us of maples. / - Two things.
- Maples. / - And Niagara Falls.
- Niagara Falls. / - Yes.
- Over there... / - You just spoiled the entire trip.
Really?
- Is that it? / - Niagara Falls is great.
- No, and the Maple Road. / - Maple...
- Maple Road. Right. / - Maple syrup.
Canada is a great country
but it's already been on Battle Trip.
- But this place is a first. / - Right.
Personally,
I heard from people that this country is a paradise.
I heard that too.
- Is it Jeju-do? / - Let's find out where they went.
- It's Ulleungdo. / - We went to the country...
With world-class music, art, and movies.
It's the center of culture
and the center of Europe as well.
We visited Austria.
Austria! I love it.
- I've been to Austria. / - Where?
- How was it? / - Did you go to Hallstatt?
- Hallstatt is wonderful. / - Hallstatt is great.
- Have you been there? / - Of course, I have.
To fully enjoy Vienna,
you have to reach a certain age.
- Good job. She's good. / - Only then, you can...
- Understand Egon Schiele's work. / - That's right.
- She's right. / - She knows a lot.
She said too much.
- It must have been really good. / - But we...
- That's why she remembers all that. / - Right.
- Yes, it was nice. It was indeed. / - Wendy...
- She studied in Canada. / - Where?
- Were you born there? / - I studied in Toronto.
- My parents live in Toronto. / - Toronto.
Is Toronto good or bad?
- Well... / - That's it.
- Your question is so scary. / - It's hard.
- She can't say it's bad. / - Toronto...
Or Austria? Where would you want live?
Do you know the movie, "Before Sunrise?"
- Yes. / - I love that film.
Austria was the setting of the movie.
- The one with the train? / - They travel by train.
- They spend a night. / - That made people go there.
Thinking that they'd meet a girl like Julie Delpy.
People get on the train expecting it
to be like the movie.
But the KTX is better.
- That's not right. / - Come on.
- People must know the truth. / - I agree.
Did you go to Vienna just like the couple in the movie?
Yes, and also where "The Sound of Music" was shot.
- That's the paradise. / - Salzburg.
- Yes, that's right. / - The mountain there is amazing.
- It was so beautiful. / - Right.
Since it's our 100th episode,
they're getting very competitive.
- They are. / - Tell us one main activity.
As we admired Niagara Falls...
- We rode the zip-line. / - Zip-line.
- You ride down... / - Are the Falls under you?
It's right next to you.
You enjoy the view as you're on the zip-line.
- That sounds so fun. / - Since you're so close...
- You get splashed. / - Didn't you all get wet?
- No, it was like a face mist. / - Natural mist.
- To keep you moisturized. / - It's organic mist.
Tell us an activity that will beat that from Austria.
We got to admire the view of Salzburg
and feel the Alps as we went paragliding.
- We won! / - We won. What? Paragliding?
- We did it. We won. / - We won.
- We won this battle. / - They went paragliding?
The battle will be cutthroat.
No matter how much we fight over it,
they will be the judge of it.
We have our 100 impartial judges.
- Nice to meet you. / - Hello.
- We hope you like our trip. / - We hope you like it.
- Please vote for us. / - Forget about Niagara Falls.
- Showing one city would be boring. / - Right.
They combined the trips for a metropolis
and a small city.
It won't be a single round.
It will be a two-round battle.
- Right. / - The team with higher total vote wins.
- Which team should go first? / - I think...
- Our team should go first. / - No.
- No? / - No.
- We should go first. / - According to my observation...
- Teams that go first usually... / - Right.
- Score higher numbers. / - He has a valid point.
- We'll let you go first. / - It's an advantage.
- We're confident about our trip. / - Go ahead.
She's an expert on traveling. He's her best friend.
Let's see how realistic their trip was.
Let's set out to Canada.
(One of the top three waterfalls in the world)
(Blown away by Mother Nature in Canada)
It's like I'm being sucked in.
It's Niagara Falls.
I'm going to save all of this in my eyes.
It's so great that there's no fine dust.
- The air is so fresh here. / - Isn't it really fresh?
It's so beautiful.
It's so cute.
It's like we're in Europe.
- What's that? / - It's so pretty.
- It was really beautiful. / - What is that?
They're called the Thousand Islands.
It's really beautiful.
I might end up moving to Canada.
(Realistic Sibling Tour in Canada)
What are you up to?
- Just something... / - You're playing games again!
Let's go! Come on.
Let's go.
(One afternoon before the trip)
Hello. I'm Seo Hyorim.
I'm happy to be on Battle Trip again.
- She's an expert. / - It's so nice to see you again.
I was given a chance to go on my second trip.
I believe I'll get to enjoy this trip more
than my first time.
She's an expert indeed.
She's not an easy match.
You had so much fun in Dubai.
Right.
(Dubai and Italy trip on episodes 27 and 30)
(She made an overwhelming stopover in Dubai)
I feel like my heart will explode.
(From overwhelming stopover in Dubai)
(To beautiful Southern Italy)
(She planned a stopover trip for Dubai and Italy)
- She always drank in one go. / - Her eyes widen.
She seems to really enjoy it.
It's so delicious.
Last time, I went to Positano in the Amalfi Coast.
I really liked the region.
A while ago, I stayed there for two weeks in March.
- She went there again. / - It's great there.
Even though it was my second time there,
I still had a great time.
After that, I visited Germany too.
I went to Paris, Japan
and Hong Kong.
- I kept going on trips. / - She's an expert indeed.
It's hard to see her in Korea.
Are you going on a trip with Lee Chunga again?
No, this time, I can't go with her which is a shame.
Oh, right. Chunga was really scared of going on trips
but now, she got hooked on traveling.
It's hard to see her in Korea now.
So this time...
I'll go with this friend who likes traveling
but can't go on trips because of his busy schedule.
My travel companion should be
someone I'm comfortable with.
- That's right. / - It's better that way.
When I asked my friend to join me,
he said yes right away, so we'll be going together.
I'm looking forward to it but I'm extremely worried.
I mean it.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- It's Honggi. / - Gosh, he's putting on an act.
I wasn't. It wasn't part of my act.
Let me introduce my friend. It's Lee Honggi.
Hello, I'm Lee Honggi.
(The five member rock band of 11 years)
- 11 years. / - It's already been 11 years.
It's been 11 years?
(Lee Honggi, the main vocalist of FTISLAND)
In 2009, I was pretty young too.
That's when I filmed the music video for their song,
"Bad Woman."
(Seo Hyorim)
(It's Hyorim's clip from 9 years ago)
- You were the bad woman. / - Yes.
Back then,
your song was ranked 1st place for a long time.
After the music video,
we always sang that at karaoke.
- We did. / - We sang a lot.
- Right. / - So, where are we going this time?
This time, it's about a country we'd want to live in.
- It's Hawaii. / - Hawaii?
- You want to live there the most? / - Yes.
- Right. Hawaii is great too. / - Exactly.
After doing some research, personally,
places that are good to live in are Austria...
But I've been to Austria.
So among the countries I haven't been to,
I checked the rankings for the best country to live in.
- I found Canada on it. / - Canada is on top of the list.
- The U.S. is common. / - My mom went the other day.
- Really? Ask her for some tips. / - She sent photos...
- A bear was on the road. / - Really?
- There really is a bear in the photo. / - It's true.
- Look. Bear. / - Bear.
- That's the bear. / - That's a real bear.
- Isn't it too close? / - A deer.
My mom came back 2 days ago.
- They are on the road. / - Look at the photos.
That's great. Since your mom just visited Canada,
we'll be able to get more information.
How does Canada sound?
- Canada is great. / - Right.
Niagara Falls.
Second best country to live in.
And the first place?
(Mother Nature is evident in the nation of the maples)
(Canada)
Canada is famous for Neegara Falls.
"Neegara."
We hear about it all the time.
- Top 3 waterfall in the world. / - We read a lot about it.
I've never seen it in person.
- The photos look grand like this. / - But my friends...
Told me that Niagara Falls is much prettier
from Canada than the U.S.
- People do say that. / - Right, I heard that too.
- Yes, it's true. / - Seriously.
I heard it looks different depending on your location.
Then, we won't get to do any extreme activities?
We will.
- We will? Really? / - Of course. It's you and I.
(Impressed)
This is cheating.
(The ultimate package of activities at Niagara Falls)
It feels like I'm getting sucked in.
Unbelievable.
Oh, my God. Do you see this, everyone?
(Niagara trip planned more special than ever)
- You mentioned Niagara Falls. / - Right.
- We have to go there. / - We must. We ought to.
- We must. / - We can do many activities there.
There are nice villages around Niagara Falls.
- Maple Road is famous too. / - Isn't that the road?
- What? / - Maple Road.
I don't know much about it.
- Sault Ste. Marie? / - Yes. That's right.
Yes. How did you know?
- Maple leaves. / - Yes, yes.
It's so picturesque.
It's like a photo from a calendar.
- Did I get it right? / - Amazing.
(Maple Road, Canada's famous tourist attraction)
Gosh, look at that.
- Stress be gone. / - Isn't this "Before Sunrise?"
- It's a bit similar. / - You saw this in person?
- Yes. / - This is so beautiful.
I want to leave now.
Personally, I've been traveling a lot.
Now, I'm really interested in visiting small cities.
- You travel a lot. / - Right.
Think about it. When you go on trips,
you usually visit major cities.
- Right. / - That's why...
We should visit small cities on this trip.
Places people don't usually visit.
- Uncommon places? / - That's right.
Kingston. We can go to Kingston.
It's called Niagara-on-the-Lake.
It's close to the Falls. It's 30 minutes away.
It's beautiful. Small cities have their own charm.
- I agree. / - Right.
Then I'll just follow your lead.
I don't know much about it.
- Just follow me. / - Niagara Falls and Maple Road.
We need a name for our tour.
A name for our tour. For my first tour,
it was Dubai and Italy, so I named it Dubaitaly.
Are you laughing at me?
(I'll think of a better name)
It's completely up to us.
Can we use Realistic Sibling Tour?
- Realistic Sibling Tour? / - Yes.
If real siblings go on a trip, it'll be us.
I think I'm closer to you
than your younger sister is to you.
- I know about you more than her. / - That's true.
- I know more than Jayeong, right? / - Right, right.
- She knows her name. / - Yes.
- Let's have fun on our trip. / - Yes.
- Realistic Sibling. / - Tour!
Even the locals don't know about this place.
(Travel expert Hyorim and free spirited Honggi)
Hurry up.
You're so embarrassing.
Geez.
- Realistic Sibling. / - Tour.
They look like a real brother and sister.
Seagulls, attack her!
You're crazy.
That was the can.
I'm experiencing all sorts of things traveling with you.
Aren't you going to listen to me?
You'd be so dead, if you were my real sister.
Why you!
That's so pretty.
This is it.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
It looks like a commercial.
(Finally, the day of their departure for Canada)
Travelers get excited when they arrive at the airport.
- It's when you're the most excited. / - Hello.
You can't sleep the night before.
We have arrived.
Did Honggi arrive already?
I think he did.
(Bingo)
Tell her to hurry. What's taking her so long?
Hyorim!
How many years are you apart?
We have a big age gap.
Okay. I see.
- You didn't have to say that. / - Too much detail.
- I won't go into details. / - Hey.
Where is Honggi? Since we're going to...
Canada
I should give him a call.
(A smart way to look for one's brother)
(Looking around)
I'm right here. Right here.
Hey, there you are.
- I was surprised at that time. / - Hurry up, will you?
- Look at us. / - Hurry up. What?
(They're wearing matching robes?)
- We didn't plan it. / - We really didn't.
- You both wore robes. / - I was so surprised.
- Come on. You copied me. / - You copied me.
- Stress. / - People might think we're a couple.
(Honggi and Hyorim wear similar outfits)
(No one got the wrong idea)
- Why were you late? / - Hey.
I was trying to get here quickly...
- But I got hungry. / - Because of makeup?
- No. / - Gosh, you think you're an actress.
You think you're an actress.
- She is an actress though. / - That was harsh.
But he's dressed up just as much.
Honggi, you look more like the actress.
You're acting like an idol singer.
You think I'm an idol singer?
Yes, you're an idol singer.
They can only say that to each other...
- Because they're close. / - Right.
- Are you going to Canada? / - Yes.
- May I see your passports? / - Passport?
(Their trip begins now)
1, 2, 3.
(Their preparation to set out is about done)
This is light.
Gosh, you're a man.
- Exactly. / - Right.
I feel like we're really going on a trip now.
Gosh, for me...
- I wish I was there already. / - Right?
No lighters, portable chargers or...
- Electronic cigarettes in the luggage, right? / - No.
What if she's prone to explosion?
Your boarding gate is 23.
Please be at the gate by 5:15.
You have to claim your luggage in Toronto.
There's a direct flight to Toronto?
- Yes, there's a direct flight to Toronto. / - 13 hours.
But to see the Maple Road,
you have to make a domestic transfer.
You just have to pay extra $20 for the domestic flight.
- $20? / - Yes, $20.
You can get on another flight with just $20.
You'll land in Sault Ste. Marie.
Oh, that's French.
(It takes 13 hours to Toronto International Airport)
We'll head over to Sault Ste. Marie now.
Bye. See you soon.
If you go to Sault Ste. Marie by bus,
it takes about 10 hours.
The return ticket costs $150, but we only spent $20.
- $20. / - We have arrived now.
We're in Sault Ste. Marie.
- Sault Ste. Marie. / - We took...
An hour and 20 minute domestic flight here.
- Right here... / - Wait, we just made an extra day.
That's right.
- We departed at... / - It was 6 p.m.
We left at 6 p.m., so only 6 hours have passed.
Exactly. We got an extra day.
Right. It only took us 6 hours to arrive in Toronto
and get on another flight to Sault Ste. Marie.
- We're 13 hours behind. / - Right.
- That's right. / - For me, this is...
The best time zone because...
- I sleep around this time. / - We could...
- It worked out perfectly. / - It's time for you to sleep.
Oh, right. I heard that
there are not that many taxis in this city.
I contacted the hotel
and requested the pick-up service.
- Hyorim is really thorough. / - We're going.
- Bye. / - She makes it so convenient.
She does.
Let's go.
(They will start their trip in Canada tomorrow)
- At last. / - It's their first day of the trip.
- Yes. / - The sky is so pretty.
- We were right across it. / - We were facing the U.S.
If you cross over, it's the U.S.
If you live in a country with clean air,
you can get up right away in the mornings.
Of course.
- Yeah. / - It's refreshing.
- Good morning. / - Good morning.
It's our first morning in Canada.
- We must get coffee in the morning. / - Right.
Did you sleep well?
I didn't get a wink of sleep.
Really? You sounded like you wouldn't be jet-lagged.
No, it's not that. Something was off with my system.
- Was there an error? / - My body system.
It gets worse.
When I was young, I didn't feel jet-lagged either.
I feel jet-lagged in Korea.
- It's a short walk. We can walk. / - But...
Where are we going?
We're going to the train station for the Maple Road.
Right. We ought to see that.
It's summer in Canada.
I heard the green Maple Road is just as beautiful.
(Special ways to enjoy the Maple Road)
Those were views I'd only seen on postcards.
Maple Road. Even the name is pretty.
(Fresh, green Maple Road)
The very sight looks like the air would be clean.
I really want to visit there.
(Healing Day in Mother Nature of Canada)
(Maple Train)
Is this it?
You should book the train ticket beforehand.
- I booked them online. / - Book in advance.
- Cart 3? / - Cart 3. It's right behind us.
- There are no seat numbers? / - No.
You just have to go in early and get your seat.
(You can choose your seat within the assigned cart)
- Bye. / - Bye.
(Agawa Canyon Tour Train, $84 per person)
- My gosh. It's coming. Let's go. / - Here it comes.
We see these trains in the movies.
- It's amazing. / - No way.
(Agawa Canyon Tour Train runs 360km for 8 hours)
- Look at the train. / - Hurry. Take some photos.
- The train. / - Photos. Photos.
Camera. Gosh, there's so much I have to do.
Selfie. Let's take a selfie now.
(They take a selfie with the incoming train)
Here comes the train.
It's not a train station we're familiar with.
- Right? / - Yes, indeed.
It's an open space.
- Let's go. / - Agawa Canyon.
Let's go.
(They set out to Agawa Canyon by train)
Here we go.
(It's always exciting to set out to a new place)
Trains ought to chug.
(Chugging)
- I feel like I'm going backwards. / - Yes.
Oh, my God.
Is that why there's a plastic bag?
(That's for rubbish)
(It's a travel brochure given to every passenger)
What's this?
It must be a guide book.
Is there one in Korean?
Sault Ste. Marie.
- Oh, my God. / - We'll see that.
We'll see that.
Right. Exactly. That's it.
We're starting from here.
- We were in Sault Ste. Marie. / - Yes.
We'll pass through here.
Agawa Canyon is our destination.
I see. We're passing by Agawa River.
Doesn't it mean we should've come here with a baby?
Exactly. That's why you're here.
I bet it'd look fantastic during the fall here.
The sky is really blue like it's been painted.
The weather is great.
- The weather is amazing. / - Yes.
(Just looking at the scenery makes you feel good)
(You're allowed to bring your food)
It'd be nice to go with anyone.
I think everything tastes good when you're on a train.
- That's so true. / - Don't you agree?
It depends on who you eat with.
Why you little...
- Yes, that's right. / - I see.
What?
I was going to say it's nice to eat with you.
You should listen until the end.
You're happy that you came with me, right?
You two look really close.
They're all maple trees on the side.
- Yes. / - Amazing.
- It must be very pretty in October. / - Yes.
It must be really pretty.
Look at the lake.
- This is really pretty. / - What?
This really looks like a foreign country.
This really looks like Canada.
This is Canada.
He looks like an immature younger brother.
(Honggi is like an immature brother)
This really looks like Canada.
This is Canada.
(The lake reflects light brilliantly)
- This is what I saw in textbooks. / - Yes.
Look at the color.
- It looks like computer graphics. / - It's so pretty.
How can it be that color?
(Montreal River Bridge is at 144km point)
- It's really clear. / - It doesn't look stressful at all.
That's amazing.
(Gosh, it's so pretty)
It's so pretty.
The moment you get on the train,
there is no signal.
(You can completely relax in nature)
- That's great. / - So you can...
- Turn your phone off. / - Yes.
(It's currently 11 p.m. in Korea)
- He's jet lagged. / - He slept so well.
So I couldn't see much.
Since there was a forest,
I kept looking for bears or deer. Then I fell asleep.
But sleeping like that makes you feel at ease.
(They arrive at primitive nature)
That's pretty.
(That was formed 2.5 billion years ago)
(The final destination, Agawa Canyon)
Agawa Canyon.
Yes, it's Agawa Canyon Tour Train.
That's so pretty.
We're here.
The weather is wonderful.
Do you get off here and look around?
- Yes, you get 1.5 to 2 hours. / - There is...
An observatory where you can see everything.
You were sleeping
so you missed a huge lake.
(Honggi is still jet lagged)
They are going that way to see the waterfall.
This way is to the observatory.
Tomorrow, we'll see a bigger waterfall anyway.
So we'll see the observatory first.
It looks like you'll abandon Honggi.
You slept too much.
Gosh, the grassy smell.
Grassy smell, my foot.
You're just saying that.
What? I can smell grass a lot.
It's super blue.
It's all blue, isn't it?
I was so bored for four hours on the train.
- It's sparkling. / - Because he was sleeping.
(Canada's nature is unreal)
- It's so pretty. / - It's beautiful.
Oh, my God. I want to take a picture here.
I want to go back!
You have to do those things.
(Something you want to shout on a train track)
- Why did I do that? / - Isn't this it?
Because you just woke up.
(Hyorim takes pictures for Honggi)
I want to go back!
(Same train tracks, different feel)
Honggi gets peevish after sleep.
- You want this way? / - I want this way.
(Hyorim wants the train in the background)
I'm going to jump. Take a picture for me.
- This way. / - A jump shot is the best.
You should jump on the spot.
1, 2, 3.
(Honggi doesn't take it)
One more time, 1, 2, 3.
- Good. / - Did you get it?
I think you made me jump more on purpose.
It's upsetting if they take bad pictures
when you jump so hard.
I want to see the pictures.
- That's good. / - You took it well.
- I'm a good photographer. / - He's good.
I'm bad at taking selfies
but I take good pictures of the others.
You shouldn't just take one picture
but take bursts of pictures.
You can delete the bad ones later.
(They head to the observatory)
At least you're wearing long pants.
Gosh, this is...
(The trees are densely packed)
I really hate bugs.
Do you hate bugs?
Seriously. What's this?
- No. / - It's just a twig!
(Honggi is scared of a twig)
- Goodness. / - Poor Honggi.
It's a twig!
I really hate bugs.
(Come on, Honggi)
I don't think this is good.
I feel you, Honggi.
- You know what, Hyorim? / - What?
I hurt my leg.
- Really? / - Suddenly?
- Oh, no. Did you hurt your leg? / - Yes.
Goodness. I'll give you a piggyback ride.
(I'll give you a piggyback ride)
- Come on. / - No.
- Come here. / - You go.
- I'll go back down. / - You hurt your leg?
Be careful.
I'll help you.
What's this?
- You look like his mom. / - She's like his mom.
(Hyorim is climbing the canyon with a baby)
- Is that a cub? / - A cub?
Yes, that. No, it's a squirrel. There it is.
- A squirrel. / - It's that one.
- Yes. / - It's cute.
Gosh, I hate bugs.
I really hate bugs.
You're not my type.
Because the nature is so nice...
- There are so many bugs. / - You're not my type.
I see.
We're almost there.
(You just need to climb about 300 stairs)
Aren't there like 1,040 stairs?
I'll remember this, Honggi.
(She clenches her teeth)
(I'm watching you)
Hurry up, will you?
You said we'd go to somewhere fun and cool.
We'll go there tomorrow.
We're half way there.
This is so nice. You get a leg workout.
- It's nice. You can exercise. / - Right.
- 200. / - The air is fresh too.
We just climbed 200 stairs.
(They talk less and less)
Seriously.
I'm tired.
We're here.
- She's like a mom. / - She really is.
- It looks different from above. / - It was magnificent.
- I think it'll look fantastic. / - It'll look great in fall.
Honggi, it's amazing.
- It looks picturesque. / - Goodness.
- It's like a scene from a movie. / - Yes.
(You can see everything up on the observatory)
It looks fabulous when the leaves turn colors.
(I have to take pictures)
(Honggi finally gets to the top safely)
(It looks different from here)
Isn't it amazing?
It's wonderful when the leaves change colors.
The water is red.
It does look red.
- Yes. / - It does.
It looks kind of like coffee.
It's because the dirt has
a lot of iron.
- It's not limewater. / - It's so unique.
Did you see "The Lord of the Rings?"
I saw all of them.
It looks like a fantasy movie.
It reminds me of...
- Old war films. / - Yes.
Way before that.
They must film a lot of movies here.
- They do in Canada. / - Right?
(Nature from 2.5 billion years ago)
It looks pretty.
- This has to be in the picture. / - Okay.
He complains but he does everything.
He does.
Pictures are what you have left in the end.
- That's right. / - Yes.
(Like a character from a movie)
That looks wonderful.
(Looking for a friend who'll find the ring with me)
Honggi complained but he took the most pictures.
Yeah.
(Let's go find the ring!)
- Let's go back. / - We'll go back.
- I'm so hungry. / - We'll get back on the train.
We should have Canadian food since we're in Canada.
- Canada... Steak? / - Yes.
- Will we have steak? / - Yes, we will.
Let's go.
(It's time to go back to Sault Ste. Marie)
(After a 2-hour stop, train returns to Sault Ste. Marie)
You go back...
Heading to Sault Ste. Marie, right?
- Yes. / - Where we got on the train.
(Traditional Canadian food)
What is their traditional food?
(After a long train tour, they have dinner)
Sault Ste. Marie is a small town,
so you can walk everywhere.
Look at the time.
- It's 6:45 p.m. / - Yes.
- But the sun hasn't set. / - The sun is still out.
Was it 9 p.m.?
The sun was still out at 9 p.m.
Because it's summer, the day is really long.
So are we going to eat meat or not?
We'll have steak like I said before.
- You like steaks. / - Yes.
Canadian steaks.
We picked poutine as the main menu.
Then we picked a menu that would go well with it.
So we'll have poutine and steaks.
(An old factory turned into a classy restaurant)
This place must be famous.
There are so many people.
I can't believe I'm here with you.
What about it? Are you sad that you're here with me?
Steak and...
They're realistic siblings.
The younger brother that never listens.
- The annoying type. / - And she's a nagging sister.
When I think of Canada,
poutine is the first thing that comes to mind.
You know what poutine is, don't you?
The president of Russia?
- The president? / - Oh, my.
What is poutine?
Poutine is French fries with
cheese and different ingredients.
It's a typical Canadian dish.
Gravy sauce is the most
delicious and the fattiest sauce in the world.
- Really? / - Yes.
It's really delicious.
- I want to try it. / - It's very delicious.
Baby back ribs and rib eye steak.
If we order them in big portions,
it should be enough for us.
The ribs were really good.
And it's cheaper than in Korea.
It comes in huge portion too.
It was so big.
(They start with a glass of cold beer)
Oh, my God.
- Thank you. / - I'm going to get the water for you.
Canadian beer.
This is Canadian beer.
Different color.
No head.
- No head. / - He's good at English.
- Cheers. Thank you. / - Happy New Year.
- Out of the blue. / - So random.
(This is cranberry juice)
- It's so refreshing. / - Is it?
(It looks delicious)
- Mine is pretty sour. / - It's quite strong.
- Strong? Really? / - It's a bit strong.
It's like...
Just one sip of beer makes my face red.
- So I wasn't going to drink it. / - With a straw?
- Once you start drinking... / - She'll drink it all.
I don't know how to put it.
It's a bit strong.
It's like German beer.
(My goodness)
She eats aggressively with the cute face.
It's like German beer. With high alcohol content.
It's going down.
It's not easy to drink it with a straw.
It's like that beer.
Because I'm drinking all his beer.
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
- What do you think you're doing? / - He's ruthless.
How could you hit me in the forehead?
- You're ugly. / - My goodness.
What did you just say?
Is that so?
(I'll make you pay for this)
How can I put it? It's strong but...
- It was very delicious. / - It must have been soft.
It feels like flat beer.
It's not that carbonated.
I'm so angry right now.
- I'm so mad. / - Could you film us separately?
A camera for her and one for me.
We...
How dare you hit me, you little twerp?
Please film us separately.
- You come here. / - What is this? Whiskey?
Yes.
- You can drink it in a gulp. / - Canadian whiskey?
Yes, it's Canadian whiskey.
He was convinced that it was whiskey.
Is it maple syrup?
- This is Hyorim's counterattack. / - Try a sip.
I was saving it so I can eat it with meat later.
- It smells different. / - It smells like sugar.
- Try it. / - Is whiskey supposed to be this thick?
He's quick.
(He finally drinks it)
(What does Canadian whiskey taste like?)
(It tastes like sweet syrup)
He fell for it.
- Honggi doesn't like sweet things. / - Really?
Really?
Gosh, it's so sweet.
(Honggi drank syrup)
This is what you drizzle on pancakes.
That's right. It's maple syrup.
(It's a specialty of Canada, maple syrup)
(Finally, Hyorim got revenge)
The score is now 1 to 1.
- It's delicious. / - We were on Maple Road today.
- He's drinking more. / - Don't drink it out of the bottle.
My mouth already became sweet.
This is really good.
It's sweet, but it's sweet.
(What does that even mean?)
(Drinking)
Some might think I'm drinking whiskey.
Hey.
(I'm the unruly youngest of this area)
What was wrong with me?
You're always like that.
- Oh, my God. / - It's poutine.
- So, this is poutine? / - Yes, this is poutine.
This is one of the typical dishes of Canada.
It has cheese and potato in it.
- Exactly. And the sauce. / - It looks so delicious.
This is really delicious.
It's very greasy and salty.
- I love the sauce. / - The sauce is a little sweet.
The potatoes are salty and the sauce is sweet.
- The potatoes are salty. / - The cheese is sweet.
It's sweet and savory.
Its taste makes you feel guilty.
- It's so delicious. / - It was really good.
- It's a high-calorie dish. / - It's sweet and savory.
Wendy, you must know how it tastes.
Hang on. Seulgi seems like she's been won over.
It looks so delicious.
- What sauce is it? / - It's gravy sauce.
It's sweet and savory.
- It's so good. / - My gosh.
This is really delicious.
It's more like a bar snack than a meal.
It tastes really good with beer.
- I want to eat that again. / - I'm hungry.
(The main dish is served)
- This is rib eye steak. / - Hungry, right?
- It's so big. / - I'm so hungry right now.
Baby back ribs.
- Oh, my God. / - It looks so soft.
The meat looks so juicy.
It was really delicious. I'm telling you.
- Is it pork or beef? / - It looks so good.
The steak is quite big.
- It's a big steak. / - It looks so delicious.
It's perfectly cooked.
It's so delicious.
The meat is so juicy.
The steak is so tender.
- It's so big. / - This must be a famous restaurant.
(Mmm)
- It's delicious. / - Right?
The steak is bigger than steaks in Korea.
It's perfectly seasoned.
You don't need any sauce.
It looks so delicious.
You can eat meat in Korea as well...
- But this tastes better. / - It has a beautiful color.
(He likes it)
(She's already eating the ribs)
(Baby back ribs, $27)
- It's baby back ribs. / - It's really delicious.
- The sauce was amazing. / - It was really delicious.
You can easily eat 100 ribs.
You're so right.
- It's seasoned very well. / - It's so tender.
Ribs are always delicious.
The sauce is different. If you order ribs in Korea...
- It's usually brown. / - It's brown.
That's common.
But I think they used tomato sauce here.
- It's a little spicy. / - It's like sweet ketchup.
It's like ketchup with sugar in it.
The ribs are much tastier than the ribs in Korea.
The meat just falls off the bone.
(Honggi gulps down the food)
It's really delicious.
The sauce is delicious.
- He makes it look really tasty. / - He eats so well.
I like this too but...
Poutine is traditional Canadian food.
Right.
They say you must try poutine in Canada.
- I really want to try it. / - This is...
- How can I say? / - I must try it.
As you know, I like beer.
This makes you crave for alcohol.
They sell this in Korea as well, right?
- It tastes different here. / - I haven't tried...
- Poutine in Korea yet. / - It's like mac and cheese.
- You must eat poutine in Canada. / - I see.
Eating this, it really feels like I'm in Canada.
- Looks so good with beer. / - He's happy now.
(You have been complaining the whole day)
It's really delicious.
(Healing in Mother Nature, the end)
Tomorrow, we're going to Niagara Falls.
I'm going to bring you there.
It's one of the places you must visit before you die.
- It's 1 of the top 3 biggest falls. / - It is.
I'm looking forward to it.
I believe there will be something more than just that.
Of course. I'm sure you'll like it.
(The real trip in Canada begins now)
It looks amazing.
Isn't it just a waterfall, after all?
It's not just a waterfall. There's a lot more to it.
(To make it more thrilling)
(They ride down to the falls)
(They have a closer look at the falls)
- Did you take a boat there? / - I've seen that a lot.
I really want to try this.
It feels like we're going to get sucked in.
(They enjoy Niagara Falls in special ways)
(Everything about Niagara Falls)
Our trip in Canada has just begun.
(Niagara Falls won't let you down)
(Killing Day in Mother Nature of Canada)
(Zip-line, cruise, dinner)
The next day, we went to Toronto.
- You flew to Toronto. / - Yes.
(Sault Ste. Marie, Toronto, Niagara Falls)
(70 minutes from Sault Ste. Marie to Toronto)
Here we are.
Finally, we're going to Niagara Falls.
My nose is runny.
- Really? / - Yes.
Once you see Niagara Falls, you will get better.
(Disappointed)
(I was just joking)
Here we are. We can take an airbus here.
You ride it with many people.
It takes about 90 minutes. It won't take long.
- You can get there right away. / - Yes.
- Air bus. / - You don't have to go to the city center.
You can reserve an airbus like we did.
It not only saves your time...
- But also, it's convenient. / - You need to spend a bit.
- For the convenience. / - Time is money.
It's written there, Niagara airbus.
It's about $70 per person.
It's convenient to ride this.
Otherwise, we have to go to the city center first
and then take a bus there,
which takes about 4 hours.
If you take a bus from here, it takes about 90 minutes.
- Nice to meet you. / - Hello.
Welcome to Niagara Falls.
- It was a really nice car. / - Was it comfortable?
It was a really nice car.
It looks nice.
It's a nice bus.
Do you like it?
Yes, we like it.
The car doesn't have to be full to depart.
As long as you have a reservation...
- It will take off right away. / - That's nice.
(Toronto Airport, Niagara Falls)
(A fancy street reminds them of Las Vegas)
This area is called Clifton Hill.
It's a town that is right in front of Niagara Falls.
Seriously.
The Canada trip has just begun.
- I also... / - I love it here.
I also feel like I came to a city from the countryside.
I like it to be crowded like this.
He's happy to be in a city.
Honggi is excited.
(He releases the cheerful energy)
(The bubbles alone make him excited)
Honggi loves this kind of place.
It's really nice here.
It's nice, isn't it?
(She feels proud)
I knew you would love this place.
(This place is 100% Honggi's type of place)
(Hyorim is busy looking for a restaurant)
It's really nice here.
I found it.
Funnel cake.
(What is funnel cake?)
I heard it's famous here.
(It's deep-fried pastry with syrup, ice cream, toppings)
- It's funnel cake. / - This...
- It's... / - Wendy got excited.
- She just got so excited. / - Do you know it?
- She reacted right away. / - I'm sorry.
It's so delicious.
Is it different from normal cakes?
It's not a cake. It's more like cookies with
fruits and different kinds of toppings.
- You choose your toppings. / - It's really good.
- Let's see. / - Let's eat this.
We don't have time for this.
There are so many things to do.
(Hyorim goes to buy funnel cake alone)
What should I order?
(There are different toppings you can choose)
Could you please give me recommendation?
- Recommendation? / - Yes. Famous...
Do you like fresh fruit?
Would you like the strawberry and ice cream one?
- Yes. / - Okay.
(She chooses strawberries and ice cream)
I wonder how it'd taste.
I have never tried this before.
(1. Deep fry pastries in twisted-shape)
(2. Add fruits and syrup)
That's it.
- Strawberries on top. / - Sugar powder.
- Sugar powder is the best. / - Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
Everything delicious goes in it.
Syrup!
That costs about $10.
- It's cheap. / - It was so delicious.
That's really delicious.
Honggi said he hates ice cream and fried food.
(A funnel cake, $10)
Honggi must hate this dish.
- It looks amazing. / - I want to try it.
That must be really delicious.
(Caramel syrup, ice cream, strawberries, pastry)
- It's ready. / - There you go.
It looks delicious.
- Enjoy. / - Thank you.
(She heads out to taste the funnel cake)
Ta-da.
Canada doesn't really have local traditional food.
I think that's why they have good desserts.
What do you think?
(They focus on dessert on this trip)
(She takes a big bite)
The ice cream tastes ordinary
but the donut is chewy.
The donut is delicious.
The donut was very chewy and crispy.
- I have never tasted such bread. / - It looks so good.
What do you think?
(She's expectant and worried)
It's too sweet.
- My gosh. / - He's honest.
- He's indeed the youngest. / - It's really tasty.
Do you not like sweet things?
No, I don't like sweet things.
I'm glad there are strawberries.
It'd be so bad without the strawberries.
I'll start eating it for real now.
(I can't believe you can eat more of this sweet thing)
(She keeps eating)
This is a must-try. It's really delicious.
(While Hyorim eats, Honggi waits for her to finish)
Stop eating. You finished it.
I'm finished now. Don't nag me about eating.
You're eating this for 30 minutes now.
The rides will be closed soon.
- We're going to ride them now. / - Really?
Go?
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
- Do you feel better now? / - Let's hurry. Yes.
- Let's go. / - Take your time.
They seem to make a pretty good team.
- Follow me. / - Let's go.
(Hurry up and follow me)
This is Canada.
I knew you'd like this place.
- Did you see that road earlier? / - Yes.
- It was shiny. / - It was so shiny.
This is my kind of place.
I'm really looking forward to the trip today.
Finally, we arrived at Niagara Falls.
- Is this it? / - No.
Is this Niagara Falls?
Look behind you.
I look so stupid.
- This way. Hurry up. / - Where?
- Where? / - Let's go.
Ta-da!
(Wow)
(He dropped his jaw in awe)
(What does Niagara Falls look like?)
Where is it?
It's over there.
(What does Niagara Falls look like?)
It's fascinating.
This is something you must see before you die.
(It's one of the top 3 waterfalls in the world)
(The one in Canada is 55m high and 671m wide)
That one is in the U.S.
Do you see the one on the right?
The more amazing looking one.
That's Niagara Falls on Canada side.
This place is really close to New York.
If you cross one big road,
it's New York.
- New York? / - Yes, New York is right next to it.
- New York? / - New York, the state.
There's a U.S. flag over there.
If you cross Rainbow Bridge over there,
you're in the U.S.
From what I heard, the waterfall on the Canada side
is much cooler than the ones on the U.S. side.
The falls in Canada look more magnificent.
This is amazing.
This is really amazing.
Just watching it gives me goose bumps.
I should visit Niagara Falls.
This is something you must see before you die.
I heard it looks much more amazing
from down there...
- Than from here. / - But we can't go down there.
- We can. / - We can?
We should.
You said you like outdoor activities.
- That's not an activity. / - You're wrong.
- There's something fun down there. / - What is that?
Let's go.
Where is it?
- Where is it? / - We're finally here.
- Do you see it? / - Oh, this?
The activity that you like.
It's a zip-line.
(The first way to enjoy Niagara Falls is by the zip-line)
(You've seen a lot of zip-lines on our show)
(Forget about all the other zip-lines)
(This zip-line is on another level)
(You can see Niagara Falls while riding this zip-line)
(The spectacular view and the thrill is a bonus)
(Exciting activity, a zip-line)
This place is open only from June until October.
I can't miss something like this.
- Exactly. / - We came all the way here.
It looks pretty high.
Come on. It's not high.
Can you go on the zip-line at any time?
You have to queue first.
- You have to queue there? / - Is it a long queue?
You can ride the zip-line only from June...
- Until the end of October. / - Why?
Because it could be dangerous. It can be cold.
In November, it's open only on weekends.
Thank you.
(They sign the agreement)
- Let's go. / - It's done. Let's go.
We're finished.
We had to sign the agreement.
(They walk out with light steps)
We have to weigh ourselves.
It's quite complicated.
You have to weigh yourself too.
That was a bit...
I don't like that.
(You have to weigh between 29kg and 139kg)
Can I take off my shoes?
I should weigh myself precisely.
- Thank you. / - You're welcome.
(Let me weigh myself precisely)
Just do it.
Why don't you just do it? Gosh.
What are you doing?
(Honggi's perspective of Hyorim)
The cameraman kept trying to film it.
(She feels uneasy)
(She desperately covers the number)
- Thank you. / - There you go.
(She successfully and secretly got a helmet)
- It's this way. / - It's measured in pounds.
How many pounds are you?
(He won't tell her)
I was about 105 pounds.
(If I'm 105 pounds, that means)
How many kilograms is that?
It's 47kg.
47kg?
(Laughing)
You can air this.
47kg.
When she's so tall? She's so skinny.
To be honest, I'm 50kg.
You're so skinny.
Let's go. We're on top now.
We can see the waterfall better.
(You can see Niagara Falls in one glance)
It's so nice.
- They're going. / - They're going.
(Just in time, other tourists are starting to take off)
(They're going down at a faster speed than expected)
- Oh, my. / - It looks fun.
It must be fun.
- How high is it? / - It's high.
- Is it very high? / - It's quite high.
Are you kidding me?
(Gosh, it's not that much of a big deal)
It's still scary.
How is this scary?
(Deep breaths)
(Hyorim is nervous about the zip-line)
- We're ready now. / - I'm a little nervous.
Why would you be nervous?
I've never tried this before.
I have a lot of problems.
(The reason why she is so nervous)
I'm acrophobic.
Oh, acrophobia.
I'm scared.
It was higher than I thought.
(Will she be able to go on the zip- line safely?)
(Her mouth is becoming parched)
(It's their turn to get on the zip-line)
(They are all set to go)
It's too high.
This is scary.
I told you that it was scary.
It's really scary right before it starts.
Especially when the door opens.
(Surprised)
(Her heart is about to burst before she takes off)
- Oh, my. / - But...
(Snaps)
(They take off the moment they were unguarded)
(They move forward towards Niagara Falls)
It's really refreshing.
(They dart off without hesitation)
It felt so nice and cool.
Oh, my God. Can you see the view?
- Wow. / - It's Niagara Falls.
(The vast Niagara Falls is spread out before them)
(The magnificent view makes them forget their fear)
Oh, my God. The waterfall is so near.
It's splashing water on us.
Hello.
That looks so fun.
- Oh, my God. / - Hear the sound of the wind.
(Experiencing Niagara Falls with their entire bodies)
We're almost there.
It's short.
It's quite short.
- I wanted more. It was too short. / - It was short.
This was the scariest part.
(They arrive at the end wanting more)
(Excited, sad that it ended)
(The Niagara zip-line was short but intense)
Oh, my God.
This felt so cool.
You get sprayed by a natural mist
while you come down.
(A limited edition mist only from the Niagara zip-line)
But it was so strong...
- I couldn't open my eyes. / - You get sprayed a lot?
Yes, I got sprayed a lot.
It's amazing. It's cool.
- I liked it. / - It was a natural mist.
- Wasn't it nice? / - It really...
- Made me cheerful. / - Are you happy now?
There's a cruise that will take us right to the falls.
- Let's go. / - Do you feel better now?
(Killing Day in Mother Nature of Canada)
(Cruise)
This was amazing.
(You can experience it from up close)
(Niagara cruise)
(You can see the U.S. and Canadian waterfalls)
- It looks fun. / - Oh, my.
(You can experience Niagara Falls from up close)
(The mandatory activity course for Niagara Falls)
(The starting point)
(U.S. waterfall, Canadian waterfall)
(A course going around both waterfalls for 30 minutes)
- You move around the border, right? / - That's right.
It's right on the border.
That's interesting.
- Hi. / - Welcome.
(Niagara Cruise, $21.60)
- Hi. / - Hi.
It was about $21.
- Thank you. / - I can hear the waterfall.
Let's go.
(You can see the waterfall amid the red raincoats)
- It's so pretty. / - There are...
Red raincoats and blue raincoats.
- Yes. / - The blue ones represent the U.S.
and the red ones represent Canada.
How did you know that?
- I asked earlier. / - But...
- I asked in English. / - Really?
- Did you ask in English? / - Of course.
Smart.
Honggi, if you like exciting things,
you don't have to wear the raincoat.
(Okay, I won't wear it)
Let's not wear it.
(Taken aback)
- We came all the way here. / - I don't like exciting.
We have to get sprayed by natural mist.
Why would you wear a raincoat?
Okay, I also won't wear it.
- Don't wear it. / - Okay.
- You don't have to wear it. / - Okay.
- It pours, it's not a mist. / - That's right.
(They start to get on the cruise)
(They go to the second floor)
(You can spot them well from anywhere)
(Excited)
- You both aren't wearing raincoats. / - Yes.
There's a reason why they're all wearing raincoats.
- There's a reason why. / - Of course.
We're moving.
Good-bye.
Let's go.
Go, go, go.
We're moving.
How long does the cruise take?
- About 30 minutes. / - About 30 minutes.
(The cruise is moving to the first waterfall)
I feel like we're about to get sucked in the waterfall.
It's amazing.
It was really grand.
We realized how grand the nature was again.
- There's a rainbow. / - You can see a rainbow.
- It's a rainbow. / - There was a rainbow, too.
(They kept making exclamations as they got close)
It's so beautiful.
- This is the U.S. waterfall. / - Yes, the U.S. one.
This is the Bridal Veil Falls,
and that is the Luna Falls.
It's really beautiful.
(Bridal Veil Falls, Luna Falls)
There are a lot of rock faces
around the U.S. waterfalls.
The U.S. waterfalls had a lot of rocks.
- So we couldn't go near them. / - A rainbow.
(Don't forget to take photos)
Stand here.
(It's a great shot)
Is it amazing?
It looks great.
(Niagara Falls right before our eyes)
(The white spray of water surrounds the cruise)
- The water spray is beautiful. / - It's spraying.
The water is that strong.
- Oh, my God. / - Wait a minute.
It's starting to splash.
Did you enjoy the mist?
It's like when you take a shower
and the hose breaks and sprays your face.
- Oh, my God. / - Wait a minute.
I don't think this is right.
You said it was mist.
(I guess we should have worn the raincoats)
It's nice.
I can't see anything.
(Mist gauge)
It's from the force of the waterfall.
Look at those birds.
(Seagulls are completely surrounding the cruise)
- They are seagulls. / - That's a lot.
- Are the white things all seagulls? / - Yes.
- That's amazing. / -  While looking at the birds
(He turned into a singer for a second)
I also want to follow them
Let's fly.
(Are they flying?)
What is this?
Why am I doing this?
(They are becoming one)
This is so beautiful.
(The cruise continues to move on)
(Today's main highlight, the Canadian waterfall)
This isn't a joke.
- This was amazing. / - This is the Canadian fall.
- This is the highlight. / - Okay.
It's amazing.
It's so beautiful.
(They're getting near the Canadian waterfall)
We're moving towards it.
How is it possible to capture this on camera?
We're going inside there.
- We're going in. / - We're going in.
- We went right up to it. / - Did you go right up to it?
- Really? / - It comes back like this.
(A magical view before their eyes)
That waterfall looks like a horseshoe,
so it's named Horseshoe Falls.
That's amazing.
(It looks like a horseshoe from above)
It's so beautiful.
- The fog... / - This is amazing.
- It's amazing. / - Gosh.
- We were speechless. / - Gosh.
(The scenery is impossible to put into words)
This was made by nature.
- We're moving closer. / - Good.
- Did you go inside there? / - Oh, my.
You went inside quite far.
It was scary.
(Screaming)
(They're enjoying a powerful mist)
- It was really strong. / - Our clothes were all wet.
It was shocking.
- Some people have their shirts off. / - Yes.
(Mist gauge)
(It's on another level)
Wait. Hang on.
(The Niagara water park is open)
(He's getting completely soaked)
I don't think this is right.
This isn't...
(I don't think this is)
- You were wearing it alone. / - I was very nervous.
I didn't want to get caught.
(Why is Hyorim wearing a raincoat?)
(What is going on?)
(She snuck a raincoat without telling Honggi)
(Honggi was getting ready to face the waterfalls)
She's putting it on alone.
I was so nervous.
(She managed to put it on)
Honggi, be careful.
(He feels betrayed)
Come here.
- Come over here. / - No!
You tore it all up.
Look at this. You tore it.
It's pointless to wear this.
They really are like siblings.
What do you think? Is it extreme?
(Do you think it's an extreme activity?)
It's an activity.
(He strongly agrees)
(The waterfall meets their eyes)
You must go there at least once.
(Niagara Falls is just amazing)
Let's take a selfie.
(They take a selfie with the waterfall)
- Can we take a selfie with this? / - Yes.
How does it work? We don't even have the selfie stick.
We're just shooting a video.
(The cruise goes back after 30 minutes)
- It must've been sad to leave. / - It was.
Gosh, I'm so cold.
I got too cocky and I'm so cold now.
And I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
Okay. Let's go eat.
Let's go.
(Off to their last Niagara stop)
(Killing Day in Mother Nature of Canada)
(Dinner)
This is the last way to enjoy
our time at the Niagara Falls.
(A restaurant located near Niagara Falls)
- Isn't it cool? / - Because of that...
- It looks like the White House. / - I was so...
Impressed with Hyorim.
(The day at Niagara Falls is coming to an end)
This is nice.
- We can have dinner watching the falls? / - Yes.
- I can see it so well from here. / - Right?
They have night lights on at the waterfalls.
(Niagara Falls lights up in many colors at night)
- It lights up. / - And the color changes.
It'll be so romantic if you go there with your lover.
- You can eat with the waterfall. / - It looks amazing.
It's so beautiful.
(Excited)
- And there's music playing. / - There was a live band.
Plus, they played all my favorite rock songs.
He's totally different from when
he was in Sault Ste. Marie.
(The little brother is just excited)
I love this place.
(100% satisfied)
Where's our food?
It'll be here soon.
(I'm hungry)
(The food is finally served)
Oh, my God.
(The best dinner at Niagara Falls)
Goodness.
In this restaurant, anything would taste good.
(The dishes are as beautiful as the waterfall)
What's that?
(Pork ribs, salmon steak, grilled chicken)
(Bread with cheese, all for $93)
Thank you for the food.
I think that's pork ribs.
- Pork ribs. / - Is it pork?
Oh, my God. Like this?
We had beef yesterday, we're having pork today.
(Dipping it in a sauce)
Oh, my God. Like this?
(He takes a big bite)
This is strawberry jam.
- Really? / - Yes.
It's not good.
- Strawberry jam? / - Pork with strawberry jam?
It tastes just like strawberry jam.
The pork ribs didn't taste good with the sauce.
- You don't like sweet things. / - Right.
(It's not to Honggi's taste)
(Hyorim tastes the salmon steak)
- This is good. / - What's that?
(Perfect harmony of tender salmon and savory sauce)
(It's really good)
(Is this good?)
Cheese and bread.
Let me try.
(A perfect combination of cheese and bread)
It must be really good.
- It looks delicious. / - Wendy loves it.
- Wendy knows how it tastes. / - It looks so good.
It must be good.
(Cheese and bread, $10.80)
- What is this? / - Do you like cheese?
- I love cheese. / - You do?
(But she feels nervous even before he tries it)
Making me look bad.
(He takes a big bite)
It looks delicious.
Do you want me to eat it?
The bread goes with this jam.
He went all the way to Canada
to eat bread with strawberry jam.
(Honggi doesn't like the cheese and bread either)
I loved it.
It's crispy. I like it.
It's crispy but not too hard.
(Perfect combination of soft bread and cheese)
This is so good.
(I like it a lot)
You really don't like the same foods.
We have totally different tastes. Completely different.
(They have the ace in the hole)
But you just need to feed Honggi meat.
(It's the taste you can't resist, chicken)
(Grilled chicken, $26.70)
(Dancing like a chicken out of joy)
He loves chicken.
Come on, chicken.
(What does the chicken taste like?)
(He takes a big bite)
(Hesitant)
- What's wrong? / - Why?
- Oh, no. / - It has to be good.
(Smiling)
It's good.
What a relief.
(Chicken is always good)
It has cheese in it.
- Do you like cheese? / - I love cheese.
(He likes the combination)
(He focuses on the chicken)
People don't really come here for the food.
They come for the view.
The food is good though.
(When they're about to finish their meal)
Gosh, you startled me. What happened?
- Why? / - What's wrong?
I was so startled.
Gosh, you startled me. What happened?
- My goodness. / - It was amazing.
Gosh.
(Hyorim's last gift at Niagara Falls)
It looks amazing.
(Magnificent fireworks light up the falls)
It's beautiful.
(They watch in awe)
- It was amazing. / - It's beautiful.
(The fireworks fill the night sky with beautiful colors)
It's been a long time since I watched fireworks
so close up.
Me too.
(The beautiful fireworks open out before their eyes)
This is wonderful.
This is the best place.
(Niagara Falls gives them unforgettable memories)
Take the cruise to see the falls,
then enjoy dinner with fireworks.
- This is the course. / - Right.
You should go there with a lover.
Niagara Falls look even more beautiful with the lights.
- It's wonderful. / - It's so beautiful.
(The therapeutic killing day comes to an end)
(But the real charm of Canada begins now)
- The real charm begins now. / - Really?
- Did you enjoy it? Let's go. / - Yes.
Let's go!
(Small towns in Canada)
They are small towns unknown to Koreans.
(Fascinating cities in Ontario)
- Things are cute. / - It's pretty.
It was heavily influenced by the U.K.
- It does look different. / - It's called Thousand Islands.
They call this place Thousand Islands.
It actually has 1,800 islands.
They froze it in the ice.
This is it. This is what I like.
(They fall in love with it)
(Excited, loud, lively)
Honggi came back to life.
(Please look forward to the Canadian small city tour)
- As expected. / - Niagara Falls.
- Niagara Falls is the best. / - What an amazing sight.
People must go there at least once in their lifetime.
- That's right. / - For real.
Doesn't it make you feel cool just by watching?
Even if it costs more money,
taking the boat is a must, right?
But the actual cruise wasn't
as expensive as expected.
It was about $20.
It is about $20.
If I had to choose between the zip-line or cruise,
the cruise is more cost effective.
You experience more on the cruise.
Isn't the zip-line expensive?
Yes, it was more expensive than I expected.
It's better to go during a warmer season, right?
That's right.
It's nice if you go in September or October.
- Go there in September. / - September or October.
- Before it gets cold? / - Yes.
Prepare slowly after watching this show.
- I think you should make reservations now. / - Yes.
Okay.
Would you like to go to Niagara Falls in Canada
according to the Realistic Sibling Tour?
Please vote.
(Planned a trip to the country you'd want to live in)
(What will the judges choose?)
Okay, only the opposite team...
- Can see the results now. / - I'm curious.
- Their faces... / - We'll give hints with our faces.
- You'll act, won't you? / - We'll see it first.
Didn't it look really fun?
The results were reflected on Sikyung's glasses.
- It's higher than expected. / - Yes.
I was expecting it in the 70's but it's over 80.
- That's right. / - It's reflected on his glasses.
Is it 92 votes?
I think they might cry.
In my opinion, we can win
just by drinking beer in Austria.
- Do you want to see? / - No.
The last number is either 8 or 9, isn't it?
- This is the result of your action. / - I'm surprised.
(67 votes)
That's a lot of votes.
I really didn't think...
- They would do that. / - Their reactions...
The results must be low.
- No. / - No.
- Trust me. / - No.
I think it's higher than our expectations.
- No, it's not over yet. / - Calm down.
- We still have the second part. / - Yes.
- Okay. / - Next, Red Velvet prepared...
A trip between same-age friends.
Please look forward
to a refreshing trip from the refreshing Red Velvet.
(Next episode)
(The country where people want to live, Austria)
It's so pretty.
It's beautiful.
(A midsummer night's dream)
Is that real?
(Their trip is so juicy)
Let's eat then.
It's good.
I think Austria is a place we can make
all our fantasies come true.
Let's come back with our members next time.
(Battle Trip)
("Love U" by Chungha)