(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
(Lee Hwijae, special host, Hur Youngji)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
(They are cheering very loudly today)
- It's like an army base. / - It's so loud.
Are we at a military camp or what?
Is it because of today's special host?
I think so. Everyone, our special host, Hur Youngji.
(Hur Youngji will be the special host for 2 weeks)
(Make some noise)
This doesn't happen in our show. This is weird.
Really? It's not usually like this?
- They just applaud like this. / - It's different with you.
Thank you.
- Do you like to travel? / - I love to travel.
- But I haven't traveled a lot. / - Oh, no.
- You're too busy. / - I'd like to go on more trips.
Now that I'm the special host here,
I want to get a lot of good tips.
And I heard she loves to eat.
- She does love to eat. / - She can go on a trip and...
Where did you recently travel? Who did you go with?
With my older sister.
Not too long ago.
- Why? Am I being too tactless? / - It's so obvious.
Why would she travel with her sister
when she has a boyfriend?
She should travel with her sister.
- Where did you go? / - With my sister...
- I went to Hong Kong. / - Hong Kong.
How was it?
My sister did a good job of planning the trip.
- That sounds nice. / - Is "sister" his pet name?
(His pet name is sister?)
No.
She wouldn't call her boyfriend "sister."
It sounds sweet.
No, I even posted my photos on my social media.
Sisters go on trips together a lot.
We used to fight a lot when we were young.
But after we grew up,
we became the best friends.
I went to New York with my sister 10 years ago.
And she still talks about it.
Because it still remains in her memory.
We haven't gone anywhere since then,
so she just keeps talking about that trip.
- I guess she loved the trip. / - As you get old...
You feel the most comfortable around your family.
- We sometimes have a fight. / - Right.
But it just feels comfortable.
- The fight doesn't last long. / - You know each other.
And the memory is unforgettable.
So for the first time in Battle Trip,
we had real sisters go on a trip together.
It's our first time to have real sisters here.
- It's our first time. / - I see.
Let's meet today's trip planners then.
- Please come on out. / - Please come on out.
(Who are the trip planners?)
(Mijoo and Jisoo of Lovelyz)
(Yang Heeeun, Yang Heekyeong)
So pretty.
Since when did you have so many male fans?
- I guess your entire fan club is here. / - Right.
- How have you been? / - How have you been?
I heard if you eat rice rolls in your car, you're an idol.
- That's right. / - You're an idol, right?
I recently
worked with Sikyung for my new song.
And it's been well received by the public
since the moment it was released.
I'm having concerts in many big cities...
- Until the end of the year. / - She's amazing.
Win or lose, I think their trips will be a lot of fun
because Heeeun has so much travel experience.
She is really amazing.
Sometimes I ask her how she is doing,
and she says, "I went to Iceland."
- "I went to Japan." / - I know.
She's been everywhere.
- Do you often travel together? / - Of course.
Do you guys get along well on a trip?
We've been compatible since we were young.
We are very different but compatible.
And Heeeun takes the lead most of the time.
I just follow her lead
and let her make plans for our trip.
We have very different traveling styles,
so I mostly follow her.
What's the biggest difference?
She eats breakfast first thing in the morning
but I skip breakfast.
After breakfast,
she goes out immediately and travels around all day.
- Heeeun does that? / - She is fit.
And I follow her gasping.
I once took a trip with Heeeun.
During the trip,
she woke up at around 6 and had breakfast.
- I was so tired. / - It's like fuelling up.
So...
I even pretended to be asleep.
- You didn't want to wake up? / - Right.
You wanted to sleep.
Even though we are different,
she never forces me to follow her.
That's why you can go on trips together.
Have you guys been on a trip together?
- We've never been together before. / - I knew it.
Let's be honest. You two aren't that close, right?
We're close.
- We are just too busy. / - They don't have time.
So this was your first trip together?
Yes, it was.
- You two must've fought a lot. / - Yeah.
I was worried because we both are quite noisy.
You two are noisy?
- Do you guys chat until you fall asleep? / - Yes.
We use up all our energy and just fall sound asleep.
(They are very passionate when they travel)
They're energetic.
You can expend energy by talking
or by moving around.
And I think they do both.
- That's true. / - We do both.
(Energetic)
- Wait. / - I should keep it down?
You should calm down a little.
So, did you two plan your trip together?
I looked for information on the internet.
But I just looked over it.
Because I don't want to copy exactly what they do.
Those who post about their trips are mostly young.
So their itinerary doesn't
quite work for me.
So, I just read various articles and sources
and put them together in my head.
Then I come up with my own plan.
When we take a trip together, she does the job.
But when I go with someone else, I do it.
Actually, this means a lot.
A lot of retired people in their 60s say...
They want to travel without the tour guide.
But they mostly take a package tour instead.
There's the so-called "senior backpackers" these days.
Finally, so...
It's not that only young people go on backpacking.
I want them to watch our trip carefully
and go on a trip with our itinerary...
- With a little courage. / - She's right.
- Anyone can go backpacking then. / - That's right.
I suppose you chose the destination
with certain standards in mind.
- Heeeun? / - Yes.
For me, I have certain standards in mind.
First of all, the flight time shouldn't be too long.
- You're right. / - Right.
And somewhere without too big a time difference.
- Just 1 or 2 hours. / - Otherwise it's too tiring.
- Next, the food has to be good too. / - Yes.
- Food is important. / - And it has to be cheap...
So that after we exchange the money,
we can enjoy spending it.
Somewhere I can be generous about money.
We tried to find a place that meets
all these conditions.
You've made good points.
- But is there such a place? / - There is.
China.
- China? / - China.
That makes sense. Japan is a little expensive.
- Exactly. / - That's why...
We went to the small Europe in China.
Europe?
It's where Chinese people
want to live the most after retirement.
- Where is it? / - It's a city in China.
- Xiamen. / - Xiamen.
Xiamen.
Xiamen is like Jeju-do for Chinese people.
- That's right. / - Many Chinese want to go there.
- It's a famous vacation spot. / - I see.
- How long was the flight? / - About 3 hours.
3 hours.
- 3 hours. / - And for people of our age...
It's very convenient to travel there.
Our generation learned Chinese characters.
We can read the signs and menus.
Although there are a lot of simplified characters,
we can still read most of them.
- It's not so hard. / - It's not hard for the elderly.
They have great food as well.
The food here especially suited our taste.
And the time difference is only one hour...
- Which meant no jet lag at all. / - No jet lag.
There are many buildings that are like those from...
- Europe in the 19th century. / - There are?
It felt like we were in Europe, Southeast Asia,
Taiwan and China.
That's what it felt like.
- Alright then... / - This is going to be tough.
Jisoo and Mijoo of Lovelyz.
Where did you go?
We went to Taiwan.
Oh, no. Taiwanese food is delicious.
- I love Taiwan. / - In Taiwan...
There were so many delicious food.
We visited the hidden gem of southern Taiwan.
We went to the Hawaii and Jeju-do of Taiwan, Kenting.
- Kenting? / - Kenting.
I've never heard of Kenting.
- I have never heard of it either. / - Me neither.
I've heard of "renting" and "venting."
- Such a funny joke. / - Yes.
Is there a reason why you chose to go there?
Yes, there is.
Many people travel to Taiwan
but most of them just visit Taipei.
- You're right. / - And nearby cities.
But we wanted to visit the unknown places.
But we always ask why people don't go there.
There must be a reason.
- But this place was... / - Yes.
Amazing.
(Confident)
Could you tell us a little bit about it?
It was a nice place to travel.
It's a small city,
so you can look around the city on a scooter.
We wanted to look around the city on scooters but...
That's all I can say for now.
- But? / - But what?
It rained, right?
No, it was amazing.
Alright.
Good, good.
I'm curious.
On the count of 3...
It was amazing!
So, it's a match between Xiamen, China
and Kenting, Taiwan.
Since they're not famous places,
they'll go viral once this is aired.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
Welcome.
(100 judges in the audience)
Which one should we watch first?
I'm curious about Xiamen.
- It's such a pretty name, Xiamen. / - Xiamen.
- It's a pretty name. / - Xiamen.
It was really nice. And it's next to the sea.
- It's an island. / - There must be seafood.
The seafood there is incredibly fresh,
cheap and delicious.
The place was full of such seafood.
You can't help but be captivated by this place.
It was amazing.
- What was that? / - She made that work.
- It sounded different. / - That's our saying.
Shall we watch theirs first? Is it okay?
- Yes, sure. / - Yes.
- Xiamen first. / - Yours is amazing, so it's okay, right?
- Of course. / - Because our trip is amazing.
It's a match between real sisters and fake sisters.
- Don't say that. / - Amazing fake sisters.
- Amazing sisters. / - Let's just say amazing sisters.
- Don't say fake sisters. / - Let's start with Xiamen.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
(Unexpected Gift Tour in Xiamen starts)
(Heeeun's house, one evening in August)
You live next door, right?
Yes, she lives in the front.
Do you have something to eat?
- Of course, she has. / - Why do you always...
Look for food at my place? So annoying.
You prepared some fruits.
I found food.
You prepared it already. Why the complaints?
Why can't you just say,
"I prepared some fruits. Have some?"
I don't want to talk to you.
Okay, don't talk. Show me with your actions.
When should we go and come back?
I'm only free on weekends.
On weekdays, I host the live radio show.
I can't go anywhere.
I'm having my concert soon.
You're almost 70 but you're awesome.
How long will I last? I won't be able to keep at it.
Still, you're working at that age.
- I'm just doing my best to the end. / - You're blessed.
When does your play start?
September 1st. It ends on December 31st.
9, 10, 11, 12. You're stuck for 4 months.
I'm available only for two days.
Should we go on a weekend for 3 days and 2 nights?
Usually, people of her age watch dramas at home...
The highlight of the week is when their children call.
- But isn't it so nice that they're so busy? / - It is.
When I go on a trip with others, I plan the trip.
But when I'm with you, I don't.
(Heeeun will plan the trip)
I love planning trips with books.
Planning is where the trip starts.
She's very active on social media.
Where were you in the first picture?
Iceland. Thailand.
The most enjoyable thing in the world
is when I find a food that I love.
I think that's when I'm at my happiest.
- You don't like meat. / - No.
- You like seafood. / - Right.
- You don't like meat? / - No.
- She doesn't. / - You prefer seafood.
I want to go somewhere that's nice to walk around.
Somewhere flat.
- I can't climb up and down. / - No.
- Even with sneakers, it's hard. / - It is hard.
So I did some research...
And I found a place called Xiamen.
- Xiamen. / - I've never heard of that place.
Xiamen?
I don't know many people that know China well
but one of my friends once told me Xiamen was nice.
- I was told it's where... / - Do you remember that?
Chinese people like.
- I see. / - It's a vacation spot.
Most people...
- Most haven't heard of it. / - Won't have heard of it.
(Fujian tulou, Xiamen)
- What is that? / - It's a tulou.
It's called tulou. It's a type of ancient dwelling.
- It's a dwelling. / - It's pretty.
This is an island called Gulangyu.
It's 15 minutes from Xiamen by boat.
It's so pretty.
- It's like Europe. / - I told you.
It's like Europe with Chinese lighting.
Exactly.
That's the lighting Chinese love.
- It's always gold and red in China. / - That's true.
(Xiamen)
How long does it take?
3 to 3.5 hours.
- 3 hours is pretty long. / - It's pretty long.
It's right next to Taiwan, so it's pretty far.
The flight hours are very important. I hate flying.
If you fly for too long, you get tired.
In the late 1800s,
powerful foreign countries came in
and opened trade.
This area was designated for foreign residents.
That's why there are European-style buildings here.
It says it doesn't look like typical China.
I didn't read much in detail though.
My eyes were getting tired.
If you travel with Heeeun,
she teaches you a lot about the history.
- I majored in history. / - Exactly, I love it.
- I should do some research at home. / - Do it.
Where do we sleep?
You have to sleep alone, right?
You don't sleep alone?
I can sleep with others.
- You can? / - Absolutely.
But others can't sleep with you.
(Laughing)
- I can sleep well. / - You would just sleep.
- Others can't sleep next to me. / - Exactly.
I don't eat breakfast.
Then we should book a room without breakfast.
- I don't need breakfast. / - I always eat breakfast.
If you don't eat breakfast, you'll faint. You need it.
- I need breakfast. / - As soon as you open your eyes.
I have to take a shower and eat.
Around 6:30 to 7 a.m. in Korean time.
I have my first meal at 12 p.m.
- Let's book our rooms separately. / - Separately?
- We're such funny sisters. / - We are.
So you have to sleep separately.
- Heekyeong is a bit more sensitive. / - Yes.
And Heeeun is a heavy sleeper.
- She sleeps well and eats well. / - I see.
Even twins...
- Seojun doesn't eat breakfast. / - They're different.
While Seoeon has a big breakfast.
- It's very interesting. / - Twins can be so different?
From the same stomach but totally different.
Do we have our team name?
- Unexpected Gift. / - What?
Unexpected Gift.
Because this trip is like an unexpected gift.
This short break after work feels like a gift to me.
- Unexpected Gift. / - Unexpected Gift Team.
Team.
We're never in synch.
Nothing works out.
This is when we were young.
How adorable.
(They've been standing by each other for 60 years)
(The sisters are going to receive an unexpected gift)
You should film using this.
- Why should I use this? / - Come on.
(In reality, bickering is part of their daily lives)
She's not even using it.
- Toilet is important. / - And so is a department store.
We held hands all day long.
From here on...
- We're the raincoat sisters. / - Sisters.
My goodness, how pretty.
- Let's walk. / - No.
I can't do this.
I like bugs.
Move your hand. Your fingers look like silkworms.
Just what are you thinking about?
I'm scared.
Use your body.
You ruined it.
- You think I can last? / - Yes, I do.
(Yang Heekyeong, 65-year-old younger sister)
(They look around the city and enjoy it to the fullest)
This is very delicious.
(From Xiamen-style breakfast which they love)
- That looks delicious. / - That was delicious.
- Are those eggs? / - Yes.
- I strongly recommend this. / - My goodness!
This is right up my alley.
It's been a long time...
- The scenery is pretty. / - How pretty.
This has been such a precious day.
- So pretty. / - What an expected gift today has been.
(The day before the trip at Heeeun's house)
Xiamen is one of the cities that the Chinese locals
want to live in when they get older.
Everyone, her dogs are
the only animals on Earth that can attack Heeeun.
I've been away a lot recently.
They're making a scene so I won't go.
I'm trying not to
pack a lot of things.
Even until now, I'm not satisfied with the way I pack.
Hey, there.
(First essential of the oldest trip planner, a unique hat)
Like this? The first-aid kit.
- You always carry that around. / - Yes.
These are linen pants. These are my pajama pants.
I'm sure one pair would suffice.
Heekyeong learned how to sew...
- And made these two shirts for me. / - My gosh.
- Really? / - I'm sure a trip by a 67-year-old...
And a 65-year-old will be different from
the young people's.
I researched on social media
and read the posts that young people uploaded.
And I've been to a few of those places.
It could be that my palate along with everything else
weren't in agreement with the youngsters these days.
Unless I go around and find new places myself,
it won't be easy to find good places.
I'm looking forward to this a lot.
- See the suitcases behind her? / - Yes.
Imagine how often she travels
that they're always on standby.
- Just like pot plants. / - Yes.
I'm not good at researching things online.
That's why I asked my son for help
to find places to go.
I'll see you soon.
Hello.
(Her 40-year-old son can use the internet)
The street in Zeng Cuo An Village.
- They sell ice cream there. / - And food street there.
This is the street food they sell there.
They look delicious. What is that one?
It's Dongpo pork.
- The fried eggplants look great. / - Seafood stew.
- Seafood stew? / - She reminds me of my mom.
This is the shrimp pie.
Oyster fritters. Mango shaved ice.
Zhongshan Road is the paradise for shoppers.
Is that so?
- You can shop and eat. / - What could I buy there?
- What? / - If not food?
Buy me a gift.
(Laughing)
- Do you like shopping? / - Yes, I do.
- We like browsing. / - I see.
It's really fun to go shopping with Heeeun.
She tells us what we wouldn't have known.
- "You can only find this cotton here." / - That's right.
I bought a handkerchief with her, and I still use it.
- It's really good. / - Right?
She tells people what they should buy.
- And you like buying things. / - Right.
- That's the best combination. / - We're perfect.
- Good job. / - Don't fight with aunt.
I won't.
1, 2.
(They finally depart for Xiamen, the mysterious city)
(Xiamen)
- A 3-hour flight is great. / - That's perfect.
- I'm curious. / - It's warm there in winter, right?
- Yes, it is. / - Right.
- It's really nice from November. / - It's the best.
It'd be perfect to go there after this airs.
- People can visit then. / - That's right.
We're in Xiamen.
We have arrived in Xiamen.
(This is Heekyeong's very first selfie stick)
I've never held a selfie stick before.
- We have arrived... / - Wait, this person is blocking you.
In Xiamen. Come on, you do it too.
- Why? We can look at that one. / - Right now...
No, film it with this camera.
(These sisters in their 60s are still very energetic)
- They're so realistic. / - They will air this.
Alright.
We are at the airport in Xiamen.
It took us 3 hours to get here.
Right now, it's 2:10 a.m. in Korea.
The public transportations don't run at this hour.
Okay.
That's why we have to take a taxi.
- Okay. / - Let's take that.
They aren't very friendly.
We can't ride with this in the seat.
Thank you.
(Taxi from the airport to hotel, $3.20)
How's the taxi fare there?
- It's not that expensive. / - I see.
(15 minutes by taxi from the airport to the hotel)
- Yours is on that side. / - Mine is 1001.
- Go to the right then. / - Okay.
- Good night. / - Good night.
- See you in the morning. / - See you tomorrow morning.
(They bid an unexpected farewell)
They're splitting. That's unusual.
- And we are sisters. / - They're nice suites.
I'll wash up and change into my pajamas.
You can leave now.
Then good-bye.
I'll see you tomorrow morning.
If I'm not out by 9 a.m., just leave without me.
(Will their trip in Xiamen be okay?)
- It's fine to leave first. / - Okay.
- Everything is close by. / - That's right.
- You can catch up soon. / - You can.
("Autumn Morning" by Yang Heeeun)
That's Bailuzhou Park.
(What's the start of Unexpected Gift Tour?)
(Main street with European-style buildings in Xiamen)
(Zhongshan Road)
(Unexpected Gift Tour in Xiamen)
(Zhongshan Road and local breakfast)
There is this street called Zhongshan Road.
It's a street only for pedestrians.
We can look at European-style architecture there.
The street is very exotic.
And locals in Xiamen go all the way there
to have seafood.
If the timing works out, we can have seafood there.
- This is Zhongshan Road. / - Zhongshan Road.
- Zhongshan Road. / - Zhongshan Road.
Hey, you're not supposed to speak Chinese like that.
- Zhongshan Road. / - Stop trying to copy the accent.
According to what I read in a book about here,
there are traces of European-style architecture here.
People come here to shop too.
The upper floors are apartments.
Stores are on the first floors.
- It's a residential complex. / - Yes.
(It's a mix of Chinese and Western architecture)
- This looks like Hong Kong. / - It does, doesn't it?
Whenever you're on a trip, it always rains.
Since I was born in the Year of the Dragon,
I like the rain.
- I don't care about the rain. / - I'm famous for that.
Ever since you were in elementary school...
- It rained on your field trip days. / - That's true.
That's why people used to say that
it's raining because dragons are going on a field trip.
- "No cars here." / - There are no cars here.
- This is so nice. / - It's really nice here.
I was wondering why you were walking on the road.
- But cars can't go there. / - There are no cars there.
Cars can't go on certain roads once a week or so.
But it's all year long over there.
(When the sun sets on this elegant Zhongshan Road)
Not only can you find food on this street...
- But you can also shop there. / - We went again at night.
I heard that it's pretty there at night.
- That's true. / - Because of the night view.
A lot of people came to look at that.
- It was crowded. / - It's like Myeong-dong in Korea.
- That's right. / - Yes, it is.
(The splendid night view will be revealed later)
- Are those residential apartments? / - This...
Do you see laundry? I see it.
People must live there then.
It's like a residential complex.
- People live in those buildings. / - You're right.
These apartments are really modest.
But property here must be expensive.
Goodness, that's crazy.
Look at the wedding photo shoot.
Would you look at that?
- My gosh. / - It's a wedding photo shoot.
But it's raining.
She's sweeping Zhongshan Road.
- My goodness. / - She's using the dress to clean.
"Cleaning Zhongshan Road."
They're done cleaning.
They should wash the dress.
(They start to explore Zhongshan Road)
What is that?
- Mango? / - I don't know.
It's mango.
- These? / - Yes.
Excuse me. Papaya?
- Mango? / - Mango?
- It's mango. / - Mango.
- Those are... / - They're huge.
It's as big as two hands put together.
- Dried fish. Beef jerky. / - This is the beef jerky.
- Hey. / - My gosh.
This is seafood.
- It's dried seafood. / - Yes, dried seafood.
And these are dried fruits.
- Do you remember that? The squid. / - The squid.
You press it flat like this.
I thought it was a straw mat.
They're like straw mats.
I find that place the most interesting.
- Heeeun. / - Goodness.
Fresh-water pearls.
Are these pearl oysters?
(Stirred up)
- Are they all pearls inside? / - Yes.
Pearls are stuck inside.
Are these pearl oysters?
There are dozens inside.
It looks gross.
They say pearls are good for women.
Especially pearl necklaces.
When pearls touch this acupuncture point...
Because pearls supplement the yin energy,
they're good for women.
(Pearl harvesting, $8.20)
Can you make accessories with those pearls?
Yes, you can make them there.
- Can you make a ring? / - Ring, bracelet, everything.
- And that's only a few dollars? / - $8.
You can buy the pearls for $8.
- And harvest them. / - $8.
You have to pay extra to make something.
- I only bought the pearls. / - Are they pretty?
- Yes. / - They're nice.
Because they have irregular shapes.
- They look natural. / - That's right.
Let's harvest one.
You don't know how many you'll get.
I'll choose it. Wait.
I can pick one from here.
- Here. / - Okay.
Can't I eat the clam?
I'm interested in eating.
Let's open it. Yes, you can eat it.
- Pearl oyster. / - Goodness.
- Gosh. / - Like this.
- Look at that. / - Goodness.
They give you those?
Yes, you take them home.
- All of that for $8? / - Yes.
The pearls are embedded in the flesh.
That's why they're called wounds.
They must hurt a lot.
They must hurt. I think so.
Let's do this one.
(It's Heekyeong's turn)
Why pick the one she chose?
I was going to choose that anyway.
(Heekyeong is the passive sister)
(How many pearls will Heekyeong get?)
- You need to pick a good one. / - You do.
Because some oysters don't have many.
- I want to try that. / - Wow, that's a lot.
Heekyeong got more.
They're much bigger too.
Mine are small.
You got more.
(Heekyeong's pearls, Heeeun's pearls)
- This one is cute. / - Goodness.
It's a baby.
It's your lucky day.
Lucky.
She must think you're scolding her.
She doesn't know what you're saying.
She got taken aback.
Wait a minute.
I'll use the translator.
Your business will prosper.
(Will the translator work?)
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(Even the translator makes the sisters happy)
There's a place here where we can have breakfast.
Let's go and find out how it tastes.
I'm curious.
I want to eat that when I go to China.
There are sweet beans in China.
It's a type of bean.
I want to eat things like that,
so when I was in Taiwan,
I ate at a restaurant at an intersection
where local people went to eat breakfast.
It was pretty good.
When we go to China...
- We can find local restaurants. / - Let's find them.
- That'll be nice. / - It'd be good.
- Look. / - We're here.
It's a place approved by the Chinese government.
- I see. / - Peanut.
- Soup, soup. / - Peanut soup shop.
Goodness, this is what I wanted.
- What is? / - This kind of breakfast.
Restaurants like that are...
- Delicious everywhere. / - I like that kind of restaurant.
(Food from various regions can be tasted)
Goodness.
(You can get a lot of food for a cheap price)
(Locals come to this restaurant more than tourists)
(A special payment method)
(First you pay cash to charge up a card)
(Money on the card gets deducted as you buy food)
(Money leftover is refunded when you leave)
This is oyster fritter.
(There are plenty of fresh seafood)
- I'll try that. / - Okay, just a little.
(She orders one oyster fritter)
(20 yuan has been paid)
(That's interesting)
- I want that. / - That one.
(Heekyeong gets vegetable rolls)
(That looks like fun)
(I'll try it too!)
Peanut soup.
- Did it work? / - One soup.
(Serious)
(It worked)
(Heekyeong buys a peanut soup)
(Laughing)
This is fun.
That's the laughter of a master.
My sister and I did it...
- So you can do it too. / - You can do it.
This is your second breakfast.
(Heeeun had breakfast as soon as it opened)
- She had breakfast like that. / - I ate alone...
At an empty breakfast buffet.
That's like a warm up.
(This is Heeeun's second breakfast)
I think...
When women are traveling...
Rather than going to expensive and fancy restaurants,
I go to a place where a lot of locals go to eat.
I highly recommend that you eat like the locals.
Wherever you go, go to where the locals go.
- Then you won't fail. / - That's right.
I'll try the oyster.
That looks like bulgogi but it's oyster, right?
- Oysters are cooked thoroughly. / - They're tiny oysters.
- They're cooked thoroughly. / - I see.
Then at the end, they fry the oyster...
- With eggs. / - Yes.
- Then they're mixed. / - The oysters...
Are very small like Korean oysters.
Like this.
In the past,
Seosan's salted oyster with pepper was this small.
People made salted oyster with tiny oysters.
(What does Xiamen's oyster taste like?)
(Heeeun is shocked)
If you haven't tasted the old oysters...
- You can't compare. / - Goodness.
- It must be delicious. / - She knows that taste.
She knows it too.
I haven't tasted this in so long.
This kind of oysters can't be found anymore in Korea.
(It's a flavor from the past)
First, cook the oysters and green onion
on the frying pan for a while.
Then you stir the oysters around.
Once the oyster and green onion are cooked,
beat the eggs and pour over it.
You cook it until the egg is cooked.
- Look at these tiny oysters. / - Yes.
That was really fragrant and delicious.
- I'll have to go there. / - All that oyster...
And it costs $3.20.
(Heeeun's explosive response)
It's so good.
That must be really delicious.
Heeeun only does that when it's super delicious.
She says, "Mmm, not bad" when the food is good.
- That must be really good. / - When she hums...
- Then it's extremely good. / - Right?
Yes.
It's so good.
(How good is it?)
It must be hard to peel all the oysters though.
I highly recommend this.
- We recommend it. / - If you remember...
The taste of salted oyster from the old days...
It's the same oyster but it's cooked.
You look like you went there to try every food.
- That looks good. / - That really looks good.
- You don't need anything else. / - It's that good.
You must try the oyster fritter when you're here.
Even though I had breakfast, this is good.
You can eat again in 2 hours.
I don't eat as much because I'm old now.
Our mom said...
Heeeun ate five meals a day.
- When I was young? / - Yes.
I'm like this because I stretched my stomach out
so much when I was young.
- Alright. / - Peanut soup.
(Peanut soup is next)
- Peanut soup? / - That's their specialty.
Because Xiamen is by the sea...
- Peanuts grow well. / - Yes.
Why is it sweet?
I told you it was sweet.
There is...
No trace of peanuts. You don't need to chew.
It's so soft.
It's very clean.
It's like porridge made of rice.
Hard peanuts have been boiled for a long time.
So the peanuts are mushy.
They started boiling it at night and
turned it off in the morning.
- I don't like the sweetness. / - It could be good.
I came home and cooked that.
- Until it becomes mushy. / - I tried it.
When peanuts get thoroughly cooked...
- They become like fermented soybeans. / - I see.
- They fall apart. / - They get soft.
It's sweet.
Chinese people love beans.
- Yes. / - I used...
Oat milk to make that soup at home.
- It was good. Yes. / - It tasted similar?
People who cook well
know how the food is made after tasting it.
You know how it's combined.
Try the vegetable rolls.
- I want to try that. / - That was good.
- Goodness. / - They're vegetable rolls.
- Heeeun, this is good. / - It looks delicious.
You can taste all the vegetables.
It has a bit of cilantro in it.
It's only a tiny bit
so no one can recognize it.
This was a great choice.
- What do we call this? / - A wheat wrap.
You can find wheat wraps at dim sum places.
They use tapioca starch to make the rolls chewy,
but this one tastes like it has more flour in it.
- Seriously. They don't stop. / - What?
- We kept eating. / - It was because it was delicious.
We were just filming ourselves eating.
- People who eat a lot, pick great dishes. / - True.
- They have experience. / - They know what's good.
- That one was really delicious. / - That looks good.
(Pork bone broth with peanut powder, condensed milk)
- Only $7.30 when it has abalone in it? / - Yes.
That's the best for your hangover.
Does this broth have peanut too?
I bet it has peanut.
- Yes. / - They're famous for peanuts.
- This is nice. / - Yes.
I can taste that there are no artificial seasonings.
They used the abalone to make the broth.
That looks like spicy seafood noodles.
Yes, it looks like spicy seafood noodles.
(She drinks it from the bowl)
(In agony)
Jisoo's completely immersed right now.
I really like spicy seafood noodles.
And since it looks like it...
- It does. / - I want to try that.
(The very sight arouses her appetite)
(What's this?)
That's fishcake.
Is it not?
- Is it rice cake? / - It's meat.
- It's meat? / - Gosh.
There's meat inside the fishcake?
(Let's share delicious food)
This is so delicious. It's really good.
It's good.
After eating the oyster fritter,
everything else tastes plain.
- You must have that last. / - Eat the fritters last.
- The order is important. / - Eat it in that order.
Let's calculate how much our meal costs.
This is 45?
- This costs 20. / - I want to go back there.
- Again. / - It's like...
I really want to have that.
People can order this one and share.
I won't order that. Instead of ordering that,
I would go with the vegetable wrap,
peanut soup and oyster fritters.
I think that combination would suffice.
They can have this meal for 30 yuan.
That's right.
This recommendation is based on Heekyeong's
and my food preferences.
Food preferences are very subjective.
- It's subjective. / - It's a personal choice.
We'd like to tell you that this is subjective and biased.
Since we have filled our stomachs...
- Let's go for a walk. / - Time for a walk.
There's this island called Gulangyu.
- We have to take the ferry. / - What?
We must go there by ferry.
There is this small island
near the coast of Xiamen.
That's Gulangyu.
- It takes 15 minutes by ferry. / - It's an island.
(The beach surrounds the island)
- There's a beach. / - My gosh.
(The small Europe in China with European architecture)
Gulangyu is like...
- A European city. / - That's right.
- It looks like Italy, doesn't it? / - That's right.
- Like Southern Italy. / - It's a UNESCO site.
There are many fusion restaurants.
There are cafes where tourists can rest at.
There is a museum too.
(Gulangyu)
- At last... / - At last...
We're at the ferry terminal.
They open at 7:20 a.m.
I thought we'd be okay since we got here at 7 a.m.
but this terminal is packed with people.
- "Gulangyu Ferry." / - It's like that here.
I have it on camera.
(They depart for Gulangyu)
The ferry is leaving now.
This city has traits of Asia,
China and Europe.
A bit of everything is mixed here.
(It's a destination with various charms)
So far, we haven't seen
any traditional Chinese houses or anything like that.
We are in the unique part of China.
This is Gulangyu.
- Right. / - Yes.
(They arrive at Gulangyu only after 15 minutes)
Look at the carts.
On this island, we'll visit the Piano Museum
and the flower garden.
- Was it called Shuzhuang Garden? / - Yes.
After that, we'll go to the beach.
Alright. When you arrive on this island,
there are no cars to protect this area.
Instead of cars, you can take the electric carts.
(The electric cart goes around the island)
Let's take the cart and look around.
Heeeun sounds almost a local guide.
- That's right. / - She has her backpack in front.
Being a guide is my dream.
It's so great to travel with her.
She explains everything to us.
You can see the palm trees on this island.
Look at that. Look at the roots.
You can see the roots here.
They painted the white stuff on the trees
to keep the bugs away.
That's what I heard.
She really explains everything to us.
(Under the cool leaves, they go through a tunnel)
(And the cool beach with palm trees unfolds)
Had the weather been clearer...
The scenery would have looked
clear and beautiful.
It might've looked clear and pretty
but it would've been hard for us.
That's right. We would've gotten tired easily.
I think we're here.
Now, we'll head to Shuzhuang Garden.
(A wealthy Taiwanese man built this private garden)
(As he missed Lin Family Mansion and Garden)
This is a private villa he built in 1913
with his own money.
It's called Shuzhuang Garden.
(The only piano museum in China exists on the island)
(As it's famously known for fostering many musicians)
And on the island, there is this piano museum...
- With 100 pianos. / - My gosh.
- That's beautiful. / - Yes, it is indeed.
- The only piano museum in China. / - Right.
- We are the raincoat sisters. / - Sisters.
What are you filming now? Are you filming me?
Are you filming me with your camera?
Am I filming you? Whatever. It's all good.
Alright, Shuzhuang Garden.
(Shuzhuang Garden admission fee, $4.90)
- That's the sign. / - "Shuzhuang Garden."
Gulangyu Piano Museum. Goodness.
It's written in Korean.
Let's go.
Let's head over to the Piano Museum.
(They cross over the 44 Bridge)
Let's go. Let's climb up there.
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
(They cross over the 44 Bridge)
Let's go. Let's climb up there.
My goodness.
Unbelievable.
(The locals are enjoying the 44 Bridge and the beach)
(It's a fantastic view of the garden with the beach)
Let's go.
(It takes 60 steps to the Piano Museum)
I have to do the cheer.
Let's go.
(100 pianos collected from all over the world)
(The largest piano museum in Asia)
- The carvings are pretty. / - They did an amazing job.
I think people from the old days were...
- More dexterous than people now. / - Gosh.
The keyboard is small compared to the soundboard.
There aren't that many keys.
They have a Steinway &amp; Sons here.
(A unique piano that's hard to come by)
This is such a collector's item.
Look. There's a candlestick on the piano.
When there was no electricity, to see the music sheet...
- They put it on the piano body. / - I see.
- The candlesticks were attached. / - Back in the day.
- When they didn't have electricity. / - To play at night.
(Laughing)
How cute.
Goodness, how dainty.
I can't believe there's an L shaped piano.
(What is that?)
How did they make...
- Something like that? / - How can you play it?
You should play it like this.
A double-keyboard piano.
It's for the corner.
- It's made for a corner. / - It's a decoration...
- And a piano at the same time. / - My goodness.
Look at these.
These are double-keyboard pianos.
(Double-keyboard piano)
- The keys are black? / - The main keys are black.
- They're reversed. / - I didn't notice it...
- Because of the light. / - The colors are reversed.
Why did they make it like this? How interesting.
(Right then, a piano stood out to them)
1788?
My goodness, this is amazing.
It's the oldest piano.
It looks like an old record player.
1788.
Look at the piano strings.
The strings are usually vertical.
But this one is horizontal.
(Heeeun is lost in thought looking at the old piano)
When I was young, mom told me to learn piano.
But I told her my head hurt and just ran away.
My head actually hurt so much.
But at some point, I started to regret that I didn't learn.
Me too.
Ever since I learned about the world
and realized how important early education is...
I regret hating piano so much
and always running away.
(The old piano reminded Heeeun of her memories)
Those who learned it and can play it
must be so happy.
She must be especially happy to play
such a special piano.
She can play a piano that others can't.
- They even play it for you? / - Yes.
You're not allowed to touch
the pianos in the museum?
- No. / - Except for that person, right?
- That's right. / - You're not allowed.
(How would a piano from 1937 sound?)
(From 9 till 4, there's a performance every hour)
It sounds...
The piano sounds wonderful.
(The mature sound of the piano)
(Brings back her memories and yearning for piano)
This piano is 81 years old.
- It was made in 1937. / - It was born in 1937.
But it sounds great.
It has a deep sound. I like it.
When I become 81,
will my voice still be stable like that?
- Yes, it will. / - Do you think I can hang on?
Just keep doing how you've been doing.
You'd better worry about your health more.
Let's go. Let's go out.
Are you going to eat again?
You just ate something. You're eating again?
Come on. That's...
After climbing 100 stairs, you get hungry.
Exactly.
- You get exhausted. / - What are you talking about?
I found a place that looked quite nice.
It's a fusion restaurant.
(They will have fusion Chinese food)
It's quite famous among Koreans.
We could end up feeling betrayed.
But I'd like to try this place anyway.
(Port of Xiamen, fusion Chinese restaurant)
- Fusion restaurant. / - Fusion restaurant.
So this is a restaurant Heeeun found, right?
Yes.
She actually doesn't like fusion food.
- But she decided to go there for me. / - Looks good.
My gosh, it's so big.
- The entrance looks impressive. / - Do we go up here?
Yes.
Do we go down?
I don't like stairs.
- What is this? / - This is the best of the best.
- You're right. / - It says it's the best restaurant.
It's in the top 100 restaurants in China.
It made it into top 50 as well.
If it's top 50 in China, isn't that a huge achievement?
- It is. / - It's definitely something.
It's a little too dark to be a restaurant.
I just realized why. I'm wearing sunglasses.
(It's dark plus she's wearing sunglasses)
You're so funny.
You complain that it's dark
when you're wearing sunglasses.
This place is very modern.
- What is that? / - Quinoa salad.
- That's right. / - There are so many choices.
- Let's order it like that. / - Okay.
Nihao.
"Nihao."
You make eye contact when you order.
- She looks into his eyes. / - I like menus with pictures.
- Right? / - Yes.
I have high expectations.
- I wonder how it will taste. / - My heart pounds.
(A treasure chest shows up)
- Oh, my. / - Wait a second.
What is that?
What is that? Is it a treasure chest?
What is it? Is it a sauce?
Are there pills in it?
- No. / - It looks like there could be.
Wait a second. It's a treasure chest.
- Ta-da. / - What is it?
The dry ice makes it look mysterious.
I feel like I'll become like a spirit after eating this.
That's not going to happen.
We don't need to become spirits.
Are the bottles in the front and back different?
- Let me see. / - They seem different.
The ones in the front and the ones in the back...
I can't read what's written on it.
Why do they give us 6 bottles?
(What is this present that every customer gets?)
Are we supposed to drink this between courses?
- They all look the same. / - They do.
Nothing is written on it.
(Let's drink it first)
(They react differently)
It's sweet and sour mango.
(It's mango flavor)
Isn't it dandelion?
Try mine.
(I like it)
(Her facial expression explains everything)
- Her face tells everything. / - I love how she reacts.
Her facial expression is so accurate.
(Argh)
What about the next one?
- Everything else is the same. / - They're the same.
Just one of them is bitter.
It's a game of chance.
You're right. Game of chance?
Game of chance...
I guess that's the case.
This actually works up your appetite.
I see.
(These welcome drinks are served to all customers)
Here it comes.
(Social media master's essential step)
My gosh, these are scallops.
My goodness, look at this.
These are scallops.
- It has to be delicious. / - I love scallops.
- It's a great combination. / - Is that an egg shell?
- Yes. / - Is that custard cream?
It looks amazing.
Let me try a scallop.
It looks quite nice, doesn't it?
This must have been steamed.
There weren't any exotic spices used.
It was perfect for our tastes.
I wonder what cream this is.
- Potato. / - Potato soup.
- It looks so delicious. / - That's a great idea.
- It is. / - I like the presentation.
- It must be fun to eat. / - They present dishes nicely.
It's not easy to cook scallops this soft, right?
It gets tough easily.
I'm glad we ordered only two.
Just tasting it is enough.
Too many of these can be a little too heavy.
I finished it.
Next one.
(What's the next dish?)
- That's... / - What is that?
- Truffle. / - Truffle.
- Truffle? / - Yes.
- It's a fish dish. / - It's fish.
- It looks so delicious. / - Fried rice with truffle and fish.
(Fried rice with truffle and fish, $11.20)
It looks like halibut.
(What would it taste like?)
- It looks delicious. / - Let's see her face.
If it's good, her face will tell.
- This is delicious. / - It means it's delicious.
It tastes mild and healthy.
It's not too salty or sweet.
Mijoo, keep it together.
You had delicious food too, right?
You're going to show us great food, right?
(Solemn)
They're not answering.
I like the flavor of the soy sauce.
It tastes similar to the Japanese rice with eel.
- Their food is too salty. / - That's too salty.
Japanese food is too salty. But this is fine.
The fish seems to be salted.
- Does it? / - It's a bit salty.
- It's dried fish. / - It's delicious.
Heeeun, I like the texture of the vegetable.
(She fell in love with the fusion dishes)
This tastes like mustard leaves. Try it.
This vegetable is cooked but crunchy. I like that.
This is impressive. It's unique.
- This is quinoa salad. / - Yes, it is.
- It looks pretty. / - I should take a picture of it...
Like young people do.
(You can enjoy the colorful dish with your eyes first)
It's called the mother of the grains.
It's getting a lot of attention as a superfood.
(Quinoa salad, $6.30)
What is quinoa?
It's a type of grain.
The one on the bottom is quinoa.
It's very small. It's smaller than millet.
- The one on the top is popped rice. / - It's popped rice.
And on the bottom,
there's quinoa mixed with blueberry yogurt.
It looks delicious.
The texture is very crunchy
because of popped rice.
The top 10 superfoods taste really bad.
They are just healthy.
- So making it taste nice is the skill. / - Right.
(Will they enjoy this dish?)
This is unique. I've never had a salad like this before.
This is new.
I liked the texture of the green leaves.
- It contains a lot of water. / - It also looks unique.
- I don't know what it is. / - We don't have it in Korea.
It's a vegetable that we don't have here.
The popped rice tastes savory.
And it has fruits and vegetables on the bottom.
I've never had anything like this before.
I want to add popped rice in my salad too.
This is my kind of thing.
People think Chinese dishes are very greasy.
But this wasn't greasy at all.
They were refreshing Chinese fusion cuisine.
We spent about $25 for two people.
- It was definitely worth it. / - I think so too.
It was an enjoyable meal.
If we go to restaurants like that in Korea,
it costs about $100 per person.
It'd cost about that much.
It looks like a fancy restaurant
but the price is reasonable.
Now we will go to...
A cafe where we can travel through time.
And they have good cakes.
We are already traveling through time.
If you think about it.
We are traveling through time.
Let's go there and eat something sweet.
- We will enjoy it. / - Let's do that.
I love the course that you've planned so far.
- Do you like it? / - Yes.
- Sook, do you like it? / - I love it.
- Let's go together. / - Let's.
I've never seen so many egrets before.
They're moving.
Some are sitting in the trees. So pretty.
("So Good" by Yang Heeeun)
The sunshine is so good.
Sing that song.
It's so good
I feel so good because you're here
I'm thankful for you
Who always smiles by my side
This is perfect.
It looks so nice.
It will be great to go there with your sibling.
For about 3 days.
You can have a lot of delicious foods.
- The streets are so clean. / - They are clean.
- It's quiet and nice. / - So clean.
There is no trash on the street.
- It's raining. / - I think this is it.
- Is this it? / - This is the place.
- It's called Goodone. / - Goodone?
(This is the cafe Heeeun was talking about)
The characters mean the light of time.
Or shining time.
Tea and coffee.
Sweet dessert and drinks.
(Heeeun loves pretty cafes)
It's a two-story building.
This is interesting.
(It's a two-story building with colorful wallpaper)
They made a deck with wooden boards.
- But the boards are old and rotten. / - Yes.
So they covered it with tiles.
- It's a substitution. / - So you don't fall through.
There are tracks of time.
Look at the chairs.
They have traces of time.
I guess they are very old chairs.
It's good that they have low chair legs.
- Heeeun, if we stay here... / - Western people...
The wooden boards might break. Let's just get in.
- It's shaking. / - I know.
What if I break it and they want me to pay for it?
- You might have to pay for the tiles. / - I can't do that.
- My gosh. / - This place looks beautiful.
It feels like sitting in a living room.
Everything in there is mismatched.
It's like decades of time gathered in one place.
- It's pretty. / - They are...
The things that grandparents
and great-grandparents would've used.
This place doesn't look like China.
- It doesn't. / - It's not typical.
What do you think about this cafe? Don't you like it?
Everything we used to have in our house is here.
It feels like we're sitting in the living room, not a cafe.
I know.
I think that's the point.
The owner didn't buy new furniture.
She just gathered up some used furniture.
(Unsure)
(The dessert is finally being served)
- She looks really happy. / - Goodness.
- Goodness... / - Her voice got higher.
- The dessert... / - It's so pretty.
Gosh, even the forks are small.
It's the perfect size for my build.
- Thank you. / - It's tiny.
They don't serve slices.
It's a small cake.
- It looks delicious. / - What is that?
- It was really good. / - It looks like pudding.
- I can eat it at a mouthful. / - Right, one mouthful.
You're right.
So pretty.
(Mango mousse egg cake, star cake, Budapest)
(Fruit tea, $6)
It's good. It has the taste of nature.
It's great, isn't it?
They didn't add sugar or artificial sweeteners.
It tastes healthy.
- The sweetness from fruits is different. / - Yeah?
You should stop talking and taste this.
Is it lemon, strawberry and coffee flavor?
I think it is chocolate or something.
(Golden stars on sweet chocolate mousse)
(It's stuffed with strawberry jam and cream)
(They take a big together)
(One more bite for me)
(One more bite for me as well)
I guess the owner is a naturalist.
Even the cake is not too sweet.
That's why I liked it.
- It's not sweet? / - No.
It has a natural sweet taste.
I think it's good for people of our age.
- This one looks good too. / - Mango mousse egg cake.
- Mango mousse egg cake. / - So pretty.
- People my age don't like things... / - Wow.
- That are too sweet. / - Stop being so impressed.
Hey, are you alright?
- I love cakes. / - I love it.
My gosh.
You should go to Xiamen.
- I shouldn't do this. / - Restrain yourself.
(It's time to try the mango mousse egg cake)
(How does it taste?)
(Sweet flavor of coconut in mango mousse)
This is a healing moment.
Young people like to go to bars
and have local craft beer.
- They do that. / - And they order French fries.
But that's not for us.
We just want to drink some fruit tea
that's hard to make at home.
After you eat like that...
- You go jogging at night? / - No.
- Why waste energy on jogging? / - Jog where?
- It's expensive to put on weight. / - She'll lose weight.
(The sisters have a relaxing time together)
(In a place where they lose track of the time)
(They are absorbed in old memories)
(Unexpected Gift Tour's trip down memory lane)
Every woman who has a younger sister
is envious of Heeeun.
That she has a sister like me.
I just do as I'm told.
(She's right)
"I heard this is good."
"You should try this."
Then I do as she tells me to do.
Then...
I tell her that it is really good.
- "Really? I should try it then." / - Like a court lady.
- A court lady? / - When we were young...
She teased me like this all the time.
Every day.
When I was asleep...
She squeezed paint on my face.
As it dried, my face felt tighter.
So I rubbed my face like this.
And she was watching it laughing.
I was once on a seesaw with my friends.
And the second Heeeun sat on the seesaw,
we bounced out.
Because she was a lot heavier than us.
As I fell to the ground,
I hit my arm on a rock and broke my wrist.
I didn't mean to do that though. I was pretty silly.
There was a bonesetter I visited a lot.
In the old MBC building.
That's why I remember MBC.
Back then, they would pull like this.
- They stretched tightly. / - That would've hurt a lot.
To set my bones.
- They did it like that in the past. / - How painful.
It really hurt.
- You were mischievous. / - When you were young?
- We finished eating. / - Yes.
The place you wanted to visit the most.
The market!
The night market.
Let's head towards the night market.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
Time to charge.
There is a night market.
Isn't the cafe similar to her house?
- Did you move to the next room? / - Yes.
- You're right. / - The next room.
- Just like that vintage cafe. / - Night market?
- We should see the ingredients. / - That's right.
We should also taste the food they make there.
I want to watch what they eat and how they live.
How happy will we be if we succeed?
- That's right. It's cheap. / - Cheap and good quality.
(Unexpected Gift Tour in Xiamen)
(Night market)
- They did so much. / - Night markets are nice.
- Night markets. / - Will they eat everything there?
Yes, they have to.
This is to my liking.
They have every food that Xiamen has.
Even insects.
Even Taiwanese food is there.
They even have every food from Taiwan.
It's really hard for the Lovelyz right now.
- Is that pork hock? / - But it's really clean.
- It's clean. / - I see.
(Their tour of the night market begins)
The lights come on in here.
It's pretty.
- The lamps are pretty. / - Yeah.
They not only sell food
but also sell a lot of souvenirs.
- That's really amazing. / - Magnets and postcards.
(What will appear if they go past the lamps?)
What could this be?
(What is the first food that Heeeun chose?)
What is this?
- We don't understand. / - We don't understand.
- What is that? / - What is that?
- Is it jelly? / - Is it royal jelly?
- That's a scorpion. / - They are bugs.
- Bugs? / - It's bug pudding.
Forget it.
What bug is this?
(Bugs that live in the beach sand)
I like bugs.
Even eating them?
I've eaten them before.
(I just don't get her)
(I just can't go like this)
(She can't take her eyes off the bugs)
- I'm going to eat it. / - Okay, eat it.
- "I'm going to eat it." / - Give me one of those.
"Give me one of those."
- They give you a lot. / - What that is...
They put bugs in gelatin.
- Then season it with soy sauce. / - Like muk?
So you eat it like muk?
That's right, like muk.
It's muk.
(She loathes it)
It's delicious.
Look at her face.
- She doesn't like it. / - The gelatin must be good.
(Don't talk about the taste unless you've tried it)
Try it.
(Heekyeong is an obedient younger sister)
It tastes really good.
(Unpleasant)
I can't be the only one who tries this. It's okay.
Try it.
- Shoot it. / - I am.
The poor camera director.
His face doesn't look good.
- He's scratching his head. / - It doesn't smell.
It doesn't smell at all.
- It doesn't have a smell. / - No.
(What is the next thing to eat at the night market?)
(Wait a minute)
- I like this. / - Me too.
- These are rice noodle roll. / - Me too.
They mix shrimp with flour...
And rolls it up
like crepes.
- Looks so good. / - With sweet soy sauce.
- That's right. / - It tastes slightly sweet.
That looks really good.
Can we eat one?
- It doesn't matter. / - This one.
- There aren't any seats left. / - Yeah.
I really want to eat this.
But there aren't any seats so we can't go inside.
Skewers.
- I don't want to eat it right now. / - Me too.
Chicken drumsticks.
(They have chicken drumsticks here)
(She's not interested)
It's okay.
Since my stomach is empty,
I want to eat something hot
or something like soup.
- Your stomach is empty? / - It's empty?
It's empty.
- She only has bugs in there. / - She climbed up stairs.
Her stomach's empty?
(Heeeun looks for rice noodle roll everywhere)
(Rice noodle roll, I'm going to find you no matter what)
Does this place...
Sell sweet red bean porridge?
(Wait a minute, that's it)
Red bean douhua.
This is the same one.
It has the same...
Picture.
That really is a specialty in China.
They only have one table.
- That other place was indoors. / - You watch him...
As he makes it.
Thank you. I wanted to eat this.
- It's the white stuff at dim sum places, right? / - Yes.
Let's try it.
The long-awaited taste.
(Wide open)
(Inhales the food)
(Let's gobble it up)
There's nothing left.
She looks so sad.
Her face looks so sad.
That's so funny.
- I also like this. / - We don't have this in Korea.
We have thin rice noodles
but we don't have flat noodles like this.
It has a really light and clean taste.
They don't use a lot of artificial flavors.
Yes, that's why it's nice.
It's good.
- It's really chewy. / - How interesting.
- It's thin. / - Rice noodles fall apart.
There are vegetables and dried shrimp.
Should we also try that red bean douhua?
It must be red beans and pudding.
(A fresh combination of red beans and silken tofu)
(A healthy dessert that is charming because it's mild)
(Red bean douhua, $1.60)
(Big red beans from tropical climates)
(The sisters' eating show)
It's silken tofu with red bean boiled down in sugar...
Topped on it.
- It's not that sweet. / - It's not sweet.
It has a very natural taste.
It's good.
It was good.
- It was good. / - Yes, it was good.
The price was so cheap.
- It's really cheap. / - It's $1.60.
I don't think they will be able to leave the night market.
- They're eating from each shop. / - Until it closes.
I don't think they can leave until they gain 5kg.
- You can't get out of there. / - That's right.
(The night in Xiamen deepens)
(They visit Zhongshan Road again at night)
- I really like Xiamen. / - Me too.
This is where we had breakfast.
We're back on Zhongshan Road.
This kind of view was unimaginable in the morning.
The night view of Zhongshan Road, especially,
is really like Myeong-dong when I was young.
- At night, the lights... / - It feels different.
Of the signs reflect.
The street looks more splendid and gorgeous.
(Unexpected Gift Tour looks back on the day)
Today was really like an unexpected gift.
You don't know how precious it was.
- It was very precious. / - You're right.
It's been so long since we've been on
an overnight trip together. It was so nice.
- Today was quite a nice day. / - It was.
(The sisters received a gift of memories)
Let's promise for the next time.
(We hope that we will also be together next time)
Sometimes when you watch these trips,
you wonder if they tried too to make it fun.
But this trip showed you the best of everything.
You're right.
Nothing seemed forced.
It's like that at our age.
When you go through everything in life,
you don't exaggerate or package things.
We just did things we want and it was substantial.
- I think the island was so pretty. / - Gulangyu?
It was like an island in Southern Italy.
- That's right. / - If we have time...
We want to walk to Gulangyu from Xiamen
and look around the island.
- A walking trip would be nice. / - It was really nice.
- We really recommend it. / - The park is really big.
If you go into the alleys, there are a lot of restaurants.
- The houses are really pretty. / - They're pretty.
Heeeun,
I thought it was so amazing
that they had the Piano Museum on the island.
- Since you're all musicians. / - Yes.
It's known as the cradle for musicians
and the island of pianos.
Because there are a lot of
Chinese musicians from Gulangyu.
- Really? / - Yes.
I think that parents will really like this place
if young people plan this trip...
- And recommend it to them. / - Yes.
They'll say no but have a great time once they're there.
- Of course. / - Of course.
- They'll say, "It's too bothersome." / - That's right.
But it'll be memorable.
- Of course. / - Of course.
It's time to find out the expenses.
We prepared a special list
of the average cost of a holiday in China.
We went to several places in China.
Park Sohyun and Hong Hyunhee went to Hangzhou.
Their final expense was...
How much was it for Hangzhou?
$289.90.
- This is excluding transportation. / - Yes.
- Chengdu spent... / - Excluding the airfare...
$269.
They all spent between $250 and $300 in China.
Why did we prepare this?
It's not like we'll say, "But we spent $700!"
- I'm a little scared. / - Yes.
- Let's find out. / - Excluding airfare...
What is the final expense?
For 2 nights and 3 days,
the final expense
Unexpected Gift Tour spent in Xiamen,
per person...
Per person?
- The total is... / - What is the total?
$327.
($327 per person)
We included $55 for tourist visa.
That's included as well.
Yes, it's included.
- It's included. / - Plus we used separate rooms.
If you share the room,
it will cost about $230 to $250.
- Under $250. / - Under $250 is possible.
- Good. / - Should we vote?
- Let's stand. / - Would you like to go to Xiamen...
According to Unexpected Gift Tour's plan?
Please vote.
(They planned a sisters' trip to Xiamen)
(What will the judges choose?)
Lovelyz, we can look forward to next week, right?
Yes, it's because our trip has a different feeling.
- Really? / - Of course.
It already looks different.
- It feels different. / - You can look forward to it.
- Really? / - I think it will be really active.
Please look forward to next week's trip to
Kenting, Taiwan.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(Next episode)
It's going off here. It's going off.
It's going off
I want to enter those clouds.
Isn't the ocean too blue?
- It's the same color as the sky. / - I know.
Hey, it's really good.
The meat tastes really clean.
It's so tender.
- This is deep-fried milk. / - Hey, it's good.
There's a reason why this is famous.
Each thing became a fond memory.
Each thing was such an experience. It was great.
(Battle Trip)
("Puzzle Moon" by GWSN)