(Naples of the East, Tongyeong and Yokjido)
Let's go!
One Day Three Meals Tour!
Let's ride!
This is cool.
- This is fun. / - Rock, paper, scissors.
(The trip for middle-aged men)
There's so much to eat. It's lined up.
It's delicious.
It feels good, right?
(Who will be the winning team?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Park Jeongcheol, Kim Seungsoo)
(Kim Hyunchul, Cho Janghyuck)
(Lee Hwijae, special host, Kim Saerom)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
We had a break last week.
We're back with the planners
for the domestic island trips.
That's right. They're here.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
Welcome.
(The team with the most votes wins)
We've prepared a lot for this week.
- Right. / - The seniors are finally going on a trip?
- Yes. / - Right.
They've waited for 3 weeks.
They are going to Haenam and Wando.
You'll see what it's like.
The thing is we're the analog generation.
We started traveling when there was
no internet or smart phones, not even beepers.
You used to carry maps, right?
Maybe that's why I'm good with maps.
- That's right. We used actual maps back then. / - Map?
You don't know it. Every car used to have a directory.
Me too.
- Directory of the entire country. / - There was no GPS.
- An actual map? / - You had to carry a map.
The route numbers.
We'd write down numbers.
And you'd always get the directions wrong.
The country was developing rapidly back then.
The roads were always under construction or blocked.
So you'd drive along and be like, "Where's the road?"
- We didn't have cell phones either. / - But these days...
It's so easy to go on a trip.
We have the KTX and we have GPS.
You just have to get yourself there.
We can go on a trip whenever we want these days.
I doubt your trip was that much analog, right?
- Not that much. / - We captured that feeling.
We traveled with that analog feeling.
As we grow older,
we become more sedentary.
When we were young, we were very active.
We wanted to visit as many places as possible.
But now, we just like to visit some place
and sit there and enjoy the scenery.
- We get energy from it. / - That's nice...
But you can't do that on our show.
But there's a lot going on in the stillness.
I'm sure your organs were moving.
It's like internal movement.
If your trip is too sedentary,
we might get bored.
In fact, Wando is a slow city.
- A slow city? / - Yes.
There are specific criteria for slow cities.
They should produce and consume organic foods.
The population has to be less than 50,000.
- Really? / - There are certain conditions.
- And the environment. / - It should develop slowly.
They have certain criteria
about the environment, culture and arts.
It has to meet the criteria...
- To be selected as a slow city. / - That's right.
And Wando is a slow city.
Albert taught me that once.
- Right. / - Really?
So Haenam and Wando are internationally recognized
as slow cities for relaxing.
Let's go on a trip to those cities now.
Please take a look at the map.
Let's check the map.
Haenam and Wando are...
- It's on the left. / - In Korea... That's right.
They are located on the southern tip of the peninsula.
There are a lot of islands around the cities.
People say it's the end of the country.
But we realized something when we went there.
It's actually the beginning of the peninsula.
That sounds about right.
That's the beginning.
And the country stretches out to the north.
That's the difference we found.
Since they are slow cities,
you can think about many things there.
- That's right. / - You get that vibe.
So it's Haenam and Wando.
I expect they discovered a lot about the places
since they enjoy food.
Actually, I love delicious foods.
- He's an epicure. / - Right.
So we enjoyed a lot of the traditional food of Jeolla-do,
and we had health food on the second day.
It's perfect for our age group.
Wando is famous for abalone.
- Abalone? / - Of course.
We ate abalone until we almost burst.
They worry because the price of abalone
is declining these days.
- So we should eat a lot of it. / - That's right.
I'm sure our team will win
because we have our ace in the hole.
- We got some tips. / - Isn't it against the rule?
We met Lee Useok, a travel journalist.
He knows all the good restaurants around Korea.
He knows good restaurants.
He even knows the address of these places.
He's on "Wednesday Food Talk."
- We got tips from him. / - We got good tips.
But it's unfair that you got help from a specialist.
It's not against the law though.
Battle Trip is open to things like this.
- Now we talk about the law? / - Just relax.
Don't worry about it.
Alright then.
When it comes to Jeollanam-do,
you can't really go against it with food.
That's right. It's so good.
I'm very confident.
We can't lose to mackerel and sweet potato.
Alright.
Please tell us your tour name.
Our tour name? He came up with it.
Why Travel Together Tour.
- What? / - Why Travel Together Tour.
Why are we traveling together?
Why on earth are we traveling together?
- Goodness... / - This could be a problem.
- That's a terrible name. / - We've won.
- They didn't want to go together. / - Our trip...
Is about figuring that question out.
You'll see what I mean.
A trip to Haenam and Wando.
Why Are We Traveling Together Tour.
- Why Travel... / - Why Travel Together Tour.
Why Travel Together Tour.
I'm concerned about this.
Let's watch the Why Travel Together Tour.
(Their trip to Haenam and Wando begins)
(The blue ocean and hundreds of islands)
Goodness.
(Wando, a smiling island)
(Why are we traveling together?)
(The experts invigorate themselves)
What's this? What led to that scene?
You'll see soon enough.
(An authentic Jeolla-do meal)
It already looks delicious.
(Abalone that you can only taste in Wando)
Wow!
That was the ultimate health food.
(Gourmet tour of domestic islands)
- You had marinated crab? / - You bet.
My gosh.
(11:30 a.m., a cafe in Sangam)
(The trip designer is enjoying a warm cup of tea)
(The composer and singer of "Addicted Love")
Why are they playing that all of a sudden?
He looks younger now.
That's the analog generation.
(He knows all about fishing)
This is aspartame.
That's a mugwort tree.
Hey, that's not it!
Hey, hey, hey.
You're like a carnivore, you fool.
You make me nag like a mom.
He was so young.
How long ago was that?
It must be at least 20 years ago.
(Cho Janghyuck, a walking, nagging encyclopedia)
Geez.
(His travel companion hasn't arrived yet)
I told him so many times not to act entitled.
I was born in early 1973.
- So he's younger than I am. / - My goodness.
I was born in February, and he was born in May.
- He can only brag about his age. / - 3 months.
He says he was born in early 1973.
I entered college in 1987, he did in 1988.
If we had met at school, I'd be his senior.
But if you become friends, it messes up your circles.
- It's already messed up. / - We don't care these days.
We just decided to be friends.
- Come in quickly. / - The traffic jam was terrible.
I had to cross the border from another city.
- The border from another city? / - My gosh.
You live in Bundang. Don't exaggerate.
- I told you to be punctual. / - Okay, I got it.
(A singer-song writer that's not limited to one era)
(When he sees food, he can't help but smile)
What on earth is that?
Alcohol? Alcohol?
- He seems genuinely happy. / - He's cute.
He looks so different now.
"Foodie and heavy drinker."
(Foodie and heavy drinker, Kim Hyunchul)
I can't believe I'm traveling with you.
Same here.
But the thing is that Battle Trip initially invited me.
I was meant to go abroad but couldn't schedule it...
You should've gone abroad.
Since I host a radio show,
I couldn't work out a schedule.
But this time, I made the time because
it's a domestic island special.
Will we fish in that island?
- No, it's not about fishing. / - He loves to fish, right?
There's a new road for bicycles.
- He likes biking. / - It's been newly built.
- So... / - You want to go biking?
Biking could be a good idea.
- They don't seem compatible. / - No, they don't.
I like biking, and you like fishing.
We can't do either one?
We must eat.
- You're an epicure. / - I'm the expert. Epicure?
I'm a glutton first.
I like to eat seafood and meat.
You do like seafood.
I'd jump to my feet if I can eat seafood.
On the south coast. And the Jeollanam-do region...
I love seafood too.
On top of that,
that's the area with the most clustered islands.
Which island do you want to visit?
I don't care.
I just want to go somewhere with a lot of good food.
Alright. I know this journalist.
- Who is it? / - He's a friend.
He's a regular guest on my radio show.
- His name is Lee Useok. / - Oh, him?
- Right, right. / - Useok?
- Welcome, welcome. / - Hello.
- That's him! / - Lee Useok.
Right.
We'll go to islands in Jeollanam-do.
- That's all we decided so far. / - An island.
We haven't chosen which island.
We don't know much about islands.
- But we want to eat seafood. / - Okay.
Both of us love seafood.
Yeosu has about 400 islands.
And you know the regions that are just islands?
- Wando. Jindo. / - Wando?
Nowadays, there are connecting bridges.
How about going to Wando to eat abalone?
Wando is known for great abalone.
It produces 80% of abalone in Korea?
The color of the ocean is great.
That's amazing.
- I'd love abalone in Wando. / - They're huge.
- That's the place of origin. / - You're right.
It doesn't compare to the fresh abalone in Seoul.
This is the place of origin that provides an experience.
What do you experience? Harvesting them?
That's right. You pick them yourself and eat them.
There's an island called Nohwado in Wando.
You can pick the abalone and eat them.
It's slightly cheaper too, and you can trust its origin.
And it's fresh too.
- Let's go to Wando. / - That's what we decided.
We decided on Wando, right?
You must visit Wando.
What else does Wando have besides abalone?
Wando is most famous for abalone.
If you've gone all the way there...
It'll be summer soon. You need to eat health food.
Health food!
Do you know what pike eels are?
- Eels from the sea. / - Of course, I know.
- Pike eels. / - I love pike eels.
- Pike eels. / - There's a pike eel stew.
Look at that.
And there are scorpion fish too.
- Scorpion fish? / - I know what it is.
It's incredibly delicious.
And you cannot miss this out.
- Cuttlefish, best type of squid. / - The cuttlefish.
Cuttlefish.
- That's delicious. / - They'll be out of season soon.
Cuttlefish is really delicious.
So abalone, scorpion fish.
- And... / - Pike eel.
- That's fresh. / - And cuttlefish.
If we can just eat all that...
We're going there to eat.
- This is such a great lineup. / - Of course.
- It's the Avengers. / - Yes, it is.
- Avengers. Iron Man. / - What a great lineup.
Wherever I travel to, food is the most important part.
If we're going to eat all this food...
I don't know what our opposing team will eat.
- They'll be so jealous. / - I doubt they can compete.
Thank you for your help.
- Thank you for your advice. / - Eat a lot.
- We will. / - We will eat a lot.
- I'll leave now. / - Bye.
If they study like that first, they'll have to win.
When people go to Wando for abalone,
they'll get their money's worth.
We'll be eating abalone from the place of origin.
That's right. It sounds like a food paradise.
I feel like I'll gain weight.
- You must wear loose pants there. / - Exactly.
- So the pants can stretch. / - So they can stretch.
He always unbuttons his pants.
To go to Wando,
we have to pass Haenam, Ttangkkeut.
- It's on our way to Wando. / - Right.
First off, it takes around 4 to 6 hours.
It takes a long time.
Let's head out at dawn. We'll leave at dawn.
We have to come up with our tour name.
We must come up with one.
Why are we traveling together?
What?
- Why are we traveling together? / - For food.
If we actually find an answer to that question...
- That'd be... / - We're going for the answer.
So why did we travel together on this trip?
It's a question mark for now.
But later on, it will become an exclamation mark.
- The question mark will straighten out. / - Curious.
Why are we traveling together?
(Traditional beauty vs. Healthy beauty)
(Breakfast meal vs. Grilled fish meal)
(Abalone experience vs. Abalone bread)
(Raw fish center vs. Arboretum)
(Hanok stay vs. Pike eel stew)
(4 a.m., Bundang, Seongnam, Gyeonggi-do)
At 4 a.m.
- Hey. / - Hey. Come here.
- Hey. / - Good work getting here.
- Sorry, I'm late. / - I'll load this...
(The "younger" Hyunchul does all the hard work)
Will we have fun on our trip?
We must find out why we're traveling together.
Yeah.
Okay...
Let's go.
- Let's head out. / - Okay.
Let's get going.
Let's go.
We're actually doing this.
- It took a long time. / - Wow.
5 hours.
So you arrived around the morning.
(Ttangkkeut, the edge)
(The start of the end of Korea, Haenam)
I can see the ocean.
It's green on this side.
And it's the ocean on this side.
- It feels refreshing. / - How beautiful.
Jeolla-do and Gyeongsang-do are different.
We set out at dawn. We must at least see the end.
Let's drive to the end.
Look at him. The elders always have their hand
on the stick even when they drive an automatic.
- I didn't know. / - Even with automatic transmission.
He's from the manual transmission era.
- Since he learned to drive with a stick. / - Right.
Back then, they only had manual transmission.
- He leaves his hand there. / - When I drive...
(Janghyuck will buy breakfast)
There's a traditional Korean restaurant here.
I think they have a breakfast menu.
There's a separate menu for breakfast.
I think it costs about $10.
Jeolla-do Korean meal.
- Is this it? / - Yeah, this is it.
They have a breakfast meal.
It's written there.
I love restaurants that serve breakfast.
That's a heavy meal for breakfast.
That's the standard spread.
- The breakfast was great. / - Indeed, it is.
It's nice and neat.
With Jeolla-do spreads, there are
the mustard leaf kimchi and the seasoned vegetables.
Every dish was delicious. Everything there was good.
(The unique taste of Jeolla-do home cooking)
- Salted fish. / - Is that soy sauce marinated crab?
Soy sauce marinated crabs.
It's a side dish for breakfast?
- That's right. / - That's right.
- Look at that. / - Stone pot rice.
- There's hijikia in the rice. / - That's really delicious.
- Marinated crabs. / - What a breakfast.
Marinated crabs for breakfast?
(A meal with 13 side dishes at a reasonable price)
I think Jeolla-do food is just like that.
That looks good.
They serve breakfast from 8 to 11 a.m.
We're going to have the stone pot meal.
That's the breakfast.
- That's only $10? / - Only $10?
- That's cheap. / - That's amazing.
I see the crocks in the back there.
I can tell this place is good now.
It means that they make their own paste.
Yes, they probably do.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm hungry too.
(It should be served right about now)
Right here. Thank you.
We were hungry.
- Seasoned vegetables. / - Look at that.
You're sitting like a mermaid.
You know people that can't sit cross-legged.
He has a bad back.
My gosh, you're giving us a lot.
Are you speaking in Jeolla-do dialect?
Thank you.
- The crabs. / - The crabs look delicious.
- That's rock crab. / - Marinated crab is delicious.
With Jeollanam-do food, it's all about the side dishes.
Even the anchovies are fresh.
Even anchovies taste good there.
The anchovy is alive when it's been fried.
It's like they fried it live. Even though it's dried.
- And I love how cheap it is. / - The dried laver.
- That's Wando laver? / - That's pickled dried laver.
- Pickled in soy sauce. / - That's pickled dried laver.
They pickled dried lavers?
It's so good. Really good.
This is probably the pickled dried laver.
(The main dish is served next)
- I'm hungry. / - Rice in a hot pot is the best.
- What's that? / - Braised mackerel with aged kimchi.
- Aged kimchi? / - What's this?
This is bean paste soup.
- All this costs $10? / - That's so cheap.
All of this.
- So this meal for two costs $20? / - Yes.
That's like a full dinner.
I'll have a taste.
- But that's only $10. / - $10 per person.
All that on a meal for $10...
They even have hijikia.
They even have jujubes and pumpkin.
The rice by itself would be good.
That was amazing.
The Jeolla-do stone pot rice is amazing.
I'm about to cry.
- It's like there's oil on it. / - You're right.
I do this...
You have to pour the water.
I pour some water in it, right?
(What?)
You're supposed to pour the hot water!
That's cold water?
Hey, it's not that water!
- What's this? / - Hey.
Is this your first time having stone pot rice?
No. Oh, it's here.
We have hot water. Why use the cold water?
- Goodness. Unbelievable. / - Let me pour it for you.
- Let me pour it for you. / - It's still good like that.
- It's not bad. / - Because the stone is hot.
For breakfast, pour cold water.
That matches the time.
Let's eat.
- Try the rice. / - The rice itself must be good.
After traveling for 6 hours...
- Did he just have 3 spoonfuls? / - He's only eating rice.
Did you just have 3 spoonfuls?
I had 2 bowls of rice.
(Driving must've been tough for Hyunchul)
Try this.
(Eat up, friend)
Have this.
It's delicious in a different way...
When you eat from the place of origin.
That's the difference.
(It's delicious when you mix rice with the crab)
- My gosh. / - Goodness.
- Eat up. / - Nice and neat.
(Just eating rice again)
That rice tastes good just with the soy sauce.
There you go!
We shouldn't throw out this soy sauce.
I'll mix rice with it.
(Mix the sauce and the innards with the rice well)
(A spoonful of the rice makes him happy)
- It gets rid of all your fatigue. / - It's so good.
Huh? Oh?
It's so good, I don't have time to say it's good.
(Saying how delicious it is would be a waste of time)
- This tastes really good. / - Mix it.
I didn't see his wriggling toes.
(He had no idea about this while traveling)
This is 100% about the taste of kimchi.
Jeollanam-do is famous for its kimchi.
- Gosh, the kimchi. / - Look at the color.
Jeolla-do kimchi!
- Jeolla-do kimchi... / - It's the best.
The color looks appetizing.
I must choose a long strip.
Get a spoonful of the rice.
Scoop up some rice.
- It can't be bad with that color. / - That's how you eat.
- Put the kimchi on top of rice. / - Right, right.
To Koreans, rice is medicine.
(Time to feast)
It's so good.
If it's that delicious, you can't speak.
- You can't talk if it's good. / - Right.
I really eat as if the food is good.
(Slurp)
This is the best.
This is 100% the flavor of the kimchi.
Since we had it, we know how it tastes.
I'm really getting hungry.
I'm getting hungry.
(The result of eating with relish)
(Empty)
- You must've been hungry. / - Yes.
(Cleared)
I have to figure out why we're traveling together.
It's the Why Are We Traveling Together Tour.
Now that I've had this breakfast,
I'm glad I came with you.
And I'm glad I came with you.
I think I've found a small reason to travel together.
But this isn't everything.
This place is full of food. There's so much food here.
The first meal was awesome.
The scorched rice water.
- That was awesome. / - You must finish with that.
When you drink something warm at the end,
it warms up your insides.
(They set to the dock to head to Nohwado)
- We'll take the ferry there. / - Yes, right.
(End of the Peninsula to Bogildo)
By the way, it's quite windy.
- The flag is fluttering hard. / - It's so windy.
It's no joke.
The ferry... It was really windy that day.
Goodness.
My goodness.
(They arrive at the dock)
That's the ferry.
(As they arrive at the ocean, the wind gets stronger)
This ferry goes to Bogildo and Nohwado.
That's how it is but...
There's so much wind today.
(Will they be able to take the ferry?)
This is where they sell the tickets.
- It's closed. / - It's closed.
- It's closed. / - Hey, come here.
"All ferries are suspended due to bad weather."
- All ferries? / - My gosh.
- What a shame. / - East, south and Jeju-do...
Is on a high seas warning.
The waves are 4m to 6m high.
That was such a shame.
We just needed to take a ferry.
(All ships must stop and evacuate)
It says you have to evacuate.
I guess they won't be sailing all day.
- Why does it have to be today? / - Then...
That was such a shame.
I don't think they're sailing.
The wind stopped the ferries.
Sing us a song to express this disappointment.
(He wants Janghyuck to sing a song now?)
(He complies with the request)
Right?
(What a nice choice of song)
("About Romance" by Choi Baekho)
You're coughing.
(These middle-aged men don't lose their cool)
- The color of the sky is pretty. / - Right.
- You almost fell, right? / - Yes.
- He staggered a little. / - It could've been really bad.
- He didn't see the step. / - My gosh.
I was going to listen to the sad boat horn and go.
Hey, this place is awesome.
(They're admiring Maemseom)
It's cold.
- Let's take a photo at least. / - What a shame.
- Hyunchul. / - Yes?
Since we're here, shouldn't we take a photo?
- With what? With this? / - Or with this?
1, 2, 3.
(Why Travel Together Tour, Ttangkkeut Village)
What a nice picture.
(Let's pick abalone next time)
(Goodbye, abalone)
That was a shame.
- It was. / - Such a shame.
- Let's... / - Let's ask the local experts.
- Let's ask. / - Since they're locals.
They'll tell us the answers.
Okay.
What a shame.
- Let's go. / - Let's get going.
Geez.
Why is it so windy?
So you gave up on picking abalone?
Yes, we did.
- You gave up? / - No harvesting.
We just ate what was harvested by others.
We just focused on eating.
Is it because we're near the ocean?
- The weather is so unpredictable. / - It is.
It's suddenly got cold.
This is a tourist information center.
Let's go ask them here.
Isn't it this way?
- Where is the way in? / - Here it is.
(Looking around)
- Hello. / - Hello.
We should talk to them over there.
(This is where you talk to them)
That's the staff entrance.
They went through the staff entrance.
My goodness.
- Okay. / - Roll camera.
- Hello. / - Look at him act like nothing happened.
- He makes me worried. / - He's such an old person.
This is our first time traveling in Wando.
We're now in Haenam, not Wando.
- Right, Haenam. / - We're in Haenam.
We wanted to go to Nohwado.
But the ferries aren't sailing today.
We got some recommendations from the locals.
Do you have any places you can recommend for us?
If you like drinking...
Drinking?
- Drinking? / - There's a rice wine place...
- "Drinking?" / - How many types did he just say that?
Drinking?
(50, the perfect age to appreciate alcohol)
- A distillery? / - Or you can go here.
- Go here? / - The Duryunsan tourist site...
Is a nice place.
- It's cold, so... / - I'd love to visit the distillery.
So this is the famous alcohol in Haenam, right?
The place has a great view as well.
The alcohol is made with glutinous rice.
You shouldn't miss a place like that.
- That looks delicious. / - It looks so thick.
Looks nice, right?
(You are my destiny)
Would you like a map?
- Yes, please. / - Yes. Thank you.
Let's go. Let's go!
I really feel like going to the distillery now.
(Why Travel Together Tour)
(Traditional distillery)
There are mountains all around.
What a nice view.
I wonder what the traditional alcohol tastes like.
I'm really looking forward to it.
- I think it'll taste unique. / - It'll be unique.
I'll look up traditional Haenam liquor.
Make sure you do a proper search.
Of course. I'm a search expert.
It's mainly made with glutinous rice.
- Glutinous rice. / - And...
- It must be thick then. / - Exactly.
And they don't add sweeteners in it.
I won't be able to drive after dinner.
Then let's buy the drink and go back.
- That's a great idea. / - We'll buy the drink...
Yes, yes.
Let's go to the fish market afterwards,
buy raw fish, and go to our accommodation.
They don't really sell that alcohol at supermarkets.
You have to go there.
(They arrive at the traditional distillery)
Goodness.
(It's less windy here)
I think this is a distillery.
Because I have a great sense of smell.
For alcohol.
- He looks much happier now. / - Right.
- It was built in 1927? / - 1927?
It's almost 100 years old.
They still have the garden from the colonial era.
It's 90 years old.
It's almost 100 years old.
(Here, they brew traditional alcohol with just rice)
How long has it been since this distillery was built?
It's been 92 years.
- 92 years? / - 92 years.
We brew the alcohol
with organic glutinous rice from the local farms.
It has unique taste from the glutinous rice.
It's not just rice. It's glutinous rice.
Organic glutinous rice.
You play songs on tape here?
Isn't that really old?
That's because...
When we make alcohol,
we want to keep the microbes happy
to produce great tasting alcohol.
That's why we play music here.
They play music to help microbes grow well.
They even care about the microbes' feelings.
- Exactly. / - This looks amazing.
Rice wine should be made in an analog way.
- I see. / - You're right.
The visitors like that.
(A beautiful garden with an analog vibe)
- There's a garden there. / - It's beautiful.
- It is beautiful. / - It looks nice on screen...
But if you go there in person...
The trees there are 70 to 80 years old.
- The trees there are very old. / - How adorable.
What is that? They're so cute.
(We're not alcoholics)
Look at this tree here.
"Grandson of Genghis Khan from the Yuan Dynasty..."
Really?
Whose grandson?
- He's so weird. / - Genghis Khan's grandson is a tree?
"Grandson of Genghis Khan..."
It says this is Genghis Khan's grandson.
His grandson is a tree?
(He has never heard of it)
No, you have to read it to the end.
- It's Kublai Khan. / - Kublai Khan is his grandson.
(It's still confusing)
- Kublai Khan is his grandson. / - That's it.
He planted the tree there.
He planted this tree here.
It's fascinating that a 700-year-old tree is still alive.
- You have many flaws, Hyunchul. / - Yes.
I just learned that now too.
(What would it taste like?)
You have to smell it first.
- I wish you good health. / - Thank you.
You shouldn't give me too much.
How good would that be?
- It was incredible. / - It looks so good.
(They smell it first)
There you go.
This is proper rice wine.
Yes.
How is it? I'm so curious.
(Cho Janghyuck's Trivial Encyclopedia)
(Traditional Alcohol)
The most commonly used sweetener is aspartame.
This doesn't have that.
Rice wine used to contain 6% alcohol content.
So you had to add water to it.
But then it becomes bland, so they added aspartame.
But this one is not mixed with water.
It's thick.
It tastes like 12% original rice wine.
That rice wine doesn't expire too quick,
even without aspartame.
- How long does it last? / - It lasts about 20 days.
- But... / - 20 days?
That's only if you store it in a proper way.
It doesn't mean anything though.
If you just leave rice wine for a long time,
it becomes vinegar.
- I see. / - It ages more.
- Like wine. / - Just like wine vinegar.
Let me have another glass.
- You want to have it too, right? / - I do.
It's very thick.
(He must be dying to try it)
- Hey. / - Just smell it.
I'm not saying you should drink it.
Here you are.
(They spontaneously came here, but seem to love it)
- Look at me. / - Why?
Why can't you look at me? You want to drink?
You can drink it soon.
- Wait there. / - We'll drink it...
You should wait there.
Wait there.
Don't waste it. Let me drink it.
Don't drink too much.
This is amazing.
(He's relieved that they couldn't sail today)
Like this. See? See?
Don't drink any more.
We should go have breakfast.
My hand just moved without thinking.
It poured without me thinking.
(This is delicious)
When I drink, I drink properly.
- I also... / - Here you are.
- Here's your rice wine. / - Thank you!
We bought a box of it.
I didn't drink anything, and I'm carrying this.
They drank 6 bottles that night.
Imagine how good it was.
Let's not go to a restaurant for abalone.
Let's go to a fish market nearby.
Let's buy fish there and eat at our place.
Our opponents are Seungsoo and Jeongcheol, right?
What is famous in Tongyeong?
I know it's famous for fishing spots.
- Oysters. / - I see. It's famous for oysters.
You can't compare oyster with abalone.
Oysters in Tongyeong are delicious.
In Tongyeong, there's this famous restaurant
that has a Japanese name.
- Dachi. / - Dachi.
- You're right. / - You can't compare.
- You can't forget that place. / - Lots of good places.
(It's easy to get to Wando thanks to the bridge)
(They cross Wandodaegyo and head to Wando)
Wandodaegyo looks beautiful.
- That's Jang Bogo. / - Jang Bogo.
Emperor of the sea, Jang Bogo.
(It's the biggest abalone producer in Korea)
(Lots of fresh seafood)
- Cuttlefish. / - It's cuttlefish.
(Wando is in uncontaminated)
There's a seafood center.
(30 minutes from distillery to Wando abalone street)
It's cold.
It's cold. I see abalone.
There's a statue of an abalone.
(Welcome to Wando)
It's a statue of an abalone.
- Look at that. / - Wow.
This is how famous abalone is there.
What is that fish called?
- This one. / - Striped sea bream.
Striped beakfish!
(Cho Janghyuck's Trivial Encyclopedia)
(Fish of the South Sea)
- It's striped beakfish. / - It has the same stripes.
It's striped beakfish.
What fish is this?
That one is...
That's what you eat in Jeju-do.
- Sawedged perch? / - But that's not it.
That's just sea bass.
I see.
It's called "gumunjaengi" in Jeju-do.
- "Gumunjaengi?" / - Yes.
In Seoul, you only get flatfish and rockfish.
But there...
- All sorts. / - Expensive fish.
They sell lots of expensive fish.
They have delicious fish.
Wow, this wind...
This doesn't feel like the wind of May.
We couldn't take the boat,
so we came up with that plan on the fly.
Going to a raw fish center and buying the fish.
- Then eat at your accommodation? / - That's right.
- That's basically a seafood market. / - Right.
That's the cheapest way.
- Does this mean 6 of them are 1kg? / - Yes.
The abalone is so big.
Exactly. The bigger it is, the more expensive.
The big ones taste different to the smaller ones.
- 8 to 9 of them cost $40. / - That's too expensive.
- $40? / - $40.
- This one looks good. / - 8 to 9 of them cost $40?
- Should we get these? / - I need to haggle.
I'm usually good at haggling.
If they sell 4 or 5 abalones at $30,
it's considered to be expensive.
- The abalones are very big. / - They're big.
The bigger ones are more expensive.
8 abalones is a little under 1kg.
9 makes it a little over 1kg.
- I see. / - We'll take 9 then.
- 9 for 1kg. / - We'll take 9.
- Do you want me to slice them? / - No, no.
- You're taking them home? / - We'll take them.
We'll take them and...
Okay.
3, 4, 5, 6...
- Do we need fish? / - We don't.
In Wando, you should eat abalone.
(I can't wait to try them)
Can you cut up half of them. Just half.
Where can we eat here? Can we eat in there?
There are seats over there.
Hey, they sell cuttlefish here.
- Cuttlefish. / - They sell cuttlefish.
This is cuttlefish. It's the best.
- It's $20 each. / - It's cuttlefish.
- Each? / - It's expensive.
- It's luxurious seafood. / - Should we buy two?
Let's take this home.
- Could you cut it for us? / - Please cut it for us.
- How much is a murex? / - It's $15.
- Each? / - No, per kilogram.
Per kilo...
We'll take it.
The murex is awesome.
It's normally for 4 but I'll throw in one extra.
They had murex there.
Murex tastes really good!
It's really good. I thought it was only in Jeju-do.
- They sell it in Wando too. / - It's very crunchy.
- Abalone. / - That's the stuff.
- That's a cuttlefish. / - This is incomparable.
Wow, cuttlefish...
Sesame oil and seeds...
- It actually looks pretty. / - With the innards.
- With the innards. / - That's the murex.
The color looks pretty.
You get the abalone and the innards.
You can't have that without soju, right?
- Right. / - Not that.
- Abalone and murex. / - Murex.
Hey, hey, hey.
The innards here and those look different, don't they?
This is beige, and this is green.
Why do you think that is?
They're both abalone innards.
- Female and male? / - Male and female.
- I got it right. / - You did.
- I want this one. / - Let's taste it first.
Start with the innards?
How did you know you're supposed to eat that first?
(Abalone innards are more nutritious than the flesh)
You can eat it just like that because it's fresh.
Not everyone can eat that.
It's savory.
When you eat abalone, you must eat the innards.
Abalone from Wando eat fresh seaweed.
- It looks so fresh. / - It looks delicious.
Some people are crazy about it.
Abalone innards are really delicious.
It's really delicious.
It has an amazing texture.
You must eat it where it's produced.
How is it different from the ones in Seoul?
The texture is different.
- The texture is different? / - Yes.
While being transported, they get tired.
- They have feelings too. / - You have to consider that.
Coming all the way to Seoul.
You can't get these for this price at restaurants.
She did nothing but cut the abalones.
You can eat a lot of them if you eat here.
We only ate half of the abalones we bought.
You said you'd cut the rest of the abalones.
We still have half left.
(The rest of them will soon show up with butter)
We will grill them with butter later at our accommodation.
Janghyuck will grill them.
Try the murex.
- This is... / - Here you are.
- That's very crunchy. / - It's delicious.
It's fun to chew.
With this...
I think 80% of seafood is about the texture.
- That crunchiness. / - The texture is amazing.
It's so delicious. After eating the abalone,
my mind is blown away.
(His dad jokes are the hindrance to their victory)
This is why my team is in trouble.
Thank you.
I've been hoping you wouldn't tell those jokes.
This might sound childish now
but you'll remember it and laugh before you sleep.
I will never laugh.
Let's hurry and take these back to our accommodation.
We should eat them properly
with the traditional alcohol we got earlier.
- Alright. / - Let me take one last piece.
Let's go.
It's like watching our dads.
It was a torture to eat it without alcohol.
You guys have a lot of stamina.
- We do. / - We had to travel a lot.
You should be exhausted by now.
He even drove the car himself.
- We're not old men. / - That's our accommodation.
It's a hanok-style place.
- It looks beautiful. / - This is nice.
- It's hanok. / - Hanok.
Look over there. Look at the sunset.
(Hyunchul booked a hanok pension)
I have never reserved such a place.
- It looks amazing. / - Beautiful.
It's the original hanok.
(It's time to finish their traditional dish tour)
- I can't wait. / - It's not just hanok-themed.
Hang on a second.
I've never slept in a hanok house before.
This is a real hanok house.
- It was great inside. / - Look.
It's cheap also.
- It's really cheap. / - It's about $50 per night.
It was a special offer.
I found a special offer.
(Inside the house is just like a traditional hanok too)
There is a bathroom inside.
It's really nice there.
It's become cold.
- Gosh, it's cold. / - It felt like -5 that day.
- It was very cold. / - It was really cold.
- Let's get changed. / - Put on long pants.
(Middle-aged men afraid of the cold)
You should wear another layer.
This should be enough.
Should this be enough?
How many layers are you putting on?
- Here you go. / - Thank you.
Hey, this will be aired in June.
But I'm cold.
(You haven't seen all of the abalone yet)
(Abalone grilled with butter on charcoal)
- You grilled that yourself? / - This was amazing.
My wish is to eat as much abalone grilled with butter
as I can.
It looks really delicious.
That looks fun.
(Shall we begin?)
Let's check out...
- Janghyuck's grilled abalone. / - Grilled abalone.
We need to rinse them at least once.
I just wash them roughly like this.
Once they're grilled, they'll be clean.
You're right. The bacteria will all die from the heat.
- I love eating outdoors like that. / - Let's grill them.
People who go fishing are good at this.
Let me slice the butter...
And put on top of the abalone like this.
Now this is grilled abalones with butter.
They're moving.
You wouldn't be able to imagine
how incredibly delicious they were.
That's "bbada" not "butter."
What on earth?
- We used to call it "bbada." / - My goodness.
- That's right. / - So true.
- It's "bbada," right? / - Yes, "bbada" bibimbap.
That's right, "bbada" bibimbap.
This is hot. Do you see it?
It's trying to spit out the butter.
- Here we go. / - Pour the rice wine.
He waited a long time.
- Have some. / - He can properly enjoy it.
This is the traditional alcohol from Haenam.
- We came all the way to Wando. / - All the way here.
Good job.
(They gulp down the alcohol)
(Now he can quench his thirst)
- Just drink up. / - Two bowls in a row.
(One is not enough)
(Shaking)
He just cleared a bottle.
He does everything in three's.
- 3 spoons of rice. / - 3 bowls of rice wine.
(Now this is satisfying)
Let me try the cuttlefish.
This is amazing.
Amazing.
(Let me take a piece too)
It's really delicious.
This is different from what I had in Seoul.
(Crunchy)
I don't know if you can hear this but the texture.
It's just awesome.
And...
The texture of the bone of the cuttlefish...
It's like eating cartilage.
No, the cuttlebone is removed.
I mean the rest of it.
- There's nothing left. / - Really?
They don't match.
- He says it's not there. / - It shouldn't be there.
Do you know the triangular part of the cuttlefish?
- That's this crunchy part. / - Really? I see.
(It doesn't matter which part as long as it's delicious)
Come here. Take a piece each.
Try a piece.
- He's so nice. / - He is.
Old people care a lot about the staff.
(Janghyuck takes care of the hungry staff)
You have the sauce on your mouth.
Open your mouth wide.
Over there.
I should cover the abalones.
That way, it'll cook faster.
We're eating the seafood that has been consumed
since long time ago.
- So... / - Wait a minute.
Hold on. I'm sorry.
That's more important to me.
It's doesn't feel like we're drinking.
We need to get an insert shot.
It looks like you're interrupting on purpose.
It's abalone with butter.
- Goodness. / - That looks delicious.
- Is it available in Seoul? / - That's amazing.
Because the abalone is fresh,
it absorbs butter really well.
Smell it.
- Don't cut it too small. / - I'll cut it this big.
That's good.
It's amazing.
With this, we'll eat the innards later.
Okay.
Since you've been through a lot today.
- I'll try it. / - Here you go.
You can have it. But we need salt, so I'll open this.
(After having a sip, he takes a piece of abalone)
- We don't need salt. / - We don't?
- No? Is it seasoned naturally? / - Yes.
- Okay. / - Was it really good?
- You don't need to dip it in salt. / - It's good.
You grilled it in butter. There's no need for salt.
It doesn't need seasoning.
Can you taste the butter?
- Yes, totally. / - Right?
Oyster can't beat that.
(He's confident about the abalone)
When you normally go to a pension,
you grill meat.
But it's quite refreshing to see seafood.
That pension wasn't that expensive.
(It's not a fancy meal, but it's very delicious)
We came here wondering why we came together.
I think I've got about 50% of the answer.
I agree.
Anyway, for tomorrow,
we'll do a tour geared toward having health food.
- We'll have to start early. / - It'll be fun.
- Yes. / - Cheers.
- Cheers. / - For our trip.
Let's have a good trip.
People will think we're heavy drinkers.
We practically are.
The atmosphere is nice.
- Isn't it? / - It's perfect for rice wine.
(The darkness fades, and the sun starts to shine)
(The trees shine brightly in the morning sun)
(It has such a beautiful, quaint atmosphere)
- That hanok pension is great. / - Isn't it so pretty?
Yes.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
Let's get going.
Hanok is really nice.
- This was my first time. / - This was your first time?
Yes, it feels nice. I feel really refreshed.
- Let's get in and go. / - Alright.
Here we go.
The weather was fantastic.
It's really nice to take your kids to a hanok pension
with grass yard.
Of course.
Today, we're having a health food tour.
Lee Useok's recommendations.
Grilled fish, abalone bread, pike eel stew.
Ripped and cut. The ripped and cut tour.
What do you think? Look at this muscle.
It'll get bigger after I eat health food.
What muscle? You don't have any.
Please add some with CG.
There's scorpion fish.
- Scorpion fish? / - I know.
First of all, it tastes amazing.
Spicy fish soup is good
but there's a grilled fish restaurant.
- You eat it grilled? / - Yes.
They even debone it for you.
(You can enjoy delicious fresh fish)
(With their hands)
(They debone it for you)
(They arrive at the fish restaurant)
This restaurant reminds me of a beer bar or a cafe...
- In the 1970s. / - It does look like a cafe.
- Doesn't it? / - Yes.
It looks like an old Western restaurant.
- I think it used to be. / - Yes.
- We'll have the grilled fish. / - Grilled fish meal.
It's $15.
I guess it's a proper meal.
Pour me a drink.
(Here, take some fresh water)
Tap for you.
It's water. We don't drink every day.
I know it's water, but let's have a toast.
We don't need to toast.
We drank all night last night.
What do you mean all night? We drank briefly.
(They drink water instead of alcohol in the morning)
(Finally, the meal arrives)
Thank you.
- Here they are, the side dishes. / - Nice.
- There are so many. / - I love that about Jeolla-do.
That's great. They bring out so much.
And they're all delicious.
- What is that? / - What's that?
Usually, they give spinach bean paste stew
or curled mallow bean paste stew.
- You can smell the ocean. / - You definitely can.
- It's unusual. / - I've never had that bean paste stew.
(The flavor suits the middle-aged men)
This is fantastic.
- They're curing their hangovers. / - They are.
(It looks like they're eating to cure their hangover)
(Here comes the real taste of the sea)
Can we eat all this?
(The grilled fish from the South Sea)
- Red sea bream. / - Spanish mackerel.
This one is scorpion fish.
They give you free abalone porridge.
- Free abalone porridge? / - What?
They could run out but they provide it every day.
- Abalone porridge is free. / - Really?
As a side dish.
(They're lucky to have abalone porridge)
This is scorpion fish.
- It's not a big fish / - It's not big.
Scorpion fish is a type of a rockfish.
- Red rockfish. / - Red rockfish.
You can't get much raw fish from rockfish.
- That's right. / - Yes.
- I'll debone it for you. / - Okay.
You'll do that for us?
(Excited)
People from Seoul love this the most.
(The service is added on top of the delicious fish)
- She took the fish apart for us. / - She did it all for us.
(The bones are all taken out)
This is the bestseller.
- Alright. / - Enjoy.
- Thank you. / - This is...
- This is scorpion fish. / - Yes.
We'll have to try the scorpion fish first.
(They eat the famous scorpion fish first)
Different fish is caught depending on the season.
- So they serve different fish. / - This is scorpion fish.
- I have to use my hands. / - Yes, use your hands.
(I'll have the delicious one twice)
The scorpion fish is good.
- I see why he said it was good. / - Lee Useok...
If he says it's good, it means it's really delicious.
The scorpion fish is really good.
- It looks like a dried corvina. / - It looks a bit hard.
- Dried yellow corvina. / - It's a bit dried.
- It's good when they're dried. / - Half-dried is good.
That's why fish was dried in the past.
- It's as good as corvina. / - That's right.
(He takes a spoonful of rice with the scorpion fish)
(He uses both hands)
Actually, this...
(Cho Janghyuck's Trivial Encyclopedia)
(Fish)
They used to throw this out when they caught this.
- Scorpion fish? / - Yes.
- Why? / - Its tail fin is poisonous.
If you get stung, you swell up.
It looks ugly and scary...
- They threw it out. / - When you fish on a boat...
The captain tells you not to touch it.
- They'd toss it out. / - He'd say not to touch it.
- You throw it out. / - They didn't think it tasted good.
So they'd throw it out and catch red sea bream.
It's really different.
The characteristics of this region
is that they dry the fish.
- That's right. / - They dry it, then grill it.
- That's why... / - So...
- It's half dried. / - It's chewy.
- It has a different texture. / - I think so.
The texture is really different
when it's dried.
When it's dried...
The size becomes smaller, but it's more nutritious.
Dried fish is more nutritious.
(Up next is a rare fish)
This is the sea bream, right?
(The prince of the sea, red sea bream)
- It's a red sea bream. / - Red sea bream.
- It's a red sea bream. / - Look at the oil.
Gosh, that with rice...
That yellow color...
You can probably finish a bowl of rice with that.
- With scorched rice water. / - With barley tea.
- Barley tea or green tea. / - Yes.
- That's right. / - Yes.
(One bite for you)
(One bite for me)
(Eating rice with red sea bream)
It tastes good with beer.
(He's reminded of a cold glass of beer)
(Beer)
It's really delicious.
(Janghyuck uses both hands)
Look how fast his hands are.
- Janghyuck has quick hands. / - That looks so good.
We aren't talking much.
- Because we need to eat. / - Because it's delicious.
We can't do two things at once.
(I'm just going to eat)
I'm going to gain weight.
I knew we'd gain weight
as soon as we decided on Haenam and Wando.
- That's right. / - I'm full.
That was so good.
(Let's go have more health food)
(Why Travel Together Tour)
(Abalone bread and seaweed latte)
- Abalone bread? / - I don't know about this one.
Ladies, take a close look.
(The whole abalone grabs your attention)
One whole fresh abalone is added in pastry.
- What? / - That's abalone on top?
There's an abalone on top.
- One whole abalone. / - It's a bit unfamiliar.
- Hello. / - Welcome.
This is the abalone bread.
Does it cost like $30 each?
- No. / - No, not that much.
Is it like a madeleine?
- It's a cupcake. / - A seaweed latte?
Two abalone breads and...
I hear the seaweed latte...
- Is famous here. / - Yes.
- We'll get one each. / - Okay.
Is it like putting anchovy...
- In a sandwich? / - No, it doesn't taste like that.
(The whole collection of Wando's signature desserts)
(Seaweed latte, loquat lemon tea, abalone bread)
- This is it. / - This is the problematic scene.
This is the problematic scene.
This isn't right.
- Yes, this is too much. / - My goodness.
Just sit there and eat.
He really is clumsy.
I don't think we should sit with roses.
What is that?
We were going to sit there but we couldn't stand it.
Let's try this.
This is abalone bread.
I'm so curious about the abalone bread.
A whole abalone is in it but it's not that expensive.
It was amazing.
This is unique.
(Hyunchul takes a bite first)
(Janghyuck also takes a bite)
They also put the abalone innards in the batter.
- It looks a little green. / - That's why it's green?
Yes, that's right.
This is delicious. It's good.
- It's delicious. / - You can't imagine the taste, right?
Right.
Isn't the bread sweet?
- It's more savory than sweet. / - It's savory.
It's savory.
This abalone bread is patented.
I'm going to buy some
and give it to my children...
- And wife at home. / - Give some to your wife.
- It's really unique. / - I want to try it at least once.
I strongly recommend the seaweed latte.
It tastes strongly of seaweed.
It kind of tastes like it has ground kelp in it.
Seaweeds is sticky.
I thought I wouldn't like the texture.
But I'm really surprised.
You know the taste of latte, right?
- Yes. / - It's not slippery like seaweed.
They got rid of all of the slipperiness.
It feels like the taste of herbs at the end.
You really need to try this.
I really recommend it. It's really delicious.
- The seaweed latte. / - Those are loquats.
(It's time to try the loquat lemon tea)
- It's similar to ice tea. / - Right?
Like lemon tea.
It's called loquat lemon tea.
What comes to mind when you think of loquats?
- The instrument. / - The instrument?
There is a fruit that only grows in the southern area.
- Fruit? / - Yes.
- Let's try this. / - You drink from that side.
It grows in Wando because it's warm.
(What does the loquat lemon tea taste like?)
- Is it good? / - Try it.
I've never tasted something like this before.
(Hyunchul also takes a sip of loquat lemon tea)
I've never experienced this fragrance before.
- It's good. / - It's unique.
The leaves of loquats really look like the instrument.
- Really? / - That's how it got its name.
These days, people not only eat health food
to be invigorated but they also take in fresh air.
When you go to arboretums,
it's full of phytoncide.
People say that phytoncide cures cancer.
Do you like to walk?
Of course.
I'm full. Let's walk.
I heard that there was an arboretum near here.
Okay, let's go.
An arboretum?
They have an amazing a broadleaf forest there.
It's really amazing.
I heard that there was an arboretum near here.
- Wow. / - Just like that.
It's really amazing.
(Fresh water and fresh air)
(The largest temperate forest habitat in the world)
(Wando Arboretum)
(Built in 1991, the size of 2,800 soccer stadiums)
(The largest temperate forest habitat in the world)
(25 minutes to the arboretum)
The arboretum must be deep in the mountains.
Wow.
(They arrive at the arboretum)
The weather is amazing today.
We had a lot of fine dust...
- Let's take in some phytoncide. / - Yes, yes.
Where are we headed to?
- We're here right now. / - Yes.
We have to go up to the forest museum.
I think there's a waterside deck
that's decorated beautifully.
- Let's take a walk around here. / - Let's go.
- Let's just take a light walk. / - Okay.
I found out that this place exists in Wando today.
Same here. Who would have thought the largest
broadleaf tree arboretum would be in Wando?
Right? We only knew because we came.
You know a little about trees, don't you?
I don't know a lot, but I have a lot of interest.
(Cho Janghyuck's Trivial Encyclopedia)
Do you also know about trees?
There's also a tree edition.
It's just trivial knowledge.
I saw that there was
a red-wood evergreen oak that I've never heard of.
It's called red-wood because it's red.
This is the red-wood evergreen oak.
It emits a lot more phytoncide than normal trees.
It emits a lot more.
The air is really clean there.
Doesn't it feel so refreshing?
- I think the air smells sweet. / - You're right.
Let's go down here.
Look here.
Look at the water.
(A cool stream of water is flowing)
(And a waterfall in the middle of the arboretum)
This is so nice. Lots to see.
- It was really nice. / - Yes.
- Places like this are amazing. / - This place is so nice.
- You should jump in. / - Can you swim there?
- No. / - Did you know Wando had that?
It's really pretty.
It's the largest broadleaf forest in the world.
I want to go in there.
(It looks refreshing)
You can put your cameras in the water.
Can I put it in?
They said that we can put our cameras in the water.
Really?
(If you say so)
Hey, come here.
Can you see this?
They're marsh snails.
Those are marsh snails.
If you go to Chungcheong-do...
You need clean water.
- You have marsh snail soup. / - They live in clean water.
They have tables and benches all around.
(Where will they go next after seeing the waterfall?)
Wow. What is this?
(They go to the waterside deck)
That looks like a palace.
(They're captivated by the charm of the arboretum)
Look at this place.
Look at the walls all lined up here.
What song comes to mind here?
"What a Wonderful World."
-  I see trees of green  / - Not that.
A Korean song.
How about...  In the afternoon sun
It's a sad song though.
I forgot that they were singers.
That's right.
- Doesn't seem like it, huh? / - They're not food fighters.
- I love it here. / - Yes.
(An afternoon with the sun shining warmly)
(Waterside deck)
This is inner healing.
I don't need anything else. This is inner healing.
So this is what it means to walk a forest path.
I love it so much.
I really like water.
The air is so nice.
The water is so clear. Look at this.
- It's water from the stream. / - Yes.
(A forest path full of phytoncide)
(Provides inner healing for all)
Look over there. It's amazing.
It's pretty everywhere.
It's so nice here.
The waterside was so beautiful.
They made it perfect for walks.
- Yes. / - Around the lake.
After you stuff yourself,
you have to walk there.
When you walk such a beautiful path,
don't you say all sorts of things unintentionally?
That's right. We talked a lot.
We can end up having meaningful talks.
It looks really peaceful.
It's a pity that we can't fish.
There's always next time.
It's a pity that we can't ride bicycles.
Gosh.
(Enjoying the fresh air at Wando Arboretum)
(Health food tour)
(Pike eel stew)
If you've gone there,
you need to eat health food.
Do you know pike eels?
- I know pike eels. / - Of course.
I really love pike eels.
- Pike eels. / - There's a pike eel stew.
(Forget about the eels you know!)
It looks so nice.
That was amazing.
That's true health food.
It's pike eel stew.
Oh, my.
I've had that.
Where did you have it?
In Haenam.
(15 minutes from the arboretum to pike eel restaurant)
(They arrive at the pike eel restaurant)
It suddenly smells like the sea.
- Does it? / - That's why this restaurant...
Catches eels here and cooks it right away.
The eels live nearby.
They live in the mudflats.
You know eel tastes better from the mudflats, right?
The owner opens the restaurant
if they catch eels that day.
- If they don't, they close. / - They don't?
When they catch fish, they cook that and sell it.
So places like that can't be found on the internet.
You have to be lucky.
- Of course. / - It's a cat.
(Looking around)
So here it's...
The highlight.
It's the highlight of the health food tour.
Drink by yourself.
I drove so...
(Heh)
This is important.
(Gulping)
- It doesn't seem like a restaurant. / - Right.
- Why are you whispering? / - In case they hear.
But the best restaurants look shabby like this.
This is the true eatery.
Other places work on the design and interior.
But this place doesn't need any of that.
They know their food tastes good enough.
(We're confident in our food)
It's similar to me. I don't need good looks.
- I rely only on my singing. / - You're handsome.
- Stop that. / - You're handsome.
- What's wrong with you? / - You're handsome.
That's how you respond.
You're handsome.
What's the most popular dish here?
The pike eel stew.
Thank you.
- Yes. / - Gosh.
(This is what health food looks like)
They cooked the whole eel.
That's cold bean soup. That tastes good too.
They serve the pike peel like that as well.
That's the eel stew.
(They try the grilled pike eel first)
- Let's try this. / - This one...
Are you eating fried eel?
- No. / - It is grilled eel.
- It's dried and grilled. / - So that's dried.
They grill dried eel.
They catch pike eel without a hook.
You just need the bait and when you throw it in...
Eels are predators so they swallow it whole.
That's when you pull it up. That's the skill you need.
That's why they're called that.
- That looks so good. / - It's amazing.
(How does it taste?)
I'll take the tail.
It's good. How did they make this?
Did they dry it and fry it?
I think it's dried then fried.
Don't they seem grilled?
Ah, the texture...
(Janghyuck tries it again)
- They fried it. / - Did they fry it?
I know when I taste it.
(They cooked the dried eel in the oven)
- I'd love to have this with beer. / - With beer...
I'll have to cut the small octopus.
- Cut it up. / - Cut it up.
The stew looks so good.
Let's cut the head off first.
- Cut it up. / - Cut it up.
(They cut up the small octopus)
(When on earth can I eat?)
- Can't we eat the small octopus? / - You can eat it.
Small octopus gets tough if you cook it for too long.
It's really big.
They caught that right in front.
It's as big as an octopus.
It's really big.
They eat so well.
- Try it. / - Okay.
(One bite for me)
(Of course, the small octopus is delicious)
Our team doesn't speak when they eat.
They only enjoy it themselves.
They have to describe the taste.
I'm going to try the eel.
(It's time to eat the eel)
(Pike eel is one of the best health foods, high in protein)
Look at this.
Take this and roll it with your tongue.
If you do that...
(Slurping)
The bone comes out.
That's a new technique.
After Moon Seyoon...
(It still tastes good if you eat it normally)
These pike eels are also precious in Wando.
- The stew? / - It's not common.
The meat is really tender.
It feels like 100% cotton.
You must have this in fish stew.
The fragrance of the water parsley...
This is amazing.
(Ah)
Are you relieving your hangover?
You sound like you're relieving your hangover.
(It seems that he's really relieving his hangover)
You can tell that this is too much for two people.
We ordered so much to have a taste.
Enjoying this much eel for $50.
You can only do this in the place of origin.
It's really cost-effective.
Are you only going to eat this?
I'm thinking about it.
I feel like I have to drive until the end...
So...
(I got you)
Our managers can drive for us.
Let's have one last one.
My manager came down on the second day.
Let's just order one bottle.
(What these men need is soju)
(Ta-da)
I'm giving in on the last day.
What are you on about?
He looks happy.
- He's happy to see the green. / - You're right.
For 2 days... Good work.
That's kind of like a tail.
He wags his foot when he's happy.
(This is so good)
The food really made me want to drink.
(They're in a trance)
It tastes better, doesn't it?
What time does this place close?
What time are you planning to stay till?
- There he goes again. / - How many bottles do you want?
What time does this place close?
- We're open until 9 p.m. / - Okay, okay.
We'll just stay till 10 p.m.
He wants to stay there till 10.
- It looks really good. / - It's good.
They don't need words to describe that taste.
- I'm salivating. / - He opens his mouth really big.
- You can't eat this every day. / - That's right.
You don't get drunk if you eat like that.
You don't get drunk.
I'm not sure.
I think they captivated the middle-aged men only.
Totally.
I've been completely captivated,
since I'm a middle-aged man.
Me too. I want to go there.
The rice wine was the most memorable for me.
I'm surprised that it's 12%.
It's 12% but it doesn't taste like 12%.
It's not.
- It tastes nutty. / - Does it have a clean taste?
12% is still pretty sweet.
- It's quite sweet. / - Really?
Yes, it has to be sweet.
- But they didn't add sugar or anything. / - It's natural.
They just mixed yeast and used glutinous rice.
That's why it's sweeter.
We've been at this for two weeks.
It's mackerel vs. eel.
That's right.
And oyster vs. abalone.
- It feels like that. / - You're right.
The expenses are important now.
We spent $190.70 last week.
This week...
The Why Travel Together Tour.
How much did they spend over the 2 days?
The total expense of traveling Haenam and Wando is...
- The total is... / - Per person.
Per person!
- Excluding travel expenses. / - Excluding.
The total is $189.
I see.
Please say your last words.
Because it's located at the end of Korea,
we think that Haenam and Wando are very far.
We think it's too troublesome to go.
But if you go there
and come back from enjoying the food and view,
you will want to go back habitually.
- That's right. / - That's the kind of place it is.
Are you ready to vote?
Would you like to go to Haenam and Wando
according to the Why Travel Together Tour?
- Please vote. / - Please vote.
(Why Travel Together Tour went to a domestic island)
(What will the judges choose?)
With the help of 60,000 local ladies,
One Day Three Meals Tour
went to Tongyeong and Yokjido.
The traditional and health foods of Jeolla-do,
plus rare rice wine.
They provided inner healing through eating.
Why Travel Together Tour to Haenam and Wando.
Which tour did the judges choose?
Here we go.
Don't worry. It wasn't bad.
- It wasn't bad. / - You never know.
- The judges could prefer the slow life. / - Is it mackerel...
Or eel?
- Is it abalone... / - Or oyster?
(A nip and tuck match)
- It's really close. / - Look at that.
- Is it a big difference? / - Is the first digit the same?
- We don't know yet. / - Mackerel!
What's the score?
Mackerel!
(Tongyeong and Yokjido won with 87 votes)
- Good job. / - I don't believe this.
- 71 is pretty high. / - It's high.
Saerom, we enjoyed having you.
I also thought that I should start
going on trips that I can enjoy.
You should go on a trip with us.
- Yes, I should. / - On Battle Trip.
It's already vacation season.
- Already? / - Whatever vacation plans you have...
You must watch next week's show.
- What is it? / - It's the specials of specials.
I don't know when these specials will stop.
It's always a special.
We'll show you vacation spots you must visit
before everyone else finds out.
I love that.
Before everyone else finds out? That's amazing.
- It's over if others find out. / - You can't let that happen.
You'll have to leave straight after the show.
Make sure you watch and fly out.
We'll be back next week.
The world is your school, life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
Thank you.
(Next episode)
You must go there before it becomes well known.
I don't think I'll forget it.
An Park Tour!
Let's go!
(So pretty)
It's so pretty.
It's so pretty here.
It's so soft.
It feels comfortable here.
An elephant!
It's an elephant.
There are so many. There are more over there.
The view is incredible.
Will you join me in this amazing place?
("BAAM" by MOMOLAND)