They say a dragon came down from heaven.
That's why it's called that.
We'll check out all of Ha Long Bay.
It's so beautiful!
Hey, this is really cool. What a view.
It's really mysterious.
It feels like "Lord of the Rings."
You'll try something you've never had before.
This is really good.
I can't stop.
I'm about to cry.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips for trips)
(Seor Ina, Shim Hyejin)
(Park Jungyu, Sandeul of B1A4)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Just like last week, it's a family trip.
We have our trip planners who went on family trips.
- Welcome back. / - Nice to meet you.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
(100 judges in the audience)
We watched Ha Long Bay, Vietnam last week.
I admit it was good.
- I wanted to try goat meat. / - Right.
- And I wanted to try the seaplane. / - Me too.
I have to admit that it was great.
You liked it too, right, NC.A?
Yes. I was impressed by goat meat.
Actually, my mom hates goat meat.
So I think Hong Kong will be
a better choice for my family trip.
But you haven't tried goat meat before.
It doesn't taste like goat meat.
- But it's goat meat. / - It's not what you think.
Think about rice noodles and bun cha with the trip.
- You're right. / - It's just amazing.
Where would you go for your family trip?
- Hong Kong. / - Hong Kong?
- Hong Kong. / - Ina.
You don't have to go anywhere else.
Hong Kong has the three key elements of traveling.
- You can take good photos... / - Good photos.
Have good food and go shopping.
I think it's perfect for a family trip.
Are you talking about photos that everyone
already has?
- What kind of photo is that? / - That's not the same.
- They're different. / - It varies from person to person.
You know what?
Shopping on a trip is such a waste.
- That's not true. / - Things you can only buy there.
- That's because... / - You can buy limited items.
You shouldn't disregard personal preferences.
You may think that way for father and son trips.
But for mothers and daughters,
it's important to go shopping together
and pick good items for each other.
That can't be ignored.
- Exactly. / - We can also go window-shopping.
And our trip has a big advantage.
Hyejin has been...
- To Hong Kong plenty of times. / - Since long time ago.
So she's just like a tour guide.
- That's what worries me. / - That's what is scary.
Hong Kong is just Hong Kong, isn't it?
Many people say Hong Kong is
a great place for shopping.
- Great night view too. / - But we didn't...
Want to do typical shopping.
We did things you would like to do it at least once.
We saw beautiful nature and had great food.
- We did a lot of things. / - Nature in Hong Kong?
Hong Kong does have nature.
- I can't imagine. / - I haven't seen nature there.
Hong Kong is a city.
- And the night view. / - There's actually nature there.
70% of Hong Kong...
- Hong Kong has forests too. / - Really?
70% of the land of Hong Kong is a green area.
- Really? / - That's just like Korea.
Yes, it's very similar to Korea.
I heard there's a trekking course we don't know about.
- Yes. / - Right.
Did you go hiking?
- Why? / - That's what we hate the most.
- Hiking is what we hate the most. / - We went...
We went hiking just once.
I can help them a bit.
I used to live in Hong Kong for some time.
Oh, really?
When you travel with old people,
it's hard to travel a long distance.
Everything in Hong Kong is nearby.
- You don't have to travel much. / - That's true.
Traveling can be less tiring and it's an advantage.
There are places where you can see great night views.
It's nice to dress up and
have a cocktail with your mother, looking at
the beautiful night view.
And you can take amazing pictures there too.
I like both Hong Kong and Vietnam but
among all the travel destinations on Battle Trip,
I think Xiamen is
the best place to travel with your parents.
The Yang sisters, Heeeun and Heekyung went there.
They loved the food and...
- The weather was perfect. / - "I'm going there again."
"I'm going there again."
They said they'd go again early next year.
- "I made reservations." / - I watched that episode.
Xiamen seemed to be worth visiting indeed.
Is there any other place you'd like to recommend?
There's an interesting survey regarding family trips.
An accommodation rental service
did a survey on the most booked
family trip destination.
Guess what the most popular family trip destination
in Korea is.
- In Korea? / - Busan?
- Jeju-do. / - Sokcho.
That's correct. It's Jeju-do.
Jeju-do is where the most reservations are made.
- For family trips. / - And?
Guess which city the Japanese make
the most reservation for family trips.
- In Japan? / - Fukuoka.
- Busan? / - It's either Sapporo or Okinawa.
- Okinawa. / - Yes, it's Okinawa.
- Okinawa. / - Yes.
It's Okinawa.
- In Japan. / - Now guess which city is...
The most popular among Australians for family trips.
- Australia? / - Australians?
- New Zealand. / - It's not in Australia.
- It's not in Australia? / - Is it New Zealand?
- Where is it? / - It's a city in Indonesia.
- Bali? / - That's correct.
- Bali. / - Bali.
They go there often because it's close.
- It's close? / - For a family trip...
- Somewhere close is preferable. / - That's true.
- A place with good food. / - You don't go backpacking...
In Europe with your family.
- That's true. / - So, we're going to Hong Kong today.
- Finally... / - I want to go to Hong Kong.
Hyejin, how long does it take to get there?
It takes about 3.5 to 4 hours...
- To get to Hong Kong. / - Not only from Incheon but...
You can fly there from Busan too.
- Busan... / - You can fly there from Daegu too.
There are flights to Hong Kong in Daegu
and even Jeju-do every day.
- There are flights there too? / - That's great.
When is the best time to...
- Travel in Hong Kong? / - When should we go?
- November to January. / - January.
- November to January. / - November to January.
The weather is the best.
- It's not that hot. / - I heard it's very hot in summer.
- It's very hot. / - It's not hot now.
It has the perfect weather now.
- It doesn't rain much either. / - No.
Anyway, I'm looking forward to seeing their trip since
they say it's different from the Hong Kong we know.
Mamma Mia Tour in Hong Kong.
Let's check it out now.
(Ina waits for Hyejin)
(While writing questions to ask her)
She likes the feeling of new things.
It has to look new.
Ina is so considerate.
Ina is really cute.
- She's the best. / - Are you known as a scary senior?
I don't know you very well.
No, she's known as an easy-going person.
- Hello. / - Hello.
(Hyejin shows up with her actress aura)
We have to introduce ourselves.
We're going on a family trip
and I'm the daughter, Seor Ina.
Hello.
(Mother, Shim Hyejin)
I'm Shim Hyejin, who has suddenly become a mother.
- Suddenly? / - Yes.
- You're so mean. / - Why?
Please be my mother.
(She's so cute)
She's cute indeed.
(Ina was Hyejin's daughter in a drama)
(By playing the mother and daughter)
(During the 6 months of shooting, they got closer)
They look alike.
It seems like they like taking pictures.
So, we're going to Hong Kong.
I don't know much about Hong Kong.
I have never been there.
I'll tell you the truth.
Many things are mixed in Hong Kong.
- They have Western culture... / - I see.
And a variety of food.
It's pretty close too.
It takes about 4 to 5 hours from Korea.
You get off the plane when you're about to be tired.
You shouldn't take your parents too far.
As a child, you'd want to do anything
for your parents,
but too a long trip can annoy your parents.
A long plane ride is tiring,
unless you can offer them first class seats.
Even that can be tiring too.
(Unless you can offer good seats, they get tired)
She knows it well.
My mother won't fly for more than 4 hours.
- It's hard. / - If it's too far, it can be hard.
How do you know it so well?
I can do some bragging if you want.
(I'm Shin Hyejin)
Nowadays, Hong Kong actors...
This is annoying.
Talking about the past isn't a good thing.
- Why? I love it. / - Talking about past...
Makes you look old.
I know what she means. "Back in the day..."
There used to be a production company that
Director Wong Kar-wai owned.
I had a contract with them
and I used to be an actress in that agency.
Tony Leung Chiu-wai, Maggie Cheung Man-yuk.
And Gong Li...
You used to work with these actors?
We used to be in the same agency.
Isn't that cool?
- Hyejin was sensational back then. / - She was.
She was one of a kind.
She couldn't be more beautiful.
(She used to work with Hong Kong's best actors)
(Hyejin was an iconic actress of the 1990s)
Back then, I used to visit Hong Kong a lot.
(Respect)
I want to look elegant but you don't let me.
(Where is the elegance?)
Why am I the one to blame?
You keep talking to me.
(I'm usually very elegant, it's your fault)
I should ask more.
Think about what you want to do with me...
A place you want me to see.
I'm going to think about the places I want you to see.
Actually, I already found some.
Really?
This is the difference between you and me.
I don't know anything about Hong Kong.
(Will she manage to plan a nice trip?)
One of the things I want to do with you is
trekking.
You can go hiking in Hong Kong?
It's the most famous hiking trail in Asia.
This is in Hong Kong?
I love it.
Isn't it beautiful?
Last April, I walked 800km on the pilgrimage trail
of Camino de Santiago.
Since then, I find hiking so fun.
- You walked 800km? / - Yes.
After that, I walked 640km in Portugal too.
- So... / - 800km?
- 800km and then 640km. / - How long did it take?
I walked over 1,000km.
Since then, I started to find trekking...
- You find it fun. / - It's fun and keeps you healthy.
You should walk too.
Maybe you should go to the army.
- I might be a born soldier. / - That's what I mean.
She should go march in the army.
It was chosen as the best trekking course in Asia.
(Dragon's Back is the best trekking course in Asia)
This is one of the things I want to try with you.
- I'm so touched. / - It's not that big a deal.
It could be very exhausting.
You said you have never been hiking before.
- That's true. / - We can't...
Do this on the day...
- We arrive. / - No.
Since you said you haven't been to Hong Kong,
we're going to spend
one day in the city.
Then I'm going to do the research on
the trekking for the second day.
That sounds good. You're so smart.
(Hehe)
What should be the name of our tour?
Actually, I have some in my mind.
What are they?
Mamma Mia.
- Mamma Mia? / - Mamma Mia means...
Oh, my goodness.
It means our trip is so great that we will say...
- I like the idea. / - Mamma Mia.
Also...
Do you know the saying, "Admire sacrifice?"
I don't like that saying.
- So... / - I prefer Mamma Mia.
- Then let's go with Mamma Mia. / - Mamma Mia.
Let's go with that then.
I'm well-prepared, right?
You did a great job.
I think you two don't really hit it off.
That's not true.
I don't think she really likes her.
"You did a great job."
- That's not how it was. / - Yes, it was.
Let's make a fun trip
that will make us say Mamma Mia.
Our trip is already half successful.
Okay.
(So fashionable no one would believe her age)
What kind of oil is this?
I like it very much.
I think she's a small size.
If you spray this, you can be like Natalie Portman.
I doubt that.
You're feeding me this for breakfast?
I don't usually give up food,
you're the only one. Eat up.
We'll start at the center of Hong Kong.
Wow. This place is incredible!
Right? This is the night view of Hong Kong.
(They make unforgettable memories in Hong Kong)
It's like a cafe area for youngsters.
It's the best at night...
- That's the hot pot! / - My gosh!
- Mamma Mia! / - It's not that spicy.
I really love mala sauce.
- The itinerary looks impressive. / - Hot pot.
I can't believe I'm on a ferry in Hong Kong.
I'm excited.
It doesn't have a scent.
You're much prettier.
I'll organize everything for the trekking day.
It's the most famous crab restaurant here.
They have crab here too!
- What is that? / - This is cheating!
My goodness.
- Goodness. / - Fried crabs are too good!
It's the most famous crab restaurant here.
(Ina's Day for Hyejin)
(The trip is full of laughter from a mother and daughter)
My husband.
No!
(The trip is also full of surprises and amazement)
My goodness. You scared me.
- The weather was really good. / - Mamma Mia!
It was the best.
You can clearly see the difference between
the guy-guy trip and girl-girl trip.
The atmosphere looks so different.
(Hong Kong)
(4-hour flight, 1 hour behind Korea)
(Koreans don't require a visa to stay up to 90 days)
(Arrival at Hong Kong International Airport at 7 p.m.)
- We're finally in Hong Kong. / - It's Hong Kong.
Yes, we arrived. I shouldn't have dressed up.
It's hot.
- Right? / - I didn't know it'd be this hot.
Let's get moving first.
(How to go to the city center from Hong Kong Airport)
(Bus, train and taxi)
We'll go by taxi today.
Okay!
(Feeling excited)
There are three types of taxis here.
There are red taxis, green taxis and blue taxis.
Red taxis can go anywhere in Hong Kong.
- Anywhere? / - Yes, anywhere.
- Green ones go to New Territories. / - They're different.
- You should write this down. / - Right.
(Blue taxis operate only in Lantau Island)
When you get on the taxi,
you can't just choose any one.
I'm saying that you should find out first.
If you can, picking up the red taxi...
- Is probably wise. / - Red taxis.
- You "pick up" taxis? / - Wait.
- Picking it up is better? / - "Pick up?"
Pick up a taxi and get in.
Let's get some rest today
and start our day early tomorrow.
Okay.
There are a lot of red taxis.
- There are mostly red taxis. / - Yes.
- Mostly red taxis. / - He's driving with the trunk open.
(30 minutes to the Central from the airport by taxi)
Hong Kong Island and Kowloon are separated.
- Right. / - Yes.
(The first day of Mamma Mia Tour arrives)
(Hong Kong City Hall, international bank headquarters)
(Big shopping mall, small stores make up the area)
(A lot of tourists visit this area)
This part of the island is lively.
This is the city.
(Central, the heart of Hong Kong)
- It's the first day of our trip. / - Yes.
This is the first day I planned for us.
That's why we're going to
start off our trip in the center of Hong Kong, Central.
Everything is around here.
Everything we need to see and food we need to eat.
Well, everyone has a different opinion
but this is just what I think.
That's a laugh of an actress.
She laughs at what she says.
She sounded like Franceska from "Hello, Franceska."
My laugh sounds terrible.
It sounds refreshing and nice.
Aren't we in the financial district?
There are things to do here, right?
(Big buildings don't look fun for her)
- Gosh. / - It looked like a financial district.
- It looks like Yeouido. / - Yeouido?
- We'll get going now. / - Go, go.
Where are we going first? Is it a secret?
I have prepared this for you.
(24 minutes to Hollywood murals from Ferris wheel)
(They go into the financial district)
Goodness, it's completely different from Ha Long Bay.
It's so crowded. How do you walk around there?
- How do you walk there? / - So many people.
When you go traveling, it's also fun
to observe people from all over the world.
That's the best.
This street is a famous one in Hong Kong.
This is called the Hollywood Road
where people take a lot of photos.
Hollywood Road?
Yes, there's a street called Hollywood Road.
I'm curious about Hollywood Road.
There are many places you can take the best photos.
- What's this? / - There are a lot of cool places.
- My goodness! / - There are a lot of murals.
Wow, so pretty.
- That looks so cool. / - Hong Kong changed a lot.
It doesn't seem like Hong Kong.
They're all mothers and daughters.
I don't see any dads and sons.
- You're right. / - This is pretty.
- Every alley looks pretty. / - Right? Isn't it pretty?
Do you see that one, decorated with the red sign?
They decorated the place with flowers.
- That was my favorite. / - I thought we could...
Go over there and take photos.
- I love it. / - Shall we cross?
- So pretty. / - People must take many photos there.
This way. Stand here so we can include the sign.
- Isn't it too far? / - That's it. That's the spot.
Move up a bit. Move forward. Okay.
(Taking a photo with her isn't easy)
1, 2, 3.
I bet the photo came out nice.
(First photo as mom and daughter in Hong Kong)
They look pretty.
What did we do on our trip?
- We should've taken photos too. / - Great photo.
- Exactly. / - You took one at the subway.
- Subway? / - Subway? Wasn't it on the plane?
It wasn't a plane. It was the subway.
It was the subway with the seatbelt.
It was more like a bus.
We can go to another one from here.
When we cross this street,
we'll see the murals where people take a lot of photos.
I'm planning to go there. Come follow me.
Let's cross the street.
(It's the mural of the old town)
You have to wait in line to take the photos.
The mural is pretty.
This is the place.
- This is it. / - You need some people there.
- Only then it feels like a trip. / - Right.
Gosh, it looks really pretty.
(They take another photo by the wall)
Your hand is shaking.
- I couldn't tap the button. / - Right?
(They take another photo by the wall)
(Starting now, we're the cool kids of Hong Kong)
- How beautiful. / - "Cool kids of Hong Kong."
(They spend some time together as they walk)
Gosh, women love this kind of walk.
Every store here looks cute.
Can you take a photo of me here?
- Do I look okay? / - They're taking photos all day.
(Acting playful)
- I took so many photos of her. / - I can see that.
What did you do with those photos?
- I sent them to her. / - Did you save them?
- I have them. I sent them. / - Was it your first time?
Yes, it was my first time in Hong Kong.
- Then this must be fun. / - All done.
(She never said they were good photos)
(They take a selfie together)
Why are you doing that with your lips?
She doesn't take ordinary photos often.
I'm sorry to point it out
but don't try to read women's minds.
- Just understand them. / - I was merely asking.
She took the photo just like this.
We just made faces to take our photos.
(Jungyu has a hard time understanding them)
We don't look normal in any of these photos.
We're not normal.
(We only keep good photos)
We should get something to eat now.
- Great, great. I'm full of energy. / - Let's eat.
(Hyejin's Day for Ina)
- Brunch! / - Wow, that photo's nice too.
Brunch.
(9-minute walk to the brunch place from the murals)
It's quite close.
So, for Ina today...
I looked up a nice brunch restaurant.
You did?
Ta-da!
I think I know where it is. Isn't that it?
- Isn't it pretty? / - When I'm in Hong Kong...
I feel as if I should have brunch.
- Right? / - Once you get the dish...
- There's not much to eat. / - No.
- You enjoy the ambience there. / - It's sweet too.
Don't you agree? Even when you drink coffee...
- You want a cute cafe. / - Thanks to Hwangbo...
I got to visit Hong Kong.
There were many great brunch places.
- There are a lot. / - That's true.
She knows more
hip and cute places than I do.
And she enjoys them more.
It's so interesting.
(This cute brunch joint charms the daughter in her 20s)
(This is the brunch, prepared just for Ina)
- That's so pretty. / - That has to be tasty.
(Sour cream)
(Salsa sauce)
(Avocado)
- Avocados! / - Yes, avocados.
- My wife cooks me that. / - That looks so good.
This...
(Avocado toast)
That's too much for brunch.
- Right? Isn't the portion big? / - It's so pretty.
It's supposed to be. It's for breakfast and lunch.
It's almost lunch. This is almost our lunch.
- It looks delicious. / - My gosh.
- What's that? / - "Pumpkin spinach egg pie."
- Gosh. / - Goodness, look at that.
- They named it after everything. / - That looks good.
They included all the ingredients.
Pumpkin spinach egg pie.
Jungyu, that's Sikyung's job.
Why are you attacking them?
I'm sorry.
- I love it. My job became easy. / - It's nice?
They used all of the ingredients.
(Mamma Mia Tour picks the table outside)
Don't brunches taste all the same?
- You think... / - I think they all taste the same.
You should get rid of that prejudice.
(At that time, someone knocks on the window)
- My gosh, through the window? / - Goodness.
- My goodness. / - Who is that?
They serve through the window?
They serve food that way?
They served it through the window.
- Okay. Thank you. / - Goodness.
- Thank you. / - You're welcome.
(Avocado toast, pumpkin spinach egg pie, $15 each)
I'll cut it. Try it.
It doesn't taste good when it's cold.
Thank you.
I'm really clumsy.
What if I drop it on you?
(Hyejin cuts it for her)
(Happy)
And now, you'll feed me.
How does it taste?
Isn't it good?
(She can't speak, so she claps)
It's a bit salty
but this is good.
Food is a bit salty in Hong Kong.
- You're right. / - "Can't believe I ate something green."
Because the weather is hot.
When you order fried rice in Hong Kong,
you have to ask them to make it less salty.
Even when you ask them to make it less salty...
- It's still salty for us. / - It is.
This is good.
I can't believe I ate something green.
(Hyejin takes a bite too)
I don't usually eat vegetables.
What's salty is...
- The salami. / - Salami makes it salty.
I think I ate too much salami earlier.
(If you eat salty salami with avocado)
Foreigners would love it.
Avocado is the best.
Avocado is rich.
The tomato sauce is fresh.
I think that'll taste good because of avocado.
Yes, that was good.
I don't usually eat green vegetables.
- Why not? / - I don't eat avocado.
(I hate vegetables)
I don't think they're tasty.
- You have to. You're an adult now. / - It's delicious.
Thanks to Hyejin...
- Did you eat them all? / - I did.
Take avocado, egg and ham.
You have to eat everything together
for a good balance.
I think I only ate the salty things earlier.
(She'll try the sweet pumpkin spinach pie)
It's pretty inside.
Sweet pumpkin.
Spinach.
I'm curious about this.
- What is it? / - Sweet pumpkin spinach pie.
(She reacts as soon as she eats it)
It's sweet.
- What does it taste like? / - She takes a big bite.
She does.
She does that thing with her eyes as well.
We have the eyes too.
- That team has Sandeul. / - I guess that's the trend.
- Yes. / - Yes.
Sandeul's eyes aren't that big though.
I was so surprised.
When I saw it,
I thought it wouldn't taste good.
But this is much more delicious, right?
(It looks like it's completely wrapped with spinach)
I can't taste the spinach.
The sweet pumpkin is overpowering.
- Inside is sweet pumpkin. / - It's like steamed egg.
It's sweet and the spinach is crunchy.
- Steamed egg? / - Crunchy spinach.
(Sweet pumpkin's sweetness)
Because of sweet pumpkin, it's not so rich...
Yet sweet.
It's because of sweet pumpkin.
This is kimchi.
- Kimchi? / - This.
This vegetable.
When it's too sweet.
- Sweet and salty. / - There's spinach on the side.
That's spinach.
That egg probably isn't steamed egg.
Is it fried?
They mixed it with cream. So it's like custard.
- You're right. / - It's egg based.
It's not steamed egg.
I hate vegetables.
People who don't like vegetables should
have the sweet pumpkin spinach pie.
(Suddenly she's reminded of their first encounter)
I met you in "Strong Girl Bong-soon."
Do you remember that I was in that drama?
I never saw you once.
After that...
I was a total rookie and I was so nervous then.
In "Sunny Again Tomorrow..."
You played my mom.
I was worried
but you thought I was really cute and lovely.
One time, I was watching you like this from afar,
you were so pretty.
- I'm not just saying this. / - I fell in love at first sight.
"Should I take a picture?" I wasn't close to you then.
So I took a picture of you secretly.
I shouldn't have.
I was looking at the screen
and our eyes met.
On the screen.
So I made a finger heart.
And you
made a finger heart back.
So I decided to send you a text message then.
I think...
You're so lovely.
You're really lovely.
You're very friendly too.
I thought you were very sociable.
(Shocked)
- What? / - What is it?
- Was it a bug? / - An insect.
You scared me.
I guess there was something in the food.
"Something in the food."
From the food.
A bird came out of the food.
So cute.
Goodness. That scared me.
(Cute)
- That's cute. / - It's so pretty.
It's cute. Why do you hate it?
- Why? / - It's cute.
It's so cute.
(The bird flies away)
Wasn't that so cute?
(Relieved)
- That was so cute. / - I'm really scared of birds.
So, we finished breakfast.
- I think this is enough, right? / - Yes, totally.
- I'm so full. / - Yes.
We'll go somewhere else.
Where?
There was something you wanted to do.
- Something I wanted to do? / - Yes.
We'll try on qipao.
- Can we rent qipao? / - She remembered.
- We can. / - Not buy it?
You can if you want to.
But just rent it.
You aren't going to wear it in Korea anyway.
- For the memory. / - You can try it on...
And take pictures.
Just enjoy it.
I'll take you there.
- You can rent it. / - Even if you buy qipao...
- You wouldn't wear it. / - Would you wear it?
- Unless it's Halloween. / - You won't get to wear it.
- It's really pretty though. / - Right.
It's so pretty.
There's something I really want to do.
I want to wear their traditional dress.
- Traditional Hong Kong dress. / - Qipao.
This?
The dress Maggie wore in "In the Mood for Love?"
- She called her Maggie. / - Maggie.
- Maggie? / - You sound like her friend.
Doesn't everyone say that?
People say that.
I call Chow Yun-fat by his first name too.
- Okay. / - What do you think?
- It's pretty. / - Don't you think it'll be pretty?
You'll look really pretty.
- You'll be prettier. / - No.
I can't wear it because of my fat belly.
(I'm sorry, I can't wear it)
- You have to wear it too. / - I'm sorry.
I have to wear a big size then.
It'll be embarrassing.
(What will the qipao look like?)
We won't reveal the size.
Okay. Goodness.
(9 minutes from the brunch place to qipao)
I'll let you try qipao on.
Because you wanted to wear it...
We're here to do that.
We're almost there.
(Let's hurry up and go)
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Can I come in? / - Yes.
(Excited)
- That's pretty. / - So fancy.
- The colors... / - Yes.
And the patterns are so extravagant.
When you rent qipao, you can borrow...
- The accessories for free. / - Really?
- Yes. / - You can borrow them.
(Qipao can be rented for $98 per day)
A father and son would never go there.
Father and son wouldn't even look at that place.
I'd say, "What is that place?" and just walk by.
They'd be scared to even look.
This is pretty too.
- Because you have a nice body. / - Me...
I ate too much at the brunch place though.
This is pretty too.
I think this will be pretty.
This is really pretty.
- She keeps recommending things. / - Look at this.
I want to go to the bathroom first.
Really?
I think this is pretty too.
(Hyejin picks out pretty qipaos for Ina)
How is this?
- Did you pick these out? / - Yes.
Hyejin picked them out for me.
I like that one.
Do you wear small?
- Maybe medium. / - Medium?
The retailer said I was a medium.
It's because I ate too much. I'm sorry.
- Do I put it on now? / - Yes.
- How about you? / - Me?
- You have to wear it too. / - No, thank you.
I don't want to be compared to you.
You have a much nicer body.
Stop talking.
- I think she'd look pretty in it. / - Yes.
Just the daughter needs to look pretty.
(Later)
Hyejin.
That's pretty.
- She's pretty. / - It looks good on her.
Mom.
(Ina bursts out laughing)
Goodness. My husband.
Pretty dress for the pretty person.
It was a surprise. I didn't know she wore it.
I wasn't thinking about wearing it.
But the men's outfit suddenly caught my eyes.
(Should I try it on?)
(She keeps adding on more items)
Men dress like this.
(Hyejin is ready)
I'm...
I'm all done.
I want to try that on too.
This isn't mother and daughter concept.
It is a mother and daughter concept.
- But I... / - Where did you get it from?
From here.
I've never worn anything like this before.
(Hyejin makes a special memory for Ina)
You're such an eccentric.
(They take a picture together)
My husband.
No!
- You look pretty tough. / - Doesn't she look pretty?
Yes, very pretty.
(Taking a souvenir photograph)
Do they take pictures for you?
- Yes. / - They do.
She tells you how to pose.
You have to pay extra for the photos.
(They make new memories in Hong Kong)
Pictures...
They print the photos for you.
(Photoshoot with 10 photos, $81.20)
$80?
- It includes 10 pictures. / - I see.
10 pictures are included.
(The fee includes 10 printed photos)
(Photoshoot with 10 photos, $81.20)
(I met my husband in Hong Kong)
- That's so nice. / - The photoshoot is worth it.
- She met her husband in Hong Kong. / - It's like...
- An old school movie. / - It's just that.
- A movie poster. / - Yes.
- Very memorable. / - You can make memories...
- With mom. / - Wearing the qipao was great.
Jungyu would've looked great in the men's qipao.
- Like wearing a gown at home. / - Ina won't like that.
I should take a lot of photos now.
(Hyejin's Day for Ina)
(Special travel gift)
When you travel, it's nice to have
something memorable or something unforgettable.
Wouldn't it be nice to have something like that?
- We can't forget about our trip. / - Right.
I'm sure everything about the trip is unforgettable.
Despite that, I want to give you a present that
you won't particularly forget about.
- What is it? / - So...
- Is it something tasty? / - No, no.
- "Something tasty?" / - So I prepared this.
This is it.
- I didn't even think about this. / - What a cute store.
- Perfume? / - Perfume?
Fathers and sons won't go there.
Since we're women.
What kind of fragrance do you like?
What do you like?
- White musk. / - White musk.
- I like flowery. / - Wait, you can make your own?
- Yes. / - You can make hand cream?
You can make it with perfume.
- Really? / - I like doing that.
We learned how to make that at the shop.
Women love that.
I like that.
Don't they just mix perfume to the hand cream?
No.
- The process itself is simple. / - In theory?
- But... / - Given the season...
- You really need hand cream now. / - Yes, you do.
- You try. / - Okay.
(She likes it)
Very nice.
(Hyejin and Ina find the fragrance they each like)
This is good too.
- You like? / - Yes.
(They will make it for each other)
(Hyejin's perfume is sweet, fresh and flowery)
(Ina's perfume has a scent of magnolia flowers)
Okay, we'll make the hand cream now.
- Yes. / - Okay.
You choose the fragrance and make the cream?
- Yes, that's how you make it. / - I want to visit there.
(Camellia oil, coagulating agent, water)
(Perfume, empty container)
Alcohol pad. You should clean all of this.
- Do you make it yourself? / - They're making it now.
Yes.
This is nice.
Next, we'll use the big spoon.
Put one spoon of water inside.
Okay. And then use the small spoon...
To take the oil. Also one spoon.
I can't wait to see how this will turn out.
And then, this is the coagulating agent.
Also one spoon.
Just like this?
- One spoon. / - One spoon?
- It's a coagulating agent. / - You can use...
The chopstick to stir.
- Mix. / - Yes, mix it well.
- Are you done now? / - It's like making candles.
- Wow. / - The scent...
What is that?
- Will it turn into cream? / - It's turning into cream.
- That's interesting. / - It was really quick.
It didn't take 5 minutes.
I guess this solidifies it into cream.
And then, you can spray the perfume inside.
Spray it 6 times.
Then you take the scent you like...
- And add it? / - You add it in.
- If you want it strong, spray more. / - That's right.
You can smell to see if it is okay for you.
If you want it to be stronger,
you can add one or two more times.
- It's weak. / - Right?
That's okay.
- I'll spray 4 more times. / - Okay.
- That's better? / - How is this, mom?
- Good. / - Okay.
Can you spray one more time?
Sure.
(They finish making the hand cream for each other)
When I filmed the drama with you,
I found out you are sensitive...
- To smell and you like perfume. / - Right.
I like perfume as well.
When I researched, I found this shop.
I thought that it would be nice to come here
and try this together.
I'm really grateful for your thought.
You didn't stop at just realizing that I liked perfume.
You could have just bought me perfume as a present.
- Right. / - But I am grateful that I got to...
Experience this special activity.
And now, we know how to make hand cream.
That's right. Who knew it would be this simple?
It's like killing two birds with one stone.
(Hyejin's Day is very fruitful)
How will you use that precious thing?
Exactly.
- You have to use it quickly. / - Since we know...
We can make it again at home.
Can you make it at home?
If you have the ingredients.
Anyone can make the hand cream
with the perfume you like.
I want to try that.
I asked my Chinese friend about this restaurant.
I heard that it is a very famous restaurant.
- It's a "huo guo" place. / - Huo guo?
I love huo guo.
This is the place.
- It's called hot pot in English. / - Right.
- I've been to this place. / - Was the food good?
It was good. It's really delicious.
I like it too. I really like hot pot.
They serve very fresh seafood.
Meat too.
- A local recommended this place? / - A local did.
That's why we have to make a reservation.
- We have to make a reservation? / - Is this...
- Shim Hyejin's regular place? / - Yes.
I bet it's delicious.
Try that restaurant when you're in Hong Kong.
- It's really good. / - Do you want their business card?
That's alright.
I'll be able to find it online.
(This is the dinner Hyejin prepared for Ina)
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
It looks so delicious.
It looks delicious.
It's seafood.
- It was really delicious. / - It looks so fresh.
- It's shrimp ball. / - I've never had seafood in hot pot.
Isn't that an oyster?
- They put oysters in it. / - Why is the oyster so big?
- It looks delicious. / - Hot pot.
This is the real health food, isn't it?
If you haven't tried goat breast, don't say anything.
Oyster is a great health food.
- He's so funny. / - I think it's very unique...
- That you add seafood. / - Isn't it beautiful?
Hong Kong is famous for good seafood.
(Hyejin's Day for Ina)
(Hot pot)
(The night falls on the first day)
We're going to a hot pot restaurant.
- We've been in the city center... / - Hot pot!
The whole day today.
There's a bad traffic jam
at this time of day.
Right.
All the people in these buildings have to go home.
So we're going to take a ferry.
There's a ferry that goes around the city.
If we ride the ferry, it takes 10 minutes
to get to where we want to go.
We can save a lot of time.
- She's right. / - It's so fast.
It's like a water taxi.
- There are water taxis? / - Yes.
If you take a taxi, you have to take a detour.
- But the ferry can go straight. / - That's right.
(10 minutes from Central to Tsim Sha Tsui, 32 cents)
This is interesting.
- 30 cents? / - It's so cheap.
It's really cheap.
Why is it so cheap?
You can sit or stand on the ferry.
It takes only 10 minutes, so take it easy.
You can see the night view on the ferry too. How nice.
It's really nice.
(Hyejin likes taking videos with her GoPro)
We're here.
I'm excited.
It's here.
It smells like the sea here, doesn't it?
(Everything is fascinating and exciting for Ina)
Here we go.
- She's so cute. / - We're taking off.
(Let's go have dinner)
I think this is one of the best things in Hong Kong.
- The ferry ride at night. / - It looks nice indeed.
You don't need a 6-hour cruise.
You can feel the refreshing wind.
- That's nice. / - Wow.
I have to show this to the viewers.
(You can enjoy the night view while being on the move)
This is so beautiful.
On the ferry, you can see everything.
You have a full 360-degree view.
- It's nice. / - How do you like it?
I'm so happy. This is amazing.
You look like the lady from the sea.
- Like a mermaid. / - The lady from the sea?
If you reveal your top half, you'd look like a mermaid.
A mermaid princess.
That looks cool, Ina.
Do I look good with my hair flying in the wind?
That must be Ina's first time.
- Right. / - She must've been so excited.
It feels so good to be on a ferry for the first time.
It feels amazing.
- It really feels like you're in Hong Kong. / - Right.
I've never watched the night view that way.
- This is amazing. / - And it costs...
It's only 30 cents, so you should ride it.
It is even more beautiful when you see it on a ferry.
(After enjoying the night view, the ferry ride is over)
We're here. We will get off the ferry
and take a taxi.
That's too bad. I wish we could get there on a ferry.
(16 minutes from Tsim Sha Tsui to the hot pot place)
I want to go to that hot pot place again.
- I'm so jealous. / - What would it taste like?
Now I can see the place.
I wanted to feed you something nice...
- So I picked this place. / - I'm so touched.
You're touched? Enjoy it.
Okay. I'll eat a lot.
- I'm so hungry now. / - Okay.
Zhang Ziyi's favorite hot pot place.
There are places like that in Hong Kong.
A lot of celebrities of Hong Kong visit this place.
This place?
I tried hot pot for the first time in Guangzhou.
So this is my second time.
It has two different kinds of broth,
and one of them is spicy.
Was that the whole pepper? What is it called?
- It's mala. / - Mala?
After I had the soup...
(As she tasted the soup, her mouth was on fire)
It felt like this.
- It's strong, right? / - It's very strong.
It felt as though my mouth was numbed.
- Mala is... / - This wouldn't taste like that.
- It's not that strong there. / - Why?
When I tried it here,
it didn't taste like that.
It's not so strong there.
- We've been to Sichuan before. / - Right.
This is different from the hot pot of Sichuan.
- This one is a lot milder. / - Peanut sauce.
(The scent and spiciness is milder in Hong Kong)
Thank you.
This is peanut sauce.
That's peanut sauce.
- I see. / - Wow.
- The peanut sauce is not greasy. / - And chili oil.
It's really good.
And add chili oil in soy sauce.
- Look at that chili oil. / - Add it all.
- And coriander. / - You like coriander now.
- Of course. / - Even on pad thai.
- I'm not a big fan. / - I didn't add it.
Use it as a dip.
(The hot pot sauce is ready)
I can't wait.
(She feels bored waiting for the food)
Do you want to watch TV?
We have to pay to watch TV.
(She laughs in amazement)
I don't know what it says,
but I see dollar signs.
(She can't read it but she sounds confident)
It's about corkage charge.
It was about bringing your own alcohol.
Having to pay to watch TV...
I just believed what she said but...
I laughed because I couldn't believe it.
Gosh, how could you say such a thing?
(Cute)
It's finally here.
(The hot pot is served while they laugh and chat)
Why is she surprised?
- What? / - It was too big.
Is it for two people?
We just picked what we wanted to eat on the menu.
They thought it'd come out in small servings.
I think we ordered too much.
(Shocked)
Thank you.
- Oh, my God. / - You can eat it all.
Sandeul, you can eat it all by yourself, right?
- Look at that. / - I can eat it alone.
- Look at the shrimp. It moved. / - It's alive.
I can eat it all by myself.
It will shrink in the soup.
It may seem big
but we have only three oysters.
I've never seen such big oysters before.
Put the oysters in it when they're fresh.
We also have meat.
I want meat.
(They put in the ingredients they want)
We don't do that with fish a lot.
- That's right. / - I like that they have it.
It tastes so good with fresh fish.
Isn't it fishy?
- It's very sweet. / - Really?
- Because it's fresh. / - It must be really good.
- I haven't tried this before. / - You can eat it raw.
Let's eat the vegetables first.
I'm going to dip it in here.
(She eats it with the sauce)
Vegetables?
- Is it good? / - Yes.
(Ina tastes it too)
It tastes like...
Isn't it great?
(Clapping like a seal)
It tastes amazing.
It's really spicy.
Which one?
- This one. / - That one?
It's really spicy. You should be careful.
(Extremely spicy)
It makes me eat vegetables.
- This is really great. / - It's so delicious.
Let's try the oysters.
It looks great. Is it an oyster?
- Is it an oyster? / - I think it is.
- It is an oyster. / - My gosh.
It looks bigger when it's cooked.
It doesn't fit in your mouth.
You can't eat it in one bite.
Oysters are very good for your health.
How is it so big? Is it farmed?
It's huge.
(Ina tastes it heartily)
- Eating one will make you full. / - It's hot.
It must have a chewy texture.
- It must be good. / - It was very chewy.
Gosh, it looks so good.
- It is sweet. / - It's so chewy.
- It's tender and... / - Chewy?
It tastes like milk.
You're right.
It's perfect with the sauce.
I'm not a fan of oysters...
- But this is really good. / - Wow.
That's our soy sauce.
It's so hard to watch right now.
You can put fish balls or dumplings in it.
- Really? / - Let's try this.
- The shrimp balls. / - It must be good.
It tastes so good.
You have to eat it.
- The shrimp balls. / - It looks amazing.
This is so good.
- My goodness. / - It's shrimp.
It makes me hungry.
I'm going to eat meat first.
(Hyejin loves the shrimp balls)
The shrimp is alive.
It can't be alive. This is serious.
That's not what I mean.
(It has the bouncy texture of shrimp)
It has a whole shrimp in it.
- It has the whole shrimp in it. / - Great texture.
- The texture is good. / - It's a dumpling.
- Right. It's really good. / - It's so firm.
Try this.
(She gives the shrimp ball to Ina)
It's really good.
(What does the shrimp ball taste like?)
Mamma Mia.
It's alive.
I know what you mean now.
(Happy)
I'll have some meat now.
(The meat is covered with the red soup)
It looks good.
- My gosh. / - It looks delicious.
It will taste good with goat meat.
- You liked the goat breast. / - Goat breast.
(She takes a big bite of meat)
Meat is the best.
It's so savory.
- It's good, right? / - Yes.
I just can't watch this.
I had the meat in the red soup
with the peanut sauce.
It's savory and not greasy at all.
It's not too spicy.
The important thing is
that the peanut sauce is not sweet.
It tastes just like peanuts.
So it tastes light.
(Ina tastes it after Hyejin)
You can try them one by one.
(Amazed)
- What do I do? / - Why?
I should open a franchiser in Korea.
- This is so good. / - Sandeul's been won over.
They've won him over. Are you okay?
No. He's not watching it. He closed his eyes.
He's training his mind.
You caved in to the meat.
She's proud.
Hyejin looks proud.
- Because she liked the food. / - I understand.
We ate almost everything.
Why are you eating for so long?
It looks even better because it's winter.
- We ordered too much. / - Right.
(Meat cooked in white broth then into the sauce)
(Straight to her mouth)
Is it good?
This is better.
(Meat cooked in the white soup is the way to go)
(Ina tries it the way Hyejin ate)
(She likes the smell)
What do you think?
I can see why you like this better.
This one tastes light.
I can appreciate the taste of the ingredients.
Each ingredient has its own taste. I like that.
I guess we can say this.
This one is like spicy beef soup
and this one is like ox bone soup.
Those who like spicy food will love the red soup.
You're right.
(If you like spicy food, try the red soup)
If you like something light and clean,
try the white soup, the vegetable broth.
(If you like light and clean taste, try the white soup)
I want to eat noodles with it.
You should add Chinese style glass noodles.
It's really good.
This is so...
I really like this.
I love meat in the soup.
So it's all about meat.
Meat is the right answer.
(Ina's love for meat is unstoppable)
(They start to eat up)
(They look like loving mother and daughter)
(Happy)
I want to eat more...
But I should stop.
Mom, you can't give up.
I'm sorry.
I'm on a diet actually.
I said that after eating so much.
Now you say that?
- After eating so much? / - I know.
It's okay. It's all protein.
The hot pot will be sad.
I'm sorry about that.
So I shouldn't betray it. I'll keep at it.
(The dinner that threatens their diet is over)
Did you enjoy it?
- It was the best. / - Was it?
Today is the first day and tomorrow is your day, right?
Yes, I'm nervous.
You will also prepare everything for me tomorrow.
I'll make you feel moved,
as much as I was moved today.
Think of this as a meal for tomorrow's trekking.
Should we end here today?
- Thank you, mom. / - I enjoyed the food.
Saved as a good restaurant.
(Mamma Mia Tour's day draws to an end)
I heard that there was a trekking course.
I thought it'd be a good idea to do it together.
Since the weather is nice.
- I'd like that. / - They said it's nice these days.
For the second day,
I'll prepare everything in regards with the trekking.
Okay.
If you're tired of obvious Hong Kong trips,
we recommend trekking.
It's called the Dragon's Back.
(She searches in detail)
- 8.5km? / - 8.5km.
It's a piece of cake.
(Shopping and night view comes to mind)
(When you think of Hong Kong)
(No more showy concrete jungles)
Was this chosen as the best trekking course in Asia?
- Yes. / - CNN chose this place as...
- The best trekking course in Asia. / - The best.
That's amazing.
- The view is amazing. / - In 2004, CNN chose it...
As the best trekking course in Asia.
- The best trekking course in Asia? / - The best.
(The course isn't difficult and the view is magnificent)
This course isn't that difficult.
- Even beginners can go here. / - Yes.
It's easy to hike.
It's impossible for Ssangdeulier Tour.
- They don't like to be tired. / - That's right.
If we hike for 15 minutes,
we will have to sleep for a little.
(Ina's Day for Hyejin)
(The brilliant stars disappeared)
(And their Hong Kong trip starts again)
They must be doing morning exercises.
- They do morning exercises. / - That's right.
- The Chinese do that... / - It's so interesting.
- In the morning. / - You see this on the news.
They're also doing it in Hong Kong.
I also need to work out.
- Mom. / - Yes?
- Are you ready? / - Should we also do that?
We have to go trekking, not exercise.
We have to go trekking today.
Before we go trekking, which you wanted to do,
we're going to eat dim sum.
It's not ordinary dim sum that everyone eats.
I prepared a special dim sum.
A special dim sum?
We will look forward to what it will be like.
They must have made dim sum into shapes, right?
You shouldn't get it right so quickly.
(It's not a difficult guess for the master of traveling)
- What is that? / - It's so cute.
It's a place where you can take a lot of photos
for your social media.
Are you going there right now?
Yes.
You've never seen a dim sum like that, right?
I heard that there are more than
100 kinds of dim sum in Hong Kong.
There are far more than 100 kinds.
- Right? / - There are so many.
You couldn't count.
I guarantee the taste.
If you can't guarantee how good it is,
I might criticize you.
I looked it up online and it looked nice...
They say that what looks good tastes good...
But I'm not sure about that.
(She's completely exhausted)
(Around the time Ina was on edge)
- Mom! / - Why?
Can you see that shining place?
- Is it that place? / - Yes.
I saw that place from photos.
- Here? / - That's right.
- Is it right? / - Yes.
There are so many pretty buildings
hidden among large buildings.
It was hard to find.
I heard that most Hong Kong people really eat
dim sum during lunch as the main dish.
You said you were on a diet.
- It smells sweet. / - Dim sum is good for diet.
It was also my first time eating dim sum.
- What? / - Really?
- What? / - I also only had it once.
It was my first time there.
This is a problem.
You can't eat dim sum elsewhere now.
- You're in trouble. / - Oh, my.
- That looks good. / - My blood pressure.
(The meatball and the juice taste amazing)
Xiaolongbay is the best.
- You mean xiaolongbao. / - Xiaolongbao?
(Xiaolongbao, $3.36)
- Looks good. / - You can't eat dim sum elsewhere now.
- But... / - Those are shrimp.
- Oh, my. / - You just ordered the basics.
These are the basics.
- We started with the basics. / - Yes.
- Those are shumai. / - Shumai!
That's delicious.
- That's nice. / - I'll take a photo for you.
You took a funny photo, right?
(Unlike Ina's worries, she looks pretty in the photo)
I'm this kind of woman.
She took a really good photo of you.
- She's good at taking photos. / - She really is.
It really looks like she having her first dim sum there.
- We should have also taken photos. / - Yeah.
That's a pity.
(Hyejin tastes them first)
(Ina is nervous for no reason)
It has a clean taste.
- Everyone will like this. / - That's right.
Men and women of all ages will like this.
- It tastes clean, right? / - It's really good.
They made it with shrimp, mushrooms
and shrimp meatballs.
A whole shrimp is in here.
- The texture is nice. / - A whole shrimp is in here.
It feels like just eating the shrimp from shrimp fried rice.
It's kind of greasy.
(It's time to taste xiaolongbao next)
- That was so good. / - Here it is.
This...
- Are you on our side now? / - What?
- Just go over there. / - Will you give me that if I go?
You need to tear it on your spoon.
- You need to cool them. / - Yes.
- It looks so good. / - It's hot because of the juice...
So you need to be careful.
- It's really good. / - It's really hot.
The juice is just popping out.
(Tasting the juice first comes when eating xiaolongbao)
(Is this right?)
(She sees how Hyejin eats and takes a bite right away)
It's hot.
The one we had before had a good texture
because it had seafood.
- But the juice is so good for this. / - That is...
Xiaolongbao is really...
- It's a new world. / - It's a new world.
A new world spreads inside your mouth.
Those dumplings are like Korean stalked sea squirt.
You need to be careful when you eat them.
- Sea squirt? / - Because it bursts?
You need to be careful when it bursts.
Stalked sea squirt?
You know what donkotsu ramen is, right?
Donkotsu ramen in Japan.
This tastes like that soup. It feels like they condensed
the soup and put it in the meatballs, right?
You have quite a unique palate.
- This is really good. / - I had this for the first time.
- That's really good. / - Yes.
- That looks good. / - It's really good.
- This is what I hate the most. / - What is it?
Two people usually come to eat in restaurants, right?
But what should you do when they give you three?
I usually don't give up food but I'll give it up for you.
Ina can eat two of those since Hyejin is on a diet.
- You should order one more. / - That's right.
You can eat three of them each.
But we ordered a lot of other things too.
- There's more? / - Yes.
It's so cute!
(Her eyes are fixed)
- How are we going to eat these? / - Oh, dear.
Is it the duck shaped dim sum from earlier?
- What is it? / - It's a torture.
- Panda! / - Panda.
- It's cute. / - That's the signature dish there.
- It's really cute. / - It's really delicious.
- Is it delicious? / - It's delicious.
I think if you go there with children,
they won't whine.
- That's scary. They are birds. / - Right?
- I'm so scared. / - They are birds.
- So scary. / - They look the same as that bird.
Do you eat it whole?
- It's fried, isn't it? / - That's cruel!
It's so cute!
I don't think I can eat that.
- What do we do? / - You must take photos.
Right?
- She's good at taking photos. / - Let's try them.
I feel sorry.
There must be cheese inside them.
- It smells so good. / - Do they have red beans inside?
No? Is it meat?
- It's coming out. / - Oh, my!
- What is that? / - I'm so surprised.
Oh, my God.
Cheese?
- What is that? / - I'm so surprised.
- Oh, my God! / - Cheese?
I'm sorry.
It's hot, so be careful.
(They apologize and take a bite each)
- It's flowing. / - It kind of feels like a pumpkin.
It also kind of feels like cheese.
I thought that it was cheese.
It's custard, so it's sweet.
But it's not that sweet.
It's a little less sweet than custard.
- It's custard. / - It's sweet egg custard.
That must be good.
- It was so good. / - It's sweet custard.
I never had this before in other dim sum places.
The custard is kind of...
- Flowing. / - It's overflowing.
- It helps to appreciate the flavor. / - It's charming.
This really suits my taste.
- It's overflowing. / - Children...
Will like to eat these.
It's the ultimate move.
- It's quite characteristic. / - Yes.
I'm sorry but I will also eat you.
They must have fried these. Gosh!
Did you eat the heads after pulling them off?
- We did. / - So cruel.
- Are those ducks? / - Yes, they're ducks.
(What does the duck dim sum taste like?)
The juice is flowing.
The juice came out when I took a bite...
- So I thought it was curry. / - Oh, my!
- I think it was duck meat and pork. / - It must be pork.
- That looks delicious. / - It was delicious.
- It looks delicious. / - They mixed...
- Duck meat and pork. / - That's why it's duck shaped.
- It kind of smells like curry. / - Curry.
Kids these days will really like this.
You get a good variety.
Plus, there are things that kids will like.
- It's so cute. / - It's not a traditional place.
- They make fusion dim sums. / - Fusion.
It will be really nice to go with your family.
You can order...
- That for the kids to see. / - That will be the best.
Are you done?
Are you full?
(They head off to their next itinerary)
Go! Thank you for the food.
(Ina's Day for Hyejin)
(Dragon's Back)
They said, "Thank you" in Korean for us.
- How will we go there? / - If you didn't rent a car...
They say that the fastest way to go to Dragon's Back...
Is to take the subway.
How to go to Dragon's Back.
Take the MTR.
Take bus 9 at exit A3.
Get off at Cape Collinson station.
I can show off to mom now.
Where do we have to get off?
We have to get off at Shau Kei Wan.
And take bus 9.
Do we have to take the bus as well?
- Yes, but that's the fastest way. / - Really?
You have to decrease the costs with this.
Ina, you're doing a good job.
You must have matched your outfits.
- Yes, we matched our outfits. / - Yes.
- We also matched our outfits. / - Yes.
(They take the Hong Kong MTR Island Line)
(30 minutes by bus to the final stop)
Dragon's Back starts from here.
We got off from the bus station.
This is the entrance.
It's right here.
(The trekking course is located right next to the stop)
It starts in front of the bus stop.
- That's nice. / - There's a dragon again.
- It looks like a dragon's back. / - That place?
- Yes. / - That's why it's Dragon's Back.
Ina, do you also like to work out usually?
Yes, I like to walk.
- Tell us the truth. / - I really do.
- Gosh. / - I hike once a day...
With my dog.
I feel bad for your dog.
What?
I just feel bad for your dog's knees.
I think dogs can come here too.
It's slightly uphill here.
- From the start? / - Yes.
Bamboo...
- Yes, bamboo. / - There's lots of bamboo.
I wish there were pandas too.
There aren't any here.
It's my little wish.
It feels more like China and Hong Kong
than Korean mountains because there's bamboo.
Does it have to have bamboo to feel like China?
Yes, of course.
I heard that there aren't a lot of fork roads there.
You won't get lost that way.
- That's right. / - You just have to go straight.
Since it only has one road?
Some paths are wide open.
Do you go back down the path that you climb up?
- Yes. / - Gosh.
(They're stepping towards the top of the mountain)
Mom, but I'm already tired.
You will get used to it once you hike a little bit more.
Let's see.
(Hyejin wants to rest while watching the view)
You should also look at the sky.
There is a big boat over there.
(Climb a little and you can see a different Hong Kong)
It's so amazing.
There really is a big boat.
- It's way up there, right? / - It's way up there.
Isn't it so amazing?
According to my search,
our destination has a far prettier view.
- Really? / - Yes.
- Let's go then. / - We only walked for 8 minutes.
(They recovered their strength after a short rest)
How many hours was that course?
It was a 3-hour course.
- A 3-hour course? / - It was 8.5km.
I'd rather be on a boat for 6 hours
than walk for 3 hours.
- I did a good job, right? / - Yes.
You're the best.
If you do this during your trip,
it will make your meal taste better.
- If you don't do this... / - If you make a round...
- Your swelling will subside fast. / - Yes.
- Yes. / - The sunlight is also so pretty.
(They recharge and head off again)
The trekking course is so pretty.
(They've traveled a third of the way)
(There are magnificent views everywhere)
The view is so amazing.
(It's not a difficult course due to gentle slopes)
The weather is also really nice.
If you get into trekking, you'll keep at it.
Isn't it so nice?
Yes, that's why you search for courses.
She works out a lot.
Hyejin really works out a lot.
People must go all the way up there.
Don't you think so?
Ina, will it be okay for you?
I don't think I'll be okay.
I tried walking for a long time
but I don't think this is really hard.
- 8.5km? / - 8.5km...
Is a piece of cake.
I didn't walk for a long time, so I'm tired.
I think she's kind of having a hard time.
It's so hot right now.
You shouldn't rest too much
when you're tired during trekking.
- You shouldn't rest. / - You shouldn't rest.
It's the water of life.
- We need it. / - We'll be in trouble without it.
(She holds it tightly in her hands)
How many kilometers did we walk?
We've come about a quarter of the way.
A quarter?
I'm sure we walked more.
A quarter plus 0.5.
(Does she really mean it?)
(They were energetic in the beginning)
(But their strength is decreasing gradually)
It's a piece of cake.
(Hyejin climbs up without giving up until the end)
(Shocked)
Mom.
Mom!
What can they see?
- Wow! / - Can they see the sea?
It was so pretty.
Everything was spread out and open.
(Wow)
- The wind feels so nice. / - I really like it.
I don't care if the wind makes my hair messy.
It doesn't feel like Hong Kong from up there.
- It felt like Europe. / - What is this?
- Did they have a beach like this? / - Right?
(The moment when their long journey bores fruit)
It's so pretty.
(The view is unbelievable even when they're seeing it)
- The feel of the wind. / - Doesn't it feel so good?
Pretend to be weak.
I'm going to be blown down by the wind.
(They must feel energetic to make jokes)
Isn't it so nice?
This is a small but certain happiness.
Do you know that?
Small but certain happiness.
(Okay)
It's hard, right?
You got used to sweet and salty.
(You're giving me a hard time)
Can you see where all the people are gathered?
I guess people take more pictures over there.
It kind of feels like the Grand Canyon.
- Have you been there? / - No.
Why do you talk like you've been to everywhere?
- Let's go over there, show off... / - Okay.
And pretend like we've been there before.
- Let's go. / - Let's take the best photo.
(They move to take the best photos of their lives)
- Mom, does this pose look good? / - Yes.
(Yay)
Mamma Mia!
That was awesome.
(Shouting on Dragon's Back, Mamma Mia)
(Ina takes photos of a running Hyejin this time)
(The travel master takes unique photos)
- Paparazzi shots. / - What is this?
- What is this? / - I took sequential photos.
- It looks scary. / - Sequential photos.
What is that?
It's kind of like the computer graphics of "Ureme."
- It's so nice. / - Isn't it so nice?
I didn't realize it earlier
why CNN chose this but I think I know now.
- That must feel good. / - It's so pretty.
- The path we took is winding. / - Yes.
It really looks like a dragon's back.
I guess that's why it's called Dragon's Back.
I can see everything from here.
It was hot earlier but it's cold now.
- Isn't that right? / - Yes.
We could fly from here.
Let's go!
(Their teamwork is perfect)
Oh, my.
(You can actually enjoy paragliding on Dragon's Back)
We indirectly experienced paragliding.
- Oh, my. / - Let's go!
- The wind was so strong. / - I was so surprised.
- Such great CGI. / - To save money on paragliding.
It's so nice.
I don't know how to explain it.
It's the best if you see this for yourself.
If you come to Hong Kong,
you should make time for half a day or a day.
I think it's a good idea to experience this.
You meant that it will be nice...
- To come to Dragon's Back, right? / - That's right.
I didn't even know that there was
a trekking course in the city.
The more I get to know it, the more I like it.
That's the charm, isn't it?
This is the last course of Ina's Day.
I heard that spicy crabs are famous in Hong Kong.
Let's end this hardship by eating spicy food.
- Let's go then. / - Let's go, mom.
(I liked every single moment we were together)
She's really good at taking photos.
(Ina's Day for Hyejin)
- It's the last supper. / - It's the last supper.
- I'm worried about this. / - What did they eat?
- What could it be? / - Please stop eating.
I really agree with that saying earlier.
It's scary because you know the taste.
- I'm about to go insane. / - That's the scariest thing.
That's right, I know that taste.
I'll just take a short break.
(From Shau Kei Wan to Causeway Bay)
(The last night arrives with the end of the trek)
(Where did they go for their last supper?)
(Causeway Bay)
(Hong Kong's commercial area, popular among youth)
There are a lot of things here.
- Isn't that right? / - There are a lot of restaurants.
- Causeway Bay. / - I'll take you to the...
Crab restaurant that is the most famous thing here.
Crabs?
- I told you earlier. / - It's over now.
- We're going to eat spicy crabs. / - I'm worried.
Spicy?
It's over now.
- That's a lot. / - Garlic.
You all know this, right?
Fried food taste good with any sauce.
- Gosh. / - Don't pour that on top.
That looks so good.
- Oh, my. / - Gosh.
Your fingernails will continue to smell if you do that.
- Your fingernails will smell. / - Until you shampoo.
It won't disappear until you shampoo your hair.
You have to wash your hair.
- It's here. / - Wow.
(An impressive sight)
It's the representative dish...
- The crab dish. / - Yes.
(Spicy crab, $96.30)
Let's try it.
(What will the spicy crab taste like?)
Listen to that sound.
(Crispy)
- We know that taste. / - It's really good.
- Isn't it delicious? / - Yes.
(What is Hyejin's evaluation?)
It's good.
Thank goodness.
(Ina also takes a bite)
- What will she do now? / - You'll lose a tooth.
(Ina is puzzled. Hyejin thinks that Ina is cute)
Were you looking at me like that?
She tried to crack it with her teeth.
She's similar to Sandeul.
It was so funny.
(Ina is puzzled, Hyejin finds her cute)
I should crack it here.
(She even uses tools)
She doesn't know how to use that.
I can't crack it.
(Hyejin does it for Ina)
It's slippery.
(Oh, so cool)
- Thank you. / - That's the wisdom of life.
- Like this. / - Wisdom?
You can do that when you become an adult.
(What will the crab taste like?)
(It's delicious)
How can you explain this taste?
It tastes like garlic.
It really is.
It was fried with garlic, so it has a savory aroma.
It also has green onions.
When you eat it with the green onions,
it tastes salty and spicy.
You can chew on the shell if the shell is thin.
It's really crispy. The flesh is also tender.
It's really good.
(It's a perfect combination with the tender crab meat)
At a glance, that garlic may seem like salt.
Because it's salty.
- All of the food is quite salty. / - Yes.
It's really delicious if you brush them off.
The crab dish is meaningless without the garlic.
- That's right. / - When we usually eat crabs...
We just steam them,
marinate them in soy sauce
or marinate them in spicy sauce to eat them.
Eating crabs like this isn't common in Korea.
- It's really uncommon. / - That's why it's unique.
This itself has a strong taste.
- The crab is just a helping hand. / - Yes.
(Fantastic combination with the light taste of crab)
Are most crabs...
Usually big like this?
This is the delicious part.
(The claws are the best part)
(Will it taste different from ordinary crab?)
I've got you, claw.
(She takes a bite right away)
It's really fresh.
This is really...
(Ina also takes a big bite)
(Her face reacts first from the impressive taste)
- The meat is so delicious. / - Yes.
The meat is so delicious.
The meat is really bouncy and tender.
It's so delicious.
This is how you eat crabs.
I'll find out what's inside the shell.
(Surprised)
(Hyejin first gives a piece of crab meat to Ina)
- You should eat. / - What is that?
- It's the intestines. / - It's the intestines.
You have to eat that.
- Mom, you should eat. / - Eat.
I'm taking the entire shell.
(Hyejin eats while holding an entire crab shell)
The meat on the shell.
That's right. You have to eat it with rice.
- Eat some bokchoy. / - It's like fried marinated crab.
- That's right. / - Fried marinated crab?
- The seasoning is strong, right? / - It has to be good.
- Chinese people eat their food salty. / - Yes.
- It's perfectly seasoned for them. / - Perfect for them.
Why don't we eat some rice?
(You can't leave out fried rice while eating spicy crab)
I like that rice.
- Me too, I really like that rice. / - Me too.
People think that it won't make you gain weight
but that's wrong.
- It makes you gain weight. / - Yeah.
- That'd be good mixed. / - You gain less weight.
I admit that this looks good.
- This was really good. / - I admit that this looks good.
(She takes a big bite)
(She's satisfied)
It's so delicious.
(Ina also takes a bite)
It kind of tastes like crab meat burgers.
It tastes like crab meat burgers?
Could you taste crab meat burgers from that?
She said that because she thought it was so delicious.
- Crab meat burgers? / - Stop nitpicking.
We all have different tastes.
But it tastes good because of the garlic.
It's nice with the rice.
(Combination of salty garlic flakes and savory fried rice)
You have to eat it with vegetables.
- Eat it with vegetables. / - If you go to China...
You should always order vegetables on the side.
- You have to eat vegetables. / - You have to.
- Morning glory. / - They have a wide variety.
It doesn't smell.
What are you doing when you brought me here?
(She tries it to not make Hyejin mad)
- She doesn't like it. / - She doesn't like it?
She doesn't eat vegetables at all.
- I don't eat it at all. / - I eat all of the vegetables.
- Of course. / - Really?
They're delicious.
It just tastes like oil to me.
- The oil taste is delicious. / - Yes.
- It's really good. / - Isn't it really good?
No, it isn't.
The seasoning is...
- A little strong, right? / - Yes.
The vegetables and fried rice
dilutes the strong seasoning a little bit.
The seasoning is too strong,
so you can't help but eat vegetables.
I think it's quite successful.
We will have to eat until the end to know that.
The fried rice looks really good.
I sometimes order more morning glory.
- There are a lot of vegetables. / - Yes.
You need to order stir-fried vegetables no matter what.
(Mamma Mia eats all of the food up in no time)
- When will Hyejin start her diet? / - Greed.
What are we going to do about it?
You?
(She laughed so much, she started to drool)
Can you see this?
(You can see the traces of an intense meal)
I had rice grains stuck on my mouth while eating.
I probably have a lot stuck on me.
- You didn't disappoint me. / - Thank goodness.
Thank you for trying.
I got to see sides of you that I didn't know about.
People who don't get along well
can break up during trips.
But people in good relationships can grow deeper
and continue for a long time.
I think we're going to be a good case.
I think we have a deep relationship already.
I'm going to wait depending on what you do.
(Mamma Mia's deepening trip is over now)
(Hyejin's Day for Ina)
Personally,
I really enjoyed the trekking and dim sum.
- It's a course that I like. / - Yes.
Actually, I like to be active.
That's why I work out a lot.
But the tip that Hong Kong had
such a beautiful trekking course...
- Was shocking to me. / - That's right.
- It's not far. You could go there. / - It's close.
Men who like to work out will run up there.
Beginners and men and women of all ages
can trek up Dragon's Back.
But if you like trekking,
there are lots of other courses as well,
other than Dragon's Back.
- Okay. / - So you should look them up.
- Is there an admission fee? / - No.
- Can you just go in? / - Yes, you can just go in.
- You can just go in. / - Get off of bus 9.
This is important. I heard that Ina
prepared something like...
A gift to celebrate this trip.
- What? / - Really?
I took a lot of photos
but it would be a pity to just have them on my phone.
Oh, my God.
Women do things like this.
She's so considerate.
- What is that? / - Look at Jungyu's face.
- "What is that?" / - Look at Jungyu's face.
- It's pretty. / - Isn't it pretty?
- It's a calendar. / - A calendar.
With the photos we took...
- How did you make that? / - Look carefully.
I can't recover my senses.
This is October, next year October.
- This is for next year. / - This is next September.
- This will be so memorable. / - That's right.
- It's like a poster. / - You'd remember for a year.
Men could never come up with an idea like this.
There's a reason why Ina is so loved.
You should have at least prepared goat bones.
- Should I wear the horns like this? / - Yes, the horns.
You received a surprise gift.
- How was it? / - I'm so surprised.
If I knew about this, I would've prepared something.
I didn't prepare anything.
I'm so thankful. I was touched for a moment.
I feel so proud. Thank you.
- Okay. / - Okay.
Let's find out the expenses now.
Ssangdeulier Tour went on an airplane tour...
- So they spent $415. / - Yes.
Excluding the airfare, let's find out
Mamma Mia Tour's final expense.
Hyejin!
Per person...
(Will it be less than Ha Long Bay's expenses?)
- How much is the expense? / - $500...
- What? / - $500?
$510.
- $510? / - That's not a big difference.
- That's not a big difference. / - That's right.
- It's a $60 difference. / - Actually...
Hong Kong is a lot more expensive...
- If you think about the cost of living. / - Right.
That's why you should go...
- With someone who knows a lot. / - That's right.
We didn't take taxis...
- And went on ferries. / - You walked a little.
If you walk a little, it's enough so
you won't have to spend a lot of money.
That's good. Thank goodness.
Just choose.
You can go to Vietnam and stay like a king
or have a really hard time in Hong Kong.
- That's right. / - You will have to walk...
- For 8.5km. / - We made a mistake while...
Ordering food once. That was quite expensive.
- Yes. / - Really?
- When you ate hot pot? / - Yes, if you look into it...
- When you ate hot pot. / - The prices will be similar.
We continued to make mistakes while ordering food.
We didn't care about the amount.
- That's right. / - We ordered a lot but it's cheap.
Why worry about the amount?
Whether you want to order freely
or stress every time you order food.
You can choose between that.
That's good.
Would you like to go to Hong Kong
according to Mamma Mia Tour?
- Please vote! / - Please vote!
(They designed a family trip with parents)
(What will the judges choose?)
Will it be Ssangdeulier Tour's
trip to Ha Long Bay, Vietnam?
Or will it be Mamma Mia Tour's trip to Hong Kong?
What will the judges choose?
(Hong Kong vs. Ha Long Bay)
Will it be Vietnam or Hong Kong?
Will it be Ssangdeulier or Mamma Mia?
- It's coming out. / - First...
- Is this "Immortal Songs?" / - The first digit!
- "Immortal Songs" and us. / - The last digit is 8!
- What is happening? / - It must be so close.
- It's close. / - If it's a 2-vote difference...
- No! / - It's 7, 8, 9.
- No! / - Is it 98?
- Is it 98? / - 2 votes?
- No! / - It's 7, 8, 9.
(Ha Long Bay wins with 90 votes)
- They got 90 votes. / - That shirt is really cute.
- It's 90 votes. / - We won.
- This is impossible. / - It happened.
- It's a 12-vote difference. / - Yes.
Hyejin, I know you're sad
but could you say something?
I think that Ha Long Bay is a really nice trip location.
- It was really cost effective. / - Yes.
The contents were also meaningful.
I also want to go there next time.
- Call me. / - Yes.
What will you do if she calls you?
I'm going to take her there.
(They make corny dad jokes until the end)
- NC.A was the host for 2 weeks. / - Yes.
Between Ha Long Bay and Hong Kong,
where would you rather go?
- Be honest. / - I want to go to Hong Kong.
- With your mom? / - Yes.
It's because I really like Chinese food.
While watching the Hong Kong episode,
I just kept thinking, "I want to go there..."
- And "I want to eat that." / - Did you write a lot down?
- She wrote a lot. / - I wrote a lot.
- She wrote a lot about Hong Kong. / - Like this.
She wrote the entire Hong Kong route.
I can see that.
She must've really disliked Vietnam episode.
No, that's not it.
- I didn't hate it. / - Women will like Hong Kong.
- Yes. / - Yes.
We will take a week off due to the awards.
The week after, we will come back...
With a special that will highlight the end of 2018.
- It's already the end. / - Yes.
We prepared a lot of unaired footage...
- That we couldn't air, right? / - Yes.
We will come back 2 weeks later.
We will see you next time.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
("Really Bad Boy" by Red Velvet)