Reset Tour! ♪ Turn it all back ♪
What's the reason we came here?
Photo of a lifetime.
The photos look really great.
A romantic couple's trip.
This was a dream of mine.
A surge of romantic love.
You were really beautiful.
Will you marry me in your next life?
I love you.
It was a success.
Congratulations.
(How did they plan the Penang trip?)
For married couples, trips are wars of love.
Battle Trip!
Last week, it really was
a love that's like war.
- That's right. / - A very happy war.
Sia will join us as our host this week as well.
Last week's episode was quite romantic, wasn't it?
I'll be honest with you.
Throughout my marriage,
I thought that I had met a great husband.
He's very good to me.
But when I saw how Dongseok treats Jiyoon,
I realized my husband has a long way to go.
Has he ever shed tears after
realizing how much he loves you?
No, he has not.
He has never cried in front of me.
He didn't even cry when I delivered our child.
I was a bit disappointed about it.
I really thought he was so cool.
- Korea's model husband. / - Seriously.
- You won over everyone. / - Last week was...
Choi Dongseok's special.
Sieun, why don't you compliment your husband too?
Brag about him.
Brag about your husband.
Taehyun is good at doing house chores.
- Before I got married... / - That's the best.
I'd never done laundry before.
I didn't know how to do it.
When my mom went away...
While I was at work,
he came to my house and did the laundry for me.
Like a genie.
Taehyun does all the cleaning and laundry at home.
And I do the cooking.
- That's amazing. / - He's so cool.
You divide your chores.
This week, we will watch
Taehyun and Sieun's trip.
I heard this is your first time traveling together.
For your honeymoon, you went to volunteer.
That's right.
When we got married,
we wanted our honeymoon to be meaningful.
So we went to an orphanage in Jeju-do
to spend time with the children.
We never got to go on a real honeymoon.
We have never gone on a trip together as a couple.
Jiyoon and Dongseok,
where did you two go for your honeymoon?
We went to a few places.
- We did... / - Really?
- A three-city tour. / - Where?
We went to Singapore,
Hong Kong and Macao.
Great course.
That must have been nice.
What about you, Sia? Where did you go?
We went to Ko Samui.
- Ko Samui. / - We went snorkeling.
My husband told me that a fish
with a thorn poked his foot.
But...
I thought he looked fine.
But he thought his foot was swollen and paralyzed.
He made such a fuss.
I was so turned off by that.
- For me... / - On your honeymoon?
I married my husband because I fell for his...
- Maturity and reliability. / - Manliness...
He acted like a baby.
I can't forget about that incident.
Honeymoon destinations change with each generation.
Back in the days,
going abroad wasn't as easy as it is now.
- Most people... / - Bugok Hawaii.
- The elders... / - Went to Jeju-do often.
They'd visit hot springs or visit Jeju-do.
But it's different now.
Things in the 1990s and 2000s...
- The 20th and 21st centuries are different. / - Right.
The 90s are separated into before and after
the Asian Financial Crisis.
They were truly tough times.
Before the Crisis, honeymoons focused on tourism.
People went to Phuket, Thailand.
Guam or Saipan.
- Places where you can take lots of photos. / - Right.
Malaysia, Bali...
They went to such places.
But after the Crisis, people went on...
- Domestic honeymoons. / - That's right.
This is when people started going to Jeju-do a lot.
- Jeju-do is great. / - It's awesome.
In the 2000s,
people started to spend more on honeymoons
to make the most of the opportunity.
That's when they started going to Europe.
Or even Las Vegas.
They'd enjoy the sightseeing and have time to relax.
A place they can do everything.
It's changed.
- The trends keep changing. / - They keep changing.
If that's the trend...
Penang, which was our destination,
will attract a lot of couples after this show.
Is it a memorable place?
It's so...
It's a place where
many cultures come together.
I love those places.
There's Europe.
- Yes, Europe. / - And Southeast Asia.
And vacation areas too.
- Vacation areas too. / - Yes.
You can enjoy sports in the ocean.
It's great for things like that.
We don't know much about Penang.
Not many know that Penang is in Malaysia.
That's right.
Well, a picture is worth a thousand words.
We'll have to head there.
Let's go there now.
I wonder what these two...
What kind of cringy things they did.
I bet it became a real honeymoon
once the cameras were off.
Yes.
Seriously, for us...
It really felt like a honeymoon.
- What's wrong with him? / - What? What?
- What? / - Sikyung, why are you crying?
- Wait, Sung Sikyung. / - Nothing, nothing.
- I'm embarrassed. / - Sikyung.
- Sikyung keeps crying. / - What's wrong with you?
- No, nothing. / - You're 40 now.
It must be time for Sikyung to go.
He keeps...
- We'll watch the footage. / - He gets excited.
Sounds weird saying it's time for him to go.
- Go where? / - Get married.
Get married?
You should say it like that then.
- Time to go. / - It sounds weird otherwise.
It's time for him to get married.
- That's right. / - Time for him to go.
Let's check it out.
(Like last week, they will watch the clip separately)
(It's time for the Penang trip!)
Let's do a throwback to the 80s.
- I don't know about the 80s. / - Remember that?
After we take turns to talk...
- You want us to do it together? / - And ask for favor.
It looks like they are dating.
- They are still newlyweds. / - Yes...
Hello, we are...
They still look fresh.
Still newlyweds, right?
Yes, we are.
We're like newlyweds
but have been married for 3 years.
- I'm Park Sieun. / - I'm Zin Taehyun.
- It's nice to see you. / - Hello.
- Nice to see you. / - They are different.
- 3 years. / - They seem so fresh.
It does feel slightly different.
- Slightly different. / - They're quite different.
It won't be over with a simple resignation.
Do you understand?
Hey, I want to buy that.
He's like a kid.
Goodness.
Don't do that.
Please don't do that.
Coconut ice cream.
We get to see things like this.
- That looks cute. / - I want to be fed too.
Try some.
I think you know how to handle your husband.
I do?
Honey, this is honestly too hard.
- You were wrong, right? / - I was wrong.
It's going down.
Seriously...
(They're still working out their differences)
(But they're a lovely couple with great chemistry)
I took some time off.
Then on the first drama
I did after my comeback...
- Taehyun was the lead. / - I remember this drama.
- And I was a supporting actress. / - So cute.
- You really met in a drama. / - He came to me...
And said, "I've always been your fan, ma'am."
He came and said that...
- With everyone around. / - She's your senior?
In 2001...
She's older too?
- Yes, by 1 year. / - I was an open recruit actor.
At MBC.
She was the lead...
- The lead and a minor role. / - Of a drama.
I had a minor role in it.
- It's like a movie. / - She was really pretty then.
I was shocked in my young age.
Shocked that such a pretty girl existed.
I'm sorry. No, but wait a minute...
I'm sorry.
- Goodness. / - Oh, no.
- That's so... / - What's going on?
That's just wrong.
I don't go that far.
- Don't do things like this. / - I don't.
I don't think that's right.
Let's see what you did in Penang.
No, no, that's...
That's a bit too...
Wait, for me...
You shouldn't have criticized him last week.
Let me start with an apology.
I feel a lot less guilty now.
We met in that drama
and she was exactly the same.
Things started working out
and I got her number.
I worked hard and chased her around.
We wanted to go to Southeast Asia
so we researched.
Recently, my sister... She lived for 5 years...
In Malaysia.
My second eldest sister.
So I asked her.
She said there's a place called Penang in Malaysia
and that she'd been there for a holiday.
When I was just researching about it, it looked so fun.
There were a lot of things to talk about.
This is the first trip we've been on alone.
That's why I was really excited.
Is this Penang?
- Yes, yes. / - What's this?
- It looks like Seoul. / - It's a city.
It's more of a city than a vacation spot.
No, no, no.
No, no!
- Come on. / - No, no.
(Thrilling activities)
You need the activities.
Oh, goodness.
That looks good.
- That's amazing. / - I like this.
I could eat these two every day.
It's good.
It's really good.
It's good we came.
With my wife.
Oh, My Honey.
He's planned a surprise too.
What the? My goodness.
Compared to Jiyoon's trip...
You didn't have things like this.
This is worse than last week.
No, no. I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Was I like this?
Wait, don't leave!
Did I do that?
I'm sorry.
Tour name.
- Team name. / - Your tour name.
- We're the lively Park and Zin couple. / - Yeah.
Park, Zin.
On tour with the lively Park and Zin couple.
- Oh, Park and Zin. / - Lively Park and Zin Tour.
That's a good name.
We want to move each other.
Thankful Tour.
We're thankful for each other.
We monitor each other.
He said monitor.
He's a bit of a jokester.
He fools around a lot.
- Park Sieun. / - And Zin Taehyun's...
Touching Tour.
Lively Park and Zin Tour.
That's a great name.
- So your sister recommended it. / - Yes.
I hadn't heard about it before.
If it's recommended by a local, it must be good.
I decided where we're going.
Where?
Kapitan Keling Mosque.
St. George's Church.
Come here.
Come over here now.
Wait.
Just keep searching quietly.
Were you upset?
I was working on something but he kept calling me.
Penang is pretty small.
What's that thing that flies in the sky?
She wants to do something weird.
There's a picture. People are flying above a boat.
I don't understand why people do that.
(He has acrophobia)
(Lively Park and Zin's challenges in Penang)
(Lively Park and Zin's healing in Penang)
We're finally heading off.
(Incheon International Airport)
(Kuala Lumpur)
(Penang)
(Takes 9 hours)
It takes quite some time.
We had a stopover in Hong Kong.
It seems like it's worth visiting. The city looks exotic.
Yes. What's amazing is that there's
a Hindu temple, a Buddhist temple, a Catholic church
and Protestant church all on one street.
It's a very unique culture.
India, China,
Malaysia, Europe. It's all mixed.
That's very unique.
That place looks like Europe.
I kept forgetting I was in Malaysia.
- That looks so good. / - It looks good.
It's like the Jeolla-do of Malaysia.
All the delicious food is there.
- The Jeolla-do of Malaysia? / - Yes, Jeolla-do.
We're finally here.
- Honey. / - Yeah.
- We're in a summer country. / - We're here.
- Now... / - What should we take?
Now whenever I see a suitcase,
I feel like someone should get on.
- I want to ride it. / - It's good, right?
Yes.
She should've rode the suitcase.
What should we take?
- Is there a bus? / - I checked it out.
- There's taxi. / - From what I found out...
Taxis here are different to what we know.
There are taxis outside...
- If you look here... / - Where are the taxis?
- The taxis... / - Which one's a taxi?
The important thing is that there are no taxis.
- The taxis aren't marked. / - They're not.
- How can you tell? / - You take a ticket.
You use that ticket as a travel pass.
So there'd be no illegal hustling
by the drivers.
At least not at the airport.
He said 69, right?
Is that $18 something?
I think so.
Thank you.
I think this is the ticket. Let's go.
We should present this ticket then?
I think so.
That's interesting.
Ticket.
Thank you.
- Penang, Malaysia. / - Now I feel the heat...
- It feels like we're really here. / - I know.
Right?
How did you know about the taxi?
It's amazing.
- The ticket taxi, right? / - Yeah.
You get ripped off so much on vacation.
That's right. This is to prevent that
here in Penang, George Town.
The city hall's...
I'm trying to talk here...
Oops, I'm sorry. I wanted to shoot the airport.
(They arrive at the hotel after an hour from the airport)
Come here.
What's this?
Come over here. I prepared something for you.
(Ta-da)
We never had the chance to do things like this.
What's going on?
- I... / - Yeah?
- I've only seen these in dramas. / - They have swans!
They have birds.
They have swans.
It's the first time I saw such a thing.
Goodness.
- It's so pretty. / - The roses are in a heart shape.
When did they... Right?
1, 2, 3.
Does your husband take a lot of photos for you?
Not as much as her husband.
Not as much...
Not like Jiyoon.
- You'll see. Pictures are all you're left with. / - Right.
Our enjoyable Park and Zin Tour...
Let's start it.
Lively Park and Zin Tour!
(Lively Park and Zin's challenges in Penang)
(Center of Penang, George Town)
Honey, look at me.
(Checking herself out in Taehyun's sunglasses)
It looks like they're on a honeymoon.
- I really felt that way. / - That's enough.
You look very pretty.
Shall we go?
Is this George Town?
Yes, it's George Town.
It's the old center of Penang.
The whole town is designated
as a UNESCO World Heritage Site.
I should definitely go there.
The buildings are beautiful.
- They look graceful. / - It feels like Europe.
- You're right. It's a variety. / - It's fascinating.
(It's a good photo spot because of the wall paintings)
- Yeah. / - They sell coconut shakes.
- I'm thirsty and hot. / - Let's try coconut ice cream.
Come here.
- What's that? / - It's coconut ice cream.
Hi.
Having an ice cream?
Coconut ice cream.
Coconut shake.
- One. / - One.
Will it taste good?
- Interesting. / - It's in here.
I love my ice cream.
I know.
- You'll eat to your heart's content here. / - Yeah.
Thank you.
How much is it?
It's $2.20 each.
That's reasonable.
- It looks good. / - This is coconut ice cream.
Don't you think you gave me too little ice cream.
Just eat it for now.
It should be half ice cream and...
Keep it down.
Half peanut...
Just try it already. How is it?
- Is it good? / - Yeah.
These things can't fail.
I can taste the coconut.
Why do you give me so little ice cream?
What are you saving it for?
Your teeth will ache if you eat it like that.
You get a headache.
If that was us, we would've ordered...
- Two ice creams. / - You're right.
- One each? / - While we've been eating this..
I discovered something.
- What? / - It will shock you.
Come here. I'll take a photo for you.
Sit down.
This village is full of murals.
The coconut ice cream is part of our tour.
- Okay. / - Sit there.
Just like him.
Oh, very good.
That's it.
- So pretty. / - That's so pretty.
- That's a painting, right? / - Yes.
It's a mural.
That window painting looks nice.
(Take a photo of me patting the kitty)
What are you doing?
Did you take it?
- What? / - You took only one photo?
Trips are all about the photos.
- That's no good. / - You need to take several to choose.
Full, tight, top half. You need all those shots.
Since the model is pretty.
I never thought of all those angles.
She's different since she's an actress.
She's so pretty.
- I... / - Can't we ride that?
What?
- That. / - I've prepared everything.
He looks confident.
It was fun.
What?
It's a remodeled bicycle.
Oh, that?
It's a trishaw.
We should go somewhere on this. Take a seat.
Hello.
- Hi. / - Hello.
- Can you sit here? / - Cornwallis.
Cornwallis.
- A fort? / - Yes.
It's a fort.
Fort, fort.
I really want to go there.
I like these things.
The fort?
I'll definitely go there.
Where?
Fort Cornwallis.
Okay.
You know why I want to go there?
Why?
You'll see once we get there.
So just follow me.
Don't look back though.
The old man is driving
so I feel guilty.
I know.
- This is good. / - Right.
It feels cool.
- It's quite cool. / - Yeah.
- But if you're big... / - It's fun.
You won't be able to share a seat.
This place looks nice.
Right?
This place looks like Europe.
The city is very attractive.
Over here.
I can see the white...
That's...
George Town city hall?
That white building might be it.
You're right. I do see a white building.
That must be it. Can you see it?
- That's the city hall. / - That building...
- Is the most famous landmark. / - That building...
It's so pretty.
- It's the George Town city hall. / - Great for photos.
It's quite small.
Countries that had been colonized
have a sad history...
- Relics. / - But the buildings are beautiful.
That's Fort Cornwallis.
Stop.
- I'll help you out. / - Okay.
Come here.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Thank you.
- There's an entrance fee. / - Yes.
This place
was built by the British.
When the British got here,
they built a fort.
Taehyun studied a lot.
- Yes, I was really surprised. / - Like a guide.
- It's true. / - He played the guide.
You studied a lot.
- You don't need a guide. / - Captain Light built it.
Here.
That's why the fort is star-shaped.
He wanted to explain that to you, Sieun.
I mean, he likes to show off by nature.
There's a real reason that
I wanted to bring you here.
What is it?
There's a legend in that cannon.
- That cannon over there? / - Yes.
If we pray while putting...
A flower inside this cannon...
No way.
Did he bring a flower?
- If we pray while putting / - Okay.
A flower inside this cannon,
we'll be blessed with a child.
This is why we came here?
- I wondered why you kept saying... / - It will...
- We had to go to the fort. / - Help you conceive.
I bet many people come with flowers.
That's right.
- Those who want kids... / - Desperately.
They'll come here.
It's just like our dol hareubang.
- Yes, like touching its nose. / - Yes.
There are a lot of flowers inside.
Really?
I'm putting it in.
Okay.
I'll have a daughter.
We always thought that we should
have a child.
But Taehyun said that
he really liked our lives at the moment.
He kept pushing it back.
- He wanted to have it later. / - Really?
- Goodness. /  - So I asked if he ever will.
And he said we'd have to.
So I suggested that we need to prepare.
And he's been determined since last year.
That we should really have a baby.
Now babies look so beautiful.
Baby girl?
So cute.
- I see. / - She was so cute.
That's so cute.
So cute.
- So a baby will be added... / - We need a daughter.
To your pictures.
I'm a son.
I can't have a son who takes after me.
That's the only reason for my wish to have a daughter.
Baby boys are beautiful
but if he takes after me...
I believe that
I'm not a mature individual.
I agree.
- Men... / - Not mature...
- A daughter like my wife. / - I find him charming.
Right?
- So have you made plans. / - I think so.
We'll have one baby first.
- First... / - But I feel like they'll need a sibling.
- At least two. / - Isn't it great to have two?
- It's great. / - It's great for them.
Three is too much.
- Three... / - Well, three for me...
I'd like a third.
I hear them speaking and...
- Your husband doesn't want a third. / - He doesn't.
- It must be too tough for him. / - What was that?
He doesn't want a third.
- What? / - I think only you want a third.
It must be too hard.
- Did you talk about a third baby? / - Yes, we are.
Did he say he wants a third child?
- No, not at all. / - He said yes.
- Really? / - He said he does.
She really wants another here.
It must've been hard with the first two.
I guess so.
Honey, I'm getting hungry.
Me too.
Should we give the Malaysian cuisine a try?
- Should we? / - I love eating local food.
- Me too. / - Me too.
I can tell this place is good.
- There's also a mural here. / - It looks good.
I'm hungrier after seeing the pictures.
What should we get?
Look at the prices.
- Why is it so cheap? / - It's extremely cheap.
- This is $1.80. / - It's really affordable there.
- $1.80? / - That's a large.
A bowl of noodles costs $1.80.
If it's that cheap,
we order around 10.
- Really? My gosh. / - Foodies do that.
Let's get that.
- These fried noodles look good. / - What's this?
I want Sambal fried rice.
- This and, oh, chicken. / - This.
- We have to have chicken. / - You can't go wrong...
Wherever you order chicken.
- Honey, can I have soup too? / - Huh?
- 10 dishes is less than $20. / - Exactly.
Sure, go ahead.
It's cheap.
But why do you ask?
You'll order what you want anyway.
Excuse me, hurry.
You're just asking him to agree.
- That's right. / - Yeah.
Telling him what I'm ordering.
This one.
(Ordering without caring about price)
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
All that...
- Was $9.30? / - It's less than $10?
Isn't it amazing?
- I love it. / - That's so good.
And it was all so good.
It looks good.
This...
- Oh, together. / - Mix it.
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
This fragrance...
That already looks good.
This is...
It's kind of like kimchi soup.
What's wrong?
Try it.
I don't think it suits my taste.
Honey.
Look at his face.
- He can't eat anything but Korean. / - It's a bit...
I think it'll be like that.
There's that face again.
Thank you.
He's a baby.
Taehyun's a baby at times like this.
It's not to his liking.
And besides, that one
came with fish meat on top.
It tasted like salty dried filefish fillet.
That was...
That sounds delicious.
Excuse me?
Dried filefish fillet is good.
But... Okay.
Thank you.
You need to stir together.
Okay, okay.
The food is served really quickly.
I like that.
Isn't it good?
I guess he doesn't like it.
- It must have a strong aroma. / - Isn't it okay?
I'm curious.
- This one tastes a bit sour. / - I think it'll taste good.
It smells of coriander.
Too much.
This one's okay.
It's like eating salty dried filefish fillet in kimchi soup.
And it's been braised it in soy sauce.
It's a mix of those two.
This is like a bowl of noodles soup
with canned fish, right?
The noodles are softer than the udon noodles in Korea.
- That looks delicious. / - The noodles look so good.
That definitely must've been good.
That's so...
I have to try the rice.
That dish was so good.
I can tell your preference.
Your style...
- I like salty food. / - Is the sambal sauce good too?
- The sauce here was good. / - This is...
Sambal.
Sambal, sambal.
Try mixing this.
I'll try the sambal.
Luckily that one suits his taste.
This is good.
This is good. This is really good.
This is to my liking.
- It tastes like egg fried rice. / - Yes.
It's like I'm mixing Tabasco sauce
with the rice.
The sauce is really spicy.
How is it?
This is to my liking.
- It tastes okay? / - Yes.
It was really good.
I can eat these two dishes
three meals a day.
He's eating alone.
You eat it.
This is perfect for Koreans.
I'll eat this until we leave.
The chicken will be good no matter what...
- So should we take it slow? / - We have to try it.
See what Malaysian chicken is like.
I feel like the chicken will taste weird.
Oh, that... Yes.
Right?
It's full of spices, right?
The aftertaste.
A slight aftertaste.
- Fried chicken always smells the same. / - No.
It has that smell I don't like.
There's a hint of that.
- Really? / - Yeah?
Maybe it's because of the other dishes but I can't tell.
You really have different tastes. Both couples.
Yes.
I was really surprised that he only likes Korean food.
I thought he'd enjoy local foods.
To be honest, I liked the fried chicken.
I didn't understand what spices he could taste.
I learned he was really sensitive.
It's good.
(Taehyun uploaded it on his SNS in the end)
(I recommend the noodles and fried rice)
That's why when I travel...
Do you pack kimchi?
The first thing I do is look for Korean restaurants.
I look up Korean restaurants.
Next, I look up McDonald's.
(Lively Park and Zin's challenge in Penang)
(Extremely high observatory)
- There's a special building here. / - What is it?
It's one of the highest buildings here.
- In Malaysia... / - 63 Square?
Higher than 63 Square.
There's such a building here?
I heard there's this pretty observatory here.
Wow, it's standing tall.
You could see all of downtown Penang.
That's right.
- You'd have to make sure you go there. / - Right.
With you, My Honey...
- Goodness, My Honey? / - That's your pet name?
Yes.
- Honey. / - Yes?
It's so hot and they're still holding hands.
Geez...
You call her My Honey?
I... Yes.
I'm sorry.
- With you, My Honey... / - Yes?
Why do you like tall buildings?
I think...
- Why do you like them? / - Maybe because I'm short.
I think you like tall buildings too much.
Why is that?
It's not just me.
Most people do.
I'm terrified of heights.
I hate high places.
Why?
I'm scared.
I think it's this way.
Yes. Thank you.
Is it a theater?
There are so many buildings.
- Aren't there? / - Yes.
It's like downtown.
That scared me.
Goodness.
How annoying. Don't do that.
- How annoying. Don't do that. / - It opens up.
It opened up so suddenly.
Don't do that. Don't do that.
You should've warned me.
I was surprised too.
- It's so... / - That's so, wow...
This isn't too bad.
This city is peculiar.
- This city of Penang... / - It really is a peculiar city.
Wow, that's so...
That's seriously so...
- It opens up to the real thing. / - Yes.
Is that a painting or what?
- It was amazing. I was so surprised. / - It's beautiful.
Penang really reminds me
of Ganghwado.
This is fun.
That was something new.
Gravity?
- What's this... / - Gravity.
- What about gravity? Why? What? / - Gravity.
I got that sick feeling in my stomach.
- Wow, seriously... / - Honey.
Something goes down here.
- I was so... / - I...
Actually brought you here without telling you.
What is this place?
What this is...
You attach a rope.
- No way. / - And walk out there.
And walk out there.
Oh, my God.
(Did you think it was a regular observatory?)
I hate it.
Jung Joonyoung and
Choi Taejun did that in Macao.
But this place is 6m higher.
That's too high.
We were so scared just watching them.
They opened this in February this year?
Yes, it's very new.
Then you don't know how safe it is.
That's so...
It's making me angry.
- That's so... / - Oh, no.
He's hating it as he watches.
I hate it.
It seems that in general, romantic husbands
have a great fear of heights.
Now I know.
- We tie a rope and go out? / - Yes.
What do we do outside?
We go out and walk around.
You're all insane.
But he's still holding your hand.
- Even as he says that. / - Why would you do this?
Don't do this.
How am I going to do this?
I can't do this.
What, honey?
- Honey, I'm sorry. / - First...
I had no idea
my wife would hide it from me.
Because she knows me really well.
But...
Why did you...
Do that to me?
He looks like he's acting.
"I can't go out there."
It's like, "If you love me, go outside."
Something like that.
"If you love me, jump."
Dongseok does everything despite his fear, right?
He seems to do everything.
- If I say I'll do it alone... / - How is he?
He does it with me because he gets worried.
- That's my husband. / - So cool.
- He's a romanticist. / - That's so cool.
Why are you asking me to do it?
You know I'm afraid of heights.
I thought maybe you might do it.
I want to try this.
I might...
Just take on the challenge.
Just here.
We can do this only in Penang.
Only in Penang.
- Just once... / - I will...
Do it fast.
There's a door in the middle.
- You noticed that? / - I did.
I saw it.
There's a door you can exit midway.
- In case you get scared. / - In the middle?
I noticed that.
You knew.
I'll come back in if I can't do it.
- Yeah, but will you be okay? / - I'll attempt it.
- Because... / -  You don't have to do it.
I'll do it.
Okay.
I'll try it.
And if I can't do it...
Sieun knows how to persuade him.
If I keep telling him to do it...
"I won't do it."
"Do it." "No."
"I won't do it." He does that.
But if I tell him, "You don't have to do it."
"Don't worry about it." "Forget it."
"It's better if you don't do it."
If I say it like that...
- That's funny. / - She has him in the palm of her hands.
He's like, "Should I?"
That's how people think.
That's my big picture.
Done?
Write your real name.
Your real name.
You're Park Eunyeong.
I'll die as Park Sieun. Got a problem with that?
Is that good?
(Happy)
I get it.
He's no longer smiling.
He's like a typical grade schooler.
It's not bad.
Relax. Calm your nerves.
What are you doing?
I'm loosening your arms.
Relax.
Here.
Are you okay?
I can do this.
That's really tough, right?
Okay, good.
Honey, just look at me.
Okay?
I'm scared too.
(They start now)
The sound is...
- It's the wind. / - That's scary.
That's...
- Honey, I'm seriously... / - The floor has holes.
Yes, it does.
Okay.
Honey...
- You're okay. / - Honey, I'm seriously so...
My wife stepped out so I had to.
His face looks so grim.
That's too scary.
This is really hard.
What do I do?
Honey, what do I do?
- I'll hold this. / - Oh...
This is too hard.
I can't look out.
Honey...
I'll take you to court right now!
Don't touch me.
Don't grab me!
Okay, okay.
- Don't grab me! / - Take you to court!
He's so charismatic in dramas...
In dramas...
Honey, this is honestly too hard.
(Smile)
This is honestly too hard.
(Smiling)
Move along. It's too hard.
(Trying to look fine for the picture)
That photo.
- He smiled for the camera. / - Yes.
He sure is an actor.
Honey.
That was really scary.
You're doing great. Come here.
I'm being courageous.
Yes. You're doing so well.
I am.
Now, there will be a great bridge.
Welcome to a great bridge.
What's going on?
What is this?
- It's like a stepping stone bridge. / - It's a track.
Yes, they have a track.
They have missions along the way.
It was fun.
It's so scary with those gaps.
- I can't do this. / - At first...
- It was easy. / - I don't want to do this.
Everybody, follow me.
I don't think I can.
I came this far.
Wait.
Excuse me.
- He'll go out? / - I'll go out.
Is he quitting?
I'm so...
You're sweating so much.
I'm proud of you.
I'm proud.
Did you quit?
I did.
Really?
- I had to. / - It's like a mom consoling her son.
She gave me permission.
You quit?
I'll call it quits here.
I'm so...
I don't recommend it to people who has acrophobia.
That'll be too difficult for them.
Honey, I'll go farther.
- More? / - Yes, I'll be back.
See you.
- Good job. / - Bye.
Good job.
Thank you.
After I sent him off,
I felt like a weight had been lifted.
- A bit... / - I was so...
Because I had to worry about him...
I was worried too.
There was an exit midway
so I told him to go inside.
That it's okay.
From then on, I could really
enjoy the tower.
I found out for the first time my wife likes this stuff.
- You're so cool. / - That's too narrow.
- I stood there...  / - The path before was wider.
Why is she doing that?
I really don't understand.
Why is she standing outside the building?
Seriously...
There's another scary challenge.
This is scary.
It's scary when you can see below...
Through the walkway.
Hey.
How am I going to take photos for her here?
This is insane.
I can't even step on that.
- She's sitting down there? / - It's like that.
Did you miss this?
I couldn't see... Oh, my...
- Put your legs like that? / - Like this...
That's a challenge as well.
Sitting down then standing up.
- You have to take a seat? / - Yes.
You're amazing.
What is she doing?
Why would you sit there?
I don't believe this...
- Stop filming now. / - In case he loses a wife.
I'm really scared.
This is nice. I find this fun.
- Oh, dear. / - Park Sieun...
You'd never expect this of her.
- She's different to how she looks. / - It's like my escape.
No way!
You do the "Titanic" here.
That was really scary.
Don't!
Not this!
Unbelievable.
That's unbelievable.
But this...
- The course is really fun. / - It is, right?
The first thing I thought was,
"Wait, that's dangerous."
I kept thinking that.
I didn't want her to do it.
Then...
I saw her enjoy it.
And I realized that...
I've been doing things that only I like.
My wife has been doing things that only I like.
She did that for me.
- He realized something through this. / - I felt bad.
- I recommend this to lovers. / - Battle Trip is so...
When you to scary high places...
- You come together. / - Oh, really?
- You become closer. / - You hold each other too.
- Rely on each other. / - That's right.
If your man holds your hand,
he seems so dependable.
You're right.
You feel like you can trust him with your life.
Did you enjoy it?
- It was fun. / - Let me see.
You look pretty.
It was so fun. Are you okay?
Honey, are you okay?
Look at me.
- Aren't you dizzy? Are you okay? / - I feel dizzy.
You do?
You did a great job too.
I thought that after I finished the course,
I thought he'd really console me.
- But as soon as I stepped in... / - That's like us.
I started to console him instead.
- It's so funny how she comforts him. / - It's okay.
I found myself comforting him.
But so what?
I think couples just need to meet halfway.
There's no law saying the man has to comfort the wife.
We can just adjust to the situation.
I believe women need to provide
their shoulders to lean on at times.
You're so cool.
A woman needs to lend her shoulder too.
- That's my style. / - I'd better learn.
(Lively Park and Zin's challenges in Penang)
(Penang style steamboat)
When I was there, I really enjoyed steamboat.
What's a steamboat?
It's like shabu shabu.
That looks good.
You add vegetables and seafood
and boil it in broth. It's really tasty.
- I'd better try that. / - It's good.
- Steamboat? / - Those things aren't fattening.
- True. / - It's diet food.
You can eat as much as you like.
I wonder why it's called steamboat.
I think there's a steamer in the middle.
Package.
(The owner recommends the popular menu)
Since we're here...
Out of A, B, and C, A is the most expensive.
It has the most.
- Let's eat the one with the most menu. / - Of course.
- They put dried noodles in it. / - Set A.
You add dry noodles to it.
You look really tired.
Me?
Before our food is served,
let me give you a massage.
You had a really hard time.
That's similar to my husband after the swing.
- He's a bit out of it, right? / - Yes, he is.
I'll give you a massage.
She's still consoling him.
- She's even giving him a massage. / - That hurts.
The husband is too high maintenance.
- That's going to air on TV, isn't it? / - Younger guys...
Tends to be cute like that.
Turn around.
That really hurts, honey.
Steamboat.
It's huge.
- Oh, I like this. / - It's really like a boat.
(A giant steamboat enters)
Let's dig in.
- It's really boiling. / - You're right.
Is there something underneath?
There's nothing there
but there is in the middle.
Do you know why it's boiling when
there's no heat source?
- Why is that? / - I was curious about that.
Is there a stove under the pot?
There's charcoal in here.
- It's heated with the charcoal. / - In here?
It's like a brass chafing dish.
There's coal in the tube
so it keeps everything warm.
- So that cooks it. / - It keeps it warm.
That's fascinating.
- Oh, it's not a fire underneath? / - No.
That's right.
Let's try the broth first.
That was really good.
That broth must be so tasty.
What is the broth made of?
- It had a garlic flavor. / - It's just regular broth.
- It's tasty. / - Clear broth.
It has a strong garlic and pepper aroma.
Shabu shabu with that kind of broth.
Is it like chicken broth?
- It's similar to that plus garlic. / - It's seasoned.
At the end of the shabu shabu,
the broth is all seasoned.
- That's so good. / - It's like that from the start.
- So it must be a bit salty. / - Yes.
Sambal.
The fish cake was much more delicious than in Korea.
They have great fishcake there.
They make it out of fresh fish.
It's homemade fishcake.
- It's good, right? / - Homemade fishcake.
It was really good.
It's good.
- Is that to your liking? / - I think so.
That's a relief.
It's like a mother asking her son, "Do you like it?"
And the boy goes, "Yes, mommy."
Oh, this...
- As you know, I only like Korean food. / - Yeah.
Nevertheless, it's good.
Let's try the fish.
- It seems like meat. / - Yeah? I'll add it.
Dip it... Then take it out and eat.
I'm going to try it as is.
- Dip then take out... / - What type of fish is it?
- Grouper? / - Grouper.
It's a saw-edged perch.
- A white fish. / - Yes.
It's too expensive in Korea.
- But it's affordable there. / - It's like deep fried puffer fish.
- The inside meat is clean. / - Right.
- Deep fried puffer fish is tasty. / - The white meat.
It's like really tender chicken.
- Deep fried puffer fish. / - Like deep fried puffer fish.
You get that at a puffer fish restaurant.
- It's really good. / - It's good on its own.
(They gulp down everything)
- I'm eating too much. / - After you finish it all...
You add the spicy sauce to the broth and...
- Then you start over. / - Reset.
Very true.
(Park and Zin's first day comes to an end)
For mothers, even if they want to go to a good place...
- It depends on whether it's kid-friendly. / - Right.
But this place is fine.
You can let your kids grab one and eat.
That's right.
They can eat that.
(Lively Park and Zin in Penang, day 2)
The ocean color is so beautiful.
Honey, what are we doing today?
Today, we're going to a beach.
- Taehyun, did you plan both days? / - Yes.
We have to go.
- Honey. / - What now?
- I really... / - You're going to say something strange.
I haven't gone shopping properly yet.
- Shopping? / - Here we go.
- Just how much shopping is proper? / - I know.
- Really? / - There were some pretty things...
But you kept pushing me to move on.
Everything was so rushed yesterday.
I really couldn't look at anything.
You don't need much time, right?
If it takes long, I might have to leave.
I'd love to go to accessory shops.
- Don't go to accessory shops. / - Alright.
Seriously, it takes ages for her.
You will make the viewers think it actually takes ages.
It does take ages.
You need to choose.
Decide what you'll buy beforehand.
- How can you do that? / - What on earth?
You can't.
- Right. / - See? They're going crazy over there.
You should know what you want and
how much it costs.
- That way, it'll end in 5 minutes. / - Don't decide there.
There's too much when you go there.
Anyway, I beg you.
(Lively Park and Zin's healing in Penang)
(George Town shopping)
(George Town)
(George Town's street art)
It's like Garosu-gil in Korea.
- There are many people on dates. / - Right.
It's similar to Samcheong-dong.
- It feels like there are more people. / - I know.
When I heard you were shopping,
I got exhausted.
But I said I won't enter any shops
I haven't looked at already.
Just the place we went yesterday.
Wait a minute. Where was that?
- The place we went yesterday. / - I'm scanning.
- I went but I couldn't buy anything. / - Accessory shop?
Pin cushion.
- The place you went yesterday. / - I have to find it.
- You've staked out a place? / - Yes.
That's why you wanted to come here.
I thought you wanted to start over.
- I did want to look in here yesterday. / - Where?
- Here. / - Oh, here?
Look around. Take a quick look around.
(I knew this would happen)
Okay.
Honey, I want to buy something for now.
- Okay. / - Choose one for me.
- Something that suits you now. / - Buy it on site...
- And wear it right away. / - That's what it's about.
- That's the beauty of travel. / - Right.
This one suits you.
- This one? / - Yeah.
Right?
They're nice but...
How about this? Is it too much of a flower pattern?
I personally like this one.
- This? / - No, no.
You chose this one earlier.
Then this one.
They look the same to him.
You can tell if you focus. He's just not looking.
Geez, what is that?
There's too much variety.
I can't choose at times like this.
- This is nice too. / - There isn't...
That much variety here.
There were so many in different colors.
You need to buy one in each color.
- When someone's waiting, you're rushed... / - Yeah.
You can't choose comfortably.
(He escapes the scene)
Honey, what do you think of this? Honey?
- Yes? / - What about this?
- The blue one looks better, right? / - The blue is better.
(End of discussion)
Honey, what do you think of this?
Do you have to use the camera?
I have to see it up close.
- Good! / - That one's nice.
It suits your clothes right now.
I prefer the other one.
- She's already chosen one. / - They're the same.
They're different.
- That one? / - Get the blue one.
- This one? / - The blue one looks good on you.
Okay. See how it looks on me.
- The blue one is really pretty. / - Right?
- The blue one looks good. / - Yes, the blue.
- How much was it? / - How does it look?
Does it suit me? It looks refreshing.
Yeah. Buy that one.
This one? Yeah, hurry it up.
Just a minute.
Honey, please cut down some time when shopping.
Decide beforehand what you want to buy.
(She must have completely forgot about that)
I choose a lot of things for her.
The shopping will end quickly when I choose for her.
I'm doing it to end the shopping quickly.
Couldn't you tell that I was uncomfortable?
How? In what way?
- I was really trying to hurry... / - When?
My eyes moved really fast.
- I tried my best. / - Shopping with a friend is best.
- You chose the one we liked. / - Yes, that's right.
You should get that one.
- Women think alike. / - You're right.
- Isn't it pretty? / - Yes. It looks good on you.
Find me that shop for me.
- I think this is right. / - It's here.
Honey, I think this is it.
- It's right. / - It is.
(Big smile)
- Let's go in. / - Great stuff.
(Sieun has entered the world of shopping)
This is...
I don't buy things right away.
Because when I was young...
She made a good choice buying those earrings.
- It goes with her entire outfit. / - It's so pretty.
I just buy it even if I don't like it.
Even if I don't like it, I buy it since I'm there.
But my wife doesn't buy it if she doesn't like it.
Then she goes back in case she regrets not buying it.
- He's frowning so much. / - That's right.
- Why do they do that? / - Frowning eyebrows...
Even with soy sauce.
Soy sauce?
Yes, even when she's buying soy sauce.
She reads up on every type of soy sauce.
- Goodness. / - She reads the labels?
Yes.
You can't sleep if you don't buy something.
- Right. / - You remember the thing you left.
- In case someone else buys it. / - Right.
(Pick everything up to look)
(Tap on everything interesting)
Is that a menu?
I'm not going to buy it but let me just try it on.
Goodness, it's so pretty.
You need to buy something in an accessory shop.
They sell so many nice things here.
It's not like that every day.
- It's only because it's cheap there. / - Yeah.
You do it for kicks.
- Honey? / - Yes?
(He's checking Sieun's mood with a sour face)
(He's leaving for somewhere without saying anything)
He's sitting.
His legs are hurting.
(He's alone by himself)
I can't believe we're back here.
Doesn't Penang really suit him?
It doesn't seem awkward.
He's a native.
- I feel like asking him, "How much?" / - Boss.
- He's like a tout. / - Boss.
"It's cheap."
(Sieun is taking her time looking around)
This was so adorable.
(The pot frames caught Sieun's eyes)
- Frames. / - Wow, that's so pretty!
- Aren't they pretty? / - So pretty.
(24 hours ago)
- Honey, let's buy this. / - She saw it the day before.
- She wanted to buy it? / - I told him...
- He said no and dragged me out. / - That's pretty?
- You think that's pretty? / - I have no clue.
It's not my style.
Why do you want to buy that?
- There's no reason why. / - To hang it up!
(I really want to buy this today)
Interesting.
These tiles are so pretty.
Where did he go?
Honey.
Honey!
Where are you?
(Where would I go? I'm right here)
I need to bring him in.
(She moves to catch the shopping slave)
- This is how you waste time. / - I know.
- You could've bought several things. / - Right.
If he was right there, she would've bought it.
Where did he go?
(Taehyun isn't here)
Honey!
(Looking around)
Where did you go?
Taehyun has all the money. Where did he go?
(It seems like she is looking at something)
She's still shopping.
- Geez. / - She shops in the middle of that?
- Unbelievable. / - That's the one.
- She's still looking. / - That's what shocked me.
So much I missed last time.
Is that a fridge magnet?
She's full of curiosity.
(Oops)
Where did this man go?
He needs to bring the money for me to buy.
He should have left the money with me.
There are so many fun things here.
This is really cool.
I really want to buy this.
This is also pretty.
- Didn't she look here before? / - Seems new again.
How long will we have to watch this?
Is this a product placement for pots?
There are too many frames.
There are so many frames.
Why are they all in different colors?
This is so painful.
It's painful.
What is the color of your wallpaper?
White.
Are you discussing it with the camera director?
The surroundings are mint colored.
Mint, blue.
I think this will suit our house.
Okay, this one. The one I liked at first glance.
I will choose the one I liked at first glance.
She was just going to buy that all along.
I'm happy.
She didn't even buy a lot.
Sook would've bought all 20 of those.
I always say this.
I never regret after buying something.
- Right. / - But I have regretted not buying it.
- It's awkward if you only hang one. / - Yes.
- You have to hang at least four. / - That's right.
(So much time has gone by while shopping)
(She finally got in touch with Taehyun)
- Hello? / - Honey?
Yes?
- Honey. / - Yes?
- Honey! / - Yes?
What is going on here?
I'm sorry.
You'll have to explain yourself well.
I'm a little shocked.
You abandoned me in another country.
No, I didn't abandon you.
- Let's talk when you get here. / - Okay.
- Sieun has a great personality. / - Where did he go?
He has to bring something with him in this situation.
- You're right. / - Taehyun better be holding something.
Why aren't you running?
You abandoned me.
In this foreign land.
What happened?
I know what that is.
- Hugging before he gets hit. / - I'll tell you the truth.
- Sit down first. / - In case he gets in trouble.
Come and sit here.
Tell me.
To be honest...
I was here the whole time.
(What?)
- I was too hot. / - He must have a reason.
Look at me. What are you looking at?
Honey?
Look at my eyes and tell me.
It's really scary when she does that.
I'll tell you the truth.
I came back from fishing.
What?
There's a good fishing spot here.
What are you on about?
I was just here the whole time.
I just had some coffee.
- Anyway... / - Let's go.
I'll let you off this time.
Since we're doing what I want now.
- Honey, Batu Ferringhi. / - Yeah, this is the beach.
That's so pretty.
- There's a vacation spot there. / - This is it.
Isn't it? No, this is...
Wait, it is this. Parasailing.
- Batu Ferringhi... / - This must be with it.
- Do we have to go parasailing there? / - Parasailing...
(30 minutes by car from to Batu Ferringhi)
- The ocean is always so nice. / - Yes.
It looks so nice.
We'll enjoy the ocean.
(Batu Ferringhi)
Wow, the beach is really long.
Isn't it really long? It's like Haeundae.
- Should we walk the beach? / - Okay.
- It's the ocean! / - This is nice.
I went to the beach last week...
But I couldn't walk the beach once with my husband.
Because of the kids?
Yes, he was too busy playing with the kids.
I'm reminded now that I watch this.
I should really travel a lot now.
So nice.
(It's like they're on their honeymoon)
I think things you like are gathered over there.
Yeah.
I really wanted to try this.
It's time to realize your dream.
(You must put on safety equipment)
Isn't this for kids?
I think this is for kids.
He's so kind.
(Heading out to sea to fulfill Sieun's wish)
I can't believe this.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
This is unthinkable for me.
I'm serious.
It's impossible to think that I will only hang
on a rope and fly in the sky.
Why would you do this?
That must be ours.
(The parasail is almost ready to fly)
I had no clue my wife liked this sort of thing.
- For 3 years? / - I found out on this trip.
(Nervous)
(Excited)
This is my wife.
She's so excited.
(It's now time to fly into the sky)
- Honey. / - Honey.
You're doing this with me since
you're my guardian, right?
This is insanity!
I did it alone in Thailand.
But it's really lonely alone.
At first, I went up excited but then...
There's no one to talk to up there.
No one to share it with.
Honey.
He stressed whether he should join me.
So it's just the two of you...
Oh, my God!
(The boat is getting smaller)
Honey!
- We're flying! / - We're flying!
- Honey. / - What are we doing?
Honey!
(Taehyun seems to enjoy it more than he expected)
Look down!
(A thrilling view below their feet)
- Honey, isn't this great? / - It's wonderful.
- How is it? / - It's wonderful.
- Good thing you listened to your wife, right? / - No...
(One can enjoy this view only in the sky)
I recommend you to do it with another person.
- It's terribly boring if you do it alone. / - Right.
I'm fine because I'm with you.
(They don't fear anything because they're together)
When we took off, it was amazing. It was so fun.
As we were pushed away from the boat, we floated...
That feeling of flying felt amazing. Plus the wind...
Ocean beneath our feet.
That feeling of climbing higher into the sky was great.
It was really fun at first.
My wife screamed as we climbed up.
Then as the speed suddenly reduced...
It felt weird when the speed reduced.
I don't think people scared of heights
like me should do this.
- Are you scared? / - Yeah, I'm getting nauseous.
- Already? / - Yeah...
This isn't good.
- Is it too much? / - Yes, it's too much, honey.
Please take us down.
Bring us down.
- They have a sign, right? / - Yes.
- To bring you down. / - It's only been 3 minutes?
Yes, yes.
I felt really sorry up there.
I shouldn't have made him do it.
I made him do things he's so scared of.
It's not just being scared.
He's feeling it all over his body.
I felt bad because I felt it was my fault.
It was a nightmare for me as well.
Honey, it's going down now.
- I'm so... / - It's going down.
Yes, take deep breaths.
It's climbing down.
- I'm sorry, honey. / - This is really tough.
We're almost there.
It feels like you're getting to know each other better.
I really didn't know it was that bad.
I only found then how severe his acrophobia is.
(He's calmed down a little now)
Goodness.
That's really worrying.
It's not like I'm scared.
It's just a fear of heights.
- I'm sorry. / - Don't say that.
I don't think I can do it.
- But from his point of view... / - It's my fault.
He must feel so bad that you had to stop.
- Because of him. / - He kept saying he was sorry.
He's scared and sorry.
My wife is amazing.
She must've been worried that something will happen.
I realized that she truly is my wife.
I was really thankful.
You confirmed your love for each other.
They look so down after doing something so fun.
That's a bit sad.
Have a seat here, honey.
- It's tough. / - You did well.
(Taehyun had it tougher than anyone)
Good work.
I was really thankful.
He had clenched his fists so hard...
People with acrophobia should never try this.
- But at least I tried. / - That's right, you did.
- I didn't not try. / - That's right. Good work.
But it's really hard.
This program makes you want to get married.
I really acknowledge these two couples.
If you're not normally that good to each other,
they can't act like this here.
When you face danger together,
you come to rely on each other.
For that purpose, this is good for newlyweds.
I think it's great for married couples.
If you do it at sunset...
- It'd be so cool. / - It's really the highlight.
(Lively Park and Zin's healing in Penang)
(Dinner with a nice view)
(The chaotic day is now over)
Since today is our last day here,
I'd like to take you to a great dinner.
In fact, I have been secretly saving some money.
- Is it an expensive place? / - Yes, it's very expensive.
- Is this the place? / - Yes.
It says it's a seafood market.
- I'll treat you to a seafood market. / - I sense lobster.
The look of the building tells that it's a fancy place.
I spent a fair bit of money.
- It looks a bit like Thailand. / - It does.
Penang is a lot of countries mixed together.
(The entrance of the restaurant is full of fish tanks)
- Is that a fish tank? / - Yes, fish tank.
- I love places like this. / - It looks delicious.
- They'd really have lobster. / - They would.
- They have every variety. / - Honey...
Here's the lobster.
They're so big.
They have Chinese cuisine, Malaysian...
- It's a rainbow lobster. / - You choose how you want it.
That's right.
Honey, look here.
- There's something we must know. / - What?
If you look here, it's $20 for 100g.
- $20? / - It's extremely expensive.
- You can come for just that... / - What will you do?
- Is the food cheaper? / - Let's just eat a decent amount.
- Want to leave or eat? / - We have to eat.
- We've come all the way here. / - Really?
Honey, turn around!
- We've come too far in. / - You're right.
We can't go back out.
Rainbow, Australian or Boston?
Who will I choose?
It's fun for us but for them...
She's a very cruel woman.
They're so scary.
It's so big.
Let's head inside.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
It's really big.
I reserved a seat for you.
- Even a seat? / - Yes.
Check out the ocean.
Honey.
Are we going to eat the lobster with this ocean view?
This is so nice.
The sunset is beautiful here but it was cloudy that day.
(They will have their perfect dinner here)
(Checking the menu)
- Please promise me one thing. / - What is it?
Please be quick to decide what to eat.
Please.
That's the hardest thing.
She can never choose what to eat.
She keeps asking for my opinion
but I have no idea either.
She always asks for my opinion.
Honey, what else should we order?
- There's so much to order here. / - I...
Why did you just ask me?
You look first.
Reading the menu is the best thing in the world.
There's so much to choose from.
It's my favorite book of all books.
I really like you.
- Vegetables... / - There's the clouds that you love.
- I should choose one with a picture. / - Yeah.
All he can think about is bean paste stew.
I think I saw a Korean restaurant on the way.
Tofu...
- Choosing the menu is a kind of shopping. / - Right.
Choose, I'll wait.
I can wait forever.
Let's ask the waiter what the most popular dish is.
Hang on a second.
Why did you even look at the menu then?
I'm just curious.
Why have you been looking at the menu all this time?
- I wanted to choose but... / - Let's discuss this.
Then you order. Choose from here...
I've already chosen. I chose as I walked in.
I'm going to eat this rice.
Me too.
You have a disorder with making decisions.
- The sun's already set. / - Yes, it went down fast.
- The food's not out yet? / - No.
They looked at the menu and the sun set.
I've always wanted to have a dinner
on the beach with the sunset.
It's nice.
I guess this is why people do this
on their honeymoons.
The sun's gone down now, honey.
- It's pitch black. / - You're right.
It's here!
Is the lobster finally here?
(Mouth wide open)
Unbelievable.
Wow, what is that?
I've never seen anything like that before.
- It was really good. / - The meat...
Doesn't it smell amazing?
(Mmm)
It's good.
(Her eyes widen)
(It melts in the mouth)
- It's good. / - It was really good.
Anything tastes good with butter and cheese.
- There's so much meat. / - There was so much.
That would be perfect with wine.
While eating this...
I'm reminded of Penang.
The more you peel back...
There's so much complexity under here.
It feels just like that.
I really want to try it.
- That looks really delicious. / - It looks so good.
I think Penang, Malaysia is...
It's so mixed here.
- They've worked together. / - To become one.
For 10, 20, 30, 40...
- 50, 60 years. / - That's right.
- They become more like each other. / - Right.
- And mix. / - Right.
It feels like that.
- That's Penang. / - You are correct.
Even if we come with kids...
- There's so much to do. / - Okay, okay.
Is the restroom outside?
Okay, okay.
Let me just take a quick bathroom break.
(While everyone was waiting for Taehyun)
I think you should check your text messages.
(Sieun checks her text messages with a stern look)
- What happened? / - What's wrong?
(She looks at her phone for a long time)
(Her eyes suddenly became teary)
She's crying.
(Someone sent her photos)
(She's about to burst into tears)
At each location!
He took one at each location.
This is good.
(Thank you)
(For living)
(With)
(Me)
That's so pretty.
That means...
- At every stop. / - At each location.
That's pretty.
I was really shocked.
- He sent each photo one by one. / - What is this?
- That will make you cry. / - Right.
(She continues to look at it for a long time)
When did he take these photos?
She usually doesn't cry.
I'm so lonely today.
Where did he go?
Where is he?
(Look to your left)
- Why is he running like that? / - Is he the village idiot?
What was that?
I didn't know that I ran like that.
(Taehyun looks nervous)
Geez, I usually don't do things like this.
Hello, My Honey.
It's been almost 8 years since we met.
Thank you for always being by my side.
This team is a complete drama.
Just like we promised,
let's live a meaningful and cheerful life.
Is Dongseok crying?
Why are you crying?
- Is he crying again? / - Is Dongseok crying?
- What's wrong with him? / - Go check on him.
Are you serious?
Why are you crying?
Is he really crying?
Is life too tough for you these days?
- Are you okay? / - It's because he ran like this.
Thank you for always being by my side.
Just like we promised before we got married...
Besides living well together...
Let's live a meaningful and cheerful life.
I love you, My Honey.
My wife, Park Sieun.
In our next life...
Please give me more allowance money.
I love you, My Honey.
- What is all this? / - What else?
Oh, My Honey.
(We could feel Taehyun's sincerity in the event)
- Is that what you were doing every day? / - Yeah.
That's what I was doing each time.
Goodness.
(One person is still touched)
- That's so cute. / - That's so nice.
Goodness, goodness.
- I made a request, right? / - I like seeing that.
In the 8 years of marriage...
I've hardly ever done a surprise for my wife?
Is that the first time?
- Never a surprise. / - Hardly ever.
Then it'd be even more moving.
I prefer to be a good husband every day.
So I've hardly ever done it...
(This is how Taehyun's surprise started)
(Step 1, cooperating with the staff)
Did he prepare earlier?
I'd like to organize a surprise for her.
I wrote this down.
That's adorable.
He prepared this when he was in Korea.
(This is how he completed it word by word)
(Step 2, preparing the flower bouquet)
Where did he go?
Seriously, where did he go?
- Oh, then! / - I felt so bad.
- Where's the florist? / - He went to buy it then?
- Then... / - It's so hard to find flowers.
This one.
She loves purple. I'm 100% sure of it.
That's right.
I felt so bad that day.
(Step 3, the big event)
- Even then... / - Is the bathroom outside?
Okay, okay.
(Everything's going as planned)
(Where Sieun is sitting)
Can you see it?
(He completes the final photo)
(Sending the photos to Sieun)
She saw it.
(Step 4, another hidden surprise)
I prepared this.
- That's your wedding photo, right?  / - Yes.
On the back. "I love you."
You took care of him like a son.
- What's that photo? / - This is us.
(Ta-da)
(The pose Sieun usually likes to do)
- That's what I do. / - That's right.
I'm so moved.
On this trip, for you and me...
It was a chance to get to know each other perfectly.
Yeah, I'm sure we'll find out new things
as we live together.
But just like the people of Penang...
Let's recognize each other and meet in the middle.
It was completely unexpected.
I realized this is why people do surprises.
As people live on...
It could become dull if it's done all the time.
But doing something small once in a while...
I realized you can move someone
with just a sketchbook.
I thought my wife leaned on me
but I realized I was leaning on her.
I realized that even more.
This tour was supposed to be us
moving each other.
But in the end, Taehyun moved Sieun.
(They always held hands wherever they went)
- It was really moving. / - So touching.
I think it was more about Taehyun moving me.
The tour name was perfect.
We need to find out about the costs.
- Since cost of living is cheap there. / - I know.
- In terms of money spent on food. / - Cost effective...
If you have time, you should visit both places.
I really want to do that.
You'll have to be jobless to do that.
You need to be rich too.
Let's hear the total expense from Sieun.
For 3 days and 2 nights, the Lively Park and Zin Tour
spent a total of this much at Penang.
- Excluding airfares. / - Excluding airfares.
- Total. / - Per person.
$396.50.
- My goodness. / - You did all that for $390?
- It was less than $400? / - $396.50.
If it's $396.50, that includes the lobster you ate.
Yes.
That lobster was $200. Then without that, $190?
It means there really isn't much to spend.
That's so affordable.
- Since food is so cheap. / - The noodles were $1.80.
That entire meal was only $10.
Next week...
- Another special? / - It's another special.
- This is a real. / - It's a real special.
This week was real too.
But this is really, really real.
It's really true.
Vietnam and the Philippines.
A true trip planned by real people.
Look out for it.
Please look forward to the next episode.
We'll say good-bye here.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
(Next episode)
You can experience the magnificence of Vietnam
that others haven't experienced.
(Hanoi, Choi Eunyeong, Ahn Sunyeong)
(Boracay, Boom, Lee Jihye)
Something a little different.
Places that haven't been visited.
Isn't it so pretty?
We're seeing a new Boracay.
I'll remember this for life.
(Battle Trip)
("Boomerang" by Wanna One)