(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
(Lee Hwijae, Kim Saerom)
Travel is war!
Battle Trip!
Nice to see you again.
We have a very special host today.
- It's Kim Saerom. / - Welcome.
In fact, a life goal for my 30s...
- Is going on trips. / - That's so nice.
So I go on a trip every month.
- Really? / - Both domestic and overseas.
Where did you go recently?
I went to Busan 2 weeks ago, Japan 3 weeks ago.
This is episode 96 of Battle Trip.
- It's almost 100. / - But the fact that we haven't...
Had a show on this theme yet shows
that we'll last a really long time.
- What is it? / - What is the theme?
Today's theme is a domestic island trip.
- Most commonly... / - We haven't had this theme?
The first islands that come to mind are Jeju-do,
Ulleungdo and Ganghwado.
- We have a lot of islands. / - Yes.
I have some statistics.
How many islands do you think there are in Korea?
3,358.
Among them, 482 are named.
That means there are over 2,000 unnamed islands.
We can do 1,000 episodes of Battle Trip...
- If we go to those 2,000 islands. / - No.
Then you'll end up being like "Korea Sings."
Should we go on a host special to an island?
That's nice. An island special.
Today's island special Battle Trip.
Let us bring out the four trip designers.
Come on out.
(Who are the trip designers?)
(Kim Hyunchul, Cho Janghyuck)
Hello.
(Park Jeongcheol, Kim Seungsoo)
You can tell right away that they'll all best friends.
- Really? / - Doesn't it feel like that?
Hyunchul and Janghyuck are friends, aren't you?
- We're friends. / - What kind of friends are you?
He was born 3 months later than me.
Why would you nitpick over that?
He only has his age to show off.
He only has his age.
What about the two on Hwijae's team?
- It's a senior-junior relationship? / - Yes.
He's 5 years younger than me.
Everyone's surprised.
- Why are you so surprised? / - He's so baby faced!
- Of course. / - I'm still young.
I've known Seungsoo for a very long time.
- But it's our first time traveling together. / - Yes.
So I was worried at first.
- Really? / - He's not just older than you.
- He's your senior actor. / - Wasn't it difficult?
- He's your direct senior. / - It's difficult.
- Is that so? / - It's difficult now.
- Are you telling me just now? / - I told...
The staff that it will either be a success or a failure...
- On this trip. / - Right.
Yes, whether we will go on the next trip together...
- Or not depends on this trip. / - That could happen.
You learn about that on the trip.
Isn't it the first time traveling together for
Hyunchul and Janghyuck too?
- Yes, it's our first time. / - It's our first time.
I didn't know I'd travel with him.
We have different hobbies.
We couldn't go on a trip together.
I think we got closer after this trip.
Will you go on a trip together again next time?
Are you insane?
It's not that bad.
It's a domestic island trip.
Seungsoo and Jeongcheol, where did you go?
We went to the Naples of Korea.
A beautiful port city, Tongyeong, Gyeongsangnam-do.
- I really want to go there. / - Tongyeong is beautiful.
- You won't fail with Tongyeong. / - And?
There's another beautiful island that's
unstained from the world.
- Yokjido. / - Yokjido?
Is Yokjido still unstained?
- It's still unstained. / - It's been a long time.
Which islands did Hyunchul and Janghyuck go to?
"Land of beautiful scenery, far and wide."
Do you know where that's from? The start.
- The start? / - It's Haenam.
- I see. / - Wow, Haenam.
- And? / - The island surrounded by clear waters.
Wando.
- Wando? / - Yes, Wando.
- What's famous there? / - It's a healthy island.
It's a match between Gyeongsang-do and Jeolla-do.
They also have very different flavors in food.
- That's right. / - This special sounds so charming.
- Let's check the map. / - Let's see it.
- They are quite far. / - Tongyeong, Yokjido.
And Wando.
- Isn't that Haenam? / - That's Tongyeong.
They're going in opposite directions.
Tongyeong has the Hallyeohaesang National Park.
Wando has the Dadohaehaesang National Park.
It's the most beautiful ocean of Gyeongsang-do
vs. the most beautiful ocean of Jeolla-do.
- I'm looking forward to it. / - Yes.
Why did you choose Yokjido?
We chose it because it's a delicious island.
- Yokjido? / - Yes.
It's famous for mackerel and sweet potatoes.
It's hard to eat raw mackerel in Seoul.
- The price is also a problem. / - It's expensive.
It's so abundant over there.
- Mackerel? / - Yes.
- They serve it at cart bars. / - Cart bars.
The mackerel is so fresh,
that you wouldn't imagine that it was mackerel.
- It's really good. / - We need to hurry to see that.
We can't lose. Why did you choose
Haenam and Wando?
On the first day, we ate Korean traditional food.
- Jeolla-do is known for food. / - Everything is good.
We ate health food the next day.
- Health foods? / - Yes.
Did it help energize you?
- More than enough. / - It was more than enough.
Did you feel something different after eating it?
You'll know when you see it.
You ate proper health food then.
He's saying not to worry.
Over 60,000 people supported us.
- What? / - 60,000?
- How? / - Did you do a live stream?
The locals are the most objective experts.
- That's right. / - The locals.
Among those locals,
there are some older women who like us.
They stepped in to help us
and gave us the best information.
- They must've been popular. / - The thing is...
Kim Seungsoo is the middle aged Park Bogum.
Park Jeongcheol is the middle aged Song Joongki.
The streets were lined with their female fans.
- Okay. / - That's good.
Tongyeong and Yokjido. Haenam and Wando.
Gyeongsang-do vs. Jeolla-do.
- Oysters vs. abalone. / - That's right.
It's singers vs. actors as well.
It's a hard match.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
Welcome.
You're not voting on just the trip you liked,
you can vote for both.
You can vote for both trips.
Yes. We are unfamiliar with Yokjido,
so we want to see it first.
Yes, sure.
Let's watch Tongyeong, Yokjido first.
What's the tour name?
It's the One Day Three Meals Tour.
- One Day Three Meals. / - You only had 3 meals?
If you watch...
- It's like 3 meals... / - I was surprised.
- I thought you were the GM. / - Alright.
Let's visit Tongyeong and Yokjido
with the One Day Three Meals Tour.
Let's see it together.
- Hi, Seungsoo. / - Hey.
You're here.
(They met to design the trip)
Sit down, sit down.
They don't look comfortable with each other.
I met you when we were in our 20s.
That's right.
He's 5 years older than me.
Back then, I wasn't comfortable around him.
Of course...
The younger ones always bring up age.
Of course it's much better now.
I'm over 40 now.
He's much more friendlier now.
After going on this trip...
- Yeah. / - I think I'll like you even more.
It's our first trip together.
- Yes. / - It will be a meaningful time.
Yeah. Thank you.
- It's an island trip this week. / - Island?
I see.
I've never even been to Ulleungdo.
I haven't been either.
The only island I've been to is Jeju-do.
I don't think I've been to many islands.
That's right. I think people don't travel to islands.
Men don't travel together to islands.
- They don't. / - You get a lot of couples.
- Or families. / - A lot of families do.
It's because the sunset is beautiful.
It's good to go with the opposite sex.
I really haven't traveled much.
- I really haven't. / - Yes, I know it.
The most important thing about traveling is food.
- I agree. / - What else is there?
We'll revolve around food.
We'll have to search for the best restaurants first.
I'm experienced at searching,
so I usually don't fail anymore.
- He likes to search. / - Search Fairy.
- I have a lot of experience. / - He's good at planning.
- Really? / - Yes.
- It's good to have people like him. / - He's the best.
That's something you have to be born with.
Have you been to any cities around Namhae?
I've been to Tongyeong about 4 to 5 times.
- Really? / - I went there for work and travel.
I've never been to Tongyeong.
You've never been to Tongyeong?
- I've seen it on TV. / - He's so worried.
With Tongyeong...
If you follow along Hallyeohaesang National Park,
there are a lot of islands around
Yeosu and Tongyeong.
- We only have a short amount of time. / - Yes, yes.
If we decide on Tongyeong, since I've been there...
- Go to islands around Tongyeong. / - That's right.
- That sounds good. / - Let's start searching then.
- Islands near Tongyeong. / - Right.
He's the Search Fairy.
There's a lot.
Somaemuldo, Yeonhwado, Yokjido, Bijindo.
- People go to Bijindo a lot. / - I've heard of Bijindo.
Yokjido is the closest.
I don't think there's anything more to consider.
Let's search Yokjido. Let's see what's here.
The name is attractive, Yokjido.
Mackerel is famous here.
The island seems to be a good size.
- I think there are things to see. / - Yes.
- Let's go to Yokjido. / - Agreed.
One day in Tongyeong and one day in Yokjido.
(A coastal city surrounded by the sea on three sides)
(It's famous for seafood)
- What is that? / - That's all abalone.
- It's common there. / - They're so big.
(You can eat raw mackerel here)
Oh, wow.
- That's the stuff. / - That's it.
Look how beautiful it is.
- It looked like another country. / - You're right.
You guys had great weather.
I'll trust you to plan the trip.
- Don't worry. / - Please do your best.
The schedule is short. We'll have a tight schedule.
- Okay. / - But we'll be able to relax...
And have fun. I'll plan it well.
So all I have to do is, "What's next?"
Of course.
Okay.
A food columnist will help out the other team.
A food columnist? Isn't that cheating?
- That's unfair. / - That's cheating.
Is it because they're older than us?
- What? / - What are they saying?
You're not that much younger.
They're not that much older.
Oh, they're much older. I see.
They might have to look at the screen like this.
They might have those problems.
So should we be understanding?
- But still, it's a food columnist. / - Yeah.
- A columnist... / - It's unfair for them to have an expert.
Yeah.
But don't worry too much.
We have our female fans there.
(Are you watching us?)
All the attractive ladies in Tongyeong and Yokjido
are on our side.
Look here. Tongyeong population.
68,000 men and 67,000 women.
- Really? / - Yeah.
(Food columnist vs. Yokjido ladies)
67,000 is a lot.
The expert can't beat them.
The expert can't beat the ladies.
Let's talk to the residents there.
That sounds good.
(Their ship cleaved Tongyeong's clouds)
I heard they were so popular.
(The support of 69,000 Tongyeong and Yokjido ladies)
They couldn't move because it was so crowded.
(The middle-aged Park Bogum?)
(No!)
Saved in our my heart.
(Kim Seungsoo, 48, debuted in 1997, old man)
(He's the epitome of a charismatic man)
(Laughs like a dolphin)
Let's go, Seungsoo!
Nice, Seungsoo.
It's our first trip.
He's a cute guy to his seniors.
Hey, this is fun.
This is awesome.
Take this!
(Like they're children again)
Look at the food.
- Goodness. This is Gyeongsang-do, right? / - Yes..
- They might beat us. / - I was really surprised.
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
That wasn't just three meals.
- Let's go. / - You need to go seaside.
You're right.
They clearly have lots to eat.
They have Chungmu rice rolls there.
In Tongyeong.
Been a while since I tried siraegi soybean paste soup.
- What's siraegi soybean paste soup? / - You know it.
It's dried radish greens.
(It's a 4-hour trip from Seoul to Tongyeong)
(They hurry and take off)
So you planned to meet in Tongyeong?
- Yes. / - On location.
(4 hours by car)
(It rained this morning)
It's a turtle ship.
Yes, Admiral Yi Sunsin.
Goodness! Look at that.
- You had great weather. / - It's so clear.
Wow.
- Did you have good weather too? / - No fine dust.
Our weather went back and forth.
Hang on a second.
It won't open.
Hang on a second. Let me do this again.
It normally opens automatically. But today...
That happens sometimes.
It looks cooler when it opens automatically.
Normally, it opens with one click.
Geez. Why didn't it work.
This is embarrassing.
It's been 6 or 7 years since I visited Tongyeong.
Nothing has changed. It's just like before.
- It's peaceful there. / - Right. It's peaceful.
It looks virtually the same.
(All alone)
Why isn't Seungsoo coming?
I will try calling him.
He's not picking up.
What if I have to travel alone today?
I feel lonely.
Jeongcheol!
He made his voice louder.
- You came early. / - It was abdominal breathing.
Goodness.
What's going on here?
This is just something simple.
There's lots to eat here in Tongyeong.
You must try Chungmu rice rolls.
- It's really nothing but it's so good. / - It's good.
- If you get it from a good place... / - Right.
Hello.
- Oh, hello! / - Ma'am.
Yes?
I searched for a good place and I found this place.
Would you like some?
We'd like some to go so we can share.
- I'll make it right away. / - It's unseasoned laver.
- That's delicious. / - The fish cake.
- The seasoned fish cake. / - With squid.
(The local dish of Tongyeong)
It was my first time in Tongyeong.
But I like Chungmu rice rolls a lot
and I was so surprised by that.
- It tastes different, right? / - Yes, it does.
Because they use great ingredients.
- It's different? / - It's different.
- The seaweed is different. / - That...
You can have around 3,000 calories worth of it.
- He's right. / - I'm serious.
You eat the fish cake, then the squid then the rice.
You keep going non-stop.
- You can't stop. / - That fish cake...
They only have it in Tongyeong.
- They serve it with squid. / - The squid.
- They go so well together. / - Yes, it tastes so good.
This is so good.
It's good, right?
It tastes like the original Chungmu rice rolls.
Yeah.
There are some good places in Seoul as well
but it's a bit too sweet there.
I can feel that the kimchi here tastes richer.
The seasoning doesn't taste too strong.
Seriously.
- That's it. / - That's the stuff.
- That's how you eat it. / - That's it.
You have to eat it with a squid leg.
- The triple combo of Chungmu rice rolls. / - Crunchy.
You're right! It's spicy and crunchy.
It seems like you're going to stay there all day.
Tongyeong food is pretty good.
This isn't the end of your first meal, right?
I actually wanted to make that the one and only meal.
It was just so good. I wanted to keep eating.
- It'd be perfect with instant noodles. / - I stopped him.
Instant noodles would make it game over.
This is your last one. Stop eating now.
There are so many things to eat.
But this is tasty.
That's your last piece.
- Geez! / - You can't stop.
See? I told you to stop eating.
- It was so good. / - It's okay. Let's go.
There's always one older friend like him.
Guys that need a lot of care.
- It's fine. / - Let's ride the same car.
- Your car? / - Yes, my car.
Sure, sure.
- Let's go. / - Okay.
Let's go.
I heard there's siraegi soybean paste soup.
- Siraegi soybean paste soup? / - Yes.
It's similar to hangover soup.
Oh, it's a local traditional dish.
It's dried radish greens in dialect.
This could be a nice breakfast or lunch menu.
If you had a drink the night before...
Exactly.
It'd be a great hangover soup.
It looks delicious.
Siraegi soybean paste soup.
Why do I keep salivating with these photos?
- What's that? / - It's salivating.
- Siraegi soybean paste soup? / - That's right.
(One Day Three Meals Tour in Tongyeong)
Is eating all you do?
You should have gone sightseeing.
We're going to the next food place right after we ate?
We don't have time. Since this is a short trip...
- Just think that we'll keep eating. / - Nice.
The restaurants in the markets taste better, right?
Exactly.
- Check out that ocean. / - The ocean!
- The weather! / - Nice colors.
Look at the road.
You have a beautiful wife and the prettiest daughter.
I'm jealous. So you should suffer today.
- Sure thing. / - You're both married, right?
- No. / - I couldn't.
- You couldn't? / - No.
He didn't.
We'll have some siraegi soybean paste soup
and I'll look for some cute girls for you.
This is going to be a very meaningful trip.
It's a short trip.
But I hope it will be an unforgettable trip.
We found the right place.
It's a traditional market.
- It's Seoho Market. / - Right, it's Seoho Market.
It does look like an old market.
- That's a nice market. / - It looks delicious already.
I love things like this.
- I love this. / - That looks so good.
- Just walking around is fun. / - The anchovies...
It will be incredibly cheap as well.
- Yes, it's really cheap. / - Can I ask something?
Do you know any good
siraegi soybean paste soup restaurants?
"H" siraegi soybean paste soup.
"S" restaurant is good.
- The ladies are very friendly. / - Yes.
Since it's you two.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Yes.
Let's just go here since it got two votes.
- Hello. / - Hello.
They must not make the broth with anchovies
but something else.
- From my memory... / - It looks so good.
- Look at that color. / - They reveal the secret.
How can it not be delicious?
With clams.
(The people in the market start the day with soup)
- The broth looks thick. / - Made of soybean paste.
They use eel.
My dad adds rice and red pepper paste in it.
- That sounds good too. / - Gyeongsang-do style.
You could drink like a liter of that without thinking.
- It's nothing special. / - Chives.
- That's so cheap. / - That's the chives.
($4.50 for rice and soup, $5 for rice in soup)
- I've never seen such a restaurant. / - Me neither.
What is that?
- Side dishes. / - You have a buffet of side dishes.
It's all you can eat.
Just like I heard, it's a buffet.
- That's so... / - They give you so much.
We'd like to have two rice and soups, please.
I will plate various dishes here.
What they don't have there...
Just plain rice with all those sides...
- They have eggs too? / - Yes.
There's meat as well.
- And it's $5? / - It is.
It's cheap.
That's amazing.
- And it's unlimited? / - Yes, it's unlimited.
- That's insane. / - You can eat...
- As much as you want and it's $10. / - Exactly.
(They finally taste the siraegi soybean paste soup)
The base of this soup is...
It's eel broth.
- Yes, it's eel broth. / - Eel broth?
It doesn't smell fishy at all.
- Isn't that right? / - It's not fishy at all.
It's the soybean paste rids of the smell.
You'd never know.
So it's a rice soup.
If they didn't have perilla in it,
the fishiness of the eel might have remained.
But the perilla completely removed the fishiness.
- It tasted clean but deep. / - Yes.
The soup has depth of flavor.
That's why the color was like that.
- Laver and chives. / - Yes, dried laver.
Isn't this health food?
- I also like to drink alcohol. / - That looks so good.
- I also like to drink alcohol. / - That's delicious.
I've tried everything to cure hangovers.
But that was the best hangover cure of my life.
Would you go to Tongyeong for this?
- Yes, I could go there again. / - Yes.
It must be really good.
Siraegi soybean paste soup is really delicious.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. / - It was so good.
Have some rice punch.
Rice punch?
Thank you so much.
We'll take some with us.
- $5 for all this. / - There's a nice spot.
- It's 5 minutes away. / - Yes?
You know Dongpirang Village, right?
- Yes, I've been there. / - I've heard of it.
We have Seopirang Village, which is just as good.
- Seopirang? / - Yes.
There's a Seopirang Village? Like east and west.
(Many visit Dongpirang Village to see murals)
- That's so pretty. / - Does "pirang" mean waves?
- No, it means cliffs. / - It means cliffs.
- Cliffs? / - Yes, cliffs.
- The west cliff and the east cliff. / - Yes.
- The names are so pretty. / - Dongpirang is famous.
I don't think a lot of people know Seopirang.
It's a nice quiet village.
You can see all of downtown Tongyeong.
It relieves all your stress.
(10 minutes from Seoho Market to Seopirang Village)
The weather is so nice, isn't it?
- It's like summer. / - Yes.
- There's a map here. / - There's a map.
Let's take a look.
- Where are we right now? / - We're right here.
The 99 Stairs.
- It's right near the entrance. / - Yes.
If we go up here, there's Seoporu.
Seopirang has only been known for 4 or 5 years.
So it's still quiet.
- It's nice. / - Hello.
- It's the Greeting Street. / - Yes
- They accepted our greetings well. / - Greeting Street.
This is a great idea. Greeting Street.
(You come across the 99 Stairs as you walk along)
Is this the 99 Stairs?
This is the start. This is the 99th step.
This is the 99 Stairs.
It means we have to go up there.
Do you have to walk up there?
- Do you have to walk up the stairs? / - It was near.
It was only 5 to 10 minutes from Seoho Market.
- Yes. / - 99 Stairs?
- It won't take long. / - It won't take long.
(Slope on the west side that connects to Seoporu)
(A path to take a leisurely walk)
We have to greet people here.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Seoulites...
That lady was really surprised.
The middle-aged Park Bogum...
She has to take her phone out.
- Middle-aged Song Joongki. / - Wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
- Give it to me, I'll take a selfie. / - We'll take a selfie.
Let me take it.
- I can't believe this. / - I'll do it.
1, 2, 3.
Thank you.
- Goodness. / - I can't believe this.
Oh, my.
- Have a nice trip. / - Bye.
Bye.
(Thank you)
I didn't know at first but it's hard.
I'm starting to run out of breath.
- Gosh. / - It's so relaxing here.
It's hard to just climb the stairs.
Let's climb with a goal.
Let's think of the old times
and do rock, paper, scissors.
This guy's a romantic.
It's been a really long time.
- Didn't people do that in the 1960s? / - Right.
When there was nothing else to play.
I've never seen men do this.
You win with rock and it's 3 steps.
- You win with paper and it's 5 steps. / - Got it.
There's a penalty.
- What is it? / - The winner gets to...
Flick the loser on the forehead.
- The forehead? / - Yeah.
I want to hit your forehead.
Okay. Sure.
It sounds like you think you're going to win.
I'm really bad at rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Look at you being greedy and playing paper.
I want to climb 5 steps.
Rock, paper, scissors.
- This is 2 steps, isn't it? / - Yes, 2 steps.
1, 2.
Rock, paper, scissors.
You're quite good.
- You get quite competitive. / - Really?
- Yes. / - I feel like a kid.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh, yeah!
There's only a few left.
What a fun way to climb stairs.
They're using abdominal breathing.
I'm in trouble.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh, yeah! 1, 2.
- I have one step left. / - Just one?
Do your best until the last round.
- It's the last round. / - You can end it in one game.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Can Jeongcheol come from behind?)
(Or will Seungsoo win as expected?)
(Seungsoo wins)
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Seungsoo, I lost.
Flick on the forehead.
I'll let you hit my forehead like a man.
I want to hit your forehead.
- You have to be a man, right? / - Yeah, yeah.
Here we go.
(Please)
He hit me lightly on purpose.
No...
- Now it's starting to hurt. / - Yeah.
- He looks upset. / - Gosh, it hurts.
- We had fun climbing the stairs. / - Seungsoo...
- It was so fun. / - Yes.
I don't even remember when I did this last.
- I know. / - It was fun doing it with you.
These are cosmos but I don't know what these are.
That's the hill of Seopirang.
There are flowers. The view gets better as you go up.
Wow, what's that?
That's really well built.
(A little further and it's Seoporu)
I saw the murals in Dongpirang a while ago.
Really?
There were a lot of people there.
It's really famous.
- Is this it? / - This is the end.
Even if you wanted to climb, there isn't anything else.
- It's really nice. / - Look over there.
You can see the ocean in the distance?
You can see all of Tongyeong.
- It's so beautiful. / - You can see it all.
(They take a short break)
- Rice punch! / - Good thing you brought that!
Good job.
You can fill it with 3 cup's worth.
(One Day Three Meals Tour)
(Luge)
There's another reason why I want to go to Tongyeong.
Have you ever heard of the luge?
- That's in Winter Olympics. / - That's right.
I don't know if it came from that
but there's a place where you can ride sleds like that.
- Like in luge? / - Yes.
When my daughter grows up,
I want to go there together.
There's the Merlion.
There are famous places.
(Luge you can enjoy in Korea)
- The course was amazing. / - It really was.
Is it 1.5km?
- Yes. / - It takes about 10 minutes.
- It's quite long. / - It's very long.
So you take the 99 Stairs up?
No, you use a lift.
- Oh, it's somewhere else? / - Yes, it's a lift.
Just like a ski resort.
Look at that.
"Once is never enough."
- It's true. / - It's true.
You need to experience it more times.
Hello.
Two adults please.
That's $24.
- Children can ride it too, right? / - Yes.
Yes, with a guardian.
It goes down without an external force
so the slope is quite steep.
- Rotate it. / - Okay.
It's been a long time since I've ever taken a lift.
- You have to go to ski resorts for these. / - Yeah.
It's about 35-floors high.
- Is it that high? / - It is quite high.
You went up quite a bit.
We're finally at the starting point.
(Tongyeong luge, 1.5km, 100m high, 30 corners)
- Is that the only one in Korea? / - Yeah.
There are only a few in the world.
People on medication shouldn't take this ride.
We have to wear safety helmets.
- Be careful not to get stuck. / - Okay.
- Your feet should stay in the cart. / - Yes.
You have to receive training as well.
- Lean right back? / - Yes, right back.
- This is the brake. / - To the left.
Shouldn't we bet something to make it more fun?
- Let's ignite our competitive juices. / - That's right.
Let's do this.
We're having dinner after this, right?
The loser pays for everyone on this trip.
- A group dinner? / - Yeah. One of us.
- Sounds good. / - The loser pays. Agreed?
- Agreed! / - Okay.
Let's start with serious determination.
- Let's go. / - Okay.
(With their pride at stake)
(This was filmed in cooperation with the staff)
- Go. / - Go.
(Start)
(Excited)
- Hey, this is fun! / - This is amazing.
(Jeongcheol is pulling ahead of the race)
I'm taking the inside lane.
Oh, the inside lane!
No, no.
(He overtakes him)
I'm right behind you.
- Wasn't that scary though? / - It was quite fast.
You must adjust your speed well.
The path down is so pretty.
Come closer.
Check out that ocean.
(Enjoying the view of the ocean is a bonus)
Hello.
- What was that? / - It dips down like a cliff.
It's quite surprising.
Jumping over it would be so fun.
(They pass through the difficult section)
I had no idea that was there.
I was so surprised.
- That was incredible. / - I agree.
What a surprise.
There are obstacles.
What's that?
- There are obstacles? / - Yes.
- That's dangerous. / - They are scattered about.
(Who is the winner?)
You can't be behind me.
- No! / - You can't take the same lane.
(Seungsoo took the same lane in)
- What's this? / - Come on.
- He followed behind me. / - He took the wrong lane.
- He should've taken another lane. / - What was that?
- It was so fun. / - Yes, this was so much fun.
This is fun.
Seungsoo, this is much better than I expected.
- Yes, this was so much fun. / - The speed...
- It accelerated more and more. / - I was surprised.
Kids will love this.
Anyway, the meal is on me.
- Can't be helped. / - Thank you for dinner.
- Well... / - Everyone, eat a lot.
Eat as much as you want.
Even though you got the flick,
I should buy the drinks.
- Thank you. You're buying. / - I ought to.
- Right. Let's go. / - Don't you want to ride it again?
- Yes, I wanted to. / - I wanted to keep going.
The kids kept riding down and then going back up.
That's the Everything Restaurant.
You get sides with every drink you order.
- My gosh, what's all that? / - What?
- That's what they serve. / - You get all that?
- Yes. / - No way. They won't make money.
That's just the start. It's really shocking.
But you didn't order many drinks. You get that much?
- That can't be true. / - More drinks mean more food.
- We were surprised. / - The dishes differ every day.
- Depending on the catch. / - That's amazing.
The locals ask the fishermen what they caught.
- What's good? / - What they have.
And they answer that they have everything.
That's why it's the Everything Restaurant.
Oh, from "we have everything."
Everything, everything, everything.
They say that's why it's called Everything Restaurant.
When will it be ready?
It's coming right up.
- We'll finally get the side dishes. / - I'm hungry.
Goodness.
(The table is full of endless side dishes)
The way the system works...
- It's all raw fish. / - It's very famous.
You pay only $30 per person.
- $30 per person? / - Yes, $30 per person.
If you order 3 bottles of alcohol, you get 20 dishes.
Every time you order another bottle,
you get a bunch of other dishes.
If you get the standard set and order more,
you get more food.
She put iced water in the bucket.
Jeongcheol.
I haven't had a beer with you in ages.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
- No, no. I should thank you. / - Thanks.
My first glass on my first trip with you.
(It tastes like honey)
- Yes, this is it. / - It's just...
- This is it. / - Yeah.
Show us what you get?
I don't know what to start with.
- Sea squirt bibimbap. / - Sea squirt bibimbap?
How is that possible?
- Seriously. That place is no joke. / - It's a base dish.
Tongyeong is famous for sea squirt.
- Yes, it's famous for that. / - I love sea squirt.
They are in season now.
It's good.
- Sea squirt can be quite fishy. / - Exactly.
Gosh, I can taste the ocean in my mouth.
With this dish, we already had an appetizer.
Yeah.
When it comes to sea squirt...
I can't believe I didn't go there.
I don't enjoy it all too much.
- This bibimbap is great. / - I'd go just for that.
- It's better with bibimbap than separately. / - Right.
(It suits their tastes perfectly)
You have to come on an empty stomach.
You'll lose out if you eat beforehand.
- How can you finish all this? / - You can't.
- The main dish hasn't been served. / - There's more?
- We'll get more dishes? / - We're just getting started.
The main dish wasn't served yet.
That was like a set of appetizers.
- That was the appetizer? / - Yes.
The main dish is coming.
- How is that possible? / - They'll start serving now.
- That's the class of Tongyeong. / - It's not over yet?
- There's more? / - We'll have to stack the dishes.
- We didn't have space on our table. / - Exactly.
It's not that we're not eating.
It's just not reducing even though we're eating them.
Here's another dish.
You have to keep eating.
Didn't she give you extra because it's Seungsoo?
That's why we asked
if she gave us more for the TV show.
But if she did that, the others would complain.
- That's right. / - That's so true.
The raw fish is cut perfectly for drinks.
One piece of fish for one sip of alcohol.
How is it?
Even the texture is very good.
It's so chewy.
- Right? / - It's so chewy.
- This tastes great. / - Exactly.
It gets tastier the more I chew.
The texture is great.
The more I chew, the sweeter it tastes.
- You'd get scared to order more drinks. / - I was.
I was scared.
- When there are many side dishes... / - What's that?
- Cuttlefish. / - Cuttlefish?
- That's the ink. / - It's a cuttlefish.
- Cuttlefish. / - Gosh, that's just...
Let me try.
(He eats it in one go with a lot of ink)
How is it?
I keep saying this.
It's the freshest.
You have to give us a smile after eating that ink.
- For the show. / - You're happy, right?
- There we go. / - He did it.
- There it is. / - He knows how it's done.
I know.
I'm getting tipsy.
The best part of traveling is this.
- It's the delicious food. / - He became the Joker.
- His lipstick color is pretty. / - I agree.
A trip with great food is the best.
Enjoying great food brings so much happiness.
(They wrap up their day as they enjoy their drinks)
(Exciting morning of their second day in Tongyeong)
That place is so awesome.
(They can take a boat to Yokjido from Samdeok Port)
- It's the next day morning? / - Yes.
We're at the port.
- You're researching again? / - Yes.
Such a researcher.
I prepared everything in advance.
- Since it's our first trip. / - The ferry.
I see. We can go there through the ferry terminal.
(50 minutes by ferry from Samdeok Port to Yokjido)
Since it takes 50 minutes, you can take rice rolls...
- Yes, you must eat on the ferry. / - You should.
We should depart from Samdeok Port.
To spend our day efficiently,
we'll start from Samdeok Port.
A person like him makes everyone comfortable.
That's great.
It was really convenient. It was for me.
- We get the tickets from here? / - Yes.
We'll take the ferry at 8:30 a.m. 2 adults, please.
Thank you. / - Thank you.
- So you need your ID. / - You must take your ID.
- Let's go. / - To Yokjido!
(One Day Three Meals Tour departs for Yokjido)
I'm excited.
We only traveled a bit on the ferry
but I see lots of small islands.
- I like the smell of the sea. / - I agree.
It's refreshing.
(The ferry cuts through the sea and heads to Yokjido)
(Ah)
This is so nice.
The inside of the ferry was amazing.
- It must be nice inside. / - It was so comfortable.
- Wow, they're eating a lot. / - What's that?
- Pork belly with oyster? / - What is that?
- What's that? / - Let me explain about Yokjido.
This region is famous for mackerel and sweet potato.
Mackerel and sweet potato?
- Is that so? / - That's why...
I plan to eat every dish made
with mackerel and sweet potato.
- Really? / - Yes.
- I love both. / - Right?
- Yeah. / - We eat both of them often.
Since it's breakfast, instead of eating sashimi...
- A meal? / - How does a mackerel meal sound?
- A mackerel meal? Okay, okay. / - Let's go.
Hey, where are we going to eat?
- Seungsoo, that place looks great. / - Which one?
- Let's eat on the second floor. / - Sure, sure.
- We can see the ocean from there. / - That's great.
Isn't that mackerel?
They have live mackerel.
- Those are live mackerel. / - That's so interesting.
- I've never seen it before. / - They go in circles.
They keep circling in the same direction.
The colors are so distinct.
That's how the color looks when they're fresh.
- This is intriguing. / - I've never seen live mackerel.
Exactly. Same here.
I heard this is the only island that can raise mackerel.
- Raising mackerel? / - Yes.
- They raise mackerel? / - Yes, they do.
This is the only island that does.
I'm getting even hungrier. Let's hurry.
Don't you think Yokjido is a funny name?
- It is. / - It sounds like "curse."
I see signs that say, "Yokji post office,"
"Yokji church," "Yokji elementary school."
Stop emphasizing the "curse" part.
- Yokji. / - Yokji.
It's a very unique name.
I wonder what it means.
I got curious and I looked it up.
In Chinese characters,
"Yok" means to "desire"
and "Ji" means "to know."
It's an island that gives you a desire
to know more about it.
That's why it's called Yokjido.
That's the story behind the name.
- That's how charming the island is. / - Exactly.
- It's a meaningful name. / - So Yokjido...
- Has a different meaning. / - It does.
- It made the island seem different. / - I see.
Yokjido.
(The fresh mackerel is now being cooked)
That must be so delicious.
That has to be delicious.
Freshly caught mackerel...
They're really tender, right?
I don't know how to describe it.
It's like, "Did mackerel always taste like this?"
Smelling the food makes me hungry.
I can smell the food.
- Oh, yes. / - Thank you.
- Hello. / - It's finally served.
It's finally served.
(Another feast is served)
This is insane. My goodness.
(It's a special mackerel dish you can taste in Yokjido)
We're going to show you a unique way to eat mackerel.
- Freshly caught mackerel. / - Yes.
You'd never dream to freeze them here, right?
Right.
If you come to Seoul,
I'll show you what frozen Mackerel is like.
Seriously.
Let's get started.
I'd like to start with the natural flavors.
(Seungsoo takes a bite first)
This fish right here...
It doesn't need anything else.
That's the face of someone who ate something good.
You have to look angry.
This is game over.
I'll try some.
It's game over.
- It must be really good. / - That's the face...
When you eat something really good.
The best mackerel of my life...
I shouldn't get used to this taste.
- Now I can't eat anything but fresh mackerel. / - Yeah.
It's so juicy.
In Seoul, the juice just tastes like oil.
But here, it doesn't just taste like oil.
It's real juice from the meat. You can taste it.
- The meat looks plump. / - I know.
- It has to be juicy. / - I want to eat that again.
I feel sad.
Oh, man...
I'm sure it's harder for the two of them than for us.
Because we know how it tastes.
- You know the taste. / - I still remember it.
My mouth keeps watering.
Let me try this as well.
I'll dip it in the sauce.
The meat is plump.
How is it?
This is so good. The chef here cooks really well.
The sauce is good.
As you know, mackerel is packed with
vitamins and minerals.
- It's the most nutritious fish. / - Yes, it is.
Wasn't it salty?
- Not at all. / - It wasn't salty at all.
Gyeongsang-do foods are normally salty.
But that wasn't salty at all.
Just that alone is tasty.
They gave us lettuce and cabbage.
I don't think there's anything that goes with lettuce.
I wondered why they gave us this
when we ordered mackerel.
- We're meant to eat it as a wrap. / - Like meat.
- Wrap the fish in lettuce. / - Radish too.
You have to go to Yokjido to taste that.
It's delicious.
- It's similar to meat wraps. / - I know.
This is interesting.
- It tastes like good meat. / - He's suddenly excited.
- I was really surprised. / - After tasting it?
I don't think you could tell it's fish if you're not told.
At first, I thought it wouldn't go well with lettuce
but now that I see how it looks, it looks delicious.
I've tried lots of dishes but...
Instead of paste, I used the pollack roe...
- It was fantastic. / - Pollack roe!
- It's a flavor you can't imagine. / - That looks so good.
- Pollack roe. / - We're eating so much interesting food.
Add that here.
(I'm feeling good)
Seungsoo, you look excited.
(His extreme happiness makes his eyebrows dance)
This is a new kind of mackerel dish.
I love eating it with pollack roe.
It accentuates the flavor.
Are there many good mackerel restaurants in Yokjido?
- There are quite a few. / - There are?
- There are quite a few. / - The flavor changes.
Yeah.
Nothing tastes bad here.
I just had the best mackerel of my life in Yokjido.
It looks just like a cafe...
- That place looks like a bakery. / - I know.
It's such a nice atmosphere.
When we go outside, there's a coastal road.
The road goes around the island.
- A coastal road? / - Yes.
I've prepared a special convertible
to cruise down that road.
- Here? It's a convertible? / - Yes.
It's open on all sides.
- Really? / - Yes.
I'm a bit worried now after this great meal.
You're worried?
- No? / - It's going to be very cool.
Okay, we need to work that out.
So you go on ahead, I'll eat some more first.
- But my legs won't move. / - They won't...
Can we take this to go?
- It must be really good. / - I want to live here.
We're going to the place I planned for you.
I told you earlier. Convertible!
A convertible?
- Open in all directions? / - That's right!
- A convertible of Yokjido? / - It's very cool car.
There it is.
Take a look.
- What is it? / - He might be scolded.
- What's that? A tricycle? / - Oh, that's a...
Convertible.
(You can rent a vehicle in Yokjido)
(ATV hire, $25 for 2 people)
- You see them on coastal roads. / - ATV!
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Hello. / - Hi.
We'd like to hire one.
How do you drive it?
You need to practice a bit.
- You need to practice? / - How do you practice?
I'm going to drive.
- Would you like to drive? / - Yes.
- I'll sit in the back. / - Okay.
- I'll get one ready right away. / - Sure thing.
- Guys normally ride separately. / - They're lovers.
(There's a sitting cushion for Jeongcheol)
(After they put on helmets, the training starts)
I get on...
Let's have just one person on for now.
Yes, okay.
- This is the brakes. / - Press the brakes.
Could you give me your hand?
(The middle-aged Park Bogum)
- Can I touch your hand? / - Yes, yes.
She touched his hand.
She's very polite.
- Can I touch your hand? / - Yes, yes.
(She grabs his hand)
You should leave the car in neutral.
Is this the gear? This is neutral and this is drive.
If you want to let it stand, press this here.
Like this?
(They even finished a practice drive)
Do you need a driver's license for that?
- You need your license. / - I see.
One Day Three Meals Tour!
(They start the tour around Yokjido)
Riding this makes me feel like...
- I've become a resident of Yokjido. / - I know.
It'd be so fun for couples to ride that.
It'd be the best.
How about we buy some dessert on the way?
- Dessert? / - Yes.
Do they sell dessert here?
There's a dessert place run by senior citizens.
- Senior citizens? / - Yes.
We must go there.
Okay, okay.
It's a place with a special dessert.
So this is the place.
Hello.
(Senior citizens took barista courses to run this place)
It's so beautiful.
Sweet potato latte is tasty.
That machine is imported
but the pitcher is a traditionally Korean pail.
(You can have various sweet potato desserts)
(Jeongcheol ordered sweet potato latte)
Excuse me, ma'am.
We brought tumblers.
Please give us the latte in these.
- Sweet potato latte. / - It looks delicious.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
- Thank you for the drink. / - Thank you for the drink.
- Stay healthy. / - Bye.
Go, go.
Go, go!
I feel good to have something delicious now.
I know.
Let's go, Seungsoo!
- Let's go. / - Where are you going now?
A place with an incredible view.
If you drive along the coastal road,
there's a photo spot there.
We'll go this way.
(They can see the amazing view of Yokjido)
It looks amazing.
This really is a coastal road.
(Yokjido has nice breezes and plenty to see)
Seungsoo, let's stop over here.
- The view here is great. / - Let's take a break here.
This place is awesome.
Oh, my. What a great location.
The view from there was fantastic.
I didn't know how beautiful Korea was.
It's just like Italy.
You have to enjoy that view with bare eyes.
It makes all your stress go away.
Check out the rocks.
Goodness, look at the color of the water.
This sea looks so exotic.
What a view.
It's different from the East Sea.
I'm not sure since I haven't been to the South a lot.
I really experienced what it was like on this trip.
It's really marvelous.
It is marvelous
but for some strange reason...
I'm hungry despite the fact that we just ate.
You're hungry, right?
You digest well here.
I'm digesting food quickly now.
It must circulate well.
The dessert we bought earlier...
Let's eat that.
- We should eat it with this view. / - Let's eat it here.
- Seriously. / - This is the best.
- Should we sit there and eat? / - Yes.
This is a nice spot.
It's a bit embarrassing but let's sit next to each other.
You sat side by side?
It'd be so funny if it ended with a confession of love.
- A happy ending? / - Yes.
I wouldn't mind any kind of romance...
(They have a sip of the sweet potato latte)
It tastes magical.
Lately, I make baby food, right?
- Yeah! / - This tastes similar to that.
It really does.
Kids will love this.
I said this on the way here.
But if I ended up meeting someone here,
I think I'd love that woman with all my heart.
- Do you want to get married? / - Of course.
- Really? / - Yes.
That's what I always tell you. Please.
If you just hold hands
and do a lap of the island, love will blossom.
(At that moment, tour vehicles pass behind them)
(I guess they're here to sightsee)
I know him!
Yes, hello.
Did you not bring your kids here?
My kids aren't born yet.
- They think you're married. / - Yes.
They see you as the character from your drama.
Yes, yes.
(I'm still a bachelor)
Seungsoo.
Did you enjoy it?
- Let's remember this tasty time. / - Okay.
- There's a place we must visit. / - Another?
- It's a must-see place in Yokjido. / - Really?
There's a place better than here?
You haven't been to Yokjido unless you go there.
- If you recommend it that strongly... / - We must go.
Yeah. But I really love this place.
Let's save this place in our hearts and get going.
- It will be amazing. / - This is...
- I should do what youngsters do. / - What is it?
Saved it in my heart.
- Youngsters do that these days? / - Yes.
Saved in my heart!
- Saved... / - Saved...
That was a bit slow.
- "Saved." / - It was very slow.
- "Saved." / - Very slow.
- They didn't save it. / - Very slow.
Saved it in my heart.
Tourist attractions in Yokjido.
This looks fun. The suspension bridge.
I love those.
Can Seungsoo handle this?
(10 minutes by ATV from observatory to the bridge)
- Is this the place? / - Yes.
- Okay. / - If we take a short walk...
We'll be there.
The view here is nice too.
So this place has a view as good as before?
- This is special. / - Yeah?
It's really special. You must cross that bridge.
Having a guardian like him made the trip so good.
- Guardian? / - He's your guardian?
I just had to go wherever he led me.
But you need someone like Seungsoo
who doesn't prepare anything and just follows.
If both people prepare things...
- You clash. / - That's right.
It's not just a regular bridge.
Is it a bridge of no return?
You're not scared of heights, right?
There it is. That's the suspension bridge, Seungsoo.
You saw that, right? The suspension bridge.
- A suspension bridge? / - The name gives it away.
- It looks like Jeju-do. / - Yes.
I don't know how much the bridge will move.
I have a bad feeling.
- There it is. / - I can see it.
(Wow)
It actually moves.
That looks like fun.
The view here was so...
Wow, that's amazing.
(Bridge above water that connects to the observatory)
- Will you be okay? / - What's that down there?
Down there...
It's quite high.
The bridge wasn't long but it was really high.
Weren't you scared?
I was scared a bit.
It really is a suspension bridge.
(Giggling)
Amazing. Hold on a second.
Amazing.
He's jumping. He's jumping behind Jeongcheol.
- There he is. / - He's jumping.
The charm of the bridge comes from this movement.
(This is fun)
Hey, it looks amazing here.
- Let's take a photo here. / - Yes. Wow, here...
What a fantastic view.
Those views are breath-taking.
This is nice.
So refreshing.
(I'll take a photo of Seungsoo)
- I'll take it. / - Okay.
(Shaking suspension bridge with beautiful scenery)
One Day Three Meals Tour!
(A fun memory at the suspension bridge)
- Let's return the ATV and go. / - Sure. Okay.
You have to hire an ATV there.
There's so much you can do with it.
The ATV provides its own enjoyment.
(They reach the drop-off point at 3 p.m.)
We have arrived.
- Did you have fun? / - Yes, it was great.
- We had so much fun. / - I see.
Can I ask you a question?
- Sure. / - Who's the opposing team?
Cho Janghyuck...
- Cho Janghyuck? / - Yes, Cho Janghyuck.
And Singer Kim Hyunchul.
(Two middle-aged men are leisurely enjoying life)
Cho Janghyuck?
What is going on there?
We have to win, right?
- We must win. / - We must win. I think we'll win.
We have this sweet potato rice wine here in Yokjido.
- Sweet potato rice wine. / - Rice wine!
Sweet potato rice wine and raw mackerel.
If you have that, I think you can win.
(A highly recommended combination)
Fish with strong flavors go well with rice wine.
- Is it nearby? / - Yes, right here.
- This is a powerful one. / - It's an ultimate.
You must beat Cho Janghyuck.
As the representatives?
Do you have something against Janghyuck?
No, I like him.
You like him?
- I'll have to visit Yokjido. / - Yeah.
I'd better go to her to hire the ATV.
- Then are you using us? / - No.
- I'm just a fan. I'm his fan. / - You're a fan.
- But you still want us to win? / - Of course.
- Thank you. / - Not at all.
Here we are.
Sweet potato rice wine.
Sweet potato rice wine from Yokjido.
They're here to buy the rice wine
- Hello. / - Hello.
This is the sweet potato rice wine?
(That looks good)
It looks like the chestnut rice wine.
The rice wine isn't bottled? It's stored just like that?
It means they makes it from scratch.
With yeast?
- You harvested them yourself? / - Come and try this.
Sure, sure.
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
To our victory!
(They have a cup of cool rice wine)
- You can't really taste the alcohol. / - Yeah, it's good.
We used to drink it as a snack.
We didn't have a lot of food back then.
So we brewed a lot of rice wine.
If you drink this, you won't feel hungry.
- It's $5 per bottle. / - $5...
(The second place the ATV lady recommended)
Jeongcheol, here...
I see the cart bar she told us about.
- The live mackerel is here. / - It's here.
- Right. I think this is the place. / - We can eat there.
It's just mackerel everywhere.
It's just a cart bar by the sea.
They're so common there.
It's really rare here.
- Hello. / - Hi.
- Let's go in. / - Come in.
(Fresh mackerel in Yokjido are raised here)
(You can taste fresh, raw mackerel here)
($30 per plate, 2 fish)
We finally get to eat raw mackerel by the ocean.
I can't believe they sell mackerel at a cart bar.
Seungsoo, check this out.
I don't know how this will look on screen.
It's like a painting.
This is a scene you dream about.
- Sitting by the sea like this. / - I love this stillness.
The wind is nice and cool.
Seungsoo, it's already past 4 p.m.
Our ferry is at 4:30 p.m.
The final ferry departs at 4:30 p.m.?
Yes, there was one at 4:30.
We were meant to hurry and move.
I'd just stay there.
- That's our last ferry? / - Yes.
We have no time.
- We're in a hurry. / - They need to bring it out fast.
Please add it in with CG.
Let's pretend we have raw mackerel and eat.
Fresh mackerel is brought out.
They just filleted it, so it looks so lustrous.
It's juicy.
- It's not fishy. / - It's not fishy at all.
Of course not. We didn't eat anything.
I thought it was real. You're such a great actor.
- Here it comes. / - Thank you.
The true color of an oily fish.
- The color is really pretty. / - Yes.
- It looks delicious. / - We'll have a drink.
I wonder what the sweet potato rice wine tastes like.
I can barely taste the alcohol.
If you didn't mention it...
They'd think it was non-alcoholic.
It has really low alcohol content.
- It does? / - Really low.
Then I can drink it too.
Have a piece of this and a sip of rice wine.
Try it as it is.
It's good, right?
That's fascinating. It's a very light taste.
- It's just savory. / - It really is savory.
- It's the best mackerel I've had. / - Yes.
- Isn't it too greasy? / - Not at all.
- Not fishy at all. / - It's fascinating.
Having it with the rice wine is the delicacy.
You drink this and it's like you didn't eat the fish.
It cleans your palette.
I could drink this forever.
(It's time to eat endlessly)
Did they add something to this?
- I feel like mackerel all of a sudden. / - I know.
Don't they sell it anywhere?
Yokjido is the place to have raw mackerel.
- It's almost time. / - We have to go now.
Everything was a success in Yokjido.
- They ate it all. / - They cleaned out their plates.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
- Hey, hurry up. / - Is the boat still there?
- What happened? / - What?
I think it's closed.
- Seungsoo. / - Did you miss the last boat?
- There was an incident. / - It's locked.
No, it can't be.
(There goes the last boat)
That was the last boat.
What should we do?
(He can't believe this situation)
(How can you laugh about this?)
Seungsoo, I'm sorry. This...
- There is no boat until tomorrow. / - Goodness.
The first boat departing Yokjido is at 8 a.m.
What should we do? What do we do?
What do we do?
Seungsoo, this is destiny.
- No way. / - This is destiny.
We need to sleep here tonight.
That sounded strange.
Why are you crying?
- Hello, ma'am. I have a question. / - Hello.
We just missed the 4:35 p.m. boat.
Aren't there anymore that go to Tongyeong?
There are, on that side.
- Where? / - Where?
- Over there. / - On the other side?
- Are there more boats there? / - I see.
Thank you so much.
- Are there two docks? / - Yes.
- There it is. / - Thank goodness.
It's at 5:50 p.m.
There are ships that leave at later times.
5:50 p.m.
You have plenty of time.
- Thank goodness. / - Seriously.
- There's always hope. / - You're right.
There's always a way.
Let's go on that boat.
- Let's go! / - Yes, let's go.
(They go back to Tongyeong safely)
Did you sleep in Tongyeong on the first night?
Yes, we did. Then we went to Yokjido.
Then we went back to Tongyeong.
You have something left to do in Tongyeong?
- It's the highlight, the oysters. / - That's the best.
That's right. This is the first time you're having oyster.
- That's right. / - It's the first time.
(30 minutes from Samdeok Port to oyster pork belly)
It's not the oyster season in Tongyeong.
So not many restaurants serve oyster course meals.
I think the last part of the journey has to be great,
so I can say that we had a successful trip.
They're oyster dishes
that we've never tried before.
They serve them in a course meal.
Really? Are you sure?
- It's the best cooked oyster dish. / - Okay.
- Let's go. / - Okay. Let's go.
- No need for explanation. Let's go. / - Okay.
- Check it out yourself. / - Just go for it.
I am curious.
It's not oyster season but
you can have this oyster dish.
You can eat it all year round.
You really prepared a lot beforehand.
King of preparation.
You can taste various oyster dishes.
I think you'll be satisfied with most of them.
Yes. I'm also wondering,
"Are there a lot of different oyster dishes?"
I know oyster fritters.
Right. What you usually see is oyster in fritters.
- Oyster soup. That's about it. / - Right.
- I have a reason for coming here. / - What is it?
They serve a dish that beats all the other dishes.
I've never even imagined this kind of combination.
- Is that right? / - I think...
We'll win because of this dish.
- This is the winner. / - I think it is.
The owner of this restaurant
made a lot of oyster dishes
for those who can't eat raw oysters.
She serves dishes that she came up with.
That... What?
It's interesting. I've only heard of it.
- She's bringing something. / - Why do we need this?
(A gas burner?)
- Why do we need this? / - Exactly. Do we cook...
What is this?
I've only seen this in pictures.
(Pork belly and oysters)
(Awesome)
That's...
- What is that? / - That's thin pork belly.
- What is this? / - What is that?
Thin pork belly, oysters and seasoned bean sprouts.
Such a dish exists?
I was shocked too.
Look how plump the oysters are.
As soon as you serve that...
- This combination... / - Exactly.
- Could this be... / - I can't trust this combination.
- Let's try something else first. / - Yes.
Try the other dishes while it's cooking.
(There's a variety of other dishes as well)
(Oyster course meal is $30 per person)
Shall we try the most familiar one?
Yes, I'll do it.
That's the real oyster.
- Is it good? / - Yes.
They catch the oysters fresh.
So they're really plump. You can see how plump.
- They're really fresh. / - I love oyster.
That's like a real health food.
Isn't this your first oyster pork belly?
Yes. We were so surprised.
This oyster is so fresh.
- This too. / - Seasoned oyster.
Yes, seasoned oyster in pepper paste and vinegar.
(Jeongcheol takes a bite)
It's good. It's sweet and sour.
Will you be okay with that?
Why do you keep smacking your lips?
- Wait till you see ours. / - Okay.
It just looks too good.
We'll watch yours next week.
The oyster season is over.
Did you harvest them recently?
In Tongyeong, we harvest oysters all year long.
When the weather is warm, we eat them cooked.
So you harvest them all year,
but you cook them because the weather is warm.
- Since you can't eat it raw. / - I see.
- The oysters are very plump. / - They are.
- They can't be if they were frozen. / - Right.
(Finally they try the grilled oyster dish)
How does it taste?
You can't tell before you eat.
We weren't sure about that combination.
- That combination. / - It's driving me crazy.
That's seriously cheating.
It's all cooking in that pork grease.
What about this?
So what's the combination? The pork belly and...
The meat, vegetables and oyster wrapped in lettuce.
With soybean paste or pepper and vinegar?
- Eat it with soybean paste. / - Just bean paste.
(It's a delicious wrap)
You had really great meals in Tongyeong.
- Seriously. / - How does it taste?
His expression is?
This is interesting. Towards the end...
It hits you.
- It's unexpected? / - Yeah.
I'll try some.
You need to chew for a while to taste the aroma.
At first, I taste the pork.
- Yes, the pork belly. / - That's what I taste.
Then midway through,
you can taste the oyster.
That'd be so good.
It has too many different tastes.
Was it too confusing?
You can't say it's confusing. You should rather say
it's entrancing.
I could feel so many different tastes at the same time.
I was busy savoring all of them.
It gets rid of the bad smell of pork.
I know. The more I chew, the more flavor I get.
This is amazing.
It changed my perceptions of oysters.
We must eat a lot of this.
(A strange combination of an oyster and pork)
It feels peculiar but charming.
(Charming)
(You have to taste it yourself)
- They're eating a lot. / - Do you go on a diet?
A diet? I had no thought of it that day.
- That day. / - There was no tomorrow.
That's how we feel when we eat something good.
There should be no tomorrow when you eat that.
I ate that last bite and...
The oyster and pork parted to different sides
of my mouth.
I had oyster in here and pork in here.
This tastes good and so does this
and when they meet in the middle, it's so good.
It's a different taste when they mix, right?
This is strange.
What was your favorite?
We went to so many restaurants
but there wasn't a single restaurant that I didn't like.
I know.
We had three meals and even dessert and snacks.
I'll never forget the set meal
with the endless serving of food.
The grilled fresh mackerel.
And the braised dish...
I feel bad about picking a favorite.
What stuck in my mind
in a short period of time
is this pork belly with oyster.
I want to cook it myself
after I go back to Seoul.
There has been nothing bad the whole day.
Thank you, Jeongcheol.
Thank you for the three meals for today.
One Day Three Meals Tour!
(One Day Three Meals Tour to the domestic island)
- I think you gained weight. / - I gained a lot of weight.
You can see the difference.
- He gained weight. / - You can see it.
You did eat a lot.
It was a proper eating show.
I thought three meals a day weren't enough at first.
But they had such abundant meals.
What did you say?
I think it's a rediscovery of Yokjido.
When you see Ulleungdo, you want to go there.
I didn't know much about Yokjido
but I want to go there now.
I think I must go there at least once in my life.
The mackerel was so good...
And I want to know more about Yokjido.
Raw mackerel looked so good
but I don't like to drink.
However, I really want to try sweet potato rice wine.
- Women would like it. / - Can I get it in Seoul?
All the dishes we had on Yokjido...
I don't think I've ever seen them in Seoul.
They make it at home.
Yes, they make it in their homes.
So the alcohol content varies.
But it's lower in alcohol proof than regular rice wine.
Much lower. You can really gulp it down.
I really want to try it.
That's good. You can drink until the last ship leaves.
Let's check the cost now.
How much did they spend?
They ate a lot.
Each meal cost at least $30 per person.
They were set meals.
Seungsoo, how much did you spend?
- Excluding transportation expenses... / - Yes.
We spent $190.70.
- Per person? / - Per person?
For 2 days.
- It's less than $200. / - If it's less than $200...
- With all that food. / - For 2 days...
$190.70 per person.
Yokjido will be very popular after this show.
- I know. / - It's time to vote now.
Will you go to Yokjido, Tongyeong
according to the plan made by
the One Day Three Meals Tour?
Please vote.
(One Day Three Meals Tour to Yokjido)
(What will the judges choose?)
We'll show you the results of the vote
after we watch the Haenam, Wando tour.
But next week, we're taking a break
for the Russia World Cup.
We have to wait for 2 weeks then.
It's a shame but we'll save the results.
We'll see you again in 2 weeks.
- Thank you. / - Thank you!
(Next episode)
What is this place?
It's the paradise of food here.
Can we finish all this?
I'm going to gain weight.
This is good.
Man, this place is awesome.
It's a real health food.
Why Are We Traveling Together?
(Battle Trip)
("Light" by Wanna One)