(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Jonghyuk, Lim Hyungjun)
(Lee Gikwang of Highlight)
Travel is war!
Battle Trip!
Just like last week,
he is back to provide us with vast knowledge.
- Kim Taehun, welcome back. / - Nice to meet you.
We're with the trip designers
who designed a unique trip
to cities of England.
- Right, welcome. / - Good to see you again.
- Where's Dujun? / - Wait a minute.
Where did he go?
Right now, Dujun...
He's playing a role of a superstar in a drama now.
- I see. / - He left due to his schedule.
You can pull this off by yourself, can't you?
Yes, I'm more than capable.
Unfortunately, Dujun couldn't join us this week
due to his schedule.
But you guys have Taehun.
- That's right. / - But isn't England hard for you?
Well, personally,
I have a long history with England.
What kind of history do you have?
I worked at an English company
before I became a freelancer.
- Goodness! / - England!
It was a music company...
- An English company. / - He's actually a pop columnist.
Thought he was a comedian, right?
I worked for the company for about 4 years.
I went on business trips to London and Liverpool often.
I also studied about the culture.
I think that's why I was invited today.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
Welcome.
The trip is divided into two halves.
- You will vote four times in total. / - That's right.
The votes won't be accumulated.
Only the final votes will decide the winners.
Well...
Last week's episode was the best of the best.
It was a dream match for soccer fans.
They got to watch the Manchester Derby.
Last week's episode was similar
to the fermented skate set.
- Why's that? / - Skate set.
People who like it really love it.
But those who don't eat it, don't even look at it.
It was kind of like that.
I like that analogy.
We've been hosting Battle Trip for around 2 years.
The audience...
- It felt like... / - They were really...
- Their faces... / - Didn't it seem like a temple stay?
They were very quiet
and with so much being about soccer,
there was a clear division of likes and dislikes.
I agree.
But the whole trip
wasn't just about soccer.
There was food.
- And activities. / - Lots to see.
- They did the indoor skydiving. / - That's right.
- There were activities. / - There was a sparrow too.
- Yes, yes. / - Sparrow...
- Sparrow? / - The sparrow was the best.
We must watch Liverpool's trip now.
Actually, we don't know much about Liverpool.
- That's true. People don't. / - We don't know.
Even in travel books,
there's no information on Liverpool.
So you must pay close attention.
- The information... / - It means people don't go.
- Pardon? / - It means no one goes there.
Well... They couldn't go because they didn't know.
Isn't this what we do on Battle Trip?
This Liverpool trip from Battle Trip...
- Will serve as a guide. / - That's right!
I shouldn't say this because
they are our opposing team.
You don't need travel books for it
because it's a small city.
Is that so?
The second reason is...
That signs explain everything.
"Ringo Starr's favorite barber."
"John Lennon's favorite restaurant."
- The signs tell you everything. / - You don't need a guide.
You only need to walk about 15 to 20 minutes to...
You can see the whole city then?
- They are all nearby. / - The population...
- You can just walk? / - Is less than 1 million.
Really?
As far as I know, its population is less than 1 million.
Then you probably didn't pay any for transportation.
- That's right. / - You can go everywhere on foot.
I have a question.
- Liverpool is known for The Beatles. / - Right.
When we think about The Beatles,
we think of that album cover on the crossing.
We went there.
- You did it, right? / - Yes.
People think it's in Liverpool...
- It's on Abbey Road in London. / - Abbey Road.
That's why we stayed a night in London
then we headed to Liverpool.
When I went to London...
I should've gone there with four friends but I couldn't.
I just took the photo when people crossed the road.
- Like that. / - You can see it behind us.
Yes, this one.
- Everyone knows it. / - This one.
- When you actually go there... / - It's very famous.
The white lines aren't there.
- Yes, they've faded. / - They're mostly gone.
To be precise, they are walking away from it.
Abbey Road Studio is located on the left.
And if you look,
Paul McCartney is walking barefoot.
When the album was released,
people wondered why he walked barefoot.
There were rumors that Paul McCartney...
- Had already passed away. / - My goodness.
- See that white car on the left? / - Yes.
Just because that car was in the album photo,
that used car was sold at millions of dollars.
Back then...
- We placed a lot of meaning in such things. / - Yes.
We must start the first half now.
- Tell us what to focus on. / - Right. We...
There are so many songs that you...
- Wouldn't have guessed it's a Beatles song. / - Right.
That's how much we can relate to The Beatles.
In everything...
- There are hidden connections. / - It's intimate.
I didn't know this either.
But we followed the path of arguably
the most famous band in history on
how they made music and recorded it.
- Is this for real? / - Yes.
I'm a bit worried though.
You didn't only go to
those famous Beatles places everyone knows, right?
- You mentioned a great point. / - I mean...
For people who don't have interest in The Beatles...
Just like the soccer last week...
- It could be worse... / - Just quietly...
- That could happen. / - Thing is...
There are lots of young people in the audience.
When you mention The Beatles, they seem unsure.
It's not an understatement to say
they influenced every musician.
- But the generation has changed. / - Exactly.
This analogy might help understand this better.
The novel, "Norwegian Wood" by Murakami Haruki.
- It used The Beatles' song. / - That's their song.
Actually, the song was used for the commercial too.
Once you hear it, you'll recognize it right away.
We need something to compete against their trip.
- Is there something huge? / - Yes, tell us, please.
Something really impressive in Liverpool?
For us... A totally huge hamburger.
They sell 3.2kg burger.
- 3.2kg burger? / - Yes.
- That's it. We won. / - The burger...
- We won! 3.2kg! / - It's almost...
- It's as heavy as an infant. / - Wow!
- An infant. / - 3.2kg burger...
- Did you finish the burger? / - I'd be sick of eating it.
You can't eat all that.
- What? / - What?
Why eat it if you can't finish it?
But seriously, the burger...
- You have to see it. / - You'll know when you do.
It was very delicious.
Then you should've finished it.
- Pardon? / - Huh?
What I mean is...
Tell them we took the leftovers.
- One serving is around 200g, 180g. / - This big.
- Big eaters can eat more of course. / - 180g.
But that burger is over 15 servings.
Everyone in the front row could...
- Get a bite. / - Of course.
- It's that big? / - Wait...
The vibes are really good right now.
- We'll head to Liverpool. / - Everyone is so intrigued.
Let's take this vibe
and head to the first half of Liverpool.
From the viewers' point of view,
JH...
- It's this. / - MK.
Since it's Minkyo.
So let's be JH.
- JH? / - Yeah.
Not Jonghyuk.
I'm not confident.
JH for Jonghyuk and Hyungjun.
Isn't that too simple? JH.
- JJ. / - Jonghyuk, Hyungjun.
JJ isn't bad either.
- JJ? / - Yeah. Jonghyuk, Hyungjun.
Doesn't that sound like a club? JJ?
That's a famous club.
- JJ's not bad. / - JJ's not bad.
JJ Tour.
Does Minkyo know about this trip?
Minkyo...
MK Tour is so famous.
He looked like a local.
We need to ride that.
Why are you so good?
- Just eat it my style. / - Okay.
Minkyo was just too good.
What if he feels betrayed?
- Call him just in case. / - Then...
What's this, "slaves of MK?"
(Let's call MK first)
I don't have the guts to call Minkyo.
Seriously.
I'm serious. I can't bring myself to do it.
Can't you keep this a secret?
- It'll be on TV. / - He'll find out.
We should plan a good trip.
I'm really worried.
Jonghyuk treats everything like it's a hassle.
Don't feel pressured.
If we have fun, it will be fun for the viewers.
My shoulders feel burdened.
Which part of England did you always want to go?
England?
I heard London is the best city.
London is...
That's London Eye.
(The center of English culture)
(London)
Musicals are famous there too.
- Right, musicals... / - It's the home of musicals.
- Yes, you have to watch. / - We majored in theater.
I've always wanted to watch something on Broadway.
But I could never afford it.
So...
I even starred in...
- He's in a musical. / - I've been in "42nd Street."
- Right. / - But I've never been to Broadway.
(It's sad but so funny)
Are there any musicians you like?
Musicians? Well...
Sting.
- Elton John. / - Elton John.
- Elton John. / - Oh, Elton John...
It's the birthplace of pop music.
- There are many famous musicians. / - The Beatles.
- Right. The Beatles. / - They're so young there.
The first pop song I heard was "Yesterday."
- "Yesterday." / - Right.
It was when I was in elementary school.
We'd write the lyrics in Korean and memorize them.
Two of the members are still alive.
There must be a lot of things to commemorate them.
That's not bad. Following The Beatles.
- Their footsteps... / - Should we?
I was a musician myself.
You know it.
Music...
- He used to be a singer. / - I was...
I was a singer.
My gosh, I was famous for my music.
You even wrote a song, didn't you?
- Of course. / - He even wrote a song?
Yes. You bet.
I get royalties for that.
My gosh, it's been a while.
- When was that? 1998? 20 years ago. / - In 1998.
How embarrassing.
Your voice is high toned.
I sang with Lee Taeseop.
- Guitarist... / - Who?
Lee Taeseop from K2.
I thought it was Seotaiji in the photo.
Lena Park.
You know we debuted at the same time, right?
We're colleagues.
We even recorded in the same studio.
She recorded before I did.
I recorded my song after she recorded hers.
The sound engineer hated it.
With my first album...
A monk recorded before me.
- That's a unique experience. / - Yes.
"Diamond Sutra..."
(Researching intensely)
Good restaurants...
Minkyo, I have no idea about England.
Hamburger.
JJ Tour.
Coming soon.
(Let us introduce the JJ Tour)
(England)
What is that?
I told you. It's no joke.
- We fell from the sky. / - Is that skeleton?
- We fell from the sky. / - What's with your face?
That's satisfaction on his face.
What is this?
That's the face of satisfaction.
(Why would you only visit London in England?)
London...
I heard it feels very different
from the surrounding cities.
(JJ Tour)
(Thought nice and hard)
I really love The Beatles.
(The Beatles)
(Liverpool?)
(The Beatles equals Liverpool?)
(All over the city)
- They gained some weight. / - They look alike.
They look alike.
- They gained a lot of weight. / - Those people....
They didn't have much hair.
There were so many great photo spots.
That's true.
(Experiencing the lives)
(Of The Beatles)
(A new look at England)
(We head there now)
(JJ Tour)
(Now)
(We begin)
You went to a lot of places.
- Beer from the brew. / - It's a tight schedule.
- They did a lot. / - Geez.
That's our favorite itinerary.
This is how far we've gotten?
We need to go 11 more hours.
First...
Liverpool.
We're going to London.
You've prepared for London, right?
I did research a few things.
For activities, we can go on the rides.
- Rides... / - Rides we can't find in Korea.
We can talk once we're there.
I've already...
Prepared everything we're doing in Liverpool.
You are...
Really...
The Beatles...
You know...
Im Jinmo?
The music, critic Im Jinmo.
You'll know more about them than him.
You will...
They really feel like old men.
The trip looks a bit depressing.
Would you like something?
I'd like some snacks.
- Shrimp crackers. / - Shrimp crackers.
Can I have two?
Sure, go ahead.
I'd like some beer too, please.
Can I have one pizza?
(Incheon International Airport)
12 hours.
- 12 hours. / - Yes, 12.5 hours.
We have arrived!
Oh, it's warm in here.
Why is it so warm in London?
It's refreshing.
Where are the palm trees?
(Let's breathe in the English air)
It must have rained earlier.
It feels...
- It's slightly humid. / - The air isn't that bad here.
Nice.
Let's head to downtown London first.
- We'll head there... / - How do we get there?
- Jump? 1, 2, 3. / - No.
Jump.
- 1, 2, 3. Jump. / - No.
- We need to go by car. / - Really?
- Jump? / - Let's do it just once.
- On the count of three. / - It's around 1.5 hours.
Let's get going first.
Yes, let's.
It's far from the airport.
Yes, a bit.
What a great view.
- They're playing a Radiohead song. / - The clock...
Clock tower.
- That's the symbol of England. / - Exactly.
When London was chosen to hold the Olympics...
The double-decker bus appeared
with the announcement.
Isn't London beautiful at night?
It was very beautiful.
I bet it was blissful.
You don't take the bus often, do you?
- This is my first time on a double-decker. / - Same.
That looks cool.
Isn't that cool?
So this is the charm of England.
It's amazing.
Because it's the evening...
- The lights... / - They're so good.
We should've sat in the front seats.
Yeah.
Ask at which stop they are getting off.
Ask them?
So we can sit there later.
Where are you from?
I told him to ask where they're going.
Not where they're from.
I like going to distant countries for trips.
That way, it feels different.
This is The Beatles' debut song.
It's called "Love Me Do."
- I love Taehun's explanations. / - Yes, this is great.
Come over here.
(They will look around London on their 2nd day)
What's up with this weather?
It must always rain in England.
But isn't it better when it's gloomy in England?
Yeah, it does kind of feel that way.
Even the houses look English.
It's my first time but the houses look right.
(They walk the street as they bask in the ambience)
(Where are they headed to?)
We're going to go get lunch now.
I found a burger place.
Is it because you couldn't find any other place?
- No, I researched this. / - A burger...
- All the way here? / - I looked it up.
It's a really unique burger.
It's still a burger though.
It's a humongous burger.
It's a gigantic burger.
If you finish it, you get something.
What is the burger Jonghyuk looked up?
It's like giant pork cutlets in Korea, right?
What's going on?
Unbelievable.
If you finish within 40 minutes, you succeed.
One person?
Yes, just one person.
This is unbelievable.
For the first time in Korea.
This will be no. 1 on the search engines.
The photos on the wall...
That's right. They're all fails and successes.
Man vs. Food.
It's a battle between man and food.
Anyone home?
Is there anyone?
The exterior of the restaurant
is the same with any other burger restaurants.
- But the photos... / - So many photos, right?
Some are from the U.S. People came from all over.
They come from all over the world.
To take on the challenge.
What's this?
What is this?
Unbelievable, right?
They're doing the challenge now?
If you look there...
It says Legends.
They're the fastest eaters.
Heroes are those who succeeded.
Zero's are the fails.
If you fail, I guess you must wear the toilet cover.
If you succeed, you get money.
It's about 250 pounds.
That's over $300.
You know a lot about this challenge.
I have a small mouth by nature.
You should try that challenge.
Okay, I'll give this a shot.
I was going to try too
but my mouth is too small.
Are we going to be doing any challenges today?
- Yeah. / - Yeah?
One person, yeah.
- We need a regular burger too. / - Small burger.
Small burger.
Small burger. Okay, no problem.
- Take a close look at my burger. / - Okay.
You can all make this at home.
Check out the bun.
- How could he finish that? / - It weighs 3kg.
That's the patty.
The patty weighs 3kg.
You have to finish eating a breast of a cow.
But the thing is
the patty literally melts in your mouth.
It's not tough at all. It was so interesting.
(Can Jonghyuk succeed in this challenge?)
First of all, don't drink cola.
If you do, you'll feel full.
But I must drink it...
- To make my stomach bigger... / - No, no, no.
To help you digest,
pretend you're on a saddle.
- On a saddle? / - Like this?
- Eat it like that. / - I've seen people hit themselves.
If you do finish this challenge,
you'll go viral.
- You must finish within 40 minutes? / - Yes.
- That sounds doable. / - You'll be the first Korean...
To complete the challenge.
The very first Korean.
Do you think I'll succeed?
But still. Don't drink cola.
Fine. I'll try to eat as much as I can.
What is that?
- That's seriously... / - That's so...
It looks really delicious.
That's one year's worth of burgers.
If successful, he wins a 250 pound cash prize.
(My gosh, Jonghyuk)
I felt a bit...
- You get sick of it. / - I felt a slight wake up call.
They put a lot of cheese too.
- That's mayonnaise. / - That's mayonnaise?
- They're making it not edible. / - Just use a ladle.
Anyway, when you're on a trip, that'd be fun.
Does it have 100,000 calories?
- You'll get sick if you eat that. / - Oh, my God.
The patty was amazing.
It was so tender.
This is unbelievable. How many slices of cheese?
How many?
- If you eat that alone... / - 8? 9?
You could die if you eat that alone.
But that looks really good.
- Putting aside the size... / - Looks so good.
The grease...
(The gigantic burger has been served)
What should I do?
The patty's thickness...
- $80? / - It looks like a children's bicycle tire.
Check this out.
I wanted to share this with you guys.
This is worth leaving a photo for.
You must take one for that.
Don't you like taking photos?
- It's fun. / - You should try that.
Is that a good spot for photos?
Eat the patty first.
Like a cake...
We're going to give you a countdown
before you cut it, okay?
Oh, my. Wow.
The patty is thick.
(They even play a song)
This is amazing.
That looks like a cake.
They're playing the "Rocky" theme.
They play the song.
- Is that from the restaurant? / - Really?
This...
You should grab it and eat it.
That's great.
Don't rush. You got 40 minutes.
You have a lot of time.
If you don't rush, you won't be able to finish it.
(First, just shove it in)
You have a good start.
I think you can finish a quarter of it.
That was a bit hard.
It doesn't look like you ate any of it.
Hey, this...
- You should've had it with ketchup. / - Just relax.
I'm speechless because I'm stunned.
How's the meat? Is it tender?
The meat? Yes.
The meat is very juicy.
Hey, I want to
move this over here.
That's a good idea.
You can get sick of it, if there's too much.
So put some aside.
(They forgot about Hyungjun's burger)
The bun looks like a donut.
(Donut burger, $21.50)
Look at my burger.
Do you see the donut on top?
- That's a donut? / - It's a sweet donut?
- It's glazed donut? / - Yes.
It's so delicious with that.
- So good. / - It is but it's seriously fattening.
Really?
- It's so good though. / - It's sweet and salty.
This is good.
How did they come up with this?
Do you think they have pickles?
You don't have any room for pickles.
Just eat it.
Yeah, I'll have the onions instead.
(They eat simultaneously)
(I don't think I can eat that)
I think the patty itself would weigh
at least 2.4kg.
2.4 to 3kg.
You're amazing if you can finish half of it.
(Jonghyuk starts devouring again)
I want him to succeed.
(Hyungjun is eating gracefully)
It's really annoying, the way you eat.
Right.
He is very relaxed.
He's like a coach.
I'm jealous.
- Why? / - Because you're almost done.
I want more.
Why does it look like it's increasing?
- Right? / - The size...
Since he's opened it up,
it looks like there's more.
Hey, don't drink cola.
Try eating this burger!
I'm super thirsty.
Think back to the days when you were
cold and hungry.
I really want more.
This was so little.
Eat some of mine.
(Have some of mine)
One more donut burger please.
Hey, try mine.
Please one more.
Yeah, one more.
Hey.
- I ordered another. / - I've failed.
I've really failed.
- You have lots of time. / - Hey, don't.
- Why not? / - Try to the end.
It's only been 8 minutes.
If only 8 minutes have passed...
- Just eat slowly. / - He should keep going.
He'll get sick of it.
You're representing Korea.
You have to try to the end.
It wouldn't be too bad if the patty wasn't so thick.
The patty is like smoked ham.
The heater isn't on, is it?
I'm not eating hot soup but I'm sweating.
You ate about a fifth of it.
- Really? Did I eat a lot? / - Yes.
(He glances over)
There's still half of it left.
Don't look at that.
Just look at what's on your plate.
Don't look. Just eat.
- I really wanted this. / - So...
- He still has the urge to finish. / - It's so small.
Did you order another one because it was so good?
(This is hard)
I feel stuffy just watching this.
It gives you a stomachache, right?
I can't even be bothered to cut it now.
How many minutes do I have left?
(23 minutes)
23 minutes?
Try harder.
You're leaving the meat and only eating vegetables.
- The patty is so thick. / - That's too thin.
It's this big.
I'm going to eat it like boiled pork.
A triple set.
With the vegetables.
Triple set?
The next meal won't be easy.
Is there a hospital nearby?
A hospital nearby...
You're representing Korea.
- You should eat at least half. / - I don't care for that.
I have a shoot when I go back to Seoul.
I can't gain weight.
I can't eat at a restaurant for a long time.
Failure is the stepping stone to success.
Actually,
I ate breakfast at the hotel.
Is it that hard?
(He cringes)
Just finish the meat.
Do we need to keep watching?
Obviously, he failed.
Must we watch all 40 minutes?
That's how tough it is.
You should think hard about it.
- I'd better give up. / - Let's walk out quietly.
I give up.
He's giving up.
Goodness.
- She's bringing out the toilet seat. / - Yeah.
Man vs. Food. Food has won.
Let's give him  a big round of applause.
- There's his picture. / - Did they put it up there?
So if we visit...
- It's there. / - We can see his photo?
- Yes. / - It's up there.
Now that we're done eating...
We'll look around the city.
This is Abbey Road.
Are you finally going there to take pictures?
This is...
Abbey Road.
There's a famous picture where
they're crossing the street.
- Abbey Road? / - Yes.
- The jacket photo. / - You've seen it.
- The Beatles walked across... / - The crosswalk.
People copy that.
It's worn down a lot.
It's here.
The Beatles. Elton John.
Many people recorded there.
That space is great for
recording classical music.
Chang Hanna recorded there too.
At the Abbey Road Studios.
There.
So that's the spot.
The Abbey Road Studios is there.
That was the last place
where all four members
recorded together.
There are drawings on the wall.
Look.
There's the studio.
People wrote stuff.
Is that the studio?
They painted over it.
These are all written by visitors.
There's a museum of the studio
in Liverpool.
They kept it the same.
People from all over the world write on that wall.
One unfortunate thing is
they paint it over after a week
because it gets filled up.
So the writings don't last long.
So this is the studio where The Beatles recorded.
That's where they took the picture.
Just like those people.
They are walking across and taking pictures.
I can't believe I'm here.
This is the road.
- Shouldn't we walk across it? / - Yes.
- Is this it? / - Yes.
Don't we need two more?
It looks good when there are four.
- You're right. / - That's right.
Let's just go, the two of us.
We have to match our strides.
If you see the picture,
they walk the same.
We served in the army.
- Like marching in the army. / - Left foot first.
- Let's go when there's no car. / - Go.
- Left foot. / - Left foot.
- Hands like this. / - Left foot.
Left foot.
He said it with so much confidence.
That doesn't look good.
- It's the camera. / - I think it's because of this.
- The road... / - Go now.
The think the road became narrower.
Let's go now.
This is it.
I'm a bit embarrassed.
Why?
- You have to get that photo. / - You went all the way.
Travelers from all over the world do that.
Also, thing is...
These lights...
They mean...
Pedestrians first.
We walk on a green light, right?
But this place is so famous.
The cars all stop.
- For the people? / - Yeah, let's go now.
- Go. / - Go.
Go.
Don't look around.
The Beatles just looked straight ahead.
- Why am I so embarrassed? / - Don't look left, right.
Jonghyuk is super embarrassed.
It was embarrassing.
Good, good.
There's no one else around.
- You got the shot. / - There are no cars.
(We added the two other members for you)
That's nice.
We should just do all these.
Oh, this London Slide...
(London Slide?)
London Slide.
It's seems different to other rides.
This really looks scary.
I want to try this.
If your ride that after eating the burger,
you'll throw up.
That's what you were talking about earlier.
Check that out.
That's what we're riding.
- See that spiral thing? / - Like a twisted bread stick.
- Like a spring. / - We must drop from that.
That looks really scary.
That's the tallest slide in the world.
- That slide? / - Yes.
I'm scared.
(It's the tallest and the longest slide)
(76m high, roughly 30 stories tall)
(It takes 40 seconds to slide down)
That looks like fun.
It's no joke.
- It looks fun. / - That's so long.
It's the largest in the world.
(The London Slide is the largest in the world)
They did this for the Olympics?
- These must be the designers. / - Must be.
They did it for the Olympics.
Then they built it...
So that people could keep coming.
That looks so pretty with the lights on.
It's taller than the Statue of Liberty.
It's so...
It looks fun.
Are we already here?
It's quite high.
This is awesome.
It's nice.
The observatory is nice.
That is what a view should be like.
That's it.
You can see the entire downtown of London.
Right here...
Another soccer field.!
If you don't play, you lose. Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Jonghyuk wins)
(Upset)
Why do you have to wear a helmet?
For safety.
They said you had to wear it.
- You sit inside. / - Looks like we go in here.
He says to go in.
- Now? / - Yes.
Bring your feet right to the bottom.
Like when we were kids...
- The rice sacks. / - Like sliding down in rice sacks.
- Since it can get hot from friction? / - That's right.
Sometimes you can see and sometimes you can't.
Is he going down now?
- It'd be scary since you can't see. / - You can't see.
That's it. You pull in.
He says to pull this.
Just grab this?
Grab and pull.
(Scared)
Wait a minute.
Are you afraid?
This is scary.
Good-bye.
You can hear the screams...
Till the end.
Look at that sudden acceleration.
(He is screaming a lot)
(Ahhhh)
The important thing is you can see the outside?
You can and then can't.
There are areas where you can.
Goodness. It's crazy that you can see the outside.
Isn't he acting?
It looks fun.
Hyungjun.
Are you okay?
It looks scary.
It was too long.
After around 3 screams...
- It's usually over. / - I can still hear him.
He must still be going down.
He's doing well.
Still...
Seriously.
After a few screams...
- It takes ages. / - 178m.
He's going down for about 200m.
This isn't a joke.
Look at his face.
He's so ugly.
Jonghyuk's in trouble.
- Are you ready? / - Yeah.
Good.
Sit down.
(He's ready)
You can go down now.
Geez.
Even Hyungjun survived. I won't die.
But this is a little scary.
(He gives him a gentle push)
(He starts screaming from the start)
(Argh)
Look at that, it's really fast.
I can hear him screaming.
That looks fun.
- It must be really scary. / - That looks fun.
It must be real scary.
I'm still going down.
No...
You'll go down faster if you're heavy.
What is this?
Hey...
- What's going on? / - What?
- What? / - At the end.
What do I do?
Hey, pull me out or something.
Swim out.
What is this?
(Crawling)
No joke, right?
Is this supposed to be sad?
It's sad.
I was shocked.
It's scary.
I slid down for ages.
- It's really fun. / - It is.
You said there's something else to see.
The next destination.
Yeah, let's hurry.
- It's starting to rain. / - Let's go.
Can kids right it too?
If they're over 130cm.
And older than 8 years.
130cm...
- You have to be taller than 130cm. / - Ice rink!
This must be like city hall.
Like city hall plaza.
Skating...
- I'm good. / - Ice rink.
But the two of us at an ice rink...
- An ice rink? / - I've never tried.
- Just like Seoul City Hall. / - Yes.
Just go to Seoul.
- You can't compare. / - I'm good with roller skates.
- It's all the same. / - Really?
- Must we... / - Yeah.
You really want to do this?
We just have to not hold hands.
Why would you go to an ice rink in England?
The women would love this place.
Why?
It's really nice.
(ArcelorMittal Orbit)
(50 minutes by car to the Natural History Museum)
This is the trendiest place in London during winter.
There's a carousel and an ice rink...
This would be great to come with family.
It's outdoors.
You can always see places like this in the movies.
Yes, they're in movies.
Can you do this?
I'll be fine.
I'm not in the right condition
to show you my triple axel though.
This was the Natural History Museum.
It was in a lot of movies like...
"Night at the Museum."
It's the ice rink next to it.
Figure means
appearance and shape.
The English aristocrats of old...
- Figure. / - They used to...
To draw shapes in the ice with a blade.
They used to skate while drawing on the ice.
That's why it's called figure skating.
(Natural History Museum Ice Rink)
(It's only open during the Christmas season)
(The most popular ice rink in London)
(Ice rink, $23 per person)
I don't think I can skate.
It looks easy.
Be careful.
(Steps on)
It's so slippery.
I don't think I can do this.
Are you okay?
I can't do this...
How do you do this?
(Just go?)
Where is Hyungjun?
Where did he go?
(He's here)
Someone's crawling.
The only one that's falling over.
I don't like this.
It would've been great to go with a lover.
- That's right. / - I'm good on roller skates.
It's all the same.
(Skating was the easiest thing in the world for him?)
(Oh, my God)
(This won't do)
(Peek-a-boo)
That is for beginners.
- They hold it while skating. / - That's a good idea.
(I'm Kim Yuna with the penguin)
(Lim Hyungjun acquired skating skills)
I almost went to the opposite way.
I almost died.
It was against my will.
- Oh, my. / - What will he do?
No one saw it.
It's like nothing has happened.
Jonghyuk, can't you skate at all?
- I can't. / - I can't do this.
I'm not riding the skates.
The skates will give me a ride.
(The skates that are giving Jonghyuk a ride)
(Did I come to England for this?)
(Jonghyuk is just assisting)
(The skates are carrying him)
(If I can't skate, I should at least be funny)
It's my first time in 10 years.
If you ride this when you're old,
you're knees will go out.
(He is very noticeable from far away)
Are you okay?
My whole body is tired already.
Skating in England seems romantic.
The atmosphere was nice.
Why didn't you grab each other's waists at least?
The cafes and restaurants right next
to the ice rink were pretty.
You can drink wine there.
(And)
Hey!
(I'll stand behind you)
This is tough. We'll lose at this rate.
Right?
- Think of the ambience. / - What ambience?
How good is it?
It's only like that because it's London...
Good, good.
Keep going.
There are women who are skating hand in hand.
Just women...
(They became closer while holding hands)
(It's okay even if we're a male couple)
It's in front of the ice rink.
- You can see the ice rink. / - Yes.
This is called mulled wine.
It's wine mixed with spices.
You drink it warm.
Oh, warm wine.
That was so good.
It was my first time.
- Mulled wine. / - It looks good.
(Mulled wine, $9 per glass)
This is nice.
- They have this in Namsan. / - Really?
- It's good for colds. / - It has spices.
It's warm wine.
It says it helps you stay healthy and get rid of cold.
It's called mulled wine in the U.K.
And it's called vin chaud in France.
- Does it... / - In Germany, gluhwein.
- Does it have alcohol in it? / - Of course it does.
It's like herbal medicinal tea.
Herbal medicinal tea?
When Europeans catch a cold,
they drink this to warm up their bodies.
It's made with mediocre wine,
orange peel, cinnamon and so on.
It's simmered to add flavor.
- Simmered. / - Only in winter...
- Organic museum? / - What?
- No... / - Natural history.
- Natural history? / - Not sudden death.
Yeah, natural history museum.
This is the natural history museum.
Just like the skating rink at Seoul City Hall.
It's like that here.
- I love the ambience here. / - Right.
I like that we can sit inside after skating.
I heard they sell mulled wine only in the winter.
- Really? / - Yeah.
Now that I think of it, we also have things like this
in Seoul and so on...
But I've never tried it there.
It's nice to do things that we don't do in Korea.
It's been a while since I skated in an ice rink.
I hear carols.
This is the first time hearing carols this year.
It's a shame that I had to hear it with you.
- Yeah? / - Yeah.
I'm really happy I heard it with you.
Really? Have a drink.
We'll head to Liverpool tomorrow.
- For The Beatles. / - For The Beatles.
(Listening to the music from 50 years ago)
Their trip has just begun.
(Heading off to Liverpool with The Beatles)
It's fun to watch this again.
We just saw the best burger ever.
The donut burger looked really delicious.
Please tell us how it was.
Normally, "melts in your mouth" isn't used for burgers.
But when I took a bite of it,
the moist donut melted in my mouth.
It's not just sweet but...
- Sweet and salty. / - Yes.
What about the giant burger? It tasted good, right?
Yes, it was.
They gave us a T-shirt as well.
Did you take that T-shirt?
- But I ate it. / - They gave us a medium.
- Did you share the rest with the staff? / - Yes.
Right? That's good.
Do you remember Abbey Road you saw earlier?
It's possible for you to watch
the road live online these days.
You can watch the people walking on the road
in real time.
- Is this live? / - Yes.
That's great resolution.
- It's recording live. / - It's real time?
When tourists cross the road...
- Cars stop for them. / - Right. To take photos.
They all cross the road.
They're waiting in line to take pictures there.
Yes, to take photos.
- You couldn't enter Abbey Road Studios? / - No.
It's closed to the public.
It's not so spacious inside.
It's separated into several small rooms.
I heard there are many sound engineers
who are good with classical music.
If you pay for it, can Sikyung...
- Go and record? / - He can.
- If you pay... / - The funny thing is...
Since this place is known for as the Beatle's studio,
many rock bands want to work there.
Bands?
And they tell them it's better to record their music
somewhere else.
- But despite that... / - They still come.
So many insist they must record there.
Since it's meaningful.
That's why there are many young people
who bring money to Abbey Road.
There's a Korean movie called "Kundo."
The soundtracks of that movie were recorded there.
It was welcoming.
It's time for the first half vote.
London, Liverpool, JJ Tour.
Will you follow their plan to England?
Please vote.
(JJ Tour designed a new plan for the U.K.)
(What will the judges choose?)
We have the result of the first half.
We're not fazed.
- We're confident. / - Yes.
Here they are.
I don't feel too good about it.
Really?
I can't read Gikwang's face.
(They got more votes than the HighMan Tour)
Something is wrong.
This is shocking.
They can't understand why we got so many votes.
- Gikwang. / - Tell us what you think of it.
- About what? The result? / - Yes.
- Actually... / - We asked Gikwang.
You two are liars. We don't believe you.
Gikwang.
He's an innocent guy.
- Well, I... / - Look at us.
- How was it? / - Don't look at them.
You're surprised, aren't you?
- The result surprised me. / - I know.
So why did it surprise you?
- I don't know. / - What are you thinking?
I'm not sure about that.
- I didn't expect this result. / - It must be high.
Alright. Let's see if it's actually nice in Liverpool.
- The second half is important. / - Should we go?
Let's check it out with our own eyes.
Looking forward to statues of The Beatles and the club.
JJ Tour heads to Liverpool. Let's go.
- Wow. / - Wow, this...
This is nice.
The Beatles. They're awesome.
How about we make it a Beatles-themed tour?
Everyone loves the Beatles.
- Koreans love the Beatles too. / - Of course.
We're not going to Liverpool for the food.
We're going for The Beatles.
Finally, we're meeting The Beatles.
I feel emotional.
The Beatles aren't in the shot.
- Isn't it incredible? / - I respect them.
- Must be John Lennon glasses. / - I bought them.
(The Beatles Tour begins now)
We're in Liverpool.
The statue is donated by the owner
of the club.
It's really incredible.
(You can find The Beatles everywhere in Liverpool)
(It's their second morning in London)
(London Euston Station)
From now on,
I'm the guide of The Beatles Tour.
Your tour in London was so poorly planned
that I was very frustrated during the stay in London.
Really?
Today we're going to ride Virgin Trains.
It's like KTX in Korea.
If we take a car, it'd take about 4.5 hours.
It's like the distance between Seoul and Pohang.
It takes about 2 hours and 10 minutes by train.
So we're going to take the train.
Just like any other tickets,
we can buy them in person
but it's cheaper online.
Listen to me.
This man invented steam locomotives.
It's cheaper online so I already made
a reservation online.
- You did a good job. / - You can't do this, right?
- $31.70. / - I don't know how to use computers.
It must be cheaper to reserve online.
We're going to Liverpool to meet The Beatles.
Nice! The Beatles.
-  Hey, Jude  / - Nice.
Keeps repeating the same thing.
I like that melody.
- It's the best. / - He says he likes that melody.
- It departs at 11:07 a.m. / - 11:07?
I see Liverpool over there.
Liverpool Lime Station, preparing.
They must be getting the train ready.
It looks like a stock market.
- Everyone is looking at the board. / - Stock exchange...
- It's up. Liverpool. / - 14.
You have to keep watching?
The platform number pops up.
Can't you wait at the platform?
- But you don't know which platform. / - It doesn't say?
It tells you which platform to go to.
Let's go.
- It departs at 11:07 and arrives at 13:19. / - It's here.
Isn't that it?
- It looks like KTX, doesn't it? / - It does.
It'd be nice if we can meet someone in the train.
- Just like in the movies. / - Makes your heart flutter.
- You know what I mean. / - Like the movies...
Wondering who will sit beside me.
(Who else would it be?)
You're traveling together.
You look like you're wearing matching tops.
I feel like I've seen a couple like them.
We're now leaving London.
There are many parks and good hiking spots here.
But the sun and weather play a big part.
Personally, I don't like big cities.
- Same for me. / - Whatever the country...
- You live in Ilsan, right? / - Yeah.
- Whichever country it is, I like the outskirts. / - Yeah.
Anyway, let's forget about London now...
We're going to Liverpool.
There are so many places to visit in Liverpool.
Yeah?
- It's a pilgrimage. / - Right.
- As fans of The Beatles. / - Right.
You two both love music.
I think it's really nice that you two go on
a Beatles pilgrimage.
I'm hungry.
Wow.
We bought lunch at the train station.
You must try the local packed lunch when you travel.
- But eating on the train... / - The time flew by.
I felt sick.
Because the train was fast.
You guys think totally differently.
Things zoom by so fast...
You should eat before you ride the KTX as well.
(The Beatles pilgrimage course)
We are in Liverpool.
Liverpool gets its name...
- From brown pool. / - So pretty.
- Much nicer than Manchester. / - Yes.
That's why it's Liverpool.
- The water is brown. / - Really?
- The city looks pretty. / - This is cool.
Liverpool, so nice.
It looks even more exotic than London.
It has a very nice view there.
There aren't many skyscrapers.
Now we're in Liverpool...
Let's go find The Beatles.
Let's go. This way.
(In 1962, a rock band made a meteoric rise)
It's an American TV show from 1964,
"The Ed Sullivan Show."
In 1964, the Beatles go to the U.S. for the first time
to be on the TV show.
In the pop industry, it's the first British invasion.
The Beatles were so popular then
that there was a saying that anyone who has
a British passport can release albums in the U.S.
It was crazy.
(The Beatles pilgrimage course)
(The Beatles statue)
(15 minute walk from Lime Street Station)
Everything is nearby.
(Pier Head)
We're near the ocean so it's quite windy here.
- I see the statue. / - The Beatles statute.
The Beatles statute!
This song is called "Penny Lane."
It's the name of a street in Liverpool.
(Paul McCartney, George Harrison)
(John Lennon)
Which of them are still alive?
Paul McCartney and Ringo Starr are still alive.
There's a club called Cavern Club which we'll visit later.
That club donated these statues.
It shows their love for The Beatles.
So cool.
The statues match well with the cityscape.
They're in the middle of the street.
Finally, we meet The Beatles.
- We should take pictures. / - We're meeting them.
- I bet many people take pictures here. / - Yeah.
(They look somewhat awkward)
- We can't see The Beatles. / - We can't see them.
We're blocking them.
I don't think it'll work even if you had really long arms.
It was really hard.
- The statues were bigger than we thought. / - Right.
We're still blocking them.
We need The Beatles in our pictures.
- Let's take pictures separately. / - Separately?
Life is live together, die alone.
- You're alone. / - It means you're alone.
Alone...
(Strict individualism, separate but together)
The Beatles.
I feel emotional.
(He seems happy to see the statues)
So cool.
The rides only operate during the winter.
The Beatles Story.
This is the museum I talked about.
We're going to The Beatles museum.
- We're here. / - Is this the place?
The Beatles Story.
- It's a museum. / - Let's go meet them.
The whole city lives off The Beatles.
It's so nice.
I couldn't help but feel awe in there.
- John Lennon. / - His actual glasses?
(Everything that The Beatles touched)
(Let's look into their glorious history)
The Beatles museum.
This is the time... The 1940s.
It must play music.
Start.
(He pressed the start button)
(But he can't understand anything)
There's no Korean translation.
I can't hear anything.
Do you remember the thing we saw earlier?
Look. It's over there.
It must play audio
if you walk around with it.
Is it?
It translates to your language.
But there was no Korean translation anyway.
We can't use it anyway.
Wow.
They were really young then.
Ringo Starr.
George Harrison.
- John Lennon. / - Paul McCartney.
- When I saw the picture... / - Feels strange, right?
I felt emotional.
- This must be Port of Liverpool, right? / - Yeah.
(It's a picture of The Beatles at Port of Liverpool)
The Beatles were from the working class
so they weren't very well dressed.
Then their manager, Brian Epstein
dressed them up in nice suits.
That's when they gained popularity with the girls.
- They're fainting. / - Lots of fans fainting.
Look.
They actually fainted from heart attacks back then.
Abbey Road Studios.
(They went to Abbey Road in London)
We saw this in London.
It's the Abbey Road Studios we couldn't enter.
The studio is recreated here.
- The inside of the studio? / - Yes.
Back in those days.
The way they recorded in there.
They're really great singers.
Recording like that...
This is the recording studio.
Let's go down.
It's small, right?
That's where they recorded music.
It's really small.
They must have been like,
"That was an excellent job!"
(Sparkle)
- Mathew Street. / - The Beatles street.
This is the recreation of the street.
This is where we will visit later.
So this is the street.
Cavern.
- This must be Cavern Club. / - It looks like it.
This is where they held their first concert.
It's Cavern Club.
So this is how it looks.
It was smaller than we imagined.
Four people can't stand in a line there
because it's too narrow.
After the Beatles debuted,
the queue to the club became so long...
Since then, the number of girls who went to
record shops and asked for
The Beatles album grew.
So the owner of the album store wanted to know
who The Beatles were.
Why are they so sought after?
He went to Cavern Club, saw The Beatles
and signed a contract.
That was the manager of The Beatles, Brian Epstein.
He must've made so much money.
This place makes you feel a sense of respect.
- It makes you humble, right? / - It does.
(They somehow feel emotional)
This was The Beatles' private jet. Let's take a seat.
It's the recreation of The Beatles' private jet.
So this was The Beatles' private jet?
This is bizarre.
"Life vest under your seat" is written in Korean.
- What is that? / - So random?
- What the? / - Huh?
What's going on?
- Was it a Korean plane? / - The private jet?
- That looks strange. / - Isn't it strange?
- It's strange. / - It was really funny.
It's written in Korean?
- What's going on? / - It must've been a Korean jet.
What is this?
They must've taken those seats from an old Korean jet.
- Is it under the seat? / - Is this really their private jet?
(Doubt it)
- There's so much to see at the museum. / - There is.
Fans of The Beatles must visit there.
(14 minutes to Mathew Street from Beatles museum)
Here we are. Mathew Street.
This is Mathew Street.
This is it.
- The street we saw in the museum. / - Right.
Since this is the street of The Beatles,
all the shops here have pictures of The Beatles.
- This is my kind of street. / - It's nice.
John Lennon's bar.
- John Lennon's bar. / - What is that?
Look here.
John Lennon worked as a part-timer here.
Really? He worked part-time here?
How nice.
And this is...
(Music plays endlessly in the street)
(There's a statue next to him)
This is...
That's what's on John Lennon's famous solo album.
- It's his pose. / - The statue.
(Polite)
Jonghyuk, your head is smaller than his.
(He poses like John Lennon)
(Meeting John Lennon again, my head is smaller)
Please take one for me too.
(Hyungjun takes a picture with the statue as well)
You look better in the picture.
Did you try to take a good picture?
- Are you sure you tried to take a good one? / - Yeah!
- Is it weird? / - It looks half hearted.
Stand there. I'll take it again.
Stand there again...
(He ends up taking a selfie with the statue)
(Selfie is the best)
(It seems they found something)
Is there something there?
It's the hall of fame of people...
- That performed here on the bricks. / - Their names?
Amazing top stars were there.
There is Michael Jackson and other stars.
It's all amazing artists.
(JJ Tour is desperately looking for a name)
- The Beatles. / - The Beatle.
I see Rolling Stones too.
This is incredible.
- A historic site. / - It's amazing.
I'll have to go there.
- Is this the Cavern Club? / - Cavern Club.
The Beatles performed here...
For the first time as the Fab Four.
(They're at a Beatles shrine)
- Didn't you see this at the museum? / - Yes.
- Actual club. / - The real club now.
- Jonghyuk! / - Yeah.
This is the highlight of our tour.
We're at the Cavern Club.
We came to Liverpool to see this.
That's not an overstatement.
The Beatles performed for the very first time here.
Let's go.
Someone must be performing here.
- Performing live. / - That's right.
The atmosphere was so great when we went inside.
(This is the sacred place of the Beatles)
(The music of the Beatles is always on)
It's not a place for young people.
It's mainly for tourists and
high school alumni of The Beatles.
(The Beatles performed here for the first time)
I'm surprised that they have footage of this.
This would be 1961.
Their first show cost 5 pounds
but their final one cost 300.
That's impressive.
Everything you see is a museum.
I loved their beer there.
This is nice.
(Fascinated)
(Looking around)
It's similar.
- Similar to the museum, right? / - Yeah.
(Beatles museum)
(Cavern Club)
It's the same.
They built it the same.
Countless singers wanted to perform here.
Adele performed here in 2011.
- Really? / - Yeah.
Is there an entrance fee or is it free?
- There's an entrance fee. / - It's $5.80 per person.
It's not that expensive.
It must have positive energy.
It must be a live performance.
(What are they doing?)
(Familiar hairstyles are entering the stage one by one)
They wore wigs and entered the stage.
I didn't know at first.
They're a Beatles tribute band.
Their voices were so similar.
(Beatles tribute band)
- They seem similar. / - Yes.
They are.
Everyone is holding up their phones in the front.
(Big smile)
They're really like The Beatles.
(Approves)
(Bounce)
(Tapping to the rhythm)
(Even lazy Jonghyuk does his best to record them)
(The reaction of the performance was amazing)
(Bravo)
Does that band perform every day?
They also have a schedule.
You can see their schedule on...
- The Cavern Club website. / - They have their schedule.
(Even if time passed by, the emotions are the same)
(The emotional voices fill the club completely)
(The atmosphere is great)
He's feeling better after a beer.
(It's really heating up)
- It'd be so nice there with a beer. / - Ireland.
Ireland, Wales, asking where people are from...
- Where they're from. / - What about Korea?
Korea!
Korea! Korea!
- They didn't say Korea. / - Italy.
- North Korea! / - Korea.
- North Korea? / - You're from the north?
We were too pumped up.
- North Korea? / - Yeah, Korea!
- North Korea! / - Not us?
He's saying it's not us.
- They were joking, right? / - Of course.
I was wondering why they were staring.
- We wanted to stay there longer. / - Lots of people.
You could drink there all night long.
- It's a good memory for you. / - In front of the club...
There's a very famous line.
What it says is...
"Four lads who shook the world."
Four youths that shook the world.
- It's really famous. / - That's right.
(They walked 14 minutes to go to the beer brewery)
- The performance was amazing. / - Wasn't it?
That club must be really famous.
People from all around the world were there.
We've seen all of Liverpool if we've seen Cavern Club.
As you can see, they make their own beer here.
I'm drinking beer tonight.
That's all beer, right?
No one would know about that place.
I love it when beer comes out of the wall like that.
(It's not a faucet)
That seems fun to choose.
It felt nice because there was so much beer.
They kept updating it.
Continuously.
- A new beer each week. / - Wow, 12 different beers.
- You can taste them. / - Pale ale.
(You can try what you want)
Even if you taste all this,
it'd be like drinking two bottles.
Let's also try that one.
(They drink and drink)
Jonghyuk tasted so many of them.
I think he'll collapse after the tasting.
I wanted to try all of them.
Snacks.
The snacks are perfect.
So many variety of cheese.
They're all cheese.
- All cheese? / - They're all cheese?
- Please laugh for him. / - You'll get it eventually.
Right.
They're all cheese.
- That looks so good. / - It was good.
(Rooibos red ale, Peanut milk stout)
That looks delicious.
Cheers.
(Savoring)
The taste is unique.
It's my first time having dark beer.
It doesn't look delicious visually.
- Really? / - But it tastes really delicious.
It's unique.
The best way to describe it is that it's rich.
- Try other ones. / - Okay.
I was going to have a barrel of that.
But it's not ready yet.
Hi, long time no see.
Long time no see?
What did you have before?
Tropical imperial stout.
That looks strong.
Thank you.
(Drinking on the way to save time)
It's really good.
It's really good. I made a good choice.
- Is it different from mine? / - Yes, it's different.
Try it.
I brought dark beer. Try it.
- This is also different. / - Right?
- This is tropical. It's fruity. / - I want some.
I really mean it.
This has a heavy taste and this is lighter.
- Is it? / - The flavor.
This one's really good.
I couldn't tell from the dark color.
It's dark beer but it's tropical.
It's different from my last one.
- How is it all different? / - This is heavy.
They're all dark beer but different.
Guess which is your beer.
Give it here.
- Which one's mine? / - In case they don't believe us.
- Are the colors different? / - They're the same.
- Close your eyes. / - You're not mixing them, right?
Okay.
(Ta-da)
I really can't tell.
They're even the same in amount.
- Taste them and guess the beer. / - Really?
- Try finding yours. / - Will he find it?
He'll know when he tastes it.
(Jonghyuk, Hyungjun)
(Jonghyuk)
(He chooses his beer confidently)
Wait a minute.
- Why are you gargling with it? / - Try this one.
(He tries the other beer)
(Will Jonghyuk be able to differentiate the beer?)
(What do you think? Do you see the difference?)
He said his tastes good.
Can I try it again after rinsing my mouth?
He's a bit tipsy.
Don't rinse with more beer.
You said you thought yours was tropical.
(Hyungjun, Jonghyuk)
This one's yours. This is the tropical.
- He got it right. / - Right?
- You're a beer expert. / - Of course.
Our U.K. trip...
It was short but we spent the time really well.
People only think about London in the U.K.
A trip to Liverpool could sound different.
We met The Beatles here.
It felt like The Beatles were alive again.
And we watched their performance.
We even went to the Cavern Club.
I could see what it felt like when they performed.
I'm glad we came to Liverpool to see that.
It's an important place just with The Beatles.
And this trip... We were on the MK Tour
and now the JJ Tour.
I can see how good Minkyo was.
I realized that he prepared a lot for our trip.
Nevertheless, I don't think he would've
been a big help even if he was here.
There's nothing Minkyo can do here.
I feel bad for Minkyo though.
So I told him I was sorry we came without him
but he said he likes Thailand.
I talked to him on the phone.
He doesn't like the cold.
It's not so cold here.
Let's bring him on the next JJ Tour.
Since you're close, you must've missed Minkyo.
- Tomorrow... / - JJ Tour.
We had a good time in London thanks to you.
I enjoyed our trip in Liverpool.
I must admit the second half was great.
Do you have to pay to get into The Beatles museum?
It was a little over $20.
- But it's worth the money. / - It is?
What's the name of the town?
The museum is in Albert Dock.
There's a port there.
You know the movie, "Titanic."
It's the port where the Titanic departed from.
- Really? / - Yes.
There are big shopping malls around the port.
Things to buy and cafes to visit.
Even if you don't go into the museum...
- There's lots to see. / - Of course. So much.
It sounds nice. We should talk about the expenses.
Oh, the expenses.
Ours was really affordable. We didn't watch soccer.
Right.
How much did JJ Tour spend in Liverpool?
The whole trip, per person...
- Per person. / - Excluding the airline tickets.
You have to include the whole cost.
$500.30.
30 cents.
Because of the cost of the Manchester match.
That's the difference.
- Gikwang. / - Yes?
- It is money well spent. / - I know.
- You have to watch that match. / - Okay.
Let's hear their finals words
before the final vote.
Jonghyuk, you go first.
I guess some of you might not know The Beatles.
But those who have heard of their music
should go to Liverpool and take a look around there.
Then you'd feel the place is worth visiting.
- I highly recommend it. / - Alright then.
Would you go to Liverpool, England,
according to JJ Tour's plan? Please vote.
(JJ Tour designed a trip to Liverpool)
(What will the judges choose?)
If Jonghyuk just finished that burger...
- The trip would've cost a little over $100. / - Right.
- The prize is $500. / - You're right!
If you eat that burger...
- Save $300. / - You can visit Liverpool for $100.
Just finish that burger.
You're right.
One team will have their third straight win today.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay. / - Let's go.
Will it be the HighMan Tour that did everything
from great activities to eating great food.
Is it the Manchester trip to England?
They're the most influential band in history.
The legendary Beatles.
A pilgrimage to their home of Liverpool.
JJ Tour's trip to Liverpool, England?
What will the judges choose?
Why does this make me nervous?
- JJ. / - What is it?
- Let's go with 3 victories. / - What is this?
- JJ. / - 3 straight wins.
- Let's get 3 wins. / - HighMan!
The last digit first.
Here it comes.
Someone will get 3 wins.
- 7! / - What the?
It's the first digit.
- What's going on? / - What is this?
- It's similar? / - No!
- HighMan! JJ! Who is it? / - HighMan!
- HighMan! / - JJ!
(Manchester wins!)
(This guy doesn't get what happened)
- What happened? / - We lost.
- We lost. / - We lost.
- I can't believe I won. / - We lost!
What's going on?
He thought we won.
What were you looking at?
- It was this side... / - After the win...
Congratulations, Gikwang.
That's 3 straight wins for Yoon Dujun.
Yoon Dujun is a legend.
Yoon Dujun.
You lost by 2 votes...
- But you had fun, right? / - It's a shame.
I really wanted to visit Manchester
like Dujun did.
I'd really like to go back to England.
Will you go with Minkyo?
No, I'll go with Dujun who won 3 times.
- That would be better. / - Alright.
Taehun, you worked hard for 2 weeks.
How was it?
As I watched the two teams travel abroad,
I want to go off somewhere
since the weather is getting warmer.
So we've been on a unique trip
in England for the past two weeks.
And we will have a special episode next week again.
It's a huge special.
Make sure you tune in.
Look forward to the next episode.
The world is a school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
Thank you.
(Next episode)
I didn't know there's a place like this in Bali.
It's Penang in Malaysia.
Reset Tour. Put everything back.
Thrilling Tour.
It's so pretty.
- It's an interesting city. / - It really is.
It's fine because I'm with you.
True 100% Bali.
Why are we here? Photo of a lifetime.
It is pretty.
A place of romantic love.
Thank you for this unforgettable memory.
It was actually my fantasy.
(Battle Trip)
("MAMMA MIA" by SF9)