This really is a city of water.
This is amazing.
I feel like I'm falling deeper in love.
I was doing well with my diet...
You have to drizzle the olive oil like this.
(Ecstatic dishes of Venice)
I can't stop eating.
I seriously love this.
This is nice. I'm just happy right now.
Spain will lose to us.
Hello, Barcelona!
It's like all the delicious flavors put together.
I just got goose bumps.
This place is just insane.
It's heaven!
Adios!
(Barcelona won the first battle)
(Which team will win?)
Gourmet trip is also war.
Battle Trip!
(Lee Hwijae, Lee Wonil)
You look depressed, Sikyung.
Well, we just had the first match
between Venice and Barcelona
for the past 2 weeks.
And Barcelona in Spain won.
Yes, that's right.
- I think it was a cheap victory. / - Why?
Why do you think it's cheap?
For today, we've prepared something special.
We would love that.
We can't win this match...
Only with a video.
We don't want to lose again,
so we prepared something.
Where are we going this week?
It might sound unfamiliar.
It's the origin of ragu pasta...
The gourmet city and the city of gluttony.
Yes, it's Bologna.
- Bologna. / - We will...
- Show you. / - Okay.
Bologna is in Northern Italy.
It's a happy place for cooks.
It's an important transportation hub,
so all the good ingredients of Italy are gathered there.
That's why it's called...
- Bologna la grassa. / - La grassa.
That's what the city is called.
- It was a nice place. / - I see.
I can't wait to see Bologna.
Spain has its most popular dish.
- It's paella. / - Paella.
It's the city where paella was first made.
And Korea's proud soccer player,
Lee Kangin plays in that city.
That's right.
You can find oranges everywhere.
- It's everywhere. / - It really is.
We had freshly squeezed orange juice there.
It was the best orange juice I've ever had.
We went to...
- Valencia, Spain. / - Valencia?
This is part 2 of the gourmet trip.
The match between Valencia, Spain,
and Bologna, Italy, is about to begin.
Since this is a gourmet trip,
I'd like to ask you why you chose those cities.
When you go to Bologna,
you can try the best quality foods
at reasonable prices there.
The city is very close
to Firenze which is famous for its beef
and Parma is right next to there.
So they get good beef and cheese.
And there's Modena.
- Balsamic. / - It's the origin of balsamic.
There are places like that,
so all the good ingredients go to Bologna.
So you can eat delicious foods
at low prices.
So you went there to have some vinegar?
We also had vinegar.
- I see. / - Yes.
We did.
And there's spaghetti Bolognese.
It's the basic pasta dish with beef and tomato sauce.
It sounds good.
This city is where it started.
I was surprised.
"So this is what it tastes like."
I think this episode will be a match between...
The paella of Valencia and ragu pasta of Bologna.
You said Valencia is the origin of paella.
That's right. We are familiar with seafood paella.
It usually has mussel and shrimp in it.
We tried paella at the restaurant
where it was originated.
Guess what is in the paella.
Is it different?
You will see for yourself.
It has very unique ingredients in it.
I think I know what it is.
It's very unique.
It's not only that.
Valencia is the home
of traditional Spanish dessert.
Dessert!
We can say all the famous desserts of Spain
started in this city.
Traditional bread, beverages and even snacks.
You can taste the original there.
It's the best place for a gourmet trip.
With us, there's coffee.
- Coffee? / - You can find good coffee in Italy.
I realized that Italy has really good espresso.
- I see. / - Since we lost last week...
I'd like to promote a little more.
I had the best steak of my life there.
It's meat?
Sikyung, I heard you cooked it for yourself.
We have to win this time.
I can't lose again like this.
It wasn't fair for the past 2 weeks.
We will also...
- Commit a small foul this time. / - Okay.
- Without getting ejected. / - Alright.
We will look forward to the best steak.
And we have this corner inside corner again.
Sook's Choice.
So far,
the best dish in my heart
is arroz caldoso.
On my way home, I thought
I really want to try it.
I hope we will have the best dishes today.
And Sook's Choice will continue.
Alright. We will go to Bologna, Italy first.
Please take a look at the menu first.
The menu has the dishes they had.
- It looks familiar. / - I've heard of panini before.
- Wine is here again. / - Panini is a kind of bread.
Three bottles of wine.
- Right, wine continues. / - Panini.
What is tortellini?
- Tortellini. / - That's like Italian dumpling.
You either mix it with sauce or eat with soup.
It's similar to Korean food yet has a unique scent.
It was pretty unique dumpling.
It's a dumpling...
- But with meat and cheese. / - Cheese?
When you take a bite, you taste meat and cheese.
- It's ricotta cheese. / - Yes.
- It must be really good. / - It must be really good.
Don't you feel hungry after seeing the menu?
- Yes. / - I'm hungry.
We have something prepared.
(Special food for the guests)
We prepared something...
I can't even talk. My mouth is already watering.
- Here we go. / - What is it?
Please bring the food.
- It's ice cream. / - What is that?
- What is that? / - Is that shaved ice?
(Bologna balsamic vinegar and sweet ice cream)
(Bologna's special dessert, balsamic ice cream)
- Thank you for this. / - Enjoy it.
It smells...
(Balsamic ice cream has a unique scent)
Is it a smell of vanilla?
- Why is it so good? / - It's so good.
- It's awesome. / - Is it caramel?
- It has a caramel scent. / - Yes.
I think I know.
- Sweet and sour? / - It's sweet and sour.
- It tastes even fresher. / - Right.
- It tastes really strange. / - It's so good.
It tastes like vinegar at first, then it tastes sweet.
- Doesn't it look good? / - And the caramel bursts.
- On the top of it... / - I want to have it too.
This isn't chocolate on the top.
I think it's caramel, vanilla...
And vinegar.
- Vinegar? / - Vinegar?
- Yes, it has the vinegar scent. / - Right.
It's a good mixture of the three.
It's really good when they're mixed.
- Sook. / - Is this a dessert?
Yes, it's a dessert.
Gosh.
- I'm so curious... / - Right.
- That I must hurry. / - Okay.
Paradise of gourmet, Bologna.
Let's go together.
(The trip to Bologna begins)
Wow, is that it? I feel like I'm in Italy now.
This really is the city of water.
It totally feels like Italy.
- Italian cuisine is simple. / - That's right. That dish!
- Oh, this one... / - I can't stop eating.
I have to be careful.
Honestly, it's so good.
It's good. It's so good.
It's so romantic.
It's overflowing with love.
It's nice being here with you.
Honey, I'll take a picture of you.
I can't help that it's good.
This really is romantic.
That was so funny.
Bromance.
In terms of food...
How about Bologna?
Koreans aren't familiar
with Bologna.
- Bologna is... / - No, we don't.
- We only know Bolognese sauce. / - Right.
It's the origin of meat sauce.
But Italians say
it's one of the best gourmet city.
There are a few places. First, it has good nature.
It's a fertile region since there are
mountains and fields.
We often go to Venice and Firenze.
It's between the two cities.
Seriously.
It's also a transport hub.
It receives various ingredients from other regions.
They do produce their own ingredients
but since they have a lot of exchange,
their recipes and food culture are more developed.
Bologna sounds good.
I think it's meaningful to visit Bologna
for a gourmet trip.
- I'm going to gain so much weight. / - Yes.
It's called Bologna la grassa, the city of gluttony.
- It's amazing. / - That steak looks awesome.
They support each other.
Wait. It's too much.
This is so good.
The ingredients support each other.
They mix, blend and complete.
- What should I do with that? / - It must the sauce.
It has really nice smell.
It will be totally different to Venice.
(The city of gluttony, Bologna)
- This looks so good. / - That?
It's sour, bitter and sweet.
Can I lick my plate? Amazing.
I can't wait to find out the one Sikyung cleaned.
(Ecstatic gourmet food makes them lose it)
- It's here. / - It's good.
It's not for the show. I'm truly happy.
(We Will Eat Tour in Bologna, Day 1)
Gourmet city?
(We Will Eat Tour in Bologna, Day 2)
(A new journey awaits in the morning in Venice)
That vibe.
(It's full of people starting their day)
(We Will Eat Tour visits the train station)
- Did you have a good sleep? / - I did.
- Today, we're heading to... / - Yes.
Europe has a good train system.
We're going to Bologna by train.
Bologna is called Bologna la grassa.
- Bologna la grassa. / - The city of gluttony.
Because it's a gourmet city?
- It's my city. / - Okay.
(Sweet Bologna is my city)
So I wore the pig color.
- Pink. / - It's the ham color.
- "Ham color." / - "Ham color."
- It's my city. / - Okay.
(Laughing)
Let's find out why it became the city of pigs.
Apparently their food is really good.
We haven't had ragu pasta, meat sauce yet.
We're going to have it there.
- Bologna. / - Let's go in.
(Train ticket, $32.50 per person. Passport is needed)
(We Will Eat Tour heads to Bologna leaving Venice)
(Italy)
(1.5 hours by train from Venice to Bologna Station)
(The city of red roofs, Bologna)
They have a different type of architecture.
(The city of love, Bologna)
- It's the city of love. / - How wonderful.
The men all look handsome.
Oh, my.
Don't you think we make more physical contact now?
We've been through a lot together.
We've been through so much.
Now, this is
Bologna Centrale. A railway station.
We're going to start...
- At the square here. / - Okay.
The square is close this way.
Let's walk to the square.
(Gourmet city's alleyways)
We were late in the morning for the train.
I have no energy because I haven't had coffee.
- We need to drink coffee straight. / - Yes.
- How about some coffee? / - Coffee.
So many places sell coffee.
I'm not pretending to be European.
I just feel like it in the morning.
Right. You crave for coffee in the morning in Europe.
That place looks like a cafe.
I know.
Shall we check it out?
We'll get a cup of coffee.
See? You can smell coffee.
Don't you smell coffee every time...
- You walk down the street? / - Yes, you're right.
Especially in Italy.
(You can't miss coffee at the start of the day)
We just went to a cafe in front of the hotel.
- It was unplanned. / - I see.
That's why we're filming it.
- And it's still good. / - How does it taste?
It's strong.
(They smell the strong coffee)
(The two drink together)
(Good)
Anywhere you go, it's above average.
(Coffee is good everywhere you go in Italy)
(He takes one more sip since it's good)
(Satisfied)
In Italy, they drink espresso a lot
but they also drink a lot of cappuccino.
When they want something lighter,
they drink cappuccino.
(A cup of light cappuccino like the locals)
(20-minute walk from Bologna Centrale to the square)
- I feel awake now. / - The scent lingers in my mouth.
It feels great.
(Smacking his lips)
(We Will Eat Tour takes a walk in Bologna)
(He's feeling good)
The buildings are pretty.
I like that brick building.
This one too.
(Everything looks nice and pretty on the trip)
Almost all buildings were like that.
We didn't have to worry about rain.
All the buildings in the city have extra space
for these arched roofs.
- Oh, that's right. / - There's a roof over all walkways.
You don't need to worry even in the rain.
- It's nice and cozy. / - You won't need umbrellas.
(The corridor connects Bologna city endlessly)
It's beautiful.
It's really beautiful.
- The ceiling is so pretty. / - I know, right?
I know it sounds obvious but it feels different.
It's big that there's no water.
It's beautiful.
(The center of the Bologna tourism)
(Piazza Maggiore)
Are there many tourists?
There are many European tourists, Italian tourists.
Italians from other regions come to travel.
I didn't see that many Asians.
- Because we don't... / - It's same for Valencia.
- Really? / - I barely met Asians in Valencia.
There were none. We only met one Korean.
We didn't meet any Koreans at all.
- None in Bologna? / - No.
When we pass there,
we'll see a cathedral.
It's the 5th largest cathedral in the world.
The pope at the time said, "Hey."
"Don't go overboard."
So they couldn't build it bigger.
Even though they stopped building,
it's still the 5th largest one.
After we pass here...
They tried to build the biggest...
- Then the pope didn't want it. / - It's huge.
(Exclaiming)
- It's a cathedral? / - It's unbelievably big.
But it looks very weird.
(Basilica di San Petronio)
- That's a cathedral? / - That's a cathedral?
They didn't finish the wall.
The top and the bottom look different.
It's surprisingly huge
when you see it, standing right there.
(Designed to be bigger but reduced due to budget)
How is that built by men?
Is that...
- All of that? / - That's all cathedral.
I can tell they stopped in the middle.
They could've made the top...
Fancy like the bottom but they didn't.
So I would say I know the half of it
but not the other half.
It's really huge.
It's unbelievable.
It's quite charming.
It's still used as a cathedral.
Seriously?
It's the size of a baseball stadium.
It can seat up to 28,000 people.
How do they come out?
The cathedral is the size of a baseball stadium?
- That's unbelievably big. / - That's huge.
(What's the next schedule after enjoying history?)
Basilica di San Petronio.
Since we've seen the grand cathedral...
Now that we're in Bologna...
We need to tour every alley.
Alleyways of Bologna is the real deal.
It'd be very different from Venice.
Yes, I can already see it in the distance.
It feels different.
That patio is pretty nice.
Let's check it out.
Sounds good.
(Cathedral)
Oh, wow.
Nice.
The color is nice.
It's different from the alleys in Venice.
- It's pretty. / - It's different.
- It's amazing. / - It's awesome.
I loved the alley right next to it.
- What is that? / - That's the ingredient market.
Every alley is a specialty store.
- It's all ham and cheese. / - Ham and cheese.
Seafood.
It's not just a market but there are cafes too.
(They even have a food walking tour here)
- It's so pretty. / - It's so pretty.
- It's all very small. / - In Bologna...
Food walking tours are very popular.
When you walk down the street,
you can see a group of 3 or 4 people.
And the person holding a flag
speaks English with an Italian accent
and describes everything.
What's good and why you eat it this way.
- They're all on a food tour? / - Yes.
- I want to go there. / - I don't need those ingredients...
- But I want to buy them. / - For real.
Yeah.
(When you go further inside the alley)
(There's an outdoor market with fresh ingredients)
(Sweet)
Looks so fresh.
Zucchini.
This is really nice. Spring onion.
I'm happy.
We'll be happy if we have our newlywed home here.
You guys aren't married yet?
I thought you did last week.
It's such a wonderful market.
You can buy it here and eat it with bread.
Look. They buy bread here.
That looks like a hidden delicious restaurant.
Let's go eat. I can't take it anymore.
This looks pretty nice. This is nice.
Shall we take a look?
(It's unplanned but they enter because it looks nice)
(You can try various food at this hidden spot)
- Goodness. / - What is that?
- That looks good. / - That looks good.
(It's packed with locals)
- It looks nothing special. / - Yes.
- But you must not miss it. / - It was good.
It's fun to eat on the street.
- That looks good. / - It's Wonil's favorite.
I wanted to say, "Everything from here to here."
Everything from here to here. All of it.
Hey, I can't take it anymore.
We need to go eat now.
You need to eat there first.
- It's got to be good. / - Oh, my.
Mozzarella and prosciutto.
(Agony)
- "Agony." / - Gosh, what is that?
Because we were on the way to eat.
We're having bread on the way to eat.
We were contemplating whether to eat or not.
- Bread digests fast as you walk. / - Yes.
- It's hard. / - How about we share one?
- Shall we get one each? / - No, it's filling.
We can finish it at night then.
Let's try it.
- Sure. / - One bread per person.
We should get a glass of white wine.
- Wine. / - That wine was also good.
(They place an order with the staff's recommendation)
So, pretty much every place sells wine?
Because it's considered a beverage.
- A beverage? / - You don't drink to get drunk.
- It's a beverage. / - Wine helps the food...
Go down smoothly.
(Prosciutto and mozzarella on top of rucola)
- That's awesome. / - Awesome.
Guys. That's my favorite ham.
- Mortadella. / - That one.
- I'm wearing that ham color. / - Yes.
(Lettuce and pecorino cheese on top of mortadella)
And pecorino made with sheep milk.
- Pecorino? / - Pecorino cheese.
- Pecorino cheese. / - It's really good.
It's really good when it's grilled.
- That looks like banh mi. / - That looks good.
- I know. / - That one...
Those sandwiches were nothing special
but they were really good.
- It feels like Chelsea Market. / - Yes.
Salute.
It's nice. It's refreshing and relaxing.
(Let me take a sip)
- It's not that strong. / - No.
That's unique. A shop in the market sells
food and wine.
That ham looks really good.
It's good.
That corn sandwich is really good.
- I want to try it. / - It looks really good.
- Is it good? / - Yes.
It's good.
It makes me crave for pasta.
- Pasta. / - It's an appetizer.
The harmony of the three.
Salty ham, not salty cheese and rucola.
This is less salty ham and saltier cheese...
- And lettuce. / - With watery vegetable.
The bun is really good.
Bread, ham and cheese.
It's like rice, kimchi and soup in Korea.
I was going to leave some but I can't.
You should talk.
Talk about what? I'm eating.
You need to eat if it's good.
No words necessary for good food.
Is that an appetizer
before the meal?
- Yes. / - Wasn't intentional.
It's antipasti.
With an aperitif?
(The glass of wine enhances the flavor)
It's perfect with wine.
It's really good.
- It's really good. / - It was a good choice to eat.
(They finish the sandwich and wine as their antipasti)
- Aren't you hungry? / - Yes, I am.
Also, this is Bologna.
You know about the food.
What comes to your mind about Bologna?
In English.
- Kimchi stew? / - Like kimchi stew. It's red.
- Bolognese. / - Yes.
Bolognese means "Bologna's."
Bologna's sauce.
We need to go try that sauce.
We've been holding back.
Yes. We didn't eat on purpose.
We didn't try tomato sauce in Venice.
We've been holding back with appetizers.
- Lead the way. / - Let's go eat pasta.
Let's go have ragu.
(Off they go without hesitating)
(We Will Eat Tour in Bologna, Day 1)
(Bolognese pasta)
Right, you must try it.
(11-minute walk from the alley to the restaurant)
We must try this.
(We Will Eat Tour is seduced by a grocery store)
Arancini.
I was curious to try everything.
- Look. / - You can't go eat?
No, there's so much food on the way.
Even before we reach the restaurant... This is bad.
One arancini and that's... Two maybe. Little bit.
(2 arancini, $6.76)
You know arancini, right? Deep fried rice.
- Deep fried rice. / - Deep fried rice and cheese.
- Cheese and rice. / - That's awesome.
These are artichokes pickled in vinegar and olive oil.
It's very soft.
(They have the artichoke like a pickle)
I could eat 12 of these.
(Agreed)
Let's eat.
(They're eating without a break)
- That looks so good. / - Did you see the cheese stretch?
- So-so? / - So-so?
It's just good.
(Whatever they eat, it's all good)
(It's good)
They haven't had the meal yet, right?
We're going to have pasta now.
- On the way. / - They keep eating on the way.
You can't help getting fat.
(They can't stop eating)
Let's go to the restaurant already. Carry it.
(He can't stop eating)
Let's go.
(Let's go have lunch now)
- Is it here? / - Yes. On your left.
It's the meat sauce spaghetti we've been waiting for.
Yes. In other countries, they call it meat sauce.
Other places in Italy call it Bolognese.
- In Bologna, they call it... / - Ragu.
Ragu.
Let's go in.
(They enter with excitement)
- Is that it? / - Yes, that's ragu.
(The original Bolognese pasta they've been waiting for)
You know what?
Koreans are familiar with Bolognese spaghetti.
Spaghetti is normally consumed in the south.
In the city of ragu, Bologna,
you must try tagliatelle.
Let's have tagliatelle. What does it look like?
Knife-cut noodles.
That place has been open for over 50 years.
- It's a time-honored restaurant. / - Look at that.
- Raw pasta. / - It's raw pasta.
They make pasta and cut it every morning.
- It must be really good. / - They make tagliatelle.
- It had a thick egg scent. / - It's so much effort.
- It was very good. / - The pasta was yellow.
- Because of the good quality eggs. / - Look so good.
That's it.
(Fresh pasta with egg)
They don't bring them from a factory.
They make the dough themselves.
(The fresh pasta is mixed with the ragu sauce)
Don't do that, don't.
Don't do this to me.
- Look at the tomato oil. / - Gosh, that's crazy.
(Bolognese pasta, $18.20)
Gosh, I don't know. I'll put this up.
It looks so good.
After seeing how it's cooked, I have to move it up.
(Fresh pasta mixed with the ragu sauce)
It's not tomato paste sauce.
Crushed tomato is mixed in with olive oil.
It's mixed with grease from meat.
- The oil becomes red. / - Right.
Like chili oil.
(Sikyung takes a bite first)
How is it?
It's so good.
(He grunts because it's so good)
The pasta is so good.
(He continues to marvel at it)
The locals line up there for lunch.
It's not just Koreans.
I've had this before.
- It's so good. / - Right?
How should I describe this?
- What should I do? / - How do you make this?
I don't know.
(He can't think)
It's so good.
How can I describe this?
This is driving me crazy.
The pasta is fresh.
It's tender and chewy.
I thought I was eating omasum.
(He's truly amazed)
This is so good.
It's like thinly sliced fried scrambled egg
and also like knife-cut noodles.
Thinly sliced fried scrambled egg snaps.
Knife-cut noodles are very chewy.
This feels right in the middle.
It's bouncy but very thin.
I can kind of feel the starchiness. It's chewy.
(The texture of the pasta brings out the flavor)
That pasta looks so delicious.
It's not thick. It's so thin.
It was so good that I got flustered.
- I really want to try it. / - How could the pasta taste...
- Stop it. / - No.
Seriously.
You have an old friend who makes amazing pasta.
That's better than his pasta.
- Goodness. / - The pasta...
(You can only taste it in Bologna)
It's so good.
- The pasta and sauce are both good. / - So good.
(Joonwoo's tip, drizzle olive oil over the pasta)
It's like adding vinegar to cold noodles.
You sprinkle like this.
(Sprinkle Parmesan cheese over Bolognese pasta)
I want to try it with Parmesan cheese.
Gosh. Wait.
(He doesn't want to cut the pasta)
What am I doing?
(Happy)
I'll sprinkle some cheese.
(Sprinkling Parmesan cheese)
(Excited)
It tastes so good with that.
The pasta is so tasty.
(Olive oil and Parmesan cheese make it even better)
In Korea, it's half meat and half sauce.
- It's like soup. / - It's American style.
Meat sauce in Korea is
tomato sauce...
- With ground meat. / - With ground meat.
But with ragu,
meat is the main thing.
It's meat with tomato flavor.
I wonder what it tastes like.
(How about going to Italy to taste the original?)
(Next dish is tortelloni)
It smells amazing.
(He's already excited)
Gosh, they're really good.
I think...
Lovelyz would faint if they tried this.
- I want to faint. / - Dumplings.
- What's that? / - What is it?
- What is it? / - It's tortelloni. Big ones.
Tortelloni. It's like dumpling.
(Tortelloni, $18.20)
The wrapping is carbohydrate.
- Inside is cheese. / - Goodness.
The sauce is...
- Butter. It's mixed with butter. / - Goodness.
(Stop it)
Please make it.
- Seriously. / - Can we skip Valencia next week?
(Is Hwijae's team giving up?)
(Inside the tortelloni is cheese)
That looks really good.
The food ingredients reached their full potential.
That's how they eat it in that region.
It's the perfect basics.
Basically, they're dumplings.
They're dumplings.
When you look at Italian pasta...
When you look at the menu,
you find names that are slightly different
from what you know.
For example,
tortellini and tortelloni.
With "ini" at the end,
it means "small."
With "oni" at the end,
it's bigger than "ini."
So I'm like Sung Sikyungoni.
Right. You'd be Sung Sikyungoni.
- Kim Sook would be Kim Sookini. / - Yes.
- Sung Sikyungoni. / - It's "ini" vs. "oni."
(Let's eat it now)
I'm curious.
It's delicious but it's not expensive.
The smell alone is a pass.
(Sighing)
That must be really good.
(Unbelievable)
If Sikyung does that, that means it's really good.
I'll take down this from last week.
Tortelloni.
Guys, thank you
for letting us win last week.
They added a lot of eggs in the pasta.
It's really tasty.
(Tortelloni pasta with a lot of eggs)
It's a dumpling that's slightly hard.
It's less steamed dumpling.
The texture is very similar to the dumpling we know.
(Similar to less steamed dumpling)
What's inside?
- Is it cheese? / - Ricotta cheese.
It's like tofu.
It has better texture.
It lingers longer on your tongue.
It doesn't disappear. It lingers.
It's like eating real cheese.
In Korea, ricotta is like cream.
(The cheese flavor lingers in your mouth)
- Gosh. / - Goodness.
- I want to try it. / - That's butter.
- Think how tasty it'd be. / - The color is so pretty.
They don't sell this in Korea, do they?
People don't make this menu a lot in Korea.
(It's hard to find in Korea)
People usually make pasta with a lot of sauce.
- Please make it. / - But these two...
- Can make it. / - We can.
- We can do it. / - We can.
- We can do it. / - They can.
We'll go to your restaurant.
I own a Western restaurant.
So you can come to mine.
- Come to my restaurant. / - We will. For sure.
You can come to mine for Korean cuisine.
We'll fill out our first evaluation in Bologna.
(Reviews based on location, price, ambience)
(They write about their recommended dish)
I commented,
"The best ragu fresh pasta."
"You've probably never tasted this.
You'll feel like you've been fooled all this time."
"Both the pasta and sauce are the best."
This pasta...
Nobody would hate it.
It's so chewy.
(Yummy)
(Average score for Bolognese pasta, 4.25 stars)
- That looks really good. / - I really want to try it.
How do you know which restaurant is good?
I walk around
and find restaurants with a lot of old customers.
Whenever I go to that kind of restaurant,
I never fail.
Old local couples
go there to have a meal.
- So that restaurant can't fail. / - That's a great tip.
(The day in Bologna comes to an end)
So far...
- I love Bologna. / - Isn't it nice?
It's been great since the start.
I found a place that'll end our day
in Bologna with a bang.
It's a place where Bolognese hipsters go.
It's a cost-effective restaurant that young people go to.
- For hipsters. / - Yes.
Clearly, I'm not a hipster.
Don't say that.
Come on. You're a hipster.
Aren't I a hamster?
I'm sorry.
Maybe.
We can try traditional Bolognese food.
And,
the thing you like.
Mortadella.
(Italian traditional food and mortadella)
- We'll eat that. / - Nice.
White wine?
You can have white wine or beer.
(He's drooling just thinking about it)
- That's good. / - I'm happy just thinking about it.
Looking at Sikyung,
I already know it's delicious.
(We Will Eat Tour's dinner menu)
(Something for a cold evening)
(Warm Italian traditional dumpling soup)
(Assorted Italian hams on a plate)
(Wine can't be left out for dinner)
(They try the wine first)
We need to taste this region's wine.
Of course.
(A bottle of white wine, $22.10)
It's light. It's perfect aperitif.
(Perfect wine for aperitif)
It's fun to have wine.
- Going to different regions. / - In Korea, you need...
To pay $40 or $50 per bottle...
- If you go to a restaurant. / - Right.
This is only 17 euros.
- For one bottle. / - $25.
(It's nice to be able to enjoy wine without pressure)
Italian wine doesn't overpower Italian food.
You can continue to enjoy it with food.
(The food is here)
(It makes his jaw drop)
What did you do?
It's like we're at a butcher shop.
Wow. Thank you.
This looks good.
Yes, it looks good. I'm drooling.
But it's so much.
That ham.
What? They gave you so much ham.
It's a ham platter.
(Salami and mortadella)
- That was amazing. / - It was only $13.
It's cheap.
I want to try that ham.
Seriously.
This is salami.
It's very famous in Italy.
Salami...
- Salami picante. / - Picante.
There's salami.
(Cured sausage made of fermented meat)
(Salame Picante is spicy salami)
(Mortadella is a half-dried sausage made in Bologna)
- That's the delicious one. / - That one.
That's the original Bologna sausage.
It looks like the sausage I had back in the day.
Spain has jamon and Italy has prosciutto.
- Prosciutto. / - Mortadella.
(Mortadella, prosciutto, salami picante, salami)
Prosciutto.
(They taste one at a time)
It's not salty.
- It's delicious. / - My hands got all greasy.
- It doesn't taste like salami. / - It's better...
- To eat them with hands. / - Right.
Does it taste good without bread?
Yes, it's not salty.
(Satisfied)
Mortadella is famous here.
(Mortadella is Bologna's typical ham)
We know the flavor because
it's sold in department stores now.
But this is high quality.
It's moist.
- They add the innards of the pig. / - Right.
It's completely ground up.
- This is less salty... / - Yes.
Compared to the others.
This has a short shelf life. You need to eat it quickly.
(Flavored with ground black pepper and pistachios)
Salami we had before were
fermented and air-dried.
But with this, ground meat is boiled once.
It's cooled down then cut.
- That's why it's so tender. / - Yes, it's very tender.
I'll try it.
(First, you cut a bun in half)
Add some olive oil.
My favorite...
Mortadella.
- Mortadella. / - Add this.
(Add the meat you like)
Add a bit of black pepper.
(Add olive oil or black pepper)
I'm excited.
When you cut marinated crab in half and eat it whole...
- That's luxury. / - Yes.
This is like that.
Luxury.
I'm excited.
It's crunchy.
It's good.
Cheers.
(The taste makes you think of beer)
- This is how you clink beer? / - Yeah.
They have various kinds of beer.
They pressed down on the dough and baked it.
So the outside is very crisp.
- That's so delicious. / - The inside is so moist.
It's really interesting.
It's kind of like baked Chinese bread.
It's kind of like sugar stuffed pancakes too.
- It must be very dense. / - Yes.
(The rice cake like bread goes well with ham)
This isn't work for me. I'm so happy. I really like this.
I can make...
A sandwich however I like.
I can have it with my favorite beer and wine.
That's nice.
- Wonil, you're giving in. / - Yes.
This is getting to you.
This is hard. They're going overboard today.
Wait. I... I need...
Excuse me. Oops, what am I saying?
(Urgent)
What?
(What's wrong?)
I'm going to order this.
- I want to put just this. / - Really?
One plate of mortadella.
- Just mortadella? / - Yes, just mortadella.
- More? / - Did he order more?
It's so good.
- For you, guys. / - Thank you.
- Enjoy. / - Thank you.
- Here it is. / - Let's just let go.
Here it is, here it is.
- Like this. / - I'm going to get fat.
(He can't stop smiling)
Who said Italian food was healthy?
(What will it taste like?)
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
It was so good. I couldn't just eat that little.
Mortadella.
Let's just let go.
He ordered just that.
- He made up his mind. / - I'm going to get fat.
(He can't stop smiling)
Who said Italian food was healthy?
This is healthy, there's no butter.
But you used so much olive oil.
(Sprinkling generously)
(Adding mortadella on top)
You've let go.
- He's let go. / - He wasn't drunk. He just let go.
How many slices did you add?
- Did you just add that? / - Yes.
(It looks so good)
(The sandwich looks delicious)
(It's tender)
It's super tender.
You need to add a lot.
I told you...
- That I was going to cheat today. / - Yes.
I'll give you mortadella later.
- Thank you. / - He said he prepared those.
- The dumpling? / - No. The ham.
I don't know what it is
but I'll move mortadella up higher.
He ordered more because it was so delicious.
(Next dish is being served)
- Are those dumplings? / - Yes.
(Tortellini, $13)
The broth is very clear.
So it soothes the stomach from a hangover.
- What's inside? / - Meat and cheese stuffing.
We call this Italian dumpling soup.
- But there's a unique difference. / - What's that?
(How is it different from Korean dumpling soup?)
- The broth is clear. / - Yes.
Korean dumpling soup is thick.
We add dumplings in the broth and boil them.
- They pour it later. / - They boil the dumplings...
And pour the broth separately.
That's the difference.
- I'll try it first. / - Okay.
(Yummy)
It's Western soup.
- This is good. / - It's sweet.
What we had earlier was
like side dish for the alcohol.
- This is like a meal. / - It warms you up.
It'll taste good on a rainy day.
- Is it cheese inside? / - I think cheese and meat.
This is salty for the Korean palate.
I've never had tiny dumplings like these.
Tortellini. It looks like a belly-button.
(They add a little bit of ground black pepper)
- It's like fishcake soup. / - Yes.
This is the magic of black pepper.
People who don't like foreign food...
- Will like this. / - Yes.
- It feels Korean. / - Right.
- With black pepper, it's... / - Even more Korean.
That's crazy.
- I love soup. / - Yes.
(Average score for dinner in Bologna, 4.4 stars)
4.4 stars. That's high.
With that ham, bread, and wine...
I would eat nonstop.
- That's undeniable. / - Right.
Tomorrow is the last day, isn't it?
It is the last day. Time flies.
I have like a pimple here.
- Why? / - I think I'm tired. I'm so upset.
(The body is expressing that it's old)
All I had was stamina.
Now I have no stamina...
No wife.
(The night in Bologna feels extra lonely tonight)
(The second day in Bologna breaks)
(Bologna Centrale)
It's the highlight of day 2 in Bologna.
We'll go to a balsamic vinegar farm.
We'll go to Modena.
What's good about Bologna is,
if we have enough time there...
There is Modena near it.
Modena is a place where they produce
balsamic vinegar.
If we have time, we can drive there
or take a train there.
We can drive there or take a train there.
We can taste great vinegar.
How about it?
Sounds great.
(Mission success!)
You can make a tour reservation.
Booking.
This is very professional.
(Balsamic vinegar tour is popular among the locals)
That looks like fun.
- I learned a lot from that farm. / - Right.
There's a balsamic tour.
We can rent a car but that's expensive.
There is a train every 15 minutes.
It takes about 20, 25 minutes.
- That's not far. / - Most tourists take the train.
True, renting a car is expensive.
So we'll take a train.
Let's go.
(Train from Bologna to Modena, $5)
(Aceto balsamico means fragrant vinegar)
(It's known for salad dressing)
(And it's used for plate decoration)
(Balsamic vinegar)
(Even a few drops are enough to change the flavor)
It's amazing, adding a few drops in risotto.
(The ingredient itself makes it real gourmet)
(To the origin of balsamic vinegar, Modena!)
(We Will Eat Tour in Bologna, Day 2)
(The origin of balsamic vinegar)
(Bologna Centrale, Modena station)
(Balsamic vinegar farm)
- We're in Modena. / - Yes.
Don't you smell it already?
Yes, it has that sour smell.
Unfortunately, the harvesting season is over.
We can't see the grapes.
They produce grapes themselves
and make vinegar.
(Oak barrels that have been used since 1512)
(There's Pierce Brosnan's personal balsamic vinegar)
Pierce Brosnan loved it so much
that he has his own barrel.
- Oh, my. / - There's also Mark Zuckerberg.
It's not a winery but "balsaminery."
- It's similar to maturing wine. / - Yes.
Is that him over there?
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. Hi. / - You too.
- Thank you. / - So, this is your farm?
This is my farm.
- He was very kind. / - We make...
Traditional balsamic vinegar here.
- Pleasure to meet you. / - Okay.
(Balsamic vinegar farm tour, $13 per person)
You can apply for a tour on their homepage,
and it's only 10 euros per person.
- Wine? / - That's grape juice.
It was sour down there
but it smells sweeter as we go up.
It smells like sherry wine.
(What kind of place is this?)
It smells very nice.
(Balsamic vinegar maturing cellar)
- It smells really nice. / - It smells very sweet.
Good.
(It's obvious that these barrels are very old)
For this production,
they cut the grapes, pressed, squeeze out the juice.
The only white grape I can use is Trebbiano.
- Trebbiano. / - It's a kind of grape.
For red, only Lambrusco.
Then the juice is cooked for about...
The only difference from wine is that it's boiled once.
It's boiled down.
You put the juice in the barrel.
(Pour boiled grape juice in the barrel and mature)
And through an observation process,
the cooked juice is transformed
into traditional balsamic vinegar.
It's important...
- In Korea... / - We just use it.
Koreans often use balsamic vinegar even at home.
You need to know the definition.
When we say balsamic vinegar in Korea,
people think it's a high quality wine vinegar.
But wine vinegar and balsamic vinegar
are two different things.
Wine vinegar is made of wine.
You make wine from grape juice
and use that to make vinegar.
That's wine vinegar.
(How to make wine vinegar)
Harvest grapes, boil grape juice
and use that to make balsamic vinegar.
It's made straight from grape.
You take a long time
to get the result solely from grape juice.
That's balsamic vinegar.
Aceto Balsamico Tradizionale.
This started in 1998.
It was even before my debut.
When SHINHWA debuted,
it began.
What's the difference between the sizes?
This set is called batterie.
(Several barrels in a set for maturing balsamic vinegar)
The small ones are always the older.
Oh, they keep moving.
It's all done manually.
The bigger, the younger and smaller ones are older
because the quantity reduces.
(The oldest vinegar remains in the smallest barrel)
Each year, I move a little quantity of product
from one barrel to another barrel.
- And it takes 12 years. / - So much work.
But we must wait minimum of 12 years.
- 12 years? / - It's 12 years minimum.
We must wait minimum of 12 years
for traditional balsamic vinegar.
It's matured for 12 years?
Balsamic vinegar can get super expensive.
- It's very expensive. / - Yes.
It's like whiskey, right?
- Whiskey also... / - They reduce.
- But in this one, no alcohol. / - No alcohol.
This isn't alcohol though.
The barrels are always open.
(There's a white cloth on top of every barrel)
As it matures,
it shouldn't contain alcohol.
So they leave the cap open to evaporate the alcohol.
As moisture evaporates, the flavor condenses.
That's how the process works.
And for the wine production,
the wooden barrels are always closed.
(Alcohol evaporates and moisture condenses)
- Now I'll show you. / - Okay.
Oh, really?
It's all moved manually using that.
(Every process is done manually)
So, every process follows the traditional way.
(Meeting traditional balsamic vinegar)
It's almost like honey.
It's like grain syrup.
Right. It's as thick as grain syrup.
Sticky.
(It's thick even to the naked eye)
Isn't that an appetizing density?
I just want to dip my finger to taste it.
Yes.
(Off they go to taste traditional balsamic vinegar)
It's a tasting area.
This is the product?
These are the products.
Very important for the traditional balsamic vinegar
to have this kind of bottle.
The shape of the bottle.
The shape of the bottle matters
for the traditional balsamic vinegar.
As for traditional Modena balsamic vinegar,
it has absolutely no additives and that's the shape.
Only the balsamic vinegar in that type of bottle
is traditionally made.
"Aceto Balsamico Tradizionale." This is what matters.
When you look here,
only the ones with no additives are authentic.
(It's a government certified mark)
Here.
- Spoon. / - Thank you.
(It's finally time to try balsamic vinegar)
First of all, balsamic vinegar.
(A regular store product with artificial additives)
This one is made with 65% vinegar.
65%.
(It's clearly watery)
Good for salad if you want.
Or if you're cooking.
- It's good but sour. / - It's light...
For salad.
It's the traditional method but young.
- 6 years old. / - It's 6 years old.
(You can see 6-year-old balsamic vinegar is thicker)
- In this case the juice is... / - It's thicker.
Cooked a little bit more. 30 hours instead of 24.
(How does 6-year-old balsamic vinegar taste?)
Since it's been matured for a while,
the scent from oak barrel controls the sour taste.
Also, it's a bit thicker.
Because we talked about grain syrup,
it tastes like grain syrup.
Yes, it's like grain syrup.
(6-year-old balsamic vinegar)
And this is white grape.
It's already thick.
- It's sticky. / - It's made of white grape.
The white label means it's 12 years old.
(Wow)
Whiskey and wine are funny.
The more you pay, the better whiskey tastes.
- Really? / - I'm serious.
Really?
Unless you pay more, it can't be good.
The more you pay, the better it is.
(12-year-old balsamic vinegar)
Minimum 25.
(Traditional balsamic vinegar matured for over 25 years)
- So this is... / - This is gold label?
- The gold. / - Yes, the gold.
(The thicker, the slower)
(He sniffs first, then tastes)
Okay.
(Very thick)
It must be really good.
Those lips are so annoying.
The stickiness spreads in my mouth,
and the smell comes out of my nose.
It was so thick.
(6 years old, 12 years old, 25 years old)
(Sticky)
It's thick.
100-year-old will be even thicker.
(Stickiness, scent, sourness)
The sour taste keeps reducing.
(Exclaiming)
- Gelato. / - Okay.
- Gelato. This is frozen ice cream. / - Gelato.
With 6-year-old balsamic.
(Another way to enjoy balsamic vinegar)
Isn't that what we had before?
For us, it's a nice combination.
They put 100% milk ice cream
and 6-year-old balsamic vinegar on it.
The sourness will go well with sweet ice cream.
This is my first bite.
(How does it taste together?)
(It's amazing)
(Thumbs up)
- Very good. / - First?
At first, it's too sour
and you think they don't go together
but then it's sweet. And the scent!
You know, you add chocolate or caramel syrup
in vanilla ice cream?
It looks and tastes like that.
It's just that it's sour from grape.
It's perfect.
If you add it in salty food,
the sourness
enhances the salty flavor.
However, when it's added in ice cream,
the sweet flavor and caramel scent add up...
- Yes. / - And enhance the sweet flavor.
I told you. It tasted like caramel.
Right.
Chef Lee Wonil seems like giving up.
If you can get original balsamic vinegar,
it'll hold its own flavor
with any kind of ice cream.
You should try it at home.
This is really good.
- The balsamic is so good. / - This is classy.
It's not just sweet and sour.
It has sour and sweet and aromatic.
It has the taste of grape and caramel.
It is very harmonious.
But we can't go back only after this.
We've come all the way here
to Modena.
In Modena,
there's a restaurant where they use
the balsamic vinegar of Modena.
I heard the place is very famous here.
We will go there and have balsamic risotto.
You've never heard of it before, right?
Balsamic risotto? That sounds strange.
I haven't tried it before.
Sweet and sour risotto? It doesn't sound good.
Actually, the ice cream didn't sound good either.
Ice cream is sweet though.
But people say it's good.
It gets good reviews.
Alright then. Let's go try
balsamic risotto.
- Let's try. / - Let's go.
Aren't you buying balsamic vinegar?
I'm buying it now.
They have to buy it.
(20 minutes to the restaurant by taxi)
This is the dish that will mark...
The end of our trip in Italy.
The best restaurant.
Isn't this romantic?
Right, it looks amazing.
- It looks beautiful. / - Because of the wood fire.
I heard they have dishes that are not on the menu.
Basic dishes like risotto and pasta
are not on the menu.
We can just order off the menu.
- In Italy? / - Yes.
We rarely do that.
We don't order dishes that aren't on the menu
unless we're regulars.
People don't like it in Korea.
But they have this culture in Italy.
The thing people usually eat here is
balsamic risotto.
Since this is our last day, we should have pasta.
Pasta?
It's coming.
(Amazed)
(The climactic last dinner of their trip)
- I can't believe this. / - Gosh, what's that?
(Gnocco fritto)
Truffle pasta.
- That's it. / - My gosh.
It looks great.
(Balsamic risotto)
(Steak)
It's finally here. Steak.
My goodness.
What's that steak?
(Steak)
(Four kinds of dessert)
What's that? It's a dessert.
They serve dessert.
(They complete their order for the last dinner)
You guys really did let go of yourselves.
Completely.
(Is team Spain giving up like this?)
(A refreshing start with white wine)
Ladies first.
- The wine was really good. / - This is our last dinner.
It was really good.
- It looks delicious. / - It has to be good.
(Cheers)
It sounds like a cathedral.
(Sipping)
This is so good.
It's delicious.
This is great.
As I sip it,
it feels like a cold and clear rock on my tongue.
It feels clear and cool.
It's called minerality.
And if you smell it...
You can feel the almond flavor.
It smells like apricot seed.
I can feel it.
It's quite dry,
cool and clear.
It stimulates your appetite.
(It's perfect for aperitif)
Those who like wine will love that.
I should go to the restaurant.
I really want to go there.
(The antipasto is served)
- Gnocco fritto. / - Gnocco fritto.
Some kind of gnocco fritto.
It's like an Italian dumpling.
I thought it was boiled but it's actually deep-fried.
It's like a fried dumpling.
It smells like sweet and sour pork because of vinegar.
It smells just like sweet and sour pork.
It smells like a Chinese dish.
(He keeps making nasal sounds)
This is an appetizer.
It's salty
and the balsamic is sour.
So it really increases your appetite.
(A fantastic harmony of saltiness and sourness)
I've never seen such food before.
What's in it?
(Parmesan cheese is hidden in the dough)
It doesn't feel like an appetizer. It's like a main dish.
(He strongly agrees)
How can we beat this?
This is too good.
There's nothing to get rid of.
I guess he is grinding it here.
(Truffle pasta)
They grind truffle like that.
Is it truffle?
- They give you so much. / - It's expensive.
It's called truffle.
As I said, it smells like musk.
It's one of the three great delicacies of the world.
It's truffle.
It's expensive.
(Truffle pasta, $20.80)
- Is that true? / - It's about $20.
- It has this much truffle on it. / - It's going down.
Oh, no.
Falling down.
They're eating.
They should go down.
(Truffle pasta, $20.80)
Truffle is called tartufo in Italian.
That's truffle.
(It makes him take pictures of it)
(Deeply moved)
What should we do?
It smells so good.
The world's best truffle is produced
in South West France and here.
(He tastes it reverently)
- It looks so good. / - Look at the pasta.
The pasta looks so good.
It must be delicious.
Wow.
It's good.
It tastes like the pasta has a lot of egg in it.
The scent of egg is very strong.
It was like chewy egg yolk garnish.
It looks so fresh.
The truffle is...
Just like a good supporting actor.
I can't believe that.
The pasta is the main here and they never miss that.
- Exactly. / - When Korean people eat meat...
They don't like it if rice doesn't taste good.
- It's the same. / - You're right about that.
It feels like I'm eating very good rice right now.
The pasta is very important.
I love fresh pasta.
(They add some olive oil to it)
Alright.
This is ragu pasta with truffle...
Parmesan cheese
and olive oil.
Gosh, nothing can beat this.
It's good.
(This is it)
I miss my parents a little bit.
When you eat something good...
- You think of your parents. / - It was so good.
So I wanted my parents to taste it.
- It was that good. / - This is the best.
This is the best dish.
(It's the best dish that makes you miss your parents)
(The next dish is served)
And this is so...
I'm sorry to say this but it's a headache.
(What kind of dish is it?)
- What is he doing now? / - Wow.
Thank you.
- Oh, it's risotto. / - Is it risotto?
It looks good.
This is just amazing.
(Balsamic risotto, only in Modena)
Made with broth and parmesan cheese.
(It's basic risotto made with broth, butter and cheese)
(It's completed with Modena's balsamic vinegar)
With traditional balsamic vinegar.
It's risotto with balsamic vinegar.
I've never tried this before.
(Balsamic risotto, $20.80)
This is so hard.
They are coming down again. My goodness.
It's super saturated.
What should I do?
What do I do with Bologna?
- Gosh, it must be delicious. / - It looks great.
It tastes good already.
They boiled the rice until it's al dente.
- It looks so good. / - It's tender...
- Risotto. / - But slightly chewy.
I like the texture.
I like the mouthful of rice starch.
Good rice
with balsamic vinegar.
It looks great.
I'm not watching it.
- Gosh. / - Wonil, you have to watch it.
- I'm not watching. / - You can't do that.
Look at that.
- Gosh, it looks so good. / - Stop it.
Balsamic, balsamic.
You have to watch this.
They are eating so well.
This is so good.
We kept saying it looked like soy sauce.
- The balsamic vinegar. / - Right.
Simply put, it tastes like
fancy and expensive rice with soy sauce and butter.
(Fancy rice with soy sauce and butter)
Rice with soy sauce and butter.
But the soy sauce is very flavorful.
Okay, I get it,
I think they can sell this in Korea.
The rice would taste different though.
All I need is this.
You can make this by grating parmesan cheese
on a frying pan and frying it.
On a special day, I should make risotto
and add balsamic to it.
It's like rice with soy sauce and butter.
And it has a fried egg on it.
- The crispy one. / - A Chinese style fried egg.
This is my favorite.
I want to go to a risotto restaurant
and take my own balsamic vinegar.
With risotto, I suggest Lambrusco.
I see.
He says the Lambrusco goes well with the risotto.
The red wine.
It's a red sparkling wine made in this neighborhood.
It's a really famous wine from this neighborhood.
- It's famous worldwide. / - Really?
We usually drink white or rose sparkling wine
but never red, right?
It's from Italy.
It's Lambrusco wine that is only grown
from that neighborhood.
- It's carbonated? / - It is and it's sweet.
Lovelyz are talking noisily.
They get noisy when you talk about alcohol.
He just said the wine would go well.
Let's drink this first and then eat.
(Lambrusco wine, $7.80 per glass)
The flavors burst inside my mouth.
- The tastes go well together. / - Yes.
I've only had white sparkling wine.
Is it a dessert wine?
- No, it's semi-sweet. / - Semi-sweet?
It's not that sweet.
It's not like ice wine, it's a little drier than that.
- The rice can be... / - That's right.
A little too rich.
It feels so nice to drink refreshing carbonated red wine
that isn't too sweet nor strong
after eating the rice.
I want to go outside on the terrace and eat this.
I think it's a perfect pair to drink this wine with this.
Look at that!
- What is it? It's here. / - I'm curious about that meat.
- Is that a T-bone steak? / - Isn't that a T-bone?
It's a T-bone steak.
Are they going to cook it in that fire behind you?
- Yes! / - They grilled it for us there.
Did they grill it for you there?
Do they grill it using the fire behind?
- That's amazing. / - Gosh.
That's amazing.
That is so nice.
You can see it in front of your eyes.
(The steak is full of olive oil and smoke aroma)
Look at it getting sliced.
(After the steak is rested, it gets cut right away)
Actually, that's not easy.
Grilling the steak in that kind of fire
and resting it to make it more delicious.
(T-bone steak, $54.60)
Sook, here.
- Just pick this up right away. / - Okay.
I'll make the decision right away today.
I won't do this today. I'll just choose this right now.
- Is this beef tenderloin? / - Yes.
The small cut is tenderloin and
the large cut is sirloin.
(Drizzling)
This is insane.
(He fully appreciates the aroma of the meat first)
I'm a little nervous right now.
You should try it first.
No, I'll try it first.
(He nervously takes the first bite of the steak)
Is this the best steak of your life?
(His face is a little ambiguous)
No, it's before the flavor of the meat has burst.
(This is amazing)
It burst.
- It burst. / - It looks really good.
Even I think that it looks good.
(This really is the best steak)
Gosh.
(Is it that good?)
(This steak is really done properly)
(An unexpected silent broadcast)
Hey...
What is this?
- This is a little... / - That is insane.
I'm not exaggerating. This is really delicious.
The inside is like really expensive tuna...
- With only red flesh. / - Yes.
- Look at the juice. / - It's so tender.
Usually, when meat is this rare...
- It's gamey. / - Yes.
But it's not and it has a pleasant aroma.
It's aroma from the meat if put in a good way
and odor in a bad way.
- But... / - That's right.
Usually, we eat tenderloin
because it's really tender and it has a clean taste.
We like to eat sirloin because
it's a little greasy and has firmer texture.
But both of them are so tender.
The sirloin isn't greasy like we thought.
- It only has a little of that. / - Yes.
(Tender yet firm, the steak is very charming)
This...
I wasn't going to put things on top again
but I have to do it.
I think I'm getting dizzy.
I'd like to give some advice to people who come here
after seeing this show.
You should try 1 or 2 pieces of the meat plain first.
After that, you should drizzle olive oil on top and try it.
All of the bitterness of the meat goes away
and it tastes sweet.
That's right.
You will experience the meat
suddenly becoming sweet.
I put too much salt.
It goes so well with the olive oil.
(It's so delicious)
(He sweeps his hair because he's moved)
He's finally doing it.
Honestly, it's so good.
Please just watch next week
focusing on the entertainment.
(How was the meal?)
Yes, we are very fine.
Can I have the menu for dessert?
Yeah.
No, no, no! Please don't take it away!
Don't break my heart.
He almost got in trouble.
What happened? I was so surprised.
I should hurry and put it on my plate.
(Clattering)
Something is coming.
(What is the noise that boasts its presence?)
What is this?
(The dessert trolley came in)
Is this?
What is that?
That's the dessert?
Amazing.
- Oh, my. / - What is this?
The dessert menu also changes every day.
This is a classic English...
(He doesn't have time to pick)
(Too busy taking photos)
- Too many I want to eat. / - You want it all, right?
Hey... We'll just get rid of this.
I'm full but I want to eat,
so I don't know what to choose.
Today has been the hardest episode of Battle Trip.
I'll have one piece of this tart.
- Yes. / - That, that and this.
- That's everything. / - These?
- Yes, please. / - Yes.
(Dessert, $2.40 per piece)
Did you eat that many desserts?
That's not a lot.
It really looks good.
- It's good. / - This one?
- The chocolate? / - The inside is moist.
This really feels homemade.
I think it's right to eat this
if you really want to feel Italy.
I should eat the last piece of meat as dessert.
Steak...
(I shall stick to my steak)
He's eating the remaining steak.
- I want to try that steak. / - The steak is...
Ridiculous.
It's my first time eating something like that.
- We gained a lot of weight. / - Yes.
- But it's sad to end like this. / - Yes.
Let's go back to Bologna.
Let's just have one more drink.
Okay, let's have one more drink.
(No matter what they say, it was a good last banquet)
I didn't have a lot of awareness for Italian beef.
After eating that, my perspective completely changed.
I didn't know that Italian meat was so delicious.
(Average score for the last supper of Modena, 5 stars)
(They recommend balsamic risotto and truffle pasta)
(We Will Eat Tour in Bologna, Day 2)
(A trendy place for dinner)
(30 minutes from the restaurant to the pub)
(The last evening in Bologna is coming to a close)
(Darkness veils Piazza Maggiore)
(The streets are lively with people)
Let's find a place to have a light last drink.
Okay, good.
- It changed like this. / - There are...
A lot of people here.
- This is the alley where we ate... / - So many people.
- The sandwich. / - Yes.
- And the fish shop. / - It seems completely different.
It's a market during the day
and they clear everything at night.
It completely changes into a street for young people.
They become like outdoor cafes and outdoor bars.
The atmosphere is almost like Itaewon.
It completely becomes a trendy place like this.
- Yes. / - There are empty seats there.
Okay, let's have some beer.
You need to have some beer to end the day well.
(Refreshing)
That must be so refreshing.
It was nice.
I think we focused on the concept of a gourmet tour
and tasted everything of the Italian cuisine.
I really liked it.
- Was it "Bologna la grassa?" / - Yes.
It means that Bologna is the city of gluttony.
I fully understand the meaning of that saying.
The cheese, ham, bread
and wine are delicious.
So if you lose your mind a little,
you will quickly become a grassa.
I think the food tasted better as time went by.
I'm happy to be here.
It was an experience that made me feel so good.
Eat, enjoy and love. This is Italy.
Italy is love.
(Their enjoyable trip ends here)
- Thank you. / - Thank you. Good job.
Italy is amazing.
It was amazing.
(We Will Eat Tour's final evaluation of Bologna)
That was amazing.
(We strongly recommend Bologna for a gourmet trip)
- Isn't that so funny? / - I think it really was...
The hardest episode to endure.
I really thank you deeply for last week.
- Wasn't the food too good? / - Just stop.
We accept it was good.
The corner inside a corner, Sook's Choice.
- Let's check the ranking. / - Okay.
Personally...
I wasn't going to put things on top.
But the balsamic risotto looked so good.
- Don't you want to try it? / - For the T-bone steak...
Sikyung judges taste objectively
because he's a gourmand.
But he said this was the best steak of his life.
I really want to try this.
I can't leave out the truffle pasta too.
Because it's only $19.
Then for 1st place...
(Deliberating)
I'll choose the balsamic risotto.
(Sook chooses the balsamic risotto)
I really want to try this.
- It was good. / - Yes.
Let's decide then. Lovelyz?
What did you choose for 1st place?
- We chose... / - We had a hard time choosing.
We wanted to try all of those.
- Isn't that right? / - All of them looked delicious.
We wanted to try everything so
we agonized a lot over it.
We finally chose the T-bone steak.
The T-bone steak.
We'll put T-bone steak in 1st place.
PENTAGON? They're still discussing.
- Our 1st place is... / - 1st place?
- The truffle pasta. / - The truffle pasta.
We have similar tastes in food. All of them are here.
There's nothing to leave out here.
- Very true. / - I put everything on top...
I didn't replace anything. The list just moved down.
- Hwijae, what's wrong? / - Yes?
Can't we watch Barcelona again?
No, we can't. This isn't the end.
We told you before.
We will continue to foul until we're ejected.
- Please ring the bell. / - Do I have to ring the bell?
Let's see what the foul is.
- What is it? / - It can't be.
We prepared the ham that is the color of my shirt.
- Gosh. / - Oh, my.
(Oh, my)
Mortadella!
The smell is amazing.
There are pistachios.
I was really curious.
This is insane.
I know now why you had so much of this with bread.
That's right. You have to eat this with bread.
Don't refrigerate the mortadella.
It has a lot of minute fat inside.
- You can just eat it as it is. / - Just enjoy it as it is.
This isn't salty.
- So you don't need bread. / - It's really tender.
You have to put a lot of slices
when you eat it with bread.
I recommend eating one piece
if you're going to eat just this.
You should eat it with beer.
You really need beer with this.
How can the texture be like this?
They sell this in Korea but it's expensive.
You can get tired of eating this,
so the way to not get tired
is to first eat like this. When you start eating a lot,
I recommend eating it with white kimchi.
- They go well together. / - It will be great with kimchi.
I want to wrap it with hot rice.
- Isn't that right? / - Yes.
PENTAGON, what do you think?
They completely emptied it.
- This answers for us. / - Yes.
- This was the best ham of my life. / - Me too.
(Mortadella was the best sausage of his life)
He said it was the best ham of his life.
They won't forget us when we did this much, right?
We need to check the most important thing now.
Instead of the total expense spent in Bologna, Italy...
- We should also check... / - Yes.
The food expense for this week.
For Venice, they spent $204.
- $204. / - I think they spent more than that.
For 1 night 2 days,
the total food expense for 7 meals is...
- Per person. / - Per person!
(How much did they spent on food in Bologna?)
(How much will it be?)
$166.
It's for 7 meals. 7 meals.
- The prices are low. / - It's for 7 meals.
Bologna isn't a tourist spot like Rome or Venice.
- It's quite cheap. / - It's much cheaper.
Why does Hwijae's face look so bad?
I'm okay.
- I'm okay. / - Wonil, are you okay?
- They will forget it next week. / - Yes.
- We'll begin afresh. / - My gosh.
We're just talking like this.
We have gourmet and also entertainment.
Chef Wonil will do slapstick comedy next week.
Please look forward to it.
(Next episode)
It's the most futuristic city in Europe.
Are we going over there to eat?
The texture of this is so unique.
I'm salivating and gastric juices are starting to pump.
My kids would love this.
Everything's so close by. No need for cars.
The warm sun of the Mediterranean.
It's been saturated in it.
This is totally nice.
It's still chewy. But it's also soft.
(Battle Trip)
("Beautiful Pain" by BTOB)