(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
(Special host, Kim Iljung)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
This week's special host for Battle Trip is
Kim Iljung. Welcome.
- Hello, I'm Kim Iljung. / - Welcome.
It's such an honor.
- I came here as a trip designer. / - That's right.
It was a big issue then because of your team name.
It was the Back to Sing Tour, right?
The related search keyword for me was "divorce."
I remember.
Battle Trip has to take responsibility for that.
Why is that our fault?
Why was it called Back to Sing Tour?
Because it wasn't our first time to Singapore.
We've been to Singapore before.
Back to Sing Tour means to go back to Singapore.
- You have to name the tour carefully. / - Right.
- I never got a divorce. / - Yes.
Actually...
- Did you win or lose? / - My team won.
- He won. / - Did he win?
We need to keep the streak alive and win again.
Of course, we have to win.
Anyway, we'll start Battle Trip right now.
First, let's see the theme of this trip
on the screen first.
(Summer vacation for office workers)
(Leave)
(You don't need an annual leave or vacation)
You don't need an annual leave...
- You also don't need a vacation. / - Nor vacation.
(Enjoy the weekend!)
(Short flight time, cheap travel expenses)
Short flight time
and cheap travel expenses.
- It's for the weekend. / - That's right.
We really went to a lot of places.
The color of the water is different for each country.
(A relaxing late vacation)
(Burdenless last-minute summer vacation)
A last-minute summer vacation.
The theme is last-minute summer vacations?
We have to focus on what comes
in front of summer vacation.
- It is "burdenless." / - A burdenless vacation.
- I really love that word. / - Yes, that's important.
Actually, for office workers, taking 1 or 2 days off...
- Makes you uncomfortable. / - That's right.
People want to save up their leaves and
use them at once.
- That's their hope. / - Right.
- But they won't have to take a day off. / - Okay.
They can leave on Friday night
and go to work on Monday with this trip.
- That's awesome. / - That's the best part.
If you're watching our show and
you were too busy to go on a vacation this year...
And if you feel like you want to take off somewhere,
the trips we will show you today...
- Don't require you to take any days off. / - Right.
Anyway,
our guests went to places where they can enjoy
without feeling burdened.
Everyone, let us introduce the four trip planners.
- Come on out. / - Come on out.
(Who are the trip planners?)
(Oh Nami, Lee Sookyung)
We won. We won.
- We won this one. / - What do you mean?
- We won this battle. / - They will be hard to beat.
I know a bit about Raeyeon.
She's an expert traveler.
- Is that so? / - Yes, she is indeed.
Unless I'm working, I like traveling around the world.
And a lot of my relatives live abroad.
- A lot of my relatives. / - Very global.
- I'm so jealous. / - All of my family lives in Korea.
First off, let's find out where each team went to.
We went to the best vacation spot in the Philippines.
It's the ultimate vacation spot.
No one on this island is in a rush. We went to...
Cebu!
- Cebu! / - That's a great destination.
- Cebu is the best. / - Battle Trip went there a lot.
- Exactly. / - Right.
Actually, I've been to Cebu a few times myself.
I remember having so much fun in Cebu.
- You can have so much fun there. / - Right.
It's a short flight which usually leaves at night.
- So you can sleep on the flight. / - How long is it?
- 4 hours and 30 minutes. / - Is it a direct flight?
- Yes, there's a flight every day. / - Every day?
Once you see the beach, you'd...
- Feel you're on vacation. / - The beach is a must...
- For your summer vacation. / - Cebu is the answer.
It's a perfect summer destination.
We did every activity
we could do in the ocean in Cebu.
- It was the best. / - What did you do in the water?
- You'll find out later. Not now. / - I almost spoiled it.
- I almost spoiled it. / - That would've been bad.
- We had so much fun. / - We'll share our destination.
We went to the best gourmet city in Asia.
This place is the center of Chinese cuisine.
- We went to Chengdu in Sichuan. / - Hold on.
Her pronunciation is so good.
- Where? / - She sounded so cool.
- Where did you go again? / - Pardon?
We went to Chengdu in Sichuan.
- Chengdu? / - Chengdu?
Sichuan is known for clean water.
Places with clean water are known
for alcohol and beautiful women.
That's why you know so much about the place.
- I have friends in China... / - That's why he knows.
- I really wanted to go there. / - Just go to Jeju-do.
It's famous for spicy food...
Gosh, I'm salivating.
- Sikyung, that's not the point. / - Yes?
Their merit is something else.
- Raeyeon is Chinese. / - You should tell us.
She's from China.
- Chinese is her native tongue. / - That's it. This is it.
- We won now. / - Are you two from Cebu?
No.
I'm not from Sichuan.
By the way, Raeyeon is the expert on China.
You've been to every part of China, right?
Over two trips to China,
I went around China for about 100 days.
- I've been to most of China. / - 100 days?
It's not easy to visit most of China.
- That's 3 months. / - I've been to most of the places.
Among those places, Sichuan cuisine is the best.
We both like food.
- That's right. / - We can handle spicy food well.
The beach in Cebu is great
but instead of going to a predictable place...
- No, no. It's not predictable. / - Predictable?
- It's a unique destination. / - What do you mean?
It hasn't been introduced yet.
- That's right. / - We chose Sichuan so we can...
Introduce you special parts of the place thoroughly.
When I go there,
I can't order food because I don't speak the language.
- They speak Korean in Cebu. / - It was so convenient.
- The menus are in Korean. / - They have Korean menus.
On top of that, Filipinos in Cebu speak great Korean.
Of course.
Among the dishes you had,
I heard you had a unique dish.
Tell us without spoilers.
- That dish. / - What is it?
We ate a nose there.
- A nose? / - Yes.
- You ate a nose? / - You're not supposed to eat noses.
- Alright. We'll do one better. / - One better?
We ate...
A jaw.
- Jaw? / - Yes.
- You ate a chin? / - Yes.
- You ate a jaw? / - It was the best jaw we had.
- Really? / - What is she talking about now?
It's a battle between a nose and a jaw.
- What else did you see there? / - Chengdu...
- Is the hometown of pandas. / - Really?
- The whole world loves pandas. / - Pandas.
- Did you see pandas? / - A baby panda.
- It was so tiny. It wriggled. / - A baby panda?
- The panda was flailing. / - It couldn't even roll over.
- That's so cute. / - The panda couldn't even roll over.
- They saw pandas. / - Let's beat that.
- We'll top that. We saw... / - Sure, pandas are cute.
A whale shark.
- You'll love it. / - You're going to love it.
You can also swim with a whale shark.
- It's a whale shark. / - With the whale shark?
- You can swim? / - You can swim together.
- It'd beat pandas. / - Alright.
It's panda vs. whale shark. Nose dish vs. jaw dish.
This will be a very weird episode.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
(100 judges in the audience)
- Let's go to Cebu first. / - Cebu.
- Let's start with Cebu. / - The Philippines...
- Consists of islands. / - That's right.
- There are thousands of islands. / - Lots of islands.
Among those islands,
Cebu is the second largest island.
- So there are many places to visit. / - That's right.
That's why we went to the south.
- To the south? / - That's a bit unfamiliar.
- South is a bit unfamiliar. / - You haven't been, right?
- Oslob? / - I've never heard of that.
- Isn't that in Europe? / - Are you going to Oslob...
To see the whale sharks?
- That's right. / - Can you see it there?
- It's the hottest thing right now. / - I see.
- Seeing whale sharks in Oslob. / - We saw them once.
It was in Cancun, Mexico. It was so fascinating.
- It was so up close. / - But a huge whale shark...
- Was passing by. / - But Cancun is too far away.
- Right. It's too far. / - Yes, indeed.
Basically, you can do everything you could do
in Cancun over in Oslob, right?
- That's right. / - Alright.
- I'm curious. / - Let's set out now.
Let's check out 52 Tour's trip to Cebu, Philippines.
(The trip to Cebu starts)
- Hello. / - Hi.
This feels awkward.
(Feeling awkward)
Hello, I'm Lee Sookyung.
Hello, I'm Oh Nami.
(Sookyung and Nami are close friends)
- How pretty. / - They look cute.
I'm so happy that I made a new friend late in life.
We can become much closer after this trip together.
We haven't been friends for that long.
So I thought it'd be good to go on a trip together
and find out more about each other.
- That's why I chose her. / - That's why I'm so excited.
- That I get to travel with you. / - As for me...
- Don't travel much. / - That's right.
She likes staying home and playing with her dog.
I love staying at home.
Whenever I have time to spare, I go traveling.
(Nami travels whenever she can)
(Nami went to Yeosu with Daeseong and Soyeong)
Come to Yeosu.
- You went to Yeosu. / - Right.
- Did you win back then? / - Yes, we did.
I made an observation.
We should eat a lot of good food.
The viewers like to see us having fun.
I love it. Whatever you decide, I'll like it.
- I can trust you and follow you. / - Really?
Most importantly, I'll make sure you have fun.
I'll plan our trip according to that.
Did you decide on a country?
This time, Battle Trip is doing
a last-minute summer vacation special.
When you think of summer vacation,
you'd think of the beach.
- I love it. / - Right?
I thought about where we could go
to the beach overseas not far from Korea.
The closest beach we can go to is the one in Cebu.
And what's important is that
Battle Trip has never introduced Cebu before.
- Really? / - We introduced the Philippines a lot.
- That's so cute. / - What is that?
- That's so adorable. / - What is that?
(The beach in Cebu is loved by Korean tourists)
- They're so adorable. / - Is that the whale shark?
- What is that? / - Wow.
Isn't that so cute?
- We won! / - You were right next to it.
- I just got goose bumps. / - Aren't they so cute?
We've won!
- It's like a painting. / - It's so amazing.
I've seen this on TV.
(Cebu is all about the beaches?)
(The ultimate guide to conquering Cebu)
- That'll be hard to beat. / - It's not predictable.
- Exactly. / - Didn't I tell you?
We enjoyed both nature and the city in Cebu.
- What's that? / - What is it?
- What is that? / - Isn't that Las Vegas?
(A parade of various dishes no one imagined)
- They have all kinds of food. / - I love that dish.
Goodness.
(Food paradise)
(A trip to Cebu you've never seen before)
Follow me.
Just trust me and follow.
You can see all of downtown Cebu at a glance.
What is that?
It's so...
I brought Sookyung.
- You're doing well, Nami. / - She's funny.
What on earth is this?
(She can scream like the dolphin)
It's here. It's here!
(Big reactions whenever she's happy or scared)
I want that one.
Yes.
She has great reaction.
- Their trip already looks fun. / - I can feel the energy.
Goodness.
- I want to go there. / - Now...
52 Tour!
(52 Tour's 52-hour trip)
(Conquering the nature in Oslob, Cebu)
(Local breakfast, whale shark, Tumalog Falls, dinner)
(Conquering the city, Cebu)
(Tropical fruit, seafood, observatory, trendy place)
I'm already worried from the start.
Nami...
(Why is Sookyung coming alone?)
We're supposed to meet there.
Our 52 Tour has begun now.
(She video calls Nami who will set out from Busan)
- Nami. / - We left for the trip separately.
- Why did she leave from Busan? / - Separately.
- Was it because of her schedule? / - Yes.
- She left from Busan. / - The Comedy Festival?
Yes.
You know the name of our tour...
- Can be pronounced as Oh Lee Tour. / - Right.
We will be on our trip for 52 hours as well.
You're smart as expected.
- Okay. Get there safely. / - Okay.
Let's go!
(They're meeting at Cebu International Airport)
Go, go, go!
I'm finally done with work. I'm going on vacation.
I look like a real office worker.
Right after I finish work, I'm setting out for my trip.
What's wrong with my face?
- Why? You look pretty. / - You think so?
Yes.
- I'm so nervous alone. / - My goodness.
- That big camera. / - It's embarrassing.
- People are watching me. / - It looks like a movie.
See you later.
(4 hours and 15 minutes to Cebu from Incheon Airport)
(4 hours and 10 minutes to Cebu from Gimhae Airport)
There's a direct flight that leaves from Busan too?
Yes, flights from Busan leave at night too.
- That shows how much we love Cebu. / - Exactly.
- That's a great tip. / - Right now.
I'm at Cebu International Airport in the Philippines.
Since I arrived before Sookyung,
I'm waiting for her as we speak.
Yes. It's hot here.
By the way, the airport is really nice.
- The airport was really nice. / - That's newly built.
(Cebu International Airport is being newly built)
(Feeling embarrassed)
I knew how to say hello in their language.
(As she feels embarrassed, she says a greeting)
- Was that a greeting? / - Yes, it was.
Bye.
(He leaves after saying good-bye)
(Looking lonely)
Nami!
(What is this familiar, high-pitched voice?)
Sookyung!
(Her affection explodes)
- Did you wait long? / - Yes.
- You met in Cebu. / - Gosh, that must feel good.
- Seriously. / - It was so nice to see her.
It would've felt strange.
This is pretty late right now.
- Yes, it's pretty late. / - That was 2 in the morning?
Yes, it was.
- But... / - Let's start our trip tomorrow.
But we can't sleep right now
because we were supposed to see the whale sharks.
- There are whale sharks in Oslob. / - Okay.
We can see the whale sharks there.
- Sharks? / - We can go into the water.
This is my first time hearing it.
I've never heard about whale sharks in Cebu.
Same here.
- I like snorkeling. / - Really?
I do too.
- It'd be fun because... / - Right? It's pretty.
- When else would you swim with a shark? / - Right.
(They're happier to see these guests in Cebu)
- It's over there. Look over there! / - Where?
(They inhabit only in the clean seas)
(Meeting a whale shark is a rare experience)
(They get to see them right before their eyes)
(This is a special once-in-a-lifetime experience)
(52 Tour will present the whale sharks shortly)
But the whale sharks come early in the morning.
- They are early risers. / - They leave at a specific time.
- We must bolt now to see them. / - Bolt to where?
We must leave now to meet the whale sharks.
We have to go to Oslob.
??Whale shark ??
??Cute ??
She's singing with Nami.
Right. She plays along too.
(They set out to Oslob to see the whale sharks)
We have a long way ahead of us. Alright.
- Let's go meet the whale sharks! / - Don't forget me.
Okay, fine. Sookyung. Get in the car first.
How will you get there?
I requested for a car to pick us up.
- It's a round trip too. / - I see. That's nice.
When you land at 2 a.m., you can sleep on the bus.
(You can get pick-up from the airport)
(Feeling excited)
- You didn't stop by at a hotel. / - We went right away.
We saved a day in the end.
That's a good plan. When you arrive in Cebu...
- You fall asleep. / - Right.
It's better to go there now.
The best part of such trips is
you can't see anything at night but in the morning,
you open your eyes and you're like, "Wow."
- You'd be impressed. / - That's true.
- We were just like that. / - Right.
(52 Tour rests up while heading to Oslob)
(As they travel to Oslob, the morning breaks)
The sun is rising.
It was great at dawn.
- Right? / - Yes.
- That'd feel strange. / - It was.
(It's a 4-hour drive)
(Conquering the nature in Oslob, Cebu)
(Local breakfast)
(Hour 40 of the 52 Tour)
- Now, we will... / - We will...
We'll see the whale sharks now, right?
Before we see the whale sharks,
there's this great restaurant that serves
delicious food and has the best view.
Aren't you hungry?
- Yes, it took us hours to get here. / - Right.
- You look tired. Are you okay? / - She looks so tired.
- She looks so tired. / - Nami.
That's not it. It's the first time I've seen this.
It's because the sun is in your eyes, right?
- It was bothering our eyes. / - It was too bright.
- The sun was really bright. / - You look like that...
After the 4-hour flight and 4-hour car ride.
- The ocean is their view. Yes. / - Really?
Let's go this way.
- The weather is great here. / - Isn't it great?
Hello.
Sookyung, it's this way.
(What will their first meal be like in Cebu?)
(The refreshing scenery blows away their sleepiness)
Look. The view isn't obstructed.
Right. It's lifting my spirits.
- It's not from a hotel. It's local. / - Right.
Local restaurant.
So the restaurant is open at that early hour?
- It is. / - They start early.
- They do? / - It's because...
A lot of people go there for the whale shark tour.
The restaurant is near the tour.
- It's here. / - Right? What's here?
- Our breakfast is here. / - I see. Our breakfast.
Hi.
- It's the sticky rice. / - What is that?
- Is that rice? / - It's sticky rice.
- Right. / - It's rice...
- Isn't that pork? / - Yes, it is.
It's like a barbecue.
- Chicken and pork. / - It costs $3.20.
- That's so cheap. / - Isn't it so cheap?
This is great.
(Chicken tocino, $3.20)
(Pork adobo, $3.20)
Is it similar to our pork bulgogi meal?
- The pork dish... / - It's braised in soy sauce.
It's braised in soy sauce.
- The egg... / - 2 dishes don't go over $10.
- Right. / - Right.
(She tries the pork adobo first)
It's braised in soy sauce.
- Isn't it like braised short rib? / - Right.
- It must be nice and salty. / - It is.
- This tastes like braised beef. / - That must be good.
That's what it tastes like, but this is just...
Served without the soy sauce.
- Let me try the chicken. / - Try the chicken.
I like it.
Both dishes were braised in soy sauce.
- This is my type of food. Yes. / - Is it?
In Korea, it's similar to soy sauce charcoal chicken.
- It tastes like that chicken. / - Right?
I can taste the smoky flavors.
- I can taste the smoky flavors. / - Right?
Sookyung, you have a palate of a kid.
I'm like a kid. And this is perfect for people like me.
I'm glad.
We should hurry over there while they're waiting
because I know that they go away at noon.
Their work hours are pretty short.
Yes, they're short. We must get going.
(They must finish up and go meet the whale sharks)
(Meat on her left fork, rice on her right spoon)
It's like a commercial.
- It does look like a commercial. / - She's an actress.
(52 Tour fills up their stomachs first)
- That's the ocean. / - Exactly.
(It's time to really meet the whale sharks)
(Conquering the nature in Oslob, Cebu)
(Whale sharks)
(We saw the whale sharks in Cancun, Mexico)
- Taegon and Kangnam. / - Right.
That's Mexico.
It startled me.
(How will the whale sharks in Oslob look?)
(5-minute walk from the restaurant)
- 5-minute walk? / - Right.
- But... / - It's quite close.
- We've arrived at last. / - We're finally going, right?
Yes.
- Sookyung, let me explain. / - Yes?
This place is managed by the government,
so there's a time limit.
- Does it mean we must hurry? / - Yes.
That's why we came here in a hurry.
- That's right. / - But look at all these people.
- There are so many people. / - It's packed, right?
It's no joke.
- I can't believe this. / - It's so crowded.
(It's packed even in the morning)
Wow, no way.
(In Mexico, they had to head out for 3 hours)
That's true. They had to go for 3 hours.
There aren't many places where
you can see whale sharks.
(In Cebu, it only takes 5 minutes)
5 minutes?
(When the fisherman throws the food into the sea)
(Whale sharks follow him around)
(Yummy)
- Goodness. / - It follows you.
It follows him like a goldfish.
- Is it a pet? / - The whale sharks...
(A goldfish? A pet?)
- Is it a pet? / - They come for shrimp.
They're so cute.
- You have to go early. / - Yes, early in the morning.
- Gosh. / - It's really big.
(Snorkeling with whale sharks)
(Whale sharks can be seen from 6 a.m. to 11 a.m.)
If you go there on the weekend and
swim with the whale sharks...
- You'll be really energized. / - Yes.
That would keep me energized for a year.
(They put on life vests)
- I'm color coordinated. / - What?
You really are!
(Finally)
(They head out)
We're finally going to see the whale shark.
It's nice.
The ocean in the Philippines is so pretty.
Yes. It's really pretty.
(The clear and pretty sea of Cebu)
- The color is so nice. / - It's so clear.
- You're going to a deeper place. / - Yes.
(Around where the color changes to darker blue)
Look. He's throwing the food.
- He's throwing shrimp. / - Yes.
He's throwing them over there.
They feed them.
Yes. They follow you when you throw them food.
Are they small? It's quite shallow here...
- Over there! / - Where?
Look over there!
- Hi! / - Can you see?
Over there. Whale shark!
- It's so cute. / - Goodness.
Goodness, it's a whale shark.
You can see them even if you aren't in the water.
(The whale shark's spots are clearly visible)
Sookyung, it's a whale shark.
- I want to see it. / - Did you see it?
- No, I want to see it in the water. / - I see.
It's over there!
He's bringing it over here.
"He's bringing it."
- "He's bringing it." / - Goodness.
(Bringing it over with food)
- Unbelievable. / - Hi.
Goodness.
- It's following him. / - It follows him.
- Gosh, how is this possible? / - It's like a puppy.
You have to clean it with spit.
It's faster to clean it with spit.
- Are you going in the water now? / - Yes.
It's here.
Nami is in a hurry.
Let's go in quickly.
- Water. / - Whale shark.
- Where? / - There.
(The whale shark is right in front of them)
Whale shark.
(Come in quick)
- Wow. / - It's right in front of you.
It's right in front of you.
- Wow. / - Goodness.
- Wow. / - It's right in front of you.
(Whale shark, Rhincodon typus)
(They grow between 12 to 18m)
- Goodness. / - It wants to eat salted shrimp.
- It's so cute. / - Gosh.
- Goodness. / - It's so cute.
- It's huge, but it's so cute. / - Isn't the tail 2m long?
(A whale shark appeared suddenly in 2011)
(Fishermen started feeding it and more of them came)
(They are gentle in nature and do not attack people)
(They only eat salted shrimp thrown to them)
- It feels weird. / - Precautions.
- You must not touch them. / - You can't touch them.
You have to stay calm so they don't get scared.
That's right. You shouldn't touch them.
They were eating right in front of me. I felt like...
- I was getting sucked in. / - They're so close.
- They know we're coming. / - Get a hold of yourself.
Get a hold of yourself.
My son loves whale sharks.
I really want to go.
(Whale sharks don't shy away)
Is that Sookyung?
I was scared.
(What is she doing?)
- Who is it? Is that you? / - Are you having fun?
- She's hanging on dearly. / - It's because...
No way.
- How is that possible? / - You're that flexible?
Are you hanging on?
- No. / - You're going backward.
Sookyung!
Why didn't you just stay on the boat?
- I wanted to see it. / - You're so funny.
- Because it's so close. / - It was too close.
- Look at your legs. / - You're holding on so dearly.
Help.
Wait. I'm not ready to meet you.
Don't come near.
(She is hanging on with her legs)
Look at that.
- In case it touches your legs? / - That's too much.
(But I'm cute, right?)
- It's so funny. / - Goodness.
- Are you okay? / - Yes.
There's a baby shark next to it. Is it its baby?
I don't think so.
It feeds on it's...
- It's a suckerfish. / - Suckerfish.
They clean the whale shark's body.
It sure is a shark. A suckerfish is stuck to it.
It cleans the body.
- Good? / - Good.
(Thanks)
Look. It's really close to me.
(They regroup and jump in for the second time)
(She's pointing at something)
- What did you see? / - What did you see?
That there are more?
There were a lot of whale sharks.
- Amazing. / - More came.
There were two, and then three.
Another one came because we were there.
- Goodness. / - They're standing.
- My gosh. / - I was surprised to see them stand.
(They keep opening and closing their mouths)
- She's saying there are 3 sharks. / - 3 sharks.
- Three sharks. / - Amazing.
(There are 3 sharks, not 2)
Gosh, it's huge.
(One shark)
It's hard to see even one in an aquarium.
- It's lovely. / - It's so cute.
They're hard to see, but there are three of them.
- Yes. / - It's so amazing that they're so close.
(There are three whale sharks)
(From above, you can see four sharks)
- Were there 4 sharks? / - Yes.
There are more of them than the boats.
Four sharks came.
- They came to have breakfast. / - Yes, for breakfast.
How can they look like that? They're so cute.
- They're so cute. / - Their mouths are so cute.
- It's so cute. / - Their eyes.
- It came. / - They're...
- It's huge. / - It's really big.
(Finally, they enjoy snorkeling)
Don't you feel blissful when you're next to them?
- You get overwhelmed, don't you? / - Yes, you do.
- I know that feeling. / - It's like a spaceship.
Yes.
Isn't it so pretty?
Everyone has fallen for the whale sharks.
I think Yujin will go there soon.
Me? I want to go.
Whale sharks are so cool!
I'm not scared.
I can say hi to them again.
When they are eating...
They suck in everything.
I felt like I was going to get sucked in too.
The mouth is huge.
- Really? / - Yes.
(Is someone talking about my mouth?)
How was it?
- It was fun. / - Was it? Really?
Why am I so tired?
(Snorkeling with the whale sharks is over)
Wasn't that so much fun?
- Seriously. / - I want to try that.
- Awesome. / - Was it Alright?
Yes.
You were so tired just now.
I was really tired earlier.
- But now I feel so refreshed. / - Really?
- Wasn't it fun? / - Yes.
Next up,
I'll take you to an even more amazing place.
- More than this? / - Yes.
You'll love it.
Everyone loves that place.
We didn't get to take pictures.
Yeah. Let's go take some photos.
We were so busy looking at the whale sharks.
- Let's go. / - Let's go quickly.
Let's take a quick shower first.
(Conquering the nature in Oslob, Cebu)
(Tumalog Falls)
You can swim in Tumalog Falls.
- Tumalog Falls. / - She studied really hard.
Nami must've studied very hard.
It was an inspiration for "Avatar."
- Did it inspire "Avatar?" / - Yes.
(15 minutes by car to Tumalog Falls)
We saw the sea...
Now the waterfall.
This is the entrance to Tumalog Falls.
We can't get in with a car.
Then do we have to walk there?
Do you see motorbikes here?
We can get there with a motorbike.
The motorbikes are the transportation
to Tumalog Falls.
- I was very popular there. / - Shall we ask for a ride...
- And go to Tumalog Falls? / - Okay.
- I'm nervous. / - Just trust me and follow me.
- Okay. / - Hop on.
(Motorbike ride, $1)
Honey, let's go.
- It's only $1. / - They're available from 7 a.m...
- To 4 p.m. / - Let's go.
It looks like Sookyung is experienced with motorbikes.
She's holding the grip with only one hand.
- She's experienced. / - That one-handed grip.
Honey, let's go!
(3 minutes from the entrance to the falls)
I've never heard of this.
Many people don't know about this place.
Nami,
it would've been horrible if we walked all the way.
Are we already here?
- 47. / - 47?
- 47. / - Yes.
- They'll wait there. / - You remember the number.
- See you. / - See you.
I feel like I'm suddenly in a jungle.
Right? Look at that.
- Okay, go. / - Thank you.
Isn't this a ticket?
- Thank you. / - The entrance fee is 40 cents.
- Yes. / - I like that it's so cheap.
- Sookyung! / - It's really amazing.
Hang on a second. This is insane.
I told you it'll be amazing.
- Their reactions are great. / - Sookyung is excited to...
Be outside of her home.
- I know. / - Everything is fascinating to her.
Sookyung is excited about everything.
- She is. / - It was really nice.
This makes the one who planned the trip so happy.
- It's amazing here. / - Hang on.
Hold on. It's amazing. Didn't I tell you that?
- Is it right there like that? / - Yes.
(Tumalog Falls is the biggest waterfall in Cebu)
(The falls is 100m high)
- The water falls from up there. / - It looks so cool.
- It's 100m high. / - 100m?
(There's one more special thing about this waterfall)
(The water is vivid emerald color)
- You can go into the water? / - Yes.
- That's amazing. / - We were there in the rainy season.
So there was quite a lot of water.
You have to go to Tumalog Falls in the rainy season.
- Sookyung, look at this. / - It looks awesome.
It's so cool, isn't it?
What is that?
Look at that color.
The color of the water is so beautiful.
Sookyung, this is the place that inspired "Avatar."
- This is the place? / - Yes.
- Really? / - It's based on this waterfall.
Even before Nami told me this,
as soon as I saw the falls,
I said it was just like in "Avatar."
- And it was actually related. / - Exactly.
Shall we go in as well?
I'm so cold.
Are you cold? Then you stay here. I'll go in.
- You can go in. / - Okay.
The water is ice cold.
(Nami goes into the water first)
(Excited)
It's so refreshing!
(She gets a waterfalls massage)
(Being under the waterfall reminds her of something)
(Training)
If you're a comedian...
That's a must.
Sookyung! It's so refreshing here.
Just trust me. Come here.
(She refuses)
But it's a waste not to go into such a beautiful place.
Sookyung, come on. Come here.
- Friend. / - Friend.
- Come down. / - Come down.
I asked them to say it.
(After much persuasion)
My goodness.
- My friend. / - She's coming.
- Friend. / - She's coming.
Friend, my friend. She's cold.
- Was it cold? / - The water was so cold.
It was really cold.
Sookyung, it's refreshing, isn't it?
(Sookyung and Nami had a lot of fun at the waterfall)
If it's like this, I'd love to jump in there.
It'd be amazing to be in cold water
in such a hot country.
It must be amazing.
(Nami is the most excited person)
I heard this is similar to
Cenote in Mexico, a natural swimming pool.
There's no need to go to Cancun.
- That's right. / - This is nearer.
- You can see whale sharks here too. / - Yes.
It's here! Don't come to me!
- Don't come to me! / - They're so cute.
- You have never done this? / - No.
- Really? / - Really.
Aren't they cute?
I've never seen doctor fish in nature.
There are so many. I must have so much dead skin.
I don't like being touched.
- Really? / - Yes.
I'll take what I can
since I never get touched.
This is amazing.
- They must've had a lot to feed on. / - They're here.
It tickles!
Sookyung's reaction is great.
(Great in reaction)
They were all firsts for me.
(Is it because she hasn't tried those things?)
(Sookyung and Nami have a relaxing time)
- They're having a party here. / - I know.
Now they're full,
shall we go eat something too?
- Sounds good. / - Let's go.
- Let's go eat something good. / - Okay.
A proper meal.
- Food. / - Now it's time for dinner.
It's time to have a proper meal.
(Hour 30 of the 52 Tour)
Are we really going to eat?
Of course.
This is where we're having dinner.
- It's a resort. / - Here? A resort?
They have Western food here. It's European.
They have European dishes.
(It's a restaurant in a resort right in front of the sea)
(Even if you're not a guest here, you can eat here)
It might be a good idea to stay here as well.
- Right? / - It's a great location to stay...
And do other activities.
We can eat with an ocean view.
It's a great location.
- There's a lizard over there. / - Where?
You're right.
It looks like a painting.
She is again fascinated.
- She's so fascinated. / - Everything's fascinating.
- Everything was fascinating. / - Right.
It's coming.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(The dishes go well with the open ocean view)
(The restaurant serves Filipino fusion dishes)
(A popular place for tourists)
(They start with a glass of beer)
- Wow, what is that? / - Is it a regular pizza?
Are there more tourists than locals in Oslob?
- Yes. / - There are a lot of tourists.
They serve Filipino fusion dishes.
- After swimming... / - It looks delicious.
- Pizza and beer are the best. / - Exactly.
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
(The beer is so refreshing)
- It's just like a soda. / - Is it?
- I normally don't drink. / - She can't handle her drinks.
But I drank just a bit.
- It's refreshing, isn't it? / - It is.
(A glass of beer after swimming is the best)
- Shall we start? / - What should I start with?
Do I start with the pizza or the pasta?
This is interesting. It's like noodles.
It's Filipino style.
- Isn't it like stir-fried noodles? / - Yeah.
- It looks delicious. / - It has meat in it.
- It looks delicious. / - It was.
- Everything was delicious. / - Everything is good.
After swimming, everything tastes good.
It was only $4.40.
It's like a fusion fried noodle dish.
It's not typical Italian pasta.
- It was a bit like Chinese food. / - Chinese noodles?
(It's similar to South East Asian fried noodles)
Why do they play Sookyung's footage in slow motion?
- Do it to Nami's footage as well. / - What about me?
- Sookyung was just moving slowly. / - Really?
Sookyung just moved slowly herself.
- This isn't played in slow motion. / - Let me see.
- Mine is just crunch. / - Listen to that sound.
- So great. / - The sound was so crunchy.
I think they make the dough and bake it here.
- It's really thin. / - It's very thin.
- It's crunchy. / - It almost looks like chips.
- It was so crunchy. / - This is unique.
- I like it. / - The dough is very thin.
It was crispy like chips.
(They enjoy their last meal in Oslob)
It's again played in slow motion.
- It's played in slow motion again. / - This is unfair.
Even her eating scene is in slow motion.
(We prepared Nami's slow motion video as well)
(Shampooing Nami, good to save on your computer)
(The night falls in Oslob)
- It's so beautiful. / - It is, isn't it?
It's really nice here.
Of the 52 hours of our tour...
- Already half has passed. / - It's so sad.
Is it? The tour is already half-over.
I just blinked my eyes three times
and it's half-over.
- We had too much fun. / - Did we?
Today, we enjoyed the nature in Oslob.
- Right? / - Yes.
Tomorrow, we're going to Cebu City.
We'll do things we can enjoy in a city.
So today's tour was about the nature.
- And tomorrow's is about city. / - It's a city tour.
(Day 2 is a city tour)
We should have fun tomorrow as well.
I'd like to propose a toast.
- Cheers to tomorrow. / - Cheers to tomorrow.
- You want to go there today, right? / - Right now.
- Before this is aired. / - Raeyeon is so going there.
She's convinced.
She's flying tonight.
I'd like to pack my bag already.
(Their exciting day is over)
(They enjoyed nature)
It's so cute.
- It's really cute. / - It's so nice here.
- We went to Cebu City. / - Cebu City.
You can experience two different places at once.
(It's new)
(It's a new way to enjoy the city view)
- Is that a ride? / - Let's not do that.
(There are endless variety of things)
I want to take this back to Korea.
(It's a feast of delicious foods)
- I can eat this the whole day. / - The food looks good.
I will never get sick of it.
- That was so delicious. / - It's so good.
It's a good thing we came here.
What is the thing you were eating, Nami?
- It's a jaw. / - It's a jaw?
You ate a whale shark?
- Come on. / - No.
I tried my best to diss them.
- It's been okay so far. / - It's so nice.
It's really nice, isn't it?
(Hour 16 of the 52 Tour)
- 52 Tour! / - You came alive again.
- Yes, we did. / - They're excited again.
Since we're in a city,
it feels somewhat different.
- Right? / - It does.
(Cebu City gives off a different vibe from yesterday)
Cebu City is really developed.
It's been over 10 years since I was there.
Really? It's totally different now.
Wow.
There weren't many skyscrapers back then.
- Nami, we're in Cebu City. / - Yes.
Where is our first spot?
As you know, the first spot is important.
- A good start is important. / - It was good yesterday.
- It was amazing. / - Right? Today...
We love fruits.
We're going to start the day with some fruits.
I was wondering what that was.
It's a cool bag.
You must eat fruits in those countries.
- You must. / - They have tasty fruits.
Fruits in the Philippines are very delicious.
- They're very sweet. / - They're incredibly sweet.
(Ramos Fruit market)
This market is called Ramos.
It's like Yeongdeungpo Fruit Market.
It's a fruit market.
We can pick whichever fruit we like.
- I like that one. / - It's good. It looks like a potato.
- Mangosteens are good. / - Mangosteen.
- Lychee. / - Lychee.
Tropical fruits are so delicious.
It's usually not easy for foreigners to shop in Cebu,
but I highly recommend this place.
A lot of fruit stands are there in a row.
Aren't the pineapples so cute?
This pineapple looks like a toy.
Right? They look like toys.
This one looks so delicious. It's a gold pineapple.
Shall we try some pineapples?
- Let's do that. / - It looks so sweet.
Excuse me. How much is it?
- 70. / - 70?
- Slice? / - Yes, slice.
You must eat many fruits there.
I thought it was on a tree.
Me too. I thought they were growing it here.
She cuts it right here.
- She looks so experienced. / - She does.
She cuts the pineapple for you right in front of you.
- The pineapple? / - Yes.
- This is fascinating. / - She's so cool, isn't she?
Sookyung, everything is fascinating, right?
To her, everything is new.
I was so happy. I liked everything.
(The gold pineapple reveals its yellow flesh)
It's so fresh.
It's indeed fresh.
(After peeling the skin, she carefully cuts out the rest)
It's interesting. They usually cut the middle part first,
but she peels the skin first.
She peels it as if she peels an apple.
By the way, if she keeps cutting it like this,
we might have only the core in the end.
- She's cutting out too much. / - No, she's an expert.
- Let her take care of it. / - Okay.
- Yes. / - It's done.
(The gold pineapple is ready to be eaten)
You can just eat it like that?
- Yes. / - How did she do that?
Can we eat the core of the pineapple?
The pineapple is so small that its core is very soft.
You can eat it as well.
- You can eat the core of it? / - She cut the cores.
(As soon as they got it, they try it)
- How is it? / - It's so good.
The core is usually too hard to eat,
but you can eat the core too.
(The core of gold pineapples is soft)
I've never seen a pineapple you can eat the core.
It feels like eating an ice cream.
- Pineapple ice cream. / - Pineapple ice cream.
It's so soft.
I love it.
- I'm curious about one fruit. / - What is it?
This. What is it?
- Santol. / - Santol?
- Let's try one. / - Shall we try one?
One, slice.
It looks hard. Maybe the knife is sharp.
I think the knife is sharp.
- It looks interesting inside. / - What is that?
- What is it? / - Something is inside.
You're supposed to eat what's inside.
What is that?
- What is that? / - How does it taste?
(How does it taste?)
(It's sour)
Is there fiber in it?
The whole fruit is big, but the flesh is so little.
- There's a seed as well. / - Its seed is also big.
It has a big seed? So there is little flesh.
It tastes like apricots and lychees.
(This is the flesh you can eat)
(Nami is interested in santol)
(Can I eat this?)
It's...
It's like a plum.
What did you eat?
- It was so bitter. / - It smells like a plum.
- Yes, it does. / - You're not supposed to eat it.
- The color is so pretty. / - Shouldn't eat that.
It's nice to have fresh fruits in the morning.
- They're delicious. / - I've never tried this before.
- It refreshes my mouth. / - It does.
- It feels refreshing. / - It was refreshing until...
I tried the skin.
It's bitter. I think I should eat something else.
Let's go eat something else.
Nami, we're in Southeast Asia.
We have to try the king of tropical fruits.
- Durian? / - Durian.
- Durian. / - I like Durians.
- Durians are good. / - You have to pick a good one.
- Durians have a strong smell. / - It's tasty, isn't it?
- No. / - Durians are...
(He tried a durian on his tour)
(They can't miss)
(The king of the fruits)
(It looks unfamiliar)
You'll start smelling it now.
(But it looks cute inside)
(Their first encounter with a durian)
(Sniffing)
The smell...
You have to eat it together with someone.
- You have to chew it. / - You shouldn't eat that alone.
It's delicious. It's really delicious.
What happened to Sookyung?
- I love durians. / - Durians are very delicious.
If you like durians, you should travel more.
- It's so ripe. / - I'm going to travel more.
Southeast Asia is a big place.
How does it taste?
It smells very uninviting at first.
(It's soft like avocados, and it melts in your mouth)
Its texture is like that of a ripe avocado.
Why am I sweating so much?
- I accepted the challenge. / - It was Nami's first time.
It tastes like it might not be completely ripe.
(She's hesitant)
Chew it.
(Her face tells how it tastes)
- Why? / - Hang on.
You can't help but react like that at first bite.
- If you're trying it for the first time... / - It was good.
I always say they should try three bites.
- You should try 3 bites. / - You should keep eating.
She's right.
(She takes another bite)
It's tasty.
- It's interesting. / - It's tasty, isn't it?
- It's really delicious. / - At first...
I almost threw up.
I'm not kidding.
Since you were enjoying it so much,
I had another bite.
- It's sweet. / - It's really sweet, right?
My body absorbed this smell.
Once you manage the first bite, it's good.
Why are you sweating so much?
After you eat that, you smell durian in your nose.
- I know. / - You keep smelling it.
- You keep smelling it. / - I keep smelling it.
We just tried a durian.
Now, let's eat the mangosteens that you like.
Okay.
(1kg of mangosteens, $8.40)
- It's delicious. / - Is it good?
- Have you tried this? / - Yes, I like this too.
I have never seen this.
This is delicious.
- You peel the skin and eat it. / - It's very delicious.
This one is very delicious.
I love this.
You can't stop eating it once you start, like peanuts.
- Have you tried this? / - Yes.
I like this one too.
I've never seen this.
- Let's take some. / - Shall we put some in the bag?
It must be very sweet. It made my hands...
- Sticky, right? / - It's so sticky.
Nami, now we had fruits...
- Sookyung. / - Are we going to walk around?
We're not walking around. Now we had fruits,
we have to go have an even more delicious meal.
We haven't tried seafood yet.
You're right. We're in an island.
Do you know what's important?
We're going to a restaurant that was never
on this show nor any other show.
- What is this? Is it seafood? / - Yes.
- It looks like meat. / - Is that a tuna?
- Is this the jaw? / - It looks like a tuna.
- It's a tuna, isn't it? / - That's correct.
That's correct.
- It's a tuna. / - It's a tuna.
It looks like beef ribs.
(Conquering the city of Cebu)
(A seafood dish that has never been on Battle Trip)
Sookyung, we're soon going to eat.
As long as you travel in the city,
I heard the taxies are cheap. Should we take a taxi?
Is it okay with you? Okay. Then let's take a taxi.
Taxi.
She calls a taxi as if she's a local.
- It looked so natural. / - She called a taxi.
- Taxi. / - Taxi.
(Basic cab fare, 84 cents)
You wanted to ride a jeepney, right?
- Yes, a jeepney. / - Yes.
But that's a little dangerous
and there are pickpocket problems.
- Really? Inside there? / - Yes.
- This is safer than a jeepney then. / - Yes, it's safer.
- And it's cheap. / - Yes?
It's cheaper than Korea.
This is more cost-effective when traveling in a group.
- It's cheaper. / - That's right.
- It's also hot. / - Yes.
- Isn't it so different? / - That's right.
It was all nature yesterday. Today it's city.
Cebu didn't have that many
high buildings 10 years ago.
- Yes, it was more... / - That's right.
- Natural-friendly. / - Many high buildings were built.
(You can enjoy various sides of Cebu in a short time)
(15 minutes by car to the seafood restaurant)
- Are we there? / - Yes, we arrived.
How much is 240 pesos?
It didn't even cost us $5 to come here.
- We came a long way. / - Yes.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
People are all moving busily.
I'm looking forward to it even more.
Look, there are a lot of locals.
(Nami picked a perfect local restaurant)
It's a popular place among locals.
- You must go to places like that. / - A family restaurant.
There were a lot of families. Like a family restaurant.
Let's order first.
Should we? I've been talking too much, right?
Excuse me?
Nami does everything.
Right.
- It's good. There are pictures. / - Yes, pictures.
I need pictures.
There's tuna.
- Fish... / - Yes.
- Fish? / - Yes, fish.
Fish?
That looks good.
- Is this alimango? / - Yes.
- Gosh. / - That looks really good.
Rice.
- Can I order a drink? / - Okay.
Nami is perfect.
Wow.
Panga.
It looks like pork ribs.
(She's carrying a tray full of food)
(It looks plentiful even at a glance)
(The seafood dishes of the 52 Tour)
I'm hungry.
- Wow. / - It must be a really big tuna.
It took a little long.
- They grilled everything. / - That looks so good.
Grilled tuna chin and alimango are both
rare in the Philippines.
If you go to a seafood restaurant,
you have to check the menu first.
- To see if they have it or not? / - Yes.
I've never had grilled tuna jaw yet.
- It was also my first time. / - I've never had it.
- It looks like meat. / - I was curious at first.
(Is this dish tuna jaw?)
- Doesn't it? / - I'm curious.
Wow, that's...
- I've never seen anything like this. / - That's right.
- They didn't have to do that. / - That's too much.
- That's cruel. / - That's so cruel.
Look at all that flesh.
(The grilled jaw is cut so tenderly)
- It looks like pork ribs. / - That's right.
- That's right. / - At a glance...
- It looks like pork. / - It looked undercooked.
- Isn't that right? / - Yes.
- We waited for a long time. / - Waited for a long time.
(What does the grilled tuna jaw taste like?)
It tastes a little like Okhotsk atka mackerel.
(Nami appreciates the scent first)
The flesh isn't flaky.
- The flesh is chewy. / - Yes, it's chewy.
- It doesn't seem like fish. / - Right.
Should we spray some of this on?
The scent will change if we spray this on.
The scent is so nice.
- I've only had that as drinks. / - Sprinkle that on.
It looks so good.
- We ate it plain at first. / - We sprinkled it ourselves.
It tastes a little different with the calamansi.
- The last taste would be fresh. / - It's really fresh.
When you go to the Philippines
and put calamansi in soju,
it tastes really good.
- That's the trend these days. / - It's like a cocktail.
(How is grilled tuna jaw with calamansi?)
- It has a particular scent. / - Yes.
But the scent changes...
When you squeeze the calamansi on.
- The tangy and sweet scent... / - Really?
- Makes it more flavorful. / - That's right.
I love it with calamansi.
(She squeezes calamansi without hesitation)
Add some more.
Why is it so sweet?
(Greatly satisfied)
They must have made a sauce that goes well...
- With the tuna. / - You're right.
- Koreans will love this taste. / - Yes.
You wouldn't know it was tuna jaw
if no one tells you about it.
Right? It's grilled tuna jaw.
It's called panga in the Philippines.
- Panga? / - Panga.
(The huge grilled tuna jaw isn't getting any smaller)
Why does it have so much flesh?
It's really big.
No matter how much we eat, it won't end.
- It has a lot of flesh. / - I want to eat it.
It has a lot of flesh. It must've been a big tuna.
That must be really good.
- That's a lot. / - It's like soy braised beef.
I think it will taste good with a little horseradish.
But here,
we'll eat it with calamansi.
(We strongly recommend it with calamansi)
(They fall in love because of the novelty)
(And because of the wonderful taste)
It's so good.
(Grilled tuna jaw! Panga!)
- The amount is plentiful also. / - Yes.
It's like a festival.
I'm also going to try the other food.
- I'm going to eat the crab. / - The crab?
(Alimango with chili sauce)
- It's a Filipino-style crab dish. / - Yes.
(Alimango with chili, $23.80)
I'm going to try the sauce first.
(The sauce that determines the taste of the dish)
- How is it? / - You have to mix it with rice.
- You need rice? / - Yes.
Is it a little spicy?
(Nami also tries a bite)
(She finally tries the crab meat)
- The meat is really good. / - Yes.
You're really picky when it comes to food.
- Is it good? / - Yes.
I can't drink alcohol but I wanted to drink
because it was so delicious.
Sookyung taught Nami how to drink,
and Nami taught Sookyung how to travel.
- That's right. / - That's right.
It's the best.
(Crabs taste the best when you eat with your hands)
You can eat the crab as a whole with Thai crab curry.
- But this one tastes stronger. / - Right.
Crabs in Thailand are softer
and they feel somewhat feminine.
This one, on the other hand,
tastes strong and passionate.
- That's right. / - Yes.
(Ah)
Ah.
(The young Nami is taking good care of her sister)
That looks good. It's good if you mix it with rice.
Seriously.
- Nami is doing good. / - Seriously.
- It's like marinated crabs. / - I've been to Yeosu.
- She eats it like marinated crabs. / - Yes.
(You can't eat crabs without eating rice in the shell)
It's so pretty, Nami.
(It tastes the best when you eat it in one bite)
Is it really good?
(The taste is spot on)
How is it?
(There's no need for words)
It feels like you're curing your hangover.
- We're full now. / - Yes.
What will we do next?
- We enjoyed nature in Oslob. / - Yes.
Now we have to see...
The panorama of Cebu City.
- At the observatory? / - Yes, at the observatory.
I planned a fun event.
(Conquering the Cebu City)
(Unusual city observatory)
(20 minutes by car to the city observatory)
The weather is really nice today.
- It's nice. Can you feel it now? / - Yes.
It really feels like we're on a city tour.
- Right? / - Where are we going right now?
There's a place where you see Cebu City in a glance.
- Really? / - Yes.
It's the highest building among all the buildings.
- In Cebu? / - Yes, among all of Cebu.
- Is it dangerous? / - No, it's not dangerous at all.
If it was dangerous, they wouldn't make it here.
- It's on the 38th floor. / - Yes.
- Even babies do it. / - Even babies do it?
You're talking about weird babies.
They always say that even babies can do it.
Did I see it wrong?
Are we going to do this?
Yes. Doesn't it seem like a lot of fun?
Do you want to do this or the skywalk?
I'll do this.
- This is better. / - Gosh.
- It's similar to the Las Vegas one. / - Yes.
- It's high. / - Gosh.
(A zip line across buildings)
- What is that? / - Gosh.
- That's so scary. / - There really isn't an age limit.
They restrict by people's height.
(But this is the reason why they came here)
- Gosh. / - Just the look of it is thrilling.
- Just the look of it is thrilling. / - This was so...
Even I was scared.
(A thrilling activity in the sky)
- I can't do it. / - Oh, my.
- Let's not do that. / - What is that?
That's ridiculous. I'm scared.
(Edge coaster and entrance fee, $11.60)
This view...
We can't see Cebu City in one glance.
- Right... / - Yes.
It'll relieve my stress.
I think they're going to make something for us.
Are they giving us safety regulations...
- And asking for our signatures? / - No.
It's just saying that it'll be fun.
It says that it'll be fun?
- That it's fun? / - Nami is doing a good job.
- Is it okay? / - It's okay. It's safe.
Won't it shake when the wind blows?
No, it's been 10 years since it opened.
They never had an accident.
- Where do you want to sit? / - But the view is...
- Really nice. / - Isn't it amazing?
It's so beautiful today.
- Isn't it beautiful? / - Yes.
I think we have a good range of visibility here.
- But it's too windy. / - Yes.
Help me? Really?
(She sits down frantically)
- It's done? / - Yes.
Okay, just hold here.
Or free hands, okay?
The view is really amazing.
What is this place?
Isn't this amazing?
The view is so nice.
- The view... / - But I wish I wasn't sitting here.
It would have been so nice.
Do you wish you weren't sitting here?
- Look, it's safe. / - What?
(Serious)
- All we do is just sit here, right? / - Yes.
As if you'd just sit there.
(She can't relax at all)
Slow, okay?
(52 Tour can't back down anymore)
- Let's go! / - Do you watch the view there?
- I also thought that at first. / - We're moving.
- I'm sure it would lean forward. / - Right.
- Oh, my God. / - It isn't that fast.
(Screaming)
What happened?
I didn't know that it would be like this.
It doesn't move straight. It tilts to the front.
(Edge Coaster starts tilting as soon as it moves)
What's going on?
(Oh, my)
- Are you looking down? / - As if you'll fall off?
Yes, it feels like you'll fall off.
(Thrilling)
(The beautiful panorama of the city is before them)
What are we going to do?
- That must be really scary. / - It really was.
(The thrilling charm of Edge Coaster)
- We kept going like that. / - Oh, my.
Nami! How can I enjoy this?
This isn't enjoying the view of downtown!
Are you sure it's not broken? Is it usually like this?
Yes, it goes like this automatically at first.
Hold on, how do I do this?
There we go. It's okay now.
- We can control it. / - I found out how to control it.
- Can you control it? / - I found out how to control it.
- Did you find out then? / - Yes.
- I was really scared. / - This is fun.
I think Sookyung will lose her voice from that.
Don't touch that.
- Don't touch that. / - Enjoy the view now.
- Can you control it? / - Yes, we can control it.
But we didn't know at first.
(She regained her peace of mind)
I wondered what this was for.
Look at that.
(After screaming, they saw picturesque views)
I can't see anything right now.
Look afar.
(It makes you feel like you can forgive anything)
No!
You have to do that.
(It's really entertaining for the viewers)
(Press)
(Excited, horrified)
This is really funny.
It must be fun.
It was fun.
Nami wouldn't have done...
Anything if Sookyung didn't react at all.
It's fun to tease people like her.
- Yes. / - It seems like she's laughing.
I think she's enjoying it.
No!
- She's playful. / - Yes, I'm playful.
- I wanted it to be fun. / - It's fun if you ride it like that.
This is so funny.
(Crying)
You're so adorable.
Why aren't they letting us get off?
Sookyung.
It's funny for the viewers to see you cry.
I don't want to show people this.
I want to be seen as the strongest person in the world.
Sookyung. Sookyung is crying.
She's still pretty.
- Isn't she so pretty? / - She's still pretty.
It's funny.
It seems like Sookyung is laughing.
(Nami enjoys teasing Sookyung)
It's so moving.
I can't explain this in words.
There's more to what you can see.
Please come here and experience it yourself.
- I want to kill you. / - Do you want to kill me?
We're going to eat...
- Your favorite food. / - She's crying.
- Yes. / - I'll do everything for you.
I made it so fun that she cried.
I'll do everything you want.
- I want to grab your hair. / - I'll let you grab my hair.
I have a lot of hair.
(Conquering the Cebu City, popular places)
(10 minutes by car from the observatory)
Is it already over? What?
- Is it already 52 hours? / - I feel sad.
- What a shame. / - Already?
It's such a shame that it's already the last day.
- This is the last location, right? / - That's right.
I heard it was nice if we end
the tour at a hot place.
This is the night market.
- The night market? / - You have to go there.
This place is called IT Park.
It feels similar to Korea's Cheongdam.
- Is this Cebu's Cheongdam? / - Yes, Cheongdam.
It feels like Cheonggyecheon...
That's right.
It feels like where there are a lot of food trucks.
- Doesn't it feel like that? / - Yes.
This place is called Sugbo Mercado.
"Sugbo" means Cebu and
"Mercado" means night market.
It's the hottest place in Cebu.
Does it open every day?
- Only on Thursdays to Sundays. / - Weekends.
- Can we go there on the weekends? / - Of course.
It starts from 5 p.m. to 1 a.m.
- You can eat before your flight. / - Yes.
That's so nice. It's a perfect course.
You should eat there and then go to the airport.
Since it's the last day, eat whatever you want.
Eat everything. There are also a lot of things to see.
What do you want? I want to eat that.
- "I want to eat that." / - That looks good.
- Let's have one each. / - That sounds nice.
- There are a lot of people. / - It's crowded, right?
- Since it's the weekend. / - You're right.
(The last bit of 52 Tour will start right now)
We should have come earlier.
It's been 3 years since this place has opened.
- About 3 years? / - Yes.
- I think it will be perfect... / - Yes.
If we end the trip like a festival and go back.
- There are so many good foods. / - This.
Do you want to eat this?
This is called lechon.
- You have to eat lechon. / - That's right.
Is that a baby pig?
You don't need anything else.
It's the traditional dish.
It's so savory.
It's a rare dish that they treat for guests.
- It's a whole pig. / - It's so tender.
I heard about this. It's a traditional Filipino dish.
Let's try a little.
The skin looks good.
- Let's try this. / - Wait in line.
Wait in line.
Everything grill?
(Crowded)
- Hello. / - Hello.
- The skewers look good. / - I want to eat shrimp.
- 99 pesos. / - Shrimp.
- Chicken? / - You need to eat one each.
(Chicken skewers and shrimp skewers)
(Pork skewers)
- Should we try one each? / - Okay.
- One, one, one. / - Yeah.
Thank you.
- Enjoy your food. / - Enjoy your food.
- It's a set. / - They have everything.
- That looks good. / - It looks good with the sauce.
(The last banquet they enjoyed before going home)
The grilled skewers were $3.10.
It looks good.
- Let's finish this and eat dessert. / - Okay.
- Thank you for the food. / - I'll try the lechon first.
(She tries the traditional Filipino dish, lechon, first)
(Crispy)
It's so good.
- I shot a movie in the Philippines. / - Yes, that's right.
I have a memory of this being really delicious.
- Really? / - Yes.
It's still good no matter when I eat it.
- It's good. / - It feels like I'm treated like royalty.
That's right.
It's so tender.
(It's delicious)
Eat the shrimp since we didn't get to eat them at all.
(They have shrimp for the first time)
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
(52 Tour fell in love with the charm of the night market)
It feels different from how it looks.
But it's good.
- How could it be so moist? / - Right?
This is perfect to eat with alcohol.
It's perfect for alcohol, but I'm afraid that we might
just stay here and eat when we have to go.
No, we can't do that.
We can't do that. That's why I'm holding back.
I love these Filipino peppers so much.
- Isn't it spicy? / - I brought it with me. It's spicy.
Should I also try it?
My mouth is on fire right now.
- Really? Is it that spicy? / - Yes.
Should I just try half of it?
- I can't eat spicy food. / - Oh, my.
- No, don't do it. / - Don't eat it.
(She tries fearlessly)
How is it?
- I knew that. / - How is it?
(The spiciness suddenly hit her)
It's spicy, right?
It'd be cool to ride the coaster while eating that.
That'd be crazy.
That'll make her mad.
It feels like I'm on a trip
where I experience extreme situations.
(The extreme experience she forgot about)
It's getting hot suddenly.
Are you okay?
Have some more of this.
I want to eat halo-halo.
- Do you want halo-halo? Okay. / - Yes.
- What's halo-halo? / - It's Filipino shaved ice.
I wanted to try something.
- Ice cream? / - Yes.
- What's mix? / - Mixed, you will have...
French vanilla and taro together.
I want that one.
That's also English. "I want that one."
- I want that one. / - They made bread themselves...
And placed ice cream on top of that.
- It looks so good. / - They eat that in France.
But they also make it there.
- Even the performance is perfect. / - Yes.
It's best performance.
- Oh, my. / - It has the devil's jam.
- What is that? / - It was amazing.
- It must be high in calories. / - What is that?
Oh, my. I can't believe it.
- Some people don't eat the cone. / - That's right.
- But they will eat all of that. / - That looks so good.
- Stop sprinkling. / - It will taste good until the end.
It's bad for your diet.
That ice cream...
Be careful, it's hot.
- It's very hot. / - Yes.
(They're enjoying their ice cream)
- What should we eat next? / - Halo-halo.
- Let's eat halo-halo. / - Okay.
We must eat something cold when it's hot.
That's right.
Halo-halo.
We have tropical.
Tropical.
What does halo-halo mean?
Halo-halo means to mix everything.
In Filipino, it means to mix everything.
It's shaved ice, but you mix a lot of ingredients in it.
It's pretty.
- It has ube ice cream. / - Ube ice cream?
The purple ice cream is ube.
(Halo-halo to blow away the heat)
(She finally takes a bite of halo-halo)
- Why? / - Try it. It's good.
Is it good?
(Enough to make them forget about the heat)
How is it? Isn't it good?
- Isn't it really good? / - Yes.
They all have different flavors. Isn't that right?
You won't get tired of it.
- I want to go there. / - You won't get tired...
Even if you hung out there until 1 a.m.
That's right.
I also saw this earlier.
- What do you want to eat? / - I saw this earlier.
What is this?
- There were so many things. / - Eat this and that.
You can enjoy eating everything.
- What is that? It's so cute. / - It's cotton candy.
I can't believe it.
Oh, my.
- Sookyung. / - Gosh.
(They're happy like little children)
Stay still. I'll take a photo for you.
Can you see it? Take it like this.
I should take it like that.
1, 2, 3.
(Just like when we were young)
- That's so adorable. / - That's so adorable.
- Hold it. / - 1...
1, 2, 3.
(Separated)
Get the straw.
- It's so hot that it's melting. / - Gosh.
I think the reason why
they put cotton candy on top of juice...
Is to stop the cotton candy from melting...
Since the weather is so hot and humid.
- It will be really sweet together. / - Yeah.
- Sookyung looks sugar high right now. / - Yes.
I really love sweets.
- I like sweets so much. / - It's really good.
(It's sweet)
Doesn't it melt in your mouth?
There's nothing left.
It disappeared in a second.
(52 hours are almost up)
We don't have a lot of time left
and this is the last stop for us.
We took a break from Friday to Sunday for 3 days.
(52 Tour spent their short time in the city and nature)
We saw the whale shark and went to the waterfall.
We spent today in a completely different atmosphere.
It was a short time but it felt like we were here...
- For a week to relax. / - Yeah.
For the last week...
I shot "Gag Concert,"
had meetings, had rehearsals
and came here right away after that.
I felt like an office worker.
I wish people would think that they will be able
to go on a trip after seeing me.
I had a sense of responsibility to provide fun.
52 Tour really used 52 hours...
Really well and beautifully.
I think these 52 hours will be the most
memorable days of this year for me.
(Hour 0 of the 52 Tour)
Nice.
- We won. / - They're our opponents...
If I was an office worker,
I think I would like to go on the weekend.
- That's right. / - I only need...
To see the whale shark to be satisfied.
Families will surely love the whale sharks.
- Of course. / - Yes.
If Seoeon and Seojun see this, they will make a fuss.
They will really enjoy it.
- Children will really like it. / - Is there anything...
To be aware of on the whale shark tour?
- You must wear a life vest. / - Yes.
You can't touch the whale shark
or do anything threatening to it.
Also, we can't stop or disturb their movements.
That's right.
What if the whale shark doesn't come out
because it doesn't feel like it?
- They might not be there, right? / - But those guys...
Have a sense of responsibility, so they'll be there.
- The whale sharks? / - Yes.
Can you see them every day?
As long as there isn't a problem with the weather,
they live around there.
- You'll be able to see. / - Also...
The government takes care of them.
- They're not locked up there. / - Right.
Let's check the expenses.
- Already? / - Are you confident about it?
- Of course. / - You saw the prices earlier.
I think they spent $500 to $600, at least.
- $500 to $600? / - For an average trip...
- For both of them? / - That's way too high.
Not including airfares,
what is the final expense?
- The expense. / - Per person.
In total...
$285.
($285 per person)
- That's quite cheap. / - It's really cheap.
- Isn't it so nice? / - Isn't it so good?
- It doesn't include airfares. / - Yes.
- With the hotel and snorkeling? / - Yes.
The pick-up service, entrance fee
and snorkeling equipment.
- All included. / - That's all included.
It's too cheap over there.
It's cheap.
We went to Oslob right after we landed.
So we didn't stay...
- At a hotel for the first day. / - That's right.
- We slept in the car. / - They slept in the car.
- They went to Oslob. / - They saved on a hotel.
People who were stressed from work
will feel better after seeing...
- The whale shark in the morning. / - Yes.
I think their plan deserves five stars.
It's because...
Okay, would you like to go to Cebu, Philippines
according to 52 Tour's plan?
Please vote.
(They planned a trip for last-minute summer vacation)
(What will the judges choose?)
We saw the Cebu trip.
Next week, the dream team will leave.
They really are the dream team.
- They can speak the language. / - Yes.
- They know good foods. / - They're gourmets.
Next week, we will reveal the Chengdu trip in China.
Please look forward to next week too.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(Next Episode)
I feel excited.
I see it, I see it. I saw a foot.
- Wow. / - Wow, this is it.
Sichuan and Chengdu equals...
- Panda... / - Oh, my goodness.
It's time to eat.
- Everyone will like this. / - Everyone.
This is the Anshun Bridge.
It's so pretty.
It expresses China perfectly.
(Battle Trip)
("Power Up" by Red Velvet)