I've chosen all the must-visit landmarks
of Bandung.
Men and women of all ages will enjoy this place.
Have a Bandung day!
Bye.
Sakhalin!
- We're in Sakhalin. / - Yeonwoo, this is Sakhalin.
I've been overwhelmed by the beauty of this place.
Yeah.
- I'm scared. / - No, no!
Screaming together
and not caring about anyone else.
I think that was so nice.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Just like last week, our special host this week
is Kim Hwan. Welcome.
- Welcome back. / - Hello, I'm Kim Hwan.
So are you the regular host now?
- No, our team lost last week. / - Yes.
I was so upset about it,
so I came again to win the battle this week.
If you keep losing,
you might be here as a permanent.
- I think that's better. / - Is it?
- That's the plan? / - He will lose again though.
I know. Our trip is so good this week.
Today,
we have very special trip planners.
So we will introduce the trip planners first.
They are special because they were our special hosts.
- That's right. / - Just like you, Hwan.
- They were right here? / - Yes.
Then this is a big match.
- A big match. / - Because...
- They know what to do to win. / - That's right.
They saw everything as they hosted the show.
They know what to do to get more votes.
So this will be a big match.
Let's meet today's trip planners then.
Please come on out.
(Who are today's trip planners?)
MOMOLAND!
(Lee Suji, Song Daeun)
(Jooe and Yeonwoo of MOMOLAND)
- We're going to win. / - We'll win.
- What makes you think so? / - Why?
Idols can't eat a lot.
Right, since they have to diet.
I heard Suji is on a diet as well.
- I'm not on a diet. / - Did you eat a lot?
I just eat three meals a day just like other people do.
That is also a type of diet.
Anyway, Suji was our special host...
- Back in May. / - That's right.
Right, it was the water festival special.
When were you our special host, Jooe?
A trip for 20-year-olds.
- That's right. / - A flower trip for 20-year-olds.
When your hair was yellow.
Yes, it was.
That's right.
Some of our special hosts
have come back as trip planners before.
But we've never had a battle between them like this.
It's the first time.
A big match is expected today.
- Suji. / - Yes?
Are you getting married soon?
- Right. / - Yes.
You're in trouble.
Why?
Please vote for her to congratulate her.
Don't say that.
We should bless her marriage.
- That's right. / - That's not the point.
By the way, it would've been good for Suji.
It might be your last trip
with your friend before your marriage.
It kind of was.
We had a lot of fun.
A trip with a friend is different from one with a lover.
But during the trip, I missed my boyfriend so much.
Then every time you had spare time,
you must've called your boyfriend like this.
Actually, my boyfriend is 3 years younger than me.
(Her boyfriend is younger than her?)
- Age doesn't matter. / - Right.
- Congratulations, Suji. / - Thank you.
Let's start the trips then.
I heard they went to special places for their trips.
Today's theme of Battle Trip is...
Hidden destinations
you must visit before everyone finds out about them.
It'll no longer be a hidden destination after this.
- Right. / - Let's find out where they went.
Let's check out where they went.
What? Sakhalin?
Sakhalin and Bandung?
- Sakhalin is very famous. / - Bandung in Indonesia?
- Sakhalin. / - Bandung.
I've never heard of Bandung before.
Have you heard of it?
Have you heard of Bandung?
What about Sakhalin?
- I've heard of Sakhalin. / - See?
They've heard of Sakhalin.
I saw it in a history book.
Please tell us about Bandung. It's very new to us.
I think there are two important things about traveling.
- The first one is photos. / - Yes.
- And the second one is food. / - I see.
- Food is the most important. / - Food is crucial.
You're right. It has to suit your tastes.
If it doesn't, it will ruin the whole trip.
And we got them both.
- In Bandung? / - I'm very confident about it.
- Let's take a look at the map. / - Where is Bandung?
- It's over there. / - It's near Jakarta.
- Jakarta? / - It's over there.
It's between Jakarta and Bali.
It's not near the coast though.
- Right, it's a city. / - It's an inland area.
Bandung is the most popular vacation place...
- For weekend trips for Indonesians. / - Really?
It's like Gapyeong in Korea.
- Exactly. / - Why?
The interesting thing is that the area is highlands.
So despite it being a hot country,
the weather is cool in Bandung.
I sweat a lot
but I didn't get hot when I was walking around.
Okay. What about Sakhalin?
We've heard of Sakhalin before.
That's right. We went to Sakhalin.
- Right. / - Wow.
- I just applauded with her. / - I admit...
Sakhalin is not new to us.
- Let's see where it is. / - Let's take a look at the map.
It's close to Korea.
- It's close. / - It's above Vladivostok.
We've been to Vladivostok.
It's the biggest island in Russia.
Around 12% of the island's population is...
- Korean. / - What?
- Is Sakhalin an island? / - Yes.
You didn't even know that, right?
- I didn't. / - See?
But I've heard of Sakhalin.
But we didn't know it was an island.
We have a painful history about the island.
- That's right. / - That's right.
- How was the trip, Jooe? / - Well...
- I've been to Vladivostok before. / - Really?
When I went there,
I didn't know what there was to see.
But you know what?
I didn't know there was Europe so close by.
- That's what I thought. / - European-style buildings.
- In Sakhalin? / - That's right.
To be honest...
- Did you like it or not? / - I loved it.
- Why? / - First of all...
When I travel abroad,
I'm worried about the language problem.
But there are a lot of people who speak Korean.
- There are many Koreans. / - Since 12% are Korean.
And there were many biracial people.
They even said...
- Hello to us in Korean. / - Really?
- Russian people did. / - It must've been intriguing.
Alright then.
Please enjoy the trips and cast your vote.
We have our 100 judges here. Nice to meet you.
- Welcome. / - Good to see you.
Hello.
You can vote for both trips,
it's not just one or the other.
But you might as well
wish the future bride well.
Let's congratulate her.
- Bandung. / - Let's go to Bandung first.
- Can we go first? / - Sure.
Let's find out how to get to Bandung.
- From Incheon airport. / - You fly to Jakarta first.
- There's no direct flight. / - Go to Jakarta...
Once you get to Jakarta,
you have three options.
You can take another flight.
- You can take the train. / - It's very far.
- Or a bus available till late at night. / - A bus.
I heard you can take the best photos of your life there.
Why is that?
The entire city of Bandung is
like a theme park.
- The whole city? / - Yes.
When you're on a trip,
you can feel wary of others as you take pictures.
But you don't have to do that.
People just go there...
- To take good pictures. / - For the photos.
So did you get some awesome photos?
- We got plenty. / - You did?
I really got a lot.
Sook loves to take photos.
I do.
I just like shots.
You mean drinking shots?
What currency do they use in Indonesia?
- It's rupiah. / - Rupiah.
Remove two zeros from the 10,000 won.
Then you get 100 won.
Then you multiply that by 8.
- 800 won? / - Yes. So it's 80 cents.
So 10,000 rupiah is about 800 won or 80 cents.
It will be so fun to spend money.
It was. Prices are so low too.
- It would feel great. / - Yes.
How did you like the trip, Daeun?
These days, it's a bit worrying
to travel around Indonesia.
But Bandung is quite far from the disaster.
So we didn't have to be concerned about safety.
It's not a region where earthquakes happen often.
- Right. / - In terms of the geography.
- Then, shall we go first? / - Yes.
What's your team name?
We are SuDa Signal!
(SuDa Signal Tour's trip to Bandung starts now)
(KBS open radio studio)
(The visitors look excited)
It's an open radio show.
(Lee Suji)
(Comedienne and radio show host)
Our Suji.
(She eats while listening to the song)
(She's focusing on her food)
(Song Daeun)
(Starred in "Heart Signal 2," regular guest on the show)
(Daeun became famous through a reality dating show)
(They host the radio show together every Friday)
She's the guest host on Friday.
(Suji and Daeun became close meeting every week)
So we're becoming travel mates.
That's right.
- Gosh, I'm honored. / - I'm pleased to be with you.
What is the place you wanted to go to the most?
I really wanted to go to Bali,
so I even bought the ticket about 3 times.
Really? I also wanted to go to Bali.
It's a famous vacation spot.
And Battle Trip went to Bali before.
- That's right. / - The married couple special.
I wanted to try the swing.
That's where you can take the best shots.
It was with Park Jiyoon.
That looks so cool.
I want to take the best shot of my life there.
Like that?
A lot of people wanted to go there.
- Taking good photos is important. / - You're right.
I wanted to go to
a beautiful place when I'm pretty...
- And leave a lot of good photos. / - Exactly.
- It's important. / - It's important.
It's the second most important after food.
- We connected. / - It is very important.
It is.
I feel a bit of pressure.
- I was a special host of the show. / - You were.
I'm sure I have some tips.
In my opinion, we should focus on something new.
Something new?
That's right.
When we think of Indonesia...
- We think of Bali. / - Right.
- It's a very typical place to go. / - It's true.
We should show them something new.
We should make people think,
"They went there?
There's such a place in Indonesia?"
We should find a place that makes people say that.
The Asian Games were recently held in Indonesia.
- They were held in Jakarta. / - Right.
No one has gone to Jakarta, right?
No one has. Let's check out the cities of Indonesia.
Major cities in Indonesia are Jakarta.
- Surabaya. / - Surabaya.
- Makassar. / - Indonesia is quite big.
- It's very big. / - This country has the most islands.
Medan, Bandung...
- Cirebon. / - Where is Cirebon?
We're going to an airport in Jakarta, right?
- Yes. / - Right?
Shouldn't we go to somewhere in the center?
- How about Tegal? / - Cirebon, Bandung...
Those are on our list.
I remember Korea playing soccer in Bandung.
The Bandung match.
Indonesia... Suji, I'll search
hashtags on social media.
- Okay. / - It's a country of islands.
(Searching the posts with the related hashtags)
People search with hashtags these days.
Then you spend an hour looking at
other people's best photos.
- That's right. / - Seeing where they took photos.
- Suji. / - Yes.
- Wait a minute. / - What?
What is it?
- I really want to go here. / - Let's see.
Isn't this really floating?
- Oh, my gosh. / - It's amazing, isn't it?
This is awesome.
- It was really fascinating. / - It was totally awesome.
- What picture is it? / - I thought it was photo-shopped.
- Let me see. / - Look.
(A floating carpet)
- What is that? / - What's that?
- It's a carpet. / - A carpet?
Isn't it fascinating?
- What is that? / - It was really fascinating.
He's standing on the carpet.
Look at this.
What is that?
There's a mountain in the background.
Try to look beautiful.
(Oh, my goodness)
(Princess Suji will ride on the carpet soon)
(Roaring)
(Will she get to take an awesome picture?)
She looks terrified.
That looks like a penalty.
- Look at her. / - This is a penalty.
This is unbelievable.
(Will they manage to take great pictures?)
- It looks amazing. / - Suji, let's go here.
Do you know the animation?
(They sing together)
- We should do this. / - You be Princess Jasmine.
- Okay. / - I'll be Aladdin.
Thank goodness. I usually don't get to play the woman.
- So this is in Bandung? / - Yes, it's in Bandung.
Let's do this. Let's search Bandung.
Welcome to the fantastic city, Bandung.
- Is that grass? / - Yes.
- Real grass? / - Doesn't it look like a theme park?
Is that real grass?
(Indonesia is on the equator and it's usually very hot)
(But Bandung is in the upper regions)
The average yearly temperature is 22.3℃.
It should be just like here now.
That sounds great. I can't stand hot weather.
Check this out. It almost looks European.
Look at the flowers.
(An exotic city with European style buildings)
- They have European buildings. / - It's like Europe.
- It's so pretty. / - It's pretty, isn't it?
- It really is. / - It's really nice to take pictures.
It developed into a tourist city by the Dutch.
That's why.
- It was colonized by the Netherlands. / - The history...
Helps us understand a lot of things.
Daeun, do you have any suggestions?
Suji, Daeun.
- SuDa? / - SuDa?
How about SuDa Signal?
SuDa Signal? That doesn't sound bad.
SuDa Signal.
- Do you like it? / - Should we go with that?
How do you send a signal?
Was it like this?
(They decided on SuDa Signal for their team name)
I like it. Then how about...
We rate each other's tour at the end of the day...
- By sending a signal? / - Aren't we being too strict...
- On each other? / - No, no.
We're a team. We shouldn't be strict on each other.
Yet, we should stay objective.
What is this?
Goodness.
It was so delicious.
I'm not kidding, it's so good.
(Daeun loves food more than Suji does)
(Daeun will be in charge of eating show)
- She can eat a lot. / - She's really something.
- We won. / - She eats a lot.
- The quiet eater type. / - She's basically inhaling.
(She's cute and sexy at the same time)
(Princess Suji will be in charge of loveliness)
(A trip with Suji and Daeun)
(Let's discover Bandung with SuDa Signal Tour)
(Incheon International Airport)
Off we go.
(It's time to check in)
I love this place.
- It makes you excited. / - It does.
It's the most exciting moment.
Checking in your luggage.
(Heading off to board the 5:15 p.m. plane)
(After a 7-hour flight, they arrive in Jakarta)
- It isn't over. / - It isn't.
The air is hot.
In the plane, the pilot made an announcement.
"The current temperature in Jakarta is 29℃."
"I wish you a nice trip." This is what he said.
You said it takes 35 minutes by airplane...
- And 3 hours by bus or train. / - That's right.
Since we don't have much time, let's keep going.
We'll take a night bus.
- It'll take from 3 hours... / - We arrived late.
- To 3.5 hours. / - So we're taking a bus.
We need to travel further.
This is the way to the bus stop.
Ticket, Bandung?
Yeah, Bandung. Two people.
(From 7:30 a.m. to 12 a.m.)
(Bus comes every 30 minutes)
11:59 p.m.?
115 rupiah.
I was shocked because I thought it was $115,
but it's just $8.50.
$8.50.
(They finally get on the bus to Bandung)
The seats are very comfortable.
It was a very comfortable bus.
The seats were very comfortable.
(They leave Soekarno-Hatta International Airport)
You should've slept on the bus.
- We slept a bit. / - We slept sound.
(3.5 hours to Bandung Bus Terminal)
It's embarrassing to be holding a camera now.
We finally arrived in...
- Bandung. / - Bandung.
I look a bit... Could you please blur my face?
- What happened? / - I slept too much.
- It's past 3 a.m. now. / - It is.
Let's wake up tomorrow morning
and start the tour while we're clean, moist...
- And cool. / - Let's make ourselves look pretty.
As you know, tomorrow is Suji's Day.
Suji's Day?
- You mean the first day. / - Yes, I planned that day.
There are must-visit landmarks in Bandung.
I'll take you to each and every one.
Hello!
A garden in the city.
So pretty!
So elegant.
(You can taste delicious local foods)
That's so pretty and cute.
This tastes so good.
Hot place.
(They get great shots at popular spots for locals)
(Take photos and eat again)
Bandung is the best city in Indonesia.
(Bandung Tour, Suji's Day)
(Tour bus, lunch in Braga Street)
(Floating market, rooftop cafe)
(Their first day in Bandung begins)
(Bandung's morning is busy)
(Due to the high altitude, the city is full of green)
It's unique. It's like a city...
- But there are also mountains. / - That's right.
- Our first day has started. / - Yeah!
Suji, did you sleep well?
I slept very well. Too well, even.
- I slept very well too. / - By the way...
I'm already in love with Bandung.
- I know what you mean. / - Even before the start.
- What do you think it is? / - It's the weather.
- Correct. / - Right?
I had no idea Bandung had such nice weather.
Since Bandung is in a high altitude region...
- It's not so hot. / - I was wearing long sleeves...
- But I wasn't sweating at all. / - I love it when...
- You can wear both short and long sleeves. / - Right.
This is the best Southeast Asian city I've been to.
It's the best. It's so dry. I must record this.
Look at how dry it is. Bandung is a blessed city.
Suji, by the way, why are we here
early in the morning?
- Is there something here? / - Let me tell you why.
- This is our first time in Bandung. / - Yes.
We're going to the must-see landmarks in Bandung.
I'll take you to each one.
The city tour bus will show us around on my behalf.
He'll pick us up here.
I was about to say that you're so cool.
- It's that way. / - It's fun to...
- Scan the city on the first day. / - Let's take the bus.
Okay, let's go.
Look at that.
(A tour bus where the guide introduces major sights)
What is that?
- The door is open. / - Depending on the color...
The destinations differ.
- The door is wide open. / - So pretty.
It costs just 80 cents.
- 80 cents? / - Yes, 80 cents.
We're going to take the yellow bus.
So we're here waiting at this stop.
- Suji, look at that. / - It's so cute.
- This is really cute too. / - It was very European.
Doesn't it feel like we're getting on a carriage?
- Okay. / - This is how you get on it.
(With Daeun's escort, Princess Suji gets on the bus)
- It's open here as well. / - What is that?
It's pretty.
It's very pretty.
How are you?
That's an Indonesian greeting.
- How are you? / - How are you?
- Here we go. / - It's finally moving.
Let's go.
The city tour bus is taking off.
Here we go.
- It's so pretty, isn't it? / - It's pretty.
The roads are so clean.
Bandung Tour on Bus.
Yes, Bandung tour.
Now, we are on the way...
A guide explains the landmarks.
(The tour bus enters downtown)
- Main street? / - This is the main street.
- This is so pretty. / - Asia-Afrika.
We call it. Long time ago in 1952, Bandung had...
- It's beautiful. / - Asia-Afrika conference.
On the right side, this is the second oldest hotel.
Alun Alun.
- Alun Alun! / - It's a big city center.
- It's like the city hall in Seoul. / - Plaza? That's right.
"Alun" means plaza.
- So Alun Alun is Plaza Plaza. / - Plaza Plaza.
The biggest mosque of Bandung is in this Alun Alun.
- The biggest mosque. / - It's beautiful.
(This symbolic landmark is the center of Bandung)
- It's grass over there. / - Yes, yes.
- You can go in without shoes. / - Without shoes?
Kids will love that.
- Of course. / - They go in without shoes.
How great is that? Kids love green, you know.
- Braga Street. / - Braga Street!
- Braga. / - That street is so pretty.
Look at the drawings.
(Many European-style buildings were built by the Dutch)
(Who have begun to plan the development of Bandung)
There are a lot of cafes and restaurants.
- Let's take a walk on Braga Street. / - Sounds good.
- Is this the crosswalk? / - That's right.
It's so cute.
They made sure even a crosswalk was artistic.
- What's that? A crosswalk? / - That's how they look.
- Crosswalks are cute. / - It's like hopscotch.
- Let's go and step on each square. / - Let's go.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, success!
(The joy of travel is appreciating the destination as is)
Good job. Well done.
Well done. We need to become fit princesses.
- Look at that! Braga Street! / - Braga Street!
Isn't that really pretty?
- Seriously. / - Even the signboard is pretty.
Daeun, look at that building.
Doesn't it look like a clock tower?
- It's the Eiffel Tower. / - Daeun.
I said I wanted to go to Bandung.
Why did you bring me to Paris?
Bandung has a nickname.
It's known as the Paris of Java.
- The Paris of Java? / - Yes.
You can see traces of Europe here and there.
It was fun to look around.
In Korea, we have the Miss Korea beauty pageant.
There also is a beauty pageant in Indonesia.
A lot of winners are from Bandung.
Really?
City of beautiful women.
- We ought to sit on this chair. / - Right.
Yes, I'm a beautiful woman.
That's right. I'm pretty.
They waved at me.
- They did. / - They like you.
Every single building was pretty there.
- It is pretty indeed. / - Daeun.
- We're finally here. / - The architecture is pretty.
- This is it. Isn't this pretty? / - Yes.
(It's a cafe and a restaurant for their first meal)
Let's go into this Art Cafe.
I can't wait.
This part has the bar.
At night, you can have drinks here.
(A cafe in the afternoon, a bar in the evening)
- Look at all the liquor. / - There's a lot, right?
It's pretty. Photos would look great in the cafe too.
- They would look vintage. / - It's so pretty.
The atmosphere was great.
- Daeun, there's a 2nd floor too. / - Such a pretty cafe.
It was so pretty.
My goodness.
Welcome. This is the garden.
- It's nature itself. / - Exactly.
This is the most suitable cafe to relax on this trip.
True nature.
How did you find this cafe?
(They will enjoy an Indonesian lunch here)
Southeast Asian cuisine... Wow.
- We should sit here. / - Should we?
It's sunny on this side.
Here's my princess.
Here we go.
(Photos in the garden of a city center)
The photos turn out great here.
Isn't it so pretty?
It's so pretty.
- You look great. / - Each photo is a work of art.
You look so pretty. You're beautiful.
Every photo here looks like an art.
- What do you think? / - I'm very satisfied.
- You're very satisfied? / - Yes.
First off, we need to have our meal at a nice place.
That's how we'll get to enjoy it.
Let's get some food since we're hungry.
I'm so hungry.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Recommend? / - Okay.
Fried rice... And mie goreng.
"Nasi" means rice.
"Mie" means noodles. "Goreng" means stir-fry.
It's stir-fried rice and noodles.
- You have to eat nasi goreng. / - You must.
Three. Okay.
- It's just the two of us but we eat like three. / - Okay.
Do you like spicy?
- I like it. / - No, no.
- A little bit? / - No, no.
- Normal, normal. / - Okay.
- It already sounds delicious. / - When you're abroad...
Very spicy isn't that spicy for Koreans.
That restaurant was famous for spicy food.
That's why we asked for a normal level of spiciness.
If you order everything with just that.
This place has to taste good for Koreans.
It'll be good no matter what.
(Nasi goreng, $2, braised short ribs, $4.20)
(Mie goreng, $2.20, 2 cups of mango juice, $3.20)
(Nasi goreng and braised short ribs)
- That looks so good. / - It's mie goreng.
(And there's mie goreng too)
Goodness, that looks really good.
This is very spicy. Extra spicy. This is a little spicy.
- Very spicy? / - Yes.
- Okay. Thank you. / - Thank you.
Which one should we try first?
- You didn't order that much. / - Let's eat.
- It's nasi goreng. / - That's right.
- It's a representative dish. / - Exactly.
- Let's try nasi goreng first. / - Nasi goreng?
- $2.20. / - It was only $2.20.
I can smell the spiciness.
Yes, I can feel it right away.
Let me try it.
(How does it taste?)
- This is spicy. / - It's that spicy?
- Is it really spicy? / - Seriously?
What was the level of spiciness we chose?
I thought it was normal.
- We asked for normal. / - Wasn't it normal?
But they gave us very spicy.
You can choose the level of spiciness.
If you can't handle spicy food...
Just pick the least spicy one.
- Even Koreans have to... / - Really?
- Choose the least spicy level? / - Yes.
I guess it's really spicy.
From the second spoonful,
I can taste its authentic flavors
instead of just spiciness.
I like this dish because it doesn't have a lot of spices.
It's not overwhelming.
Of course, it'd be delicious.
- Try it with the rice. / - I'll just drink water.
(They try it with the Indonesian chip this time)
- Is it good? / - Seriously.
- You know shrimp snacks in Korea? / - Yes.
- It tastes like that. / - It's delicious.
- We don't need spoons. / - That's delicious.
You don't need spoons.
(You can use the crispy snack as your spoon)
- You can eat that spoon. / - She's like a local.
The chip is really good.
The salty shrimp chip and spicy rice go well together.
- We'll try the mie goreng. / - Mie goreng.
- I was curious about this dish. / - Stir-fried noodles.
It's like instant noodles.
- Stir-fried noodles. / - It only costs $2.20.
- Mie goreng. / - Goodness, it's so cheap.
(They twirl the noodles and eat in one bite)
The noodles were really chewy.
You know the seasoning in instant noodle snack?
It tastes just like that.
You're right.
- I really like this dish. / - Same here.
I'll try it with the egg.
It'll go so well together.
- Eat with the egg. / - That looks great.
How is it?
- Take that out now. Hurry. / - Why?
- It's not good? / - The noodles alone taste better.
Just enjoy the taste of the noodles alone?
Aren't you stopping me so you can eat it alone?
I knew it, you brat.
Let me try it.
I didn't want her to eat it.
You wanted to keep all the good food to yourself?
You thought Suji wouldn't eat it?
(This is so delicious!)
Why did you try to stop me?
It's really delicious.
- Everything was tasty. / - I thought so too.
- Really? / - It's to die for.
Let's try the braised short ribs.
(Indonesian-style braised short ribs, $4.20)
- That dish, my goodness. / - That was so good.
- Really? / - That one was a bit expensive.
- It was 50,000 something. / - Braised short ribs?
- Braised short ribs? / - It's $4.20.
- What? $4.20? / - Those are oxtails.
- $4.20 for short ribs. / - Yes.
That looks good.
- Let me eat from the bone. / - Okay.
(The meat falls off the bone)
It's chewy. What is this? How could it be so chewy?
- It's oxtail. / - That has to be delicious.
It was so tender.
- But it's $4.20. / - Yes.
Let's try this with rice.
This is braised with the sauce nicely.
- And it's very tender. / - It's tender. It looks so good.
Let me try it like this.
(Daeun will try the chip, rice and meat together)
- Let me have a bite of this. / - Okay.
(Crunch)
The chip we had earlier and this one taste different.
- This tastes like a corn chip. / - Really?
- Even the colors seem different. / - Yeah.
- Corn chip? / - Yes.
You can really smell it.
- It neutralizes the spices. / - It neutralizes the aroma.
Okay. Then I'll try it with this.
Listen to that.
Exactly. It's a corn chip too.
Right? It neutralizes the smell.
- It's savory. / - Yes.
They also give you soup with that.
- It's kind of like short rib soup. / - I see.
Let me try the meat with the soup together.
That sounds good.
- That looks good. / - You have to dunk it in the soup.
To make it moist.
Is it perfect?
It's perfect. This tastes all different
when you eat just the meat, with the chip
and with the soup.
- It depends on how you eat it. / - It tastes different.
With the soup.
(The meat is dunked into the broth)
(It makes the meat even more tender)
It tastes different, right?
- Suji is doing well. / - If she's frowning like that...
It means it's really good.
I can just swallow the meat as is.
No need to chew.
It's so delicious.
(That was a good meal, I'm full)
We're not done yet.
Dip it in the egg yolk.
She's just getting started.
Seriously.
(Shaking her head)
Could you please fast forward the video?
The part when she's eating.
(She gracefully moves her fork and spoon)
- And the soup... / - You eat so well.
I felt bad, so I stopped eating.
Suji, I expected you to eat more.
I'm a sprinter and she's a marathoner.
- We're satisfied with our meal. / - Yes.
We're full, so what should we do?
We need to digest.
What should we do to digest?
(Sending her a signal)
Cafe?
- Shopping? / - You got it.
Shopping?
We'll shop Bandung style.
- Bandung style? / - I'm curious.
(Bandung Tour, Suji's Day)
(Floating market)
(The market is 45 minutes away by car)
- Now that we're full... / - Yes.
We need to walk a little bit.
- Shopping. / - Shopping.
We need to shop.
We'll buy stuff
and eat some street food too.
We'll have some dessert there.
I'm curious about the floating market.
It's not your typical floating market.
The space is huge.
- It's so nice. / - It is.
- It's so pretty. / - It's pretty.
- It's like a theme park. / - What's that?
Wow, that looks good.
That was good.
- Look at that. / - What's that?
- It's a steamed bun. / - Take a look.
Look how popular that place is.
It's a floating market,
but it's a tourist area with a lot to see.
- That's hanbok. / - It's great for dates.
It's like an amusement park.
- Wasn't that hanbok? / - It's like an amusement park.
They wear hanbok and BTS songs are played there.
Lots of BIGBANG and BTS songs.
They had a lot of interest in Korea.
That's interesting.
- Daeun, look at that. / - Yes.
What are those?
- It says floating market, right? / - Yes.
I'll tell you what it is.
In this market,
you have to use those tokens.
They have coins that are only used there.
Yes, like tokens.
The whole market is like a theme park.
We'll get some tokens
and buy some stuff.
On our right are souvenirs.
(Bandung specialty tea leaves)
Shall we do some shopping?
(Indonesian traditional batik store)
- That's thick. / - It is thick.
(Suji tries on a hat)
- It's pretty. / - That's cute.
- She should buy it. / - Is it nice?
- That color is great. / - It's really nice.
- We should look at this shop. / - Shall we?
- I think this is pretty. / - That's pretty.
(She shops for her partner, Suji)
This skirt is nice too.
(She picks out a matching top for the skirt)
I found it.
It's really nice.
- I found a good one. / - That's really nice.
Isn't it really pretty?
Isn't it pretty? Come this way.
They're like mother and daughter.
(They're wearing fabulous Indonesian fashion)
- It's pretty. / - The fabric was really nice too.
(From head to toe, they're wearing a similar look)
Look! This is the floating market!
They're really floating on the water.
- Skewers. / - Skewers.
At first, when I heard it was a floating market....
I thought we were going to ride a boat and shop.
The boats are just docked there.
- But it's the vendors. / - Their boats are docked.
Yeah.
- If we're going to buy food... / - Yes.
Do you see that? There's a money exchange.
Here, we'll exchange money, then we'll buy food.
- Let's exchange a lot. / - Okay.
Please exchange that.
(This much?)
She's surprised.
- "Will you eat that much?" / - That much?
That's a lot.
- The tokens can't be refunded. / - Right.
- Exchange only necessary amount. / - That's a shame.
So we just took the leftover tokens as souvenirs.
- That's the braised short ribs we had. / - We had it.
They have noodles too.
- That's nasi goreng. / - Goreng.
Durian!
- Durian. / - Durian.
I've had it once before. It was delicious.
- Durian is dangerous. / - Shall we try it as a dessert?
I've never had it before.
- Try it. / - I'll try it.
Oh, banana!
Fried banana.
It smells so sweet.
Good spots have people lined up, as expected.
- Let's line up. / - We'll wait.
(Fried banana looks good)
- I'm curious. / - It looks really good.
She keeps cutting the banana over there.
Ripe banana is so good.
- It's fried banana. / - That's 20,000 rupiah.
With cheese?
- I think it's cheese. / - Cheese?
- There's sauce too. / - Kaya sauce?
That should be delicious.
- It's kaya sauce. / - Kaya sauce.
- Okay. / - That looks amazing.
That's 20,000 rupiah, so it's $1.50.
- Yes, $1.50. / - Seriously.
- Isn't it really hot? / - Yes.
(Yummy)
It tastes like sweet potato with banana flavor.
Does it taste like sugar glazed sweet potato wedges?
It's kind of like sweet potato fries.
When they battered it...
The bananas looked white.
- It's yellow now, right? / - It's yellow inside.
This yellow sauce.
Doesn't it taste like mango?
This white stuff on top is...
Grated cheese.
This mango sauce tastes fresh.
Kaya sauce.
(She's into fried banana)
- I want a bite. / - It's fun to eat at a market.
- The sauce is so sweet. / - It's really good.
Let's pick some food.
- And sit down to eat. / - Sounds good.
Goodness.
Doraemon.
- Yes. / - So cute.
- It's so pretty. / - They're mini buns!
How can you eat that?
That's so cruel. How could you eat that?
(Character buns, $1.50 each)
Thank you.
- Skewers. / - Skewers.
Suji, skewers!
Gosh. It smells so good.
What's the best? What's popular?
- Skewers. / - That looks really good.
- That looks awesome. / - You can't walk past that.
They always smell so good.
This looks like chicken.
Chicken?
- Best menu. / - Chicken, rabbit.
- Rabbit? / - Chicken, rabbit.
- Rabbit? / - Rabbit?
Rabbit?
I thought I heard it wrong.
Rabbit good?
(Shocked)
How do you do that with your brows?
- That's so funny. / - How do you do that?
Korean? Japanese?
- Korean? / - Korean. Yes.
You order rabbit?
- Rabbit? Yeah. / - Rabbit, good?
Rabbit's good.
- He recommended it. / - A lot of people eat rabbit...
- In Europe. / - Rabbit?
(He laughs at her facial expressions)
- Chicken? / - Yes, chicken.
Excuse me.
One rabbit.
One chicken.
Rabbit?
Do you want a piece?
- Really? Okay. / - Yes.
We'll share one skewer.
- It's rabbit. / - I'm curious.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(She slowly tastes it)
I think it'll taste like chicken.
I wouldn't think it was rabbit.
(Did you really eat it?)
(I really can't eat it)
- Is it tender? / - Very tender.
It smelled good.
You can't tell that it's rabbit.
Tasty?
- It's tasty. / - No rabbit.
Chicken.
(Chicken skewer, $2.20)
- Didn't you eat rabbit? / - Only Daeun had it.
Only I had it.
- Durian. / - How was it?
She said it was really delicious.
(They buy durian for dessert)
(How do they taste?)
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
Look at this.
This is all a floating market.
(Fried banana, $1.50)
I'm scared of rabbit. Chicken, please.
(Chicken skewer, $2.20)
Let me try durian.
(Lastly, they buy durian as their dessert)
(They picked 4 types of simple snacks)
- Let's sit and eat. / - I love eating at places like that.
(They try the chicken skewer first)
- Isn't it good? / - Yes.
- It's the peanut sauce. / - The peanut sauce.
Let's try the steamed buns too.
Mine has milk filling inside.
- You're so cruel! / - So cruel!
Mine has strawberry filling inside.
Strawberry.
There are milk and strawberry flavors.
- The colors are pretty inside. / - There's a variety.
- The milk bun is... / - That looks good.
- Did she say milk tea bun? / - That looks delicious.
- I bet it's delicious. / - It's sweet and sour.
People should buy what kids want too.
- It's fun to eat cute buns. / - That's right.
(Lastly, it's time to try the durian)
- Durian! / - Grilled durian.
And this is fresh durian.
Fresh durian?
That's a bit risky.
They must brace themselves before eating.
You've had this before.
How was it when you tried durian for the first time?
I liked it because it was sweeter than it smelled.
Isn't it because of the sauce?
Without the sauce.
(She tries the grilled durian first without the sauce)
That was my first time.
People who love durian only eat that.
(Ew)
- At first... / - That was for real.
- A real reaction. / - Can't handle it?
No, it's better than I thought.
Stop lying.
(However, she can't keep a straight face)
- Did you smell it? / - It smelled like fart just now.
That's the smell of durian.
- Jooe, have you had durian before? / - No.
- I want to try that. / - My mouth smells like farts.
- She's enjoying that. / - I want Yeonwoo to try it.
- You said it smells like your feet. / - Yeonwoo...
- Daeun. / - No.
Daeun.
Let me try the fresh durian.
She put the ice on the bottom like it's shaved ice.
(Suji enjoys it as expected)
(That's delicious?)
It's good.
(They have two opposite feelings)
I guess people eat this like shaved ice.
If it's hard, don't eat it.
But I'm curious about that.
- It's good. / - Fresh durian.
There's not much flesh left.
Was the fresh durian okay?
It's like mustard, right?
- Did you like it? / - Look at her. She's so fun.
Suji, this one is tastier.
- This is better? / - The fresh durian was tastier.
Grilled ones have a stronger smell.
It smells bad at first but I can taste the sweetness.
I felt it right away.
- Right? / - I want to try it.
I'll stop eating now.
(You can have it all)
You're not stopping because you don't like it, right?
Remember when I said I've tried durian before.
I said it was sweet and tasty.
Turns out, that wasn't durian.
(It was Suji's big picture of making her eat the durian)
(She fooled me!)
Viewers, brace yourself before eating durian.
We still have the highlight of today's tour.
I'll take you to the most popular spot.
We're confident about this place.
You must go here.
- Is it a rooftop bar? / - Yes.
- Rooftop? / - Seriously.
- Look at that. / - What's happening?
(It's a popular place on social media)
In Indonesia...
- A lot of people use social media. / - I see.
That place was really popular.
Daeun, don't let this surprise you.
- Hello. / - This is very nice.
What is this place?
Look at this. Someone put a bus here.
- There was a real bus at the bar. / - That's pretty.
- It's mostly visited by young people. / - So nice.
- Daeun, should we sit here? / - Take a seat.
(Dancing)
- We ought to look chic when we sit. / - Just like this?
I thought that this would be the place you like.
I have to visit popular places.
I researched a lot online.
(You're the best)
This isn't a popular place in Korea.
It's a popular place in Bandung.
And they sell simple drinks here.
- Are you hungry? / - Yes.
You have my respect. Seriously, I respect you.
- I shouldn't eat a lot at night. / - Right.
- Let's get pizza. It's simple. / - Pizza?
Excuse me.
- One pizza costs... / - Cocktails.
- $4.80. / - How much is it?
- $4.80. / - So cheap?
Here's what you must do here.
Before they serve us our pizza,
that bus is the symbol of this place.
We must take photos there.
- Others come here to take photos too. / - Yes.
Suji, I prepared this for today.
- Earlier, we made this. / - What's that?
(After lunch, they made the toppers together)
(Self-made toppers with paint markers and OHP films)
(They can take photos just like this)
I'm going to take it like this.
(They take the best photos with handmade toppers)
You look cute, Suji.
That looks so cute.
(SuDa Signal Tour in Bandung)
Try to look cool.
A popular place in Bandung.
(Sexy at times, lovely at other times)
(Photos for social media, lovely Daeun)
- I'll hold this part of the bus. / - Okay.
(Here's the real strong woman!)
- She looks cute. / - Look at her!
(Exerting superhuman power)
It looks so real.
(Taking photos while catching everyone's attention)
The people in the back are taking photos of you.
Okay.
(A simple meal, pizza, is served)
- The pizza was really good. / - So funny.
- $4.80. / - It looks so good.
That pizza is big too.
- It was so good. / - So big for $4.80.
- We ought to... / - Take this.
That's right. We ought to eat pizza with our hands.
We have to roll it too.
Is that chicken?
Daeun, are you really always hungry?
When I see food...
- I can't stop eating it. / - I see.
- I love eating with my hands. / - Right.
(She rolls it with one hand)
(She takes a big bite)
My gosh, she eats so well.
It was to die for.
You look like you're eating buckwheat crepe.
It felt like I was too.
Isn't it really good?
I only taste the cheese, the dough...
- And meat. / - I can only taste the meat.
Do you like thick dough or thin dough?
- I like thin dough. / - Me too. I like crunchy dough.
I like it when it's like chips.
If that's how you're going to eat,
can I roll up this entire thing?
(Roll up the entire thing?)
Go ahead.
She has my respect.
(Rolling two slices into one)
She was rolling the slices like they were rice rolls.
(I have to record this)
This is how it looks.
(Looking thick)
- I like Daeun. / - It's as big as her face.
She'll eat that?
(This is thick enough for her to chew on)
- She eats a lot. / - How is she so thin?
Do you work out to eat?
- Yes, I love eating. / - I can see.
(Today's queen of eating show, Song Daeun)
How was it, Daeun?
We finished the first day of our trip.
Give me a signal to tell me how good or bad it was.
Everywhere we went was pretty.
It was prettier because we were part of it.
- Bandung has beautiful colors. / - It does.
Actually, I love the weather.
(She sends her evaluation in a text)
Let me read this for you.
"Thank you for a day full of joy and excitement.
Please look forward to tomorrow. Good night."
I'm so grateful of your comment.
You texted her when she was right in front of you?
We parodied "Heart Signal," sending the text at night.
I haven't exchanged texts in a while.
- Do you like it? / - Yes, it brings back memories.
In that show,
we sent text messages to each other at night.
Waiting for that message felt longer than a day.
- Until the message arrives. / - I bet.
On the show, I had to pretend that I got messages
for the days I didn't get any.
How did you pretend that?
How did I pretend?
I did my best to pretend but on TV, you could tell.
- You pretended to get messages. / - Yes, I did.
The caption said that they felt bad for me.
Everyone, have fun in Bandung!
- What a beautiful place. / - It was so pretty.
The next day is Daeun's Day.
- Daeun's Day. / - Daeun's Day.
(If you like taking selfies, pay attention!)
- Seriously. / - What are those houses?
(Princess Daeun and Princess Suji will set out to find)
(The best photo of their lives)
We prepared the costumes.
- I can't wait. / - What is that?
Did they lend those costumes to you?
Look at the monitor.
Why are you turning away, Hwijae?
No, I didn't turn away. I was glancing at it.
The paradise for photos will be revealed.
Everyone, remember this.
- Look at the look on Suji's face. / - My gosh.
(Screaming)
Please don't do this!
(Dizzying)
Hold on. My goodness.
This is just too scary.
What is this?
This is too scary.
(What on earth happened to them?)
(At least for today, they will be in the limelight)
(It's the Mecca for selfies)
(Day 2 of SuDa Signal Tour begins now)
Where is this? hotel?
Our second day has begun.
- Yes, it's our hotel. / - Today is Daeun's Day.
Yesterday, I had such a great time.
I'm very looking forward to today as well.
You won't be disappointed.
As I told you in the beginning,
this tour will start and end with awesome photos.
- I said I'd plan a tour like that. / - Right.
- There's one more thing I prepared. / - What is it?
Surprise! I prepared a rental car.
(1 day rent including the driver, $56.50)
- Is the driver's seat on the right? / - Isn't it expensive?
Yes, the driver's seat is on the opposite side.
They don't have international licenses here.
Since we can't drive here,
I rented a car and a driver as well.
You must have spent quite some money.
That car looks expensive.
It's cheaper to rent a car than to ride around in a taxi.
- Driver included. / - It's included and still cheaper?
- Yes, it's cheaper than a taxi. / - All day?
And if you get stuck in traffic,
the meter continues to go up.
But if you use a rental car, that's no concern.
- Would you ride the car with me? / - I will. Good job.
- Okay. / - Let's go take pictures.
- Hello. / - Hi.
- How are you? / - Hi.
He'll be driving for us the whole day.
- He'll drive us around. / - Thank you very much.
(Bandung Tour, Daeun's Day)
(The sacred place of selfies, selfie park)
(The selfie tour starts!)
- I'm getting used to this. / - What a relief.
(Hotel to the park takes about 35 minutes by car)
- Daeun. / - Yes?
Since you've been talking so much
about taking pictures,
I prepared something today.
When we take pictures,
it's important to have pretty faces.
But also...
- Our outfits are important too. The concept. / - True.
I think the concept is the most important thing.
- So I borrowed some costumes... / - Yes.
From the "Gag Concert" waiting room.
The "Gag Concert" waiting room?
You went into the wardrobe and brought them?
Yes, I carefully picked them.
Are there normal costumes in that wardrobe?
There are many pretty costumes. Goodness.
This is what I was talking about.
- They're not that pretty, are they? / - She looks cute.
- I got nervous. / - But that wardrobe...
- Has all kinds of costumes. / - I couldn't hide it.
- Let's put on the costumes. / - Yes.
I can't tell you what costumes they are yet.
I'm sure you'll be satisfied.
- Alright. / - You'll be satisfied.
- I'll be looking forward to it. / - Okay.
Let's take great pictures in the costumes.
I wanted to make the best out of it.
I brought costumes for the photos.
You should have taken the wigs too.
If you go to Disneyland,
you'll find people in costumes everywhere.
That's true.
- I mean it. All Elsa. / - They'd be a thousand Elsas.
- Elsa from "Frozen." / - There are 10,000 Elsas.
(Selfie park is popular among the youth)
People call this place as selfie park.
It's a great place to take awesome selfies.
It looks safe.
(It's a paradise for selfie lovers)
How cute.
It looks fun.
(Open from 8 a.m. to 8 p.m., tickets cost $1.50)
Even children do it.
- Yeah. / - It's safe.
The entrance fee is very cheap as well.
- $1.50. / - It's only $1.50.
The entrance fee is $1.50?
(Under the sunshine, princesses walk in)
Do you like it?
I'm very pleased.
I really like this.
Me too.
He looks so surprised.
They're shocked.
You look great in it.
You can't wear such costumes...
- When it's too hot. / - You're right.
(Princess Daeun)
(Princess Suji)
It's so fresh.
- Even the weather is... / - It's blissful.
I feel like at the end of this road,
there will be seven dwarves.
And you'll meet the Beast.
The air is so fresh here as well.
I feel like I'm in a theme park in Korea.
The wind is so refreshing.
There are a lot of places where we can take pictures.
Is the dress made of velvet?
- Yes. / - It must have been so hot.
- Weren't you hot? / - It wasn't hot that day.
- Weren't you hot? / - I was really okay.
- It looks hot. / - The weather was...
- Worth it if you get a good shot. / - There is a reason...
Why this is called a selfie park.
I can see why.
Isn't this place pretty?
I know.
Let's jump so we can wear the hats.
1, 2, 3.
(Giggling)
That yellow looks like it's dyed with gardenia seeds.
I see what you mean.
- It's a very bright yellow. / - Exactly.
Clothes in bright colors make
better and prettier photos.
You even considered that.
There are so many places we can go.
- I know. / - I'm not sure where to start.
Princess Daeun, could you sit over here?
- Here? / - Yes.
(Let me take a nice picture of you)
Our Belle is so pretty.
(Is this a fairytale? She's so pretty)
You look so pretty.
Oh, my. Prince Charming.
Prince Charming.
Oh, my goodness.
(This is the place!)
(This is where you can take great pictures)
(A photo spot recommended by SuDa Signal Tour)
My prince has a carriage.
(Flying white horses)
(Flying white horses, $2.20)
Let's go.
(She's feeling great)
♪ Bandung style ♪
(People take pictures here and there in the park)
(2nd photo spot, social media picture frame)
Shall we take a picture over there?
- We made something like that. / - We did.
It seems like many Indonesians use social media.
Because of the big population,
I heard many Indonesians use social media.
(Shall we take one too?)
(This will surely get her 10,000 likes)
- Goodness. / - What's that?
Is it this way?
(The best photo spot of Daeun's Day)
It's the carpet!
It's so amazing.
We should go somewhere that is not too common.
- Suji. / - What is it?
Have you ever dreamed of flying in the sky?
Hold on a second. Flying in the sky?
I hate climbing up somewhere high
and jumping from the top.
- That's not it. / - What do you mean?
You can actually fly here.
(A flying carpet next to a thick forest?)
How is that possible?
How does that work?
- It's hilarious. / - It looks high from that angle.
- But it's actually not that high. / - It's very safe.
(Aladdin's Carpet, the most popular spot in the park)
(This place is already popular on social media, $2.20)
Look at that.
(It's 100% manual)
- It's manually operated. / - Wait a second.
I can't ride this. This will make me feel bad.
So they pull the rope here.
- The kid seems to have enjoyed it. / - It looks alright.
She's not crying.
Kids can ride it too.
- Let's give it a try. / - Shall we?
Suji, you try first.
Okay, then please take pictures of me.
As long as you're under 100kg, it's fine, right? Good.
No problem then.
(You must put on a seatbelt)
It looks a little scary.
- There's safety gear, right? / - Yes.
- It's safe. / - You wear it on your waist.
(They look somewhat nervous)
(This is not going to be easy)
(Suji should be alright)
- Suji. / - Okay.
I'm scared.
Oh, my!
(Good luck)
- This looks interesting. / - It must be so scary.
(Screaming)
I'm so scared.
(Please help me!)
- Hold on. / - This is so scary.
Please don't do this to me.
My goodness.
(Suji, are you okay?)
Suji.
(Laughing)
(It's fun for those who watch her)
Take photos of me.
Try to look pretty.
(Screaming)
(I want pretty pictures)
What?
My goodness. When women change like that...
It really scares me.
I had to change for the pictures.
- She's so funny. / - There you go.
(She made an unforgettable memory)
(She plucks up courage once again)
I'm Snow White from Korea.
(They finally got a shot with the bubbles)
Here you go!
(She feels totally comfortable on it now)
(She even sings songs on it)
Women are scary.
Everyone, she is wearing a harness.
If you wear them under your clothes...
- Don't be scared. / - You can't see them in pictures.
I wore them under my clothes.
Princess Daeun, how is it going?
So far, it's okay.
I know. Once you sit on it, you'll feel different.
(Nervous)
Oh, my! Wait!
(Screaming)
Wait! Wait!
No, this isn't the right time.
(Suji tries her best to make the best photo for Daeun)
(It was filmed safely with expert help)
I tried to make the photo pretty.
Princess Daeun, here it comes.
(You have to take the best shots)
(I'm scared but I will take the best photos)
(Princess Suji is sending soap bubbles)
Look at the bubbles.
Women are scary when they do this.
She was crying but she suddenly changes.
The picture looks pretty though.
That's right. There's a professional photographer too.
I want to try this. What about you?
Seriously.
Where else would you get such photos?
- You're right. / - In fact, that picture made you go.
- That's right. / - That's why we decided to do it.
I think it's worth going there.
Time has changed.
People go on trips for just one photo.
True.
(The princesses are revisiting their childhoods)
- You're Snow White, right? / - It looks delicious.
Look at that. It looks like the house is floating.
Isn't that house from "Up?"
- That's right. / - The animation movie.
From the movie "Up."
I want to take pictures there.
These all are...
They're good enough to be your profile photo.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
(Today will be remembered by these funny photos)
(Bandung Tour, Daeun's Day)
(Famous restaurant, Kampung Daun)
(Selfie park to Kampung Daun, 40 minutes by car)
Suji, you did great.
Where are we now?
It's called Kampung Daun.
It's a restaurant that looks like a village.
Are we going to eat there?
Are you sure they serve meals?
- I'm sure they do. / - Okay.
(You can have a meal and take good pictures)
(Open from 10 a.m. to 10 p.m.)
I can tell they serve good food.
Sikyung has a special skill.
- The food is good. / - Once he sees a restaurant...
He can tell if the food is good or not.
All I saw was the concrete road, but it's good?
That means good food.
Really?
(As you walk down the street with engraved leaves)
The restaurant is called Kampung Daun.
It's like a chicken restaurant...
Near a mountain valley in Korea.
We can take a green shower in there.
- You can relax while you eat. / - The food is good.
(What food are they going to eat here?)
- Before we look around the place... / - Yes.
- We should eat. / - Okay.
- Let's go eat. / - Okay.
Let's hurry.
- It's a restaurant. / - This place is like a theme park too.
The place looks amazing for dates.
(They can have a private meal in a little cabin)
There are separate bungalows.
I can hear the valley.
I can hear the sound of running water.
My goodness.
The stream is flowing down the rocks.
(A small stream is flowing in Kampung Daun)
Look at the stream over there.
We should practice singing here.
Our seats are over there.
- Over there? / - Where we can see the stream.
- It looks like a resort, but it's a restaurant? / - Yes.
You can borrow the whole bungalow
and have a private meal in there.
- That sounds nice. / - It is cool.
It is amazing.
It'll be good if you go there with your parents.
(The place is crowded with tourists on weekends)
(You can choose the room through a reservation)
This is so cool.
I was so hungry.
They have a lot of dishes on the menu.
Where's the bell?
They have their own special way to take an order.
It's right there.
- It's the tube. / - You blow in it?
- What is it? / - It's a wood tube.
When you place an order...
(You bang the wooden tube to call the waiter)
That's new.
- Instead of ringing a bell? / - Right.
I should hit it four times.
"I'm hungry." Like this.
(Princess Suji is calling us, let's hurry)
(The food is being served)
I think it's nasi goreng.
(The best dish, nasi goreng, looks and tastes good)
(Nasi goreng set, $4.10)
It looks delicious.
- It must be good. / - It was so good.
- I told you. / - Was it good?
The food must be good there.
It looks so cute.
This is exactly what I saw on the internet.
Let's taste nasi goreng first then.
I hope it's not spicy.
What would nasi goreng of Kampung Daun taste like?
(How does nasi goreng taste in Kampung Daun?)
It feels like eating rice with sea.
It tastes like the sea.
It tastes different from what we had yesterday.
- It must be good. / - It was great.
- I love it. / - It tastes like seafood fried rice.
You can really taste the shrimp.
- It's very rich. / - Yeah.
I think this place can be...
Enjoyed by people of all ages.
Anyone can enjoy the food with no problem.
Exactly.
It's here.
(What's the second menu?)
(Rib soup, $7.30)
It's rib soup.
Let's taste the soup first.
Okay.
It must be delicious.
- It looks just like rib soup. / - Yeah.
Isn't it Korean food?
- It feels like we're in Korea. / - Are we in Korea?
It tastes like Korean rib soup with a little fat.
It is a little greasy, and it has some spices in it.
Just a little.
But it is not too strong.
It doesn't ruin the taste of the soup.
- Exactly. / - It works well.
It tastes like Korean food.
It's so good. What should I do?
Beef is expensive in Korea.
You should eat a lot of beef when you go there.
- It's cheap. / - Right.
- And it tastes good. / - Exactly.
That's a good idea.
Do you want to put rice in it?
Get it, get it.
- I'll put all of it in. / - Let's put it in.
It's a magic act where rice disappears.
(It's the perfect combination)
This is it.
It tastes like short rib soup
you eat after a long day of work.
(It relieves the fatigue from the day's work)
- It tastes better with rice. / - Gosh.
- It looks amazing. / - The rib soup.
And I want to try the shrimp.
(What's the last menu?)
That tastes like kimchi.
- Shrimps. / - It's barbecued.
- Shrimps. / - It looks well-grilled.
It's only $6.50.
- My goodness. / - It's so cheap.
(Daeun is removing skewers to eat the shrimp)
Daeun, can I have it on the skewer?
(I should eat the whole shrimp)
This is it.
- It looks so good. / - I guess they grilled the shrimp.
(What does the grilled shrimp taste like?)
How is it?
(How is it?)
Is it good?
Is it delicious?
(It's the best)
(I can't wait any longer, I have to eat it)
It's well-grilled.
It was really good.
We ate the whole shrimp without peeling it.
It tastes like Korean food, right?
They grilled the shrimp without peeling it.
But it's very tender.
I love it.
And the sauce is sweet and salty. It's so good.
It's sweet and salty.
I don't like to eat the shrimp shell.
But after grilling it like this...
It's tender and crispy. Here we go.
(Taking a big bite)
She's eating two at once.
It was so good.
- The shell was soft as well. / - It's so good.
It's not tough at all. It's thin and crispy.
It has a nice, crunchy texture.
- It was the best dish. / - Right.
It was the best of the best.
This is the best, right?
There's seasoned vegetable.
- It looks like kimchi. / - Right.
It looks like mustard leaf kimchi.
(This is just like kimchi)
It tastes like kimchi.
- Is it kimchi? / - Is it refreshing?
- That's interesting. / - Yes, it tastes like kimchi.
Place a kimchi leaf on my spoon of rib soup.
Am I in Indonesia or Korea?
(The perfect combination that can't fail)
It's delicious?
This is excellent.
It works well.
When I had this rib soup,
I wanted to eat some kimchi.
It tastes so good with rib soup.
It was the perfect harmony.
I was worried about the food of Southeast Asia.
Even people like me can enjoy these dishes.
- Right. / - They all are good.
It is well seasoned.
It's not too salty either.
I think it's suits the Korean palate well.
It's so cost effective.
Whatever you order, the price is very cheap.
You can enjoy the trip without worrying about money.
There aren't many dishes that cost more than $10.
- That's right. / - Okay.
What do you think? Did you enjoy the food?
Now that we had a meal...
And enjoyed the beautiful view.
- Tell me what we haven't tried. / - Coffee.
We haven't had coffee yet today.
(Time for coffee?)
Is it time for dessert?
(Bingo)
I love you.
- We haven't had bread since arriving here. / - Yeah.
It will complete our trip.
(Let's go to complete our trip)
Let's go, go.
(Bandung Tour, Daeun's Day)
(Bakery cafe for the best photos)
(Kampung Daun to bakery cafe, 40 minutes by car)
Ta-da!
Are they having a festival or what?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
- It's beautiful. / - It's chilly at night.
(Look at the beautiful lights)
If you wear a jacket, it's a bit cool at night.
(This is the hottest place in Bandung)
- So many people. / - It's pretty.
There were a lot of people.
It's a good place for a date.
- There were a lot of lovers. / - There were.
It's so affordable that it's worth going there.
Where does the cafe start and where does it end?
- All of that is the cafe. / - All of it.
- All of it? / - Yes, that entire area.
(Open 9 a.m. to 9 p.m., admission fee, 70 cents)
- It's a cafe street. / - It's really big.
- Is there an admission fee? / - It's really expensive.
- It's 70 cents. / - Yes.
- It's 70 cents. / - 70 cents.
Every spot was a great photo spot.
So pretty.
2, 3. 2, 3.
(You can't leave us out when it comes to photos)
It's so cute.
All they did was take photos.
(Can you guess which is the flower?)
- They say only photos will remain. / - That's right.
- That castle is also in the cafe. / - That's also in the cafe?
- Yes. / - Wow.
(Daeun's Day ends at a beautiful castle)
This atmosphere feels like a movie.
- It's really like "Harry Potter." / - It really is.
- Men really like that movie. / - That's right.
I think that men and women of all ages
would enjoy this place.
Right. I say this with utmost confidence
that this place is worth recommending to everyone
including family, lovers and friends.
I'm serious.
I think it was such a perfect day.
Really? Are you satisfied?
I'm satisfied but the bread isn't here yet.
Making me disappointed.
Wait a minute, Princess Daeun.
- Banana split. / - What is this?
- Banana split? / - Banana split.
Brownie with ice cream.
It's a brownie.
(Two desserts to capture the hearts of women)
(They are pretty desserts that are perfect for photos)
- This banana ice cream was good. / - What is this?
- Brownies and banana split. / - Banana split.
- Banana split? / - That looks a little expensive.
- It's only $2.40. / - What?
- Isn't it really cheap? / - That's impossible.
- All of that? / - I want to live in Indonesia.
I also want to immigrate.
Men and women are different.
Honestly, there aren't a lot of situations
where men get excited about desserts.
To be exact,
it's hard to understand why they're drinking coffee
when the sun is already set.
I can't believe this!
- It looks really good. / - It looks good.
- Should we try them? / - Should we?
Cheers.
(How does the brownie and ice cream combo taste?)
(She is lost for words)
(Bliss)
- It's like a commercial. / - Was it good?
Yeonwoo has been won over.
- We've got you. / - It went so well with coffee.
Let's be honest. MOMOLAND likes this, right?
Right?
The brownie is so moist
inside the mouth.
You could say that we drank coffee to eat desserts.
There's thick chocolate inside the brownie.
(Another bite)
(The next dessert they will taste is the banana split)
(They are tasting it)
- It's good. / - It's really good.
(Perfect combination of chocolate ice cream and fruit)
You have to eat fruit when you're there.
The sweetness is different.
(They ended the day happily with sweet desserts)
(It's time to send a signal)
(Daeun nervously planned the second day)
(She nervously waits for a text)
(She wonders if Suji enjoyed it or not?)
(Was Suji satisfied with Daeun's Day?)
(From Suji)
(Thank you for the photos and memories)
(That'll last forever)
(I'm so happy to have a friend like you)
(I felt rich here in Bandung)
(Let's be friends forever)
(She is full of cute charm)
It feels like we succeeded in becoming a couple.
I'm not that happy but it's good anyway.
- I'm happy. / - I'm also happy.
(We guess it's all good if they're all happy)
I have never been to the U.S. or Europe.
So I really wanted to go there and it was my dream.
But it feels like my dreams came true.
- That's right. / - After I came to Bandung...
It really felt like I came to Europe.
I felt it wherever we went.
It feels like I came to Europe.
- I wish a lot of people knew it. / - Yeah.
- I'm serious. / - Yes, I'm really serious.
(We hope people will feel the charm of Bandung)
What do you think about when you think of Indonesia?
Bandung.
Let's send a signal to the viewers
to come to Bandung.
Bandung...
♪ I send you a signal, send you a signal ♪
♪ Tingling, tingling, tingling, tingling ♪
(SuDa Signal's Bandung trip, the end)
From what I see...
Promoting Indonesia as a cool nation was interesting.
The prices are cheap too.
So it will be fun to spend money.
Just don't go to Bali.
If you're going to Indonesia,
you should visit the beach...
- And then go to Bandung. / - That sounds nice.
- The weather will be cool. / - It's nice to take photos.
- Was it the selfie park? / - Yes.
I think there are a lot of places to take photos there.
- That's right. / - It really is.
It's Europe on this side,
then over here, it's Southeast Asia.
It feels really different. It felt like a movie.
The admission fee was really cheap, right?
- It was $1.50. / - Yes, it was $1.50.
Do you have to pay more for the carpet ride?
Each theme has its own charge.
So you only pay for what you want.
Is the photographer included...
- In that fee? / - Yes.
The photographer is included in the fee.
It's not $2.20 for each photo.
You can receive every file for that price.
When you say every file...
- Do they take lots of photos? / - They keep taking them.
It's so cost-effective.
- Yes. / - The most important thing is...
That Yeonwoo and Jooe have been totally won over.
- Because of the food. / - Yes.
- And the photos. / - And the desserts.
They were won over by the dessert.
- They enjoyed it so much. / - They like sweets.
- It's really good. / - They took more than 1,000 photos.
That's right.
We had to delete some because the storage was full.
- Really? / - They were all works of art.
- They were so pretty. / - It looked so pretty and tasty.
Let's find out how much they spent now.
It must be close to nothing.
- How much did you spend? / - How much?
For 2 nights and 3 days, the total amount we spent
per person in Bandung, Indonesia is...
- How much? / - It's for 2 nights and 3 days.
$229.
That's including accommodation?
- Yes. / - Everything is included.
- It's included. / - Accommodation was $60 per night.
If you exclude that, they only spent $100 for 3 days.
- That's right. / - It's really cost-effective.
- It's the best. / - Yes.
Let's do the final vote.
Will you take SuDa Signal Tour to Bandung?
Please vote!
(They designed trip to a hidden location)
(What will the judges choose?)
We saw the trip to Bandung, Indonesia.
This is also my first time. Next week, we will see...
- A trip to Sakhalin, Russia. / - I'm so curious.
We will reveal the trip of Jooe and Yeonwoo.
Will you be energetic next week?
- Yes! / - Yes!
- Let's go, MOMOLAND! / - We can do it!
See you next week!
(Next episode)
Sakhalin!
- We're in Sakhalin. / - This is Sakhalin.
I've been overwhelmed by the beauty of this place.
Yeah.
Is it delicious?
Is it good?
I'm just going to trust you.
No, it's really good.
Wow, unbelievable.
Hey, seals!
I think I got one.
- I'm scared. / - No, no!
Screaming together
and not caring about anyone else.
I think that was so nice.
(Battle Trip)
("Shoot Out" by MONSTA X)