(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
(Lee Hwijae)
(Special host, Kim Minkyoung)
Travel is war. Battle Trip!
- She's finally here. / - Right, everyone.
Today's special host is Kim Minkyoung. Welcome.
Welcome.
It's nice to meet you.
I feel nervous to be here.
Really? Why are you nervous?
Since this is a food show...
- No, it's not a food show. I'm sorry. / - Travel show.
- Travel show. / - We're not a food show.
There are a lot of food though.
About 80% of the trips are about food.
So I thought,
I wouldn't be able to...
You might run out.
Host the show on an empty stomach.
- So I made sure to eat a lot. / - You did?
Since yesterday, I've eaten a lot.
This show makes me feel hungry.
You know what? Today, there will be
a fish dish that you've never seen or heard of.
And a meat dish that you can't even see sober.
A meat dish?
What should I do?
Once you hear about the destinations,
you'll want to go there to eat.
They are two prominent countries with great food.
- I just can't wait. / - Where would that be?
We are nearing our 100th episode.
Already.
When we started this show,
we saw high ratings with this theme.
And it continues even now.
- It was literally on fire. / - What is it? I'm so curious.
- It is... / - What is it?
Counterattack of Secondary Travel Destinations.
- So this is Part 2. / - We'll start Part 2 today.
In Part 1, we went to...
You all know Bangkok in Thailand.
But Kim Minkyo went to Pattaya instead.
He was like a native.
He really was.
- And we went to... / - Macao.
Macao instead of Hong Kong.
I went to the famous restaurant in Macao.
There was such a queue. I had to wait for 2 hours,
but the food was still good.
- I'm so envious. / - About what?
She must've had a lot of good food.
Aren't you full?
- No. I'm hungry again. / - So soon?
Yes, I'm so hungry.
You said you've eaten since yesterday.
But you're already hungry again?
My stomach becomes empty when I talk about food.
It gets all digested.
It'll be so hard to watch the video.
I hope today's trip designers...
- Will go to the countries of delicacies. / - Right.
Where are they going?
Counterattack of Secondary Travel Destinations 2.
Let's meet today's trip designers.
Please come on up.
(Kim Shinyoung, Mimi of OH MY GIRL)
(Park Sohyun, Hong Hyunhee)
Sohyun went to Jeonju last time.
- With me. / - She had one of the highest scores.
Right. It's still in the top 5.
Actually, she is famous for being a picky eater.
- I don't eat a lot. / - I know.
But you got a high score.
Sohyun is a little unique though.
Her appetite differs depending on her partner.
When she went on a trip with me, she rarely ate.
- Yes. / - Really?
I had good food though. It was fun.
Wait.
- You didn't eat a lot during this trip? / - Wait.
We won!
In fact, Sohyun is the mother of idols.
Is there a reason you chose Hyunhee?
Hyunhee has been a guest
on my radio show for about 2 to 3 years.
- She's family. / - It's actually 5 years.
5 years...
She doesn't even remember.
- This is disappointing. / - She has no idea.
She just loses half of her memories.
Please understand.
That's why she's still young.
I'll go again.
Do what again?
I'm about to cry.
Hyunhee has been a guest
on my radio show for 5 years.
Lee Gookju used to do it
and she became too successful.
Then Park Narae filled in for her
and she became successful again.
And Hyunhee has been filling in since.
It's a seat to success.
She always says I'll be successful
and she will give me three chances.
"Happy Together" was one of them,
but it didn't go well.
Here we go.
What about the 2nd chance?
My 2nd chance is Battle Trip.
This is your second chance?
She cares about me more than my CEO does.
So I tried my best with my specialty and sincerity.
- She'll show the audience who she is. / - Right.
Meanwhile, Shinyoung picked Mimi.
I went to Taiwan with Shin Dong before.
We toured Taiwan.
But I chose Mimi because of the language.
She speaks a foreign language?
She speaks very well. You'll be surprised.
- Really? / - Which language?
- Language genius. / - She speaks Japanese?
She speaks very good Japanese.
- I speak Japanese a little. / - You speak Japanese.
I speak a little.
But she's like a native.
Let's find out where they went.
Let's do that.
Sohyun and Hyunhee, where did you go?
If heaven is in the sky,
we have this place on Earth.
We went to Hangzhou in China.
Hangzhou.
Now that they went to Hangzhou...
- We're more likely to win. / - Right.
- The place has a lot of good foods. / - Exactly.
And there's Su Dongpo,
a Chinese writer.
Do you know Dongpo pork?
It's Su Dongpo's favorite dish.
That's why it's called that.
And it started in Hangzhou.
My head aches.
Hangzhou is the home of the Dongpo pork.
- The food in Hangzhou is... / - Is it different?
- It's totally different. / - It's different.
I fought with her as it was served in small portions.
- It was small? / - It was so small.
- It was only this much. / - So delicious.
That's my portion.
Sook would need 8 portions of it.
- Was it good? / - Really?
We say there's no difference between bibimbap
in Jeonju and one in Seoul.
- But it tastes better in Jeonju. / - It really does.
It's different from Seoul.
So Dongpo pork must be really good there.
- It's the place of origin. / - She's here.
- Minkyoung is here. / - She's here.
- Do you like Dongpo pork? / - The original.
I love it so much.
The thick pork belly marinated in soy sauce.
It's nice and sweet.
- Goodness. / - It's like a baby's buttocks.
- That's right. / - So plump.
Minkyoung. Don't worry.
Let's ask them.
Shinyoung.
Where did you go with Mimi?
- It's the country of delicacies. / - Delicacies?
It's a place where we can enjoy Japanese tradition.
- It's Kyoto. / - We've won.
Kyoto!
It's so...
I'm sorry.
So it's Hangzhou vs. Kyoto.
Let's find out where the cities are located.
We'll check that out first.
- That's Hangzhou. / - Hangzhou.
It's right below Shanghai.
When you go to China,
you'd go to Shanghai or Beijing.
Hangzhou isn't a famous city in Korea,
but Chinese people love to go to Hangzhou.
We went there on Labor Day, and it was very nice.
While Japan is a famous tourist destination,
we don't know much about China.
If you say you'll go to Hangzhou...
No one ever says that, right?
- They think it's Guangzhou. / - Guangzhou.
This will be a good lesson.
That's another case.
- But you only know limited places in Kyoto. / - Right.
When you hear Kyoto, you'd think of familiar places.
- Right. / - But you shouldn't think that today.
Not at all.
I captured the hidden sights and flavors
of Kyoto that only I know.
How many times have you been to Kyoto?
I've been there almost 30 times.
- She's been so many times. / - She's an expert.
She goes so often.
Shinyoung knows Kyoto like Minkyo knows Pattaya.
Was it your first time in Hangzhou?
No. I'd been to Hangzhou 10 years ago.
- 10 years ago? / - It's changed so much.
She went 10 years ago.
But I didn't really like that city
when I went there 10 years ago.
So I didn't expect that much.
But when I went back after 10 years,
I was astonished at how much things have changed.
So I really enjoyed the tourist attractions and food.
I'll be able to introduce to you a new Hangzhou.
It's between Kyoto, Japan and Hangzhou, China.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
Nice to meet you.
(100 judges in the audience)
She did a big bow.
You can vote once when the trip is over.
Then let's move to Hangzhou first.
Let's watch Toad Tour's trip to Hangzhou.
- Sohyun. / - Are you okay, Hyunhee?
I'm not going to receive that.
- I got you an amazing gift. / - Hyunhee.
- First, I'm so grateful. / - Hyunhee.
Let me bow to you.
- I mean it. / - Why are you bowing?
You got me on the show.
Please stay seated.
Hyunhee...
- They're very close. / - Best friends.
I always felt a debt to Hyunhee
because I always put a lot of effort in the segments,
but Hyunhee never became popular.
- You're like her mom. / - Yes.
I actually want her to get some good fortune
and prosper this year,
so I recommended her for this trip.
Open it. It's your gift. You should open it.
What is this? Does this hug me?
- It hugs you. / - Massager?
It will hug you from the back.
Oh, what is this?
- For your skin... / - Oh, soap.
- You brought everything in your house. / - Everything.
I'm going to plan a trip for you. Just for you.
I told the writers to take a break.
I'll take care of it. I know you the best.
- I'll be your guide and plan for everything. / - Really?
When you look at these books,
where do you want to go?
- Shanghai or Osaka? / - Let's take time.
You wanted to go to Osaka.
You know the Prince of Osaka?
He's Yuta.
He's the Prince of Osaka.
- Yuta, Yuta. / - Prince of Osaka.
- I know him. / - He's from NCT.
Here...
The places we can schedule together...
Singapore, Vietnam...
Osaka, Kyoto, Macao, Hong Kong, Bangkok,
Vietnam, Da Nang, Singapore and Kota Kinabalu.
I've been to Tokyo and Fukuoka, Japan.
But I've never been to China in my life.
- Many people have never been to China. / - Right.
I think it's been 10 years since I've been to China.
- I went there with my mother. / - With your family?
My mom didn't really like it.
It's hard for the elders.
- If you like the food, it's paradise. / - Too much walking.
Hangzhou is the city young people visit the most...
- After Beijing and Shanghai. / - Really?
(Hangzhou)
So nice.
- It has both the city and the traditions. / - So nice.
- Look at the night view. / - Isn't that Las Vegas?
It does feel like Macao and Hong Kong.
My first homework is to be a toad that returns the favor.
A toad?
I'll be a toad that returns the favor to you.
- I'm a toad. Toad among comedians. / - A toad.
I've been on Battle Trip for almost 100 episodes...
But I've never seen that pose before.
Toad that returns the favor.
Quiet and throbbing...
Toad, Toad, Toad Tour.
Frog.
Toad.
We made them laugh.
It looks like a folk tale.
That's from "Master Cabbage and Master Radish."
Toad. Toad.
Would you like to go on a trip with me?
Yes. I've made up my mind.
I'll plan this trip well
and return the favor.
You can trust me.
Look here.
You must eat this in Hangzhou.
When it's fun and great, I'll pay for it.
When it's boring, I'll pay for just half.
(Open or not?)
The purse... Pays for everything.
Open it up.
I'm paying for mine only today.
You have a definite theme.
The toad's effort shows off.
- Oh, that. / - That's delicious.
You have that in Taiwan.
I heard that's really good.
Hyunhee is hooked.
This is the most delicious.
Goodness.
(Toad Hong showed everything about Hangzhou)
Hangzhou is really dazzling.
- It's completely changed. / - What is that?
There's another toad.
There's a crisis.
It's Sungkyu's birthday today.
- Did she keep talking about it? / - Never stopped.
- Sungkyu's birthday. / - It's Hakyeon.
We have a setback here.
Please stop now.
Was Toad Hong able to return the favor
in Hangzhou?
The toad will be filled with venom in the end.
Up to here.
I can't wait to watch.
It sounds fun.
(Incheon International Airport)
(A woman waits alone)
(She seems to be waiting for someone)
(Hyunhee waits for Sohyun with gifts in one hand)
She's here.
You're here.
Sohyun...
- Hyunhee. / - Sohyun.
- I thought you weren't coming. / - Awesome.
What is all this? Hakyeon.
- VIXX and Lovelyz are back. / - Lovelyz.
- My goodness. / - I pasted them on myself...
This is amazing.
You really do know Sohyun well.
(Before the trip)
(She sewed it strand by strand)
This is the Hollywood, New York style.
Look here, please.
1, 2, 3.
- I was very happy. / - Lovelyz.
(Happy departure with idols)
Quiet and throbbing...
Toad Tour that returns the favor.
- Bye. / - Follow me.
We were excited.
How long does it take?
- It takes 2 hours to Hangzhou. / - Was it 69 minutes?
It's 69 minutes. It's very close.
What about the time difference?
It's an hour behind Korea.
- The time? / - Yes, the time difference.
- This is Hangzhou, Sohyun. / - Oh, my.
(Sneeze)
Maybe the air isn't right for you.
- Sohyun. / - The weather is so nice.
How do you feel to be back after 10 years?
Now that I'm back after 10 years,
- It's changed, right? / - I don't remember a thing.
I remember absolutely nothing.
I don't remember anything.
It's my first time here. I'm very excited.
As of today, I'm your guide.
You look tired. One second.
You don't need to do anything. Just turn around.
I'm happy. I'm excited.
I kept catching her attention with it.
- Does that recharge her? / - Yes.
That really does charge Sohyun.
West Lake that I've told you so many times.
- It's pronounced as Xi Hu. / - Xi Hu?
Let's go take a break there.
(Toad Tour, day 1)
(West Lake)
I've heard about it before.
(Hangzhou trip begins by taking a taxi)
It's a World Heritage Site designated by UNESCO.
As soon as we got here...
Going to a World Heritage Site first?
The four beauties...
It's as beautiful as Xi Shi.
That's why it's Xi Hu?
- Is that a lake? / - Yes.
- That's huge. / - That's in the land?
Here...
There are small islands inside West Lake.
It's like Bamseom islet in Yeouido.
Are we going to visit the islands?
Every one of them.
It was so beautiful.
The land is huge.
- It's a different scale. / - It's nice and cool.
Girls who love taking pictures must go.
Seriously.
The pictures turn out so well.
- Thank you. / - Bye-bye.
- West Lake. / - My goodness.
They must be Korean.
Travelers from all around the world are here.
All the tourists are here.
Enjoy observing the crowds first.
So many people.
We're going to take a boat in
West Lake's first scenic spot...
- The West Lake... / - Huh?
- Are you listening? / - I'm listening.
- Who am I talking to? / - I'm listening.
You're not listening to each other.
You went on a trip together.
We couldn't communicate very well.
(The 2nd scenic spot in West Lake picked by Hyunhee)
(Scenic spot 1, Xiao Ying Zhou, island inside the lake)
- That's pretty nice. / - It's really nice.
I couldn't believe something so beautiful
was so near us.
(Scenic spot 2, Three Pools Mirroring the Moon)
(Gourd-bottle-shaped stone pagodas)
What did I tell you before?
Scenic spot 1 is Xiao Ying Zhou.
Scenic spot 2 is Three Pools Mirroring the Moon.
To see Three Pools Mirroring the Moon, just look here.
- It's in the bill. / - It's in the bill?
- The 1 yuan note. / - This is where we're going.
This is nice.
It kind of feels like Thailand too.
(The boat ride costs $30 per hour)
- You have to go there. / - I want to ride that boat.
You must ride on the boat.
It's such a nice experience.
It's 180 yuan per hour.
It only costs about $30.40 for the hour.
You can enjoy great views for that price.
(It's indeed a recommended spot for travelers)
- You take a lot of photos too. / - Yes, I do.
Or I won't remember the trip.
- To leave behind memories? / - Yes, yes.
She's always out of battery.
I see it now.
- I see it. / - You can see it, right?
I can see it.
- Gourd-shaped pagodas? / - They're on the bill.
So this is scenic spot 2.
- 3 Pools Mirroring the Moon. / - That's so pretty.
It looked exactly like on the bill.
It was so interesting to visit the site on the bill.
There are three stone pagodas.
That's right. There are three.
A representative Chinese politician and a poet,
Su Dongpo, built 3 gourd-bottle-shaped stone pagodas
in the deep parts of the lake
to mark the area where fish farming was prohibited.
I can see the pavilions in this quiet
and peaceful part of the lake.
(To enter Xiao Ying Zhou, it costs $3.40)
VIXX would've liked it too.
You're right.
- We're traveling together. / - Be rejuvenated.
I took care of them.
It was built during the Tang Dynasty 400 years ago.
- 400 years ago? / - Yes.
Xiao Ying Zhou is the biggest island.
- It is? / - In the West Lake.
This island is the best place among
top 10 places in West Lake.
Oh, my. How nice.
I hear birds.
Do you not remember anything from 10 years ago?
I don't remember anything.
I'm shocked by that.
I didn't go on the boat the last time I was there.
- Right. / - This must be it.
If you look from above..
- We passed this point earlier. / - Right.
This is what it looks like from above.
It's a 400-year-old artificial island.
- It's been there for 400 years? / - Yes.
They're on a different scale.
This is amazing. Seriously.
What a view.
- Seriously. / - Amazing.
I see why this is one of the best sights.
They dug out the ground to make a artificial island.
- It's so pretty. / - The scenery with the water, land...
And nature is beautiful.
You have to go there to
understand the 400-year history.
I can't help but take photos.
(She loses herself in taking selfies)
- You two don't get along. / - I was exhausted.
No chemistry.
They're not even walking together.
Can you stop making the camera shutter noises?
I should keep turning the camera.
My gosh, that's enough.
The toad's venom filling up.
I wanted to listen to the sounds of nature.
I know that she's beautiful.
- She checks herself all the time. / - She's annoyed.
- She is angry. / - I thought she'd take nature photos.
She used the nature as her backdrop.
She took endless selfies.
I thought she did it because she was pretty.
But now, all I can remember is the clicking noise
when I think of the West Lake.
Do you take selfies when you're with a guy?
I don't remember.
But now, all I can remember is the clicking noise...
- When I think of the West Lake. / - Only photos last.
That's all I could hear.
- How is it? Isn't it beautiful? / - So beautiful.
We've said that about 100 times.
Sohyun, you kept saying that it was beautiful.
Earlier, we were at the entrance
and on the boat. You have to pay for those.
Since you said it was beautiful
so it's time for you to pay.
- She should pay. / - That's right.
- It was the first time to pay. / - Great plan.
I prepared this for you.
This looks like you.
Will I pay or not?
Since this is my first stop,
you must be objective.
(Will the purse open up wide or not?)
You have to visit that lake.
Sohyun is known to be objective.
That was the main stop.
If I really like it, I'll pay for everything.
Everything.
- Everything. / - It opened.
- The purse has opened. / - It opened up.
You have to for this place.
They're not eating much.
I'm getting a bit tired now.
Too much scenery and not enough food.
(Toad Tour, day 1)
(Qing Dynasty Street)
- Hangzhou... / - It's only 7 minutes away?
It's nearby but it's so different.
The West Lake was so amazing.
If that was nature...
Now we're at the Insa-dong of Hangzhou.
You're right.
- So cool. / - Qing Dynasty...
They're located next to those tall buildings.
Fascinating.
It's just like Jeonju Hanok Village.
What's that?
(He Fang Jie)
(Buildings from 1,000 years ago still remain)
(You can experience historical sights of Hangzhou)
This is what's really fun.
- Wow, what is that? / - I've tried that.
- That's famous. / - Is that spicy rice cakes?
I can eat 100 of those just standing there.
Minkyoung, aren't you feeling better all of a sudden?
It's interesting now, right?
It's so much fun.
I wanted to meet that guy
when I was researching for this trip.
Why is she touching the statue?
That's Laughing Buddha Statue, Sohyun.
The monk kept his belongings in a gunny sack...
- And carried it around. / - He looks cute.
When you touch his belly, you get good fortune.
People told me that I look like him a lot.
You do resemble him.
But it seems like he and I look alike.
Hyunhee, you do look like him a bit.
- Right. We should touch it too. / - Look at him.
(Similar)
(The more we look, the more she resembles him)
I got it.
- We're all the same. / - You look similar.
Our stomachs are really similar.
They draw portraits
just like the artist in Korea.
We have artists in Insa-dong too.
That's why it feels familiar.
Should we get one too?
Should we buy one that looks like us?
Wait, that's not it. Isn't this paper craft?
It's made of paper. Isn't this cut? Look at this.
It's not a drawing? No way.
- She cut this just like this. / - You're right. She's cutting it.
She didn't draw these.
- That's paper? / - Yes, that's paper.
- She didn't draw it? / - That's a paper craft portrait.
This is so interesting.
(All of the artworks are made of cutout paper)
Do you want to get one of this?
- Hello. / - Hello.
We resemble each other.
Ask her to do your portrait.
We should each get one and check if we do look alike.
They don't get along.
- Face cutter. / - Face.
- My goodness. / - Without even an outline?
My goodness.
She cuts the paper right away.
- No way. / - I mean it.
- She just folds it and does it? / - I was shocked.
This is interesting.
- She's looking at you and cutting? / - That's right.
It didn't take that long.
Her scissors aren't that small either.
- Her scissors are quite big. / - Exactly.
(Snip, snip)
I could report this on "How Is That Possible."
She got a lot of ideas from this trip.
I mean, seriously.
How could she do that without a rough sketch?
How is that possible?
She did it with her scissors.
How does she do that?
It's her first time seeing us, right?
That's Sohyun's face.
Seriously...
Me?
(Feeling nervous)
I just want her to make mine looks just like yours.
She's so talented. How does she do that?
(Will their paper portraits resemble each other?)
She carved the paper a bit more.
She's making the chin bigger.
It'd be a memorable souvenir.
Before she shows...
- My gosh! / - My gosh!
- My goodness. / - It's so pretty.
That's not me.
- That's too pretty. / - That's too pretty.
She has to make a living.
She needs a bigger face.
She's a businesswoman.
This is so cute. This looks like a cartoon character.
It doesn't look like me.
This is how she sees me.
(A paper portrait with the exact same bangs and outfit)
Our noses and mouths look similar.
- And the eyes too. / - But it feels different.
- I got it. I found what it is. / - Our vibes are different.
Your face is slender, and mine is round.
Hey, don't say that we look alike. We don't look alike.
I'll treasure this for the rest of my life.
Hey, let's go and get that. I really like that.
- That's so pretty. / - You must eat something to win.
The food we must try here is the fried blue crabs.
I heard this is very famous here.
Fried blue crabs.
- The blue crabs were huge. / - It'll be good.
It's like the old cart bars.
This is written in Korean.
Qing He Fang Street.
It's written in Korean.
That's it. Everyone must go there.
- This is the place. / - This is a nice place.
- I really wanted to try it. / - I like this place.
(They serve authentic Hangzhou dishes)
- That must be Dongpo pork. / - You can find every dish in here.
- They have everything. / - Lots of interesting dishes.
Let's check out what's here.
So much variety.
It's tofu. Isn't that stinky tofu?
- I've never tried stinky tofu. / - Me neither.
It smells really unique.
- Stinky tofu... / - It's a strong smell.
- It's not for the feint-hearted. / - Want to try one?
Let's try just one.
(Challenge accepted)
You're eating that for your first meal?
- We just gave it a try. / - How was it?
I wanted to describe it to the viewers.
Thank you.
- Stinky tofu. / - What a great price at $1.70.
I only saw the food descriptions on TV.
I heard it's slightly rotten.
Isn't that what stinky tofu is?
- Here it comes. / - Here goes.
She's still eating well.
I really enjoyed it.
Even a small bite smells so much.
It smells even more.
- It's starting now. / - It's hit her.
Here it comes.
- She's looking for a place to lean on. / - It's hit me.
It's a sudden hit.
How do I describe it?
I can't swallow it.
The more I chew, the more it smells.
(Watch me, I'm going to swallow it)
- She swallowed. / - She ate it all.
- It makes you sweat. / - I'm sweating.
When I first chewed it, it tasted like braised tofu.
The good ones my mom made for me.
It was good at first.
Of course, because it's deep fried.
It tasted like eating tofu in a toilet as I chewed more.
- I become uglier as I eat. / - That's what it's like.
But if you keep chewing, you get used to it.
- Now it really feels like I'm in China. / - Yeah.
- Finally. / - I really wanted to try this.
Now it feels like China.
- Blue crabs. / - These are the blue crabs.
This is a blue crab.
- Isn't this blue crab? / - Shrimp and crab.
- It's deep fried blue crab. / - That looks good.
That's soft crab.
You eat the shell as well.
- You eat it whole. / - They have thin shells.
They're thin. So you don't have to pull out the meat
so it's really easy to eat.
They're huge.
- It's squid. / - Let's get it.
- Squid. / - Spicy rice cakes.
Let's relax and eat.
Squid spicy rice cakes?
- They have spicy rice cakes? / - Yes, with squid.
We tried it to see how different it is from Korean food.
It costs $1.70.
It's soy sauce based and slightly spicy.
It's completely different from Korean spicy rice cakes.
- It's like royal rice cakes. / - That's right.
It's not spicy like the Korean ones
so you can just keep eating it.
- Deep fried blue crab was so good. / - What is that?
- Blue crab. / - Fried blue crab.
They're so big.
You can eat the legs as well.
Right? It's tender.
- The shell is tender. / - It's tender.
Can you eat it without beer?
I craved for a beer so much.
I sometimes have the crab snack with beer at home.
It's the luxurious version.
It's less salty than that snack.
It's less salty, yet it has more meat.
It made me forget the painful memory of stinky tofu.
The venom is rising.
She has to spray her venom once a day.
(A taste she could never forget)
(But Toad Hong forgot about the stinky tofu)
Deep crab was so good that I was so excited.
It's good.
My no. 1 food is deep fried blue crab.
Eating ends so fast.
- I want to go there. / - Let's go to Qing Dynasty street.
The night view.
You will be overwhelmed.
(Toad Tour, day 1)
(Enduring Memories of Hangzhou)
(It's dark in West Lake)
I want to go there.
The night was so different from the day.
We must buy the ticket to see West Lake.
This is what I wanted to see the most.
No way!
This is 4D.
5D!
They have performances like that.
- You went there, Hwijae. / - That was amazing.
(Enduring Memories of Hangzhou)
It was on a grand scale.
That's China for you.
There were also so many performers.
- Just that was overwhelming. / - It was.
(The auditorium is filled without space)
It feels like a baseball stadium.
- Right. / - It's exciting and...
She's on top of the lake.
Goodness. Is she on the top of the water?
No other stage can be as big as this.
The stage...
The stage stretches all the way out.
They can use it because this is an artificial lake.
- It's beautiful. / - It's beautiful.
There are many performers because the stage is big.
It's so nice.
The background is real trees and mountains.
All nature.
It's over 400 people if you include everyone in the back,
but it looks like it's over 800
because of the reflection on the water.
- That moon reflects on the water. / - I know.
It looks like there are more people.
(The reflection on the lake creates a magnificent view)
I'll pay for the whole thing, Hyunhee.
- With this. / - Pay for the whole cost.
As soon as she watched...
I can go home now.
- I can relax and enjoy now. / - Yes.
(The last performance of the show)
- Yes. The music... / - What's this song?
"Swan Lake."
They're performing on a real lake.
On a real lake.
It's ballet.
- What? / - What?
Goodness.
("Swan Lake" performed on a real lake)
(Sohyun can't take her eyes off the show)
- Doesn't it bring up old memories? / - It does.
When I was a teenager, and in my 20s.
- Since you were a teen? / - Yes.
Performing "Swan Lake" on a real lake.
This is such a famous piece.
You know this one, right?
(Because it's something she practiced so many times)
(Sohyun has mixed feelings)
Are you crying?
- It's... / - I know.
- She never cries. / - She never cries.
As soon as the music started, I felt emotional.
It reminded me of the time 30 years ago.
I felt so emotional,
but I didn't want to cry there.
I decided to enjoy it.
It has been a long time.
I tried to think about something else.
There were happy times.
It's terrific.
I should be up there.
- You must miss it, don't you? / - Yeah.
I want to do it.
Is it your first time watching a ballet show in 20 years?
Yes, I never went to a concert hall to watch it.
It was too painful to watch.
- You still feel emotional. / - Yes.
(The performance that made Sohyun cry is over)
What did you think?
My teen life was all about ballet.
I'm willing to open this up.
With all my heart.
This is your tear, longing,
and emotions.
It made me emotional too.
I suddenly want to see the show
after seeing Sohyun cry.
Right. Let's eat something delicious.
I'm hungry.
I'm as hungry as the size of China.
I'm going to eat the food at the size of China.
- That's beautiful. / - Isn't this special?
It's a traditional Chinese restaurant.
Look at the number written on there.
- Do you see 1921? / - Yes.
This is more than 100 years old.
You can't even eat at the peak hour
because the line is so long.
Really?
I told them to empty the place.
- We should hurry up. / - What should we eat?
We're going to try traditional food.
I've been telling you about Beggar's Chicken.
- Right. / - "Let's eat Beggar's Chicken."
Why is it Beggar's Chicken? It's a weird name.
I'm curious.
The emperor of the Qing Dynasty saw a beggar
enjoying chicken, and told him to give him some.
When he tried it, it was so good.
It was good because after you wrap
the chicken in lotus leaves...
- Apply mud. / - That's the one.
Roast and eat.
It removes the odor
and when you open the leaves,
you will smell the lotus.
You will eat the skin
and I'll eat the meat.
(Before that)
You need a beer.
(Local beer that will quench the thirst from Toad Tour)
(Local Hangzhou beer, $1.70)
- The glass is so small. / - It's so cute just like me.
I wish glasses in Korea would be small like this.
The alcohol content is a 2% difference, but it's mild.
When I drink beer with low alcohol content,
I'll know right away.
It's really smooth, but it's still carbonated.
Despite that, it's really smooth.
- It's only 2.5%? / - Yes.
The moment I saw it, I didn't like it.
Even the color looks light.
It's great if you're lightweight.
You look like a heavy drinker.
- She's chugging it down. / - It's really smooth.
This is so cute.
(At that time, a mysterious dish is served)
(What is that?)
(Full of anticipation)
It's very... What's that?
- It's fancy. / - It's so fancy despite the name.
- He's asking you to smash it. / - Right?
- Smash it. / - Break it?
(It didn't even leave a dent)
That's hard.
It must be harder than a walnut.
(Harder)
(Not even a dent)
That's really hard.
- You really couldn't break it? / - It breaks in one go.
- He was playing with you. / - That's not the dish.
When you hammer that, you're wishing for good luck.
- They love wishing for good luck. / - Yes.
You don't have to hit it hard.
Shamanism.
We thought that the Beggar's Chicken was inside.
Me too.
- The chicken is inside there. / - It is?
It's inside.
- It's got mud on it. / - It's a plate.
- Let's see what comes out. / - It's the best.
It looks delicious.
The visuals...
That's just so...
It's like smoked chicken.
I can smell the lotus leaves.
Just this restaurant...
They normally cook it like that.
That's the usual way.
You'll see more of it cooked like that.
Even on the streets.
(They cook it without the mud in this restaurant)
(They infuse the lotus flavor in their own unique way)
The Beggar's Chicken was served first
- That looks so good. / - It was so moist. I'm serious.
It's way more tender than the rotisserie chicken.
It melted as soon as it was in my mouth.
- It's very moist. / - It's juicy.
- Leaves removed the chicken odor. / - That's right.
Lotus leaves remove the chicken odor,
and mud seals the juice.
It holds the juice from seeping out.
(She's eating the lean meat with gusto)
You ate a lot.
How come she's eating so much?
- I was nervous. / - I really ate a lot.
Is this the Dongpo pork you mentioned?
Was it always small like this?
How do we eat this?
I thought she served us pudding.
(It's different from usual Dongpo pork with bokchoy)
(For the original dish, a whole chunk of meat is served)
- You must focus on this part. / - What a great price.
It's so thick.
It's just like a cake.
The color looks like tiramisu.
It's only $2.70.
- You could eat more than 10. / - That's $2.70?
- Per slice. / - Per slice?
- It's like fish. / - Why are you sharing?
I'll be a single bite for you, Minkyoung.
- Seriously. / - Goodness.
Should I try the skin by itself?
This is so...
- It's so soft like sponge cake. / - It's so good.
- It's like the braised short rib. / - It's rather sweet.
- It's also tender too. / - It's melting in my mouth.
I'll mix the sauce with rice.
- There you go. / - Yes, do that.
- Good job, Hyunhee. / - That's right up my alley.
I mixed rice with the sauce.
I'm having Dongpo pork here.
Hyunhee, you're hooked.
And isn't it more tender than braised beef?
It's because it's pork.
That must be delicious, but why are you getting angry?
- It was so good. / - She licked the bowl clean.
- It'd be so good. / - I ate it all.
The Dongpo pork was really good.
- That was so good. / - You should've ordered a few more.
The skin is good too.
It melts.
(Toad Tour kept on eating even after that)
She ate a lot of the meat.
- I've never seen her eat that much. / - Exactly.
I really enjoyed this meal.
This is what's important though.
Is this good enough for us to open our wallet?
I'll listen to it after I have another glass.
I can't listen to it when I'm sober.
(Will Sohyun's wallet open wide?)
- Did she open it? / - She has to pay for it.
(What will happen to these three?)
I'll open my wallet.
- I mean, she did eat a lot. / - I'll open my wallet.
- There you go. That's only fair. / - She should.
Everything was good.
Not only did she open it, but she spat out the money.
- It spat it out in one go. / - It spat out the money.
Tomorrow, we should enjoy the splendor of the city.
You'll like that.
I'm going to look very fancy tomorrow.
After we enjoy the nature,
we'll enjoy the city within the city.
It's a very fancy city.
I like the city center.
I'm so curious.
Hey, I'm getting excited.
Help me!
I love that kind of activity. I love it.
- My gosh, look at that. / - What's that?
Look at that!
That's really delicious.
- What are you doing to us? / - What is that?
I strongly recommend that.
I really want to eat that.
Wipe your mouths.
Are they in Hong Kong?
- It looks like Hong Kong at night. / - It really does.
This could beat Kyoto.
It's beyond your imagination.
And first of all, prices are reasonable there.
We don't know much...
- About the city. / - Were you there for 3 days?
Is it because of our low expectation?
This is so much fun.
(The morning of the second day breaks without fail)
We went around the city center.
It's similar to Seoul.
It's just a city.
What about the weather?
It's similar to Seoul but it's slightly warmer.
Early summer weather.
Early summer?
It's only a 1-hour difference. Why couldn't you sleep?
Normally, I'd be asleep at this hour.
But we're on a trip so we have to go for breakfast.
- It's like this. / - Don't you see my glasses?
My eyes are so swollen.
Having breakfast on a trip is
a chance to become pretentious.
To me, it's a chance to flaunt.
If you post this, it will say all about your Hangzhou trip.
This is the breakfast you must have in Hangzhou.
That's why I prepared this. It's in the city within the city.
This is it.
- Yes, this is quite famous. / - Soy milk.
It's youtiao and doujiang.
Oh, my. It's impossible for it to taste bad.
It's the best combination. It's perfect.
- I got the chills. It's so good. / - I agree.
Save me.
You saw this, right?
A lot of Chinese people have that for breakfast.
It's a very popular dish.
It'd be great if you get to try this.
You can have this breakfast at other restaurants too
but I wanted to eat at
a restaurant with sophisticated decor.
I'll explain the menu.
The one that people eat the most
is called doujiang. It's bean liquid.
- It's doujiang. Bean liquid. / - I'm not a fan.
- Bean liquid? / - I'm not a fan.
- You don't like soy milk? / - I don't.
You look like you'd enjoy that. Cold bean noodles.
I've never paid to eat cold soybean noodles.
Are you telling me in advance that you won't pay?
That you won't open your wallet?
That's not it.
But I've never paid myself to eat that dish.
Since you've never had this, it might be different.
Beans in Korea and beans in China are different.
My gosh, you're stubborn.
- Another one is youtiao. / - What's that?
- It's Chinese twisted breadstick. / - I see.
Since they go well together,
you use them to describe a good couple.
A couple is like those two dishes.
That's right.
I was relieved that it wasn't that expensive.
- I love twisted breadsticks... / - I don't like them.
(She's in despair, what can she do?)
I don't like churros.
It's sweet and delicious, Sohyun.
- Is it here? / - Here it is.
- What is that? / - It's good when eaten together.
When two people make a good couple...
- They're like youtiao and doujiang. / - Bean soup?
Do you know home-made tofu?
- It smells like the home-made tofu. / - Really?
- It's not soy milk. / - It's the real stuff then.
- Like when we go to Gangwon-do. / - It's rich.
Does it taste like soy milk?
- Yes. / - No, it's different from Seoul.
It's the bean liquid without any seasoning.
- Really? / - No seasoning at all.
- It's sweet. / - It's slightly sweet.
- It's sweet ground bean liquid. / - It's sweet.
The color looks so pretty.
This does taste sweet.
Besides, it was warm too.
It's good.
Did you like it, Hyunhee?
I loved it.
You're not drinking rice wine, right?
It smells like tofu.
- The soup is really rich. Right? / - Yes.
Since we had doujiang, we should try this.
- It's Chinese churros. / - I want to try that.
That's so big.
- How much was the bread? / - That was $1.
- That? / - That's only $1?
Everyone, the whole set costs $2.40.
Hangzhou is famous for these breadsticks.
The breadstick was eaten only in certain regions.
When it got popular, people throughout China
started eating it for breakfast.
It's good.
- It was crispy. / - They must fry the sticks daily.
- Was the breadstick good? / - It was good.
- It's so soft. / - It looks like a churro.
But like French bread, it's very chewy.
Since it's fried, it must be similar to a croissant.
- That's right. / - Exactly.
It's really good.
The breadstick itself is good.
I heard that it's delicious with doujiang too.
- Sohyun, this is so moist. / - When you dip it in?
In Korea, churros are hard.
They won't absorb the liquid.
When you eat cereals with milk,
the milk becomes sweet. It tastes like that.
- It tastes like soymilk. / - Exactly.
- This is the right way to eat it. / - Really?
You have to soak it?
At first, you should just tear it and eat it alone.
- I think you can find this in Korea too. / - Then...
But it's way cheaper there than in Korea.
- Do you like it? / - It's delicious.
- Today... / - There's the frog purse.
The thing is...
I prepared a fancy city tour.
It requires a lot of money.
You should be generous and pay for us today.
We should focus on having fun today.
If we care too much about money, it won't go smoothly.
- Really? / - Yes. It will ruin our mood.
- Then I will just pay for myself. / - Only herself?
That was the first time.
But you recommended what you must try in China.
I know.
I'll just pay for myself.
Just mine.
I gave you soy milk and youtiao this morning.
What are you saying?
But look. You ate it all.
You ate everything.
(Sohyun doesn't want to open her purse)
(I can't let her purse stay closed like this)
(I've got to open that mouth!)
(What will she do at a last resort?)
- What if I show you a talent? / - A talent?
- That's going to soften me up. / - Since you won't pay...
- Since we're in China... / - Show us.
- I'll do BewhY. / - Yes, do BewhY.
- BewhY? /- Show us BewhY.
I'm grateful to BewhY.
- Could you do this? / - This is BewhY drinking soymilk.
BewhY drinking soymilk?
It's BewhY.
The best people know what the best things are.
- They look alike. / - They do.
- They do. / - Sohyun loves it.
The real people know what the real things are.
- They look alike. / - They do.
Hyunhee...
I'm ToadwhY
I'm sorry, but I really don't like the bean soup.
The bean soup...
Okay, fine then.
- Because after this... / - I have to be honest.
- I'm confident. / - So she didn't pay.
After this, you'll pay even if I tell you not to.
I gave up on breakfast.
So the idea was...
Since you're in Hangzhou, you wanted her
to try and authentic Hangzhou breakfast.
- That's what it was. / - That's how it started.
I personally thought it was too strong.
For me.
So it smelled too strong of beans.
I thought she'd at least pay for the churros.
Hyunhee ate everything in the end.
From what Hyunhee described,
it looked very delicious.
(After breakfast, they head out to enjoy downtown)
Since we had a filling breakfast,
we should begin the city tour.
We're going to Song Dynasty Town.
This place was really fun, Song Dynasty Town.
In Yongin, we have a theme park like this.
Look at the fire show in the middle of the day.
They recreated the fortress from Southern Song Dynasty.
- It's like Folk Village in Korea. / - Oh, Folk Village.
(Song Dynasty Town)
China is so big.
It takes a minimum of 1 hour to go anywhere.
That's one bad point.
He's adorable.
Sohyun, look.
How do you feel?
As you know, Hangzhou was
the capital city of Song Dynasty.
This is the recreation of the fortress
of Southern Song Dynasty.
The entrance fee was about $50.
It's exciting.
- I love theme parks. / - Let's go in.
Since it's so hot, I have a present for you.
It's so sunny today.
NCT will protect me from the sun.
It's NCT.
(It's an idol fan)
2018.
Let's travel with NCT. What do you think?
We're going to the theme park with 18 NCT members.
We're group visitors.
We're a big group. We should get a discount.
Since we're in the Song Dynasty,
we should try Song's traditional clothes.
Is it free?
It's included in the entrance fee.
You can rent the clothes with the entrance ticket.
What do men wear?
There are men's clothes as well.
There are clothes for men too.
- Do they have all the sizes? / - Yes, they do.
- Even babies... / - You can wear men's clothes.
- Okay. / - I wore men's clothes.
Here's your ticket.
Do they have something really fancy
or something unique?
(Special episode, a toad and princess Sohyun)
Don't I look like Bao Zheng?
- This is the traditional clothing. / - Chinese zombie?
Stop that. You're scaring me.
Let's have fun in these clothes in this theme park.
It feels like fun Folk Village.
The lanterns are in the shape of a dragon.
The theme park was huge.
- I thought it was CG. / - Huh? CG?
(A golden dragon cuts across the long alley)
(You can feel the Song Dynasty from 1,000 years ago)
When you go to an amusement park in Korea,
it's full of people.
- Doesn't this feel like that? / - It's a theme park.
It's crowded and busy.
It's like an amusement park.
- What is it? / - I found toads.
- There are more toads? Where? / - There are toads?
They have toads there.
My gosh. There are toads.
They are Hyunhee goods.
- I met my friends there. / - They sell Hyunhee goods.
(Croak, croak)
That sound.
It makes that sound when you scratch the back.
(Let me scratch my back too)
I wanted to test it on myself.
They sell Hyunhee goods.
I was so happy to see that.
They sell various kinds of souvenirs there.
They sell many souvenirs.
You shouldn't miss out souvenirs.
They sell food too.
What is this?
- These things are free as well. / - So pretty.
They just give it to people.
They're for those who put on the traditional clothes.
That's so pretty.
- Like this? / - Since we're in the outfits...
They match the colors as well.
It'd really make you feel like you're on a holiday.
This is so much fun to experience.
- You want to ride this? / - The sedan chair...
- Sedan chair. / - Let's ride in the sedan chair.
Get on.
- Can I? / - He spoke in Korean.
- You can ride it together. / - We can ride it together.
- We can ride it together. / - Thank you.
I'm scared.
This might look childish, but it's fun.
- This is fun. / - I didn't expect this.
I didn't think they could lift me.
Please hold my hand.
(It looks like she's on a political campaign)
- What are you doing there? / - They all greeted me.
From behind...
- I feel like I've seen this scene from a movie. / - Me too.
I think this was on a movie.
Thank you.
It was so much fun.
Did they take pictures for you?
They asked us to take pictures with them.
They said Sohyun was so pretty.
Bye-bye.
That was fun.
What on earth is this?
They have that there?
It's there.
I thought I was in a water park.
(People run and fall)
(People keep falling into the water)
His phone, his phone.
He has to save his phone.
He must.
It was so much fun.
People in China know how to have fun with water.
This place is really popular
among young people in Hangzhou.
They all come here.
Someone crossed it.
Someone did it.
Even this game looks so Chinese.
Perfect.
Do you want to try this?
- No way. / - Try it.
For me...
Look! A child is doing it.
It made me want to try.
- It looked so fun. / - She's really good.
- Children are light. / - Right.
Then I can't do it.
Should we try this or that?
They're so good.
- I can't choose. / - You do this one.
I think you'll fall in the water for sure.
I wish someone would help me too.
Please hurry up?
You don't want to get stuck behind someone.
It was actually harder to balance than I thought.
This is not easy.
What is this?
Help me!
It was almost like a guerrilla training.
What is that?
Did you fall in the water?
(Splits)
Hyunhee, watch your legs!
- Hyunhee. / - Help me!
(When she thought she was safe)
This is hard.
It's too late to quit now.
I can't go further.
- Don't shake it. Don't shake it. / - I can't do this.
- You shouldn't go that way. / - Where should I go?
Where are you going?
- Hyunhee. / - What' with your red pants?
(Splits)
Help me!
Where are you going?
- Help me! / - Oh, no.
She's going to fall.
She's very flexible.
- Help me! / - Oh, no.
Oh, no.
And that man in the background fell into the water.
Help me.
Somebody came to help her.
I tried a bit and gave up halfway.
It was too difficult. I got tired.
What's wrong with you, Sohyun?
Hyunhee's the one that really needs help.
- You made the toad do it. / - Exactly.
Hyunhee, why did you want to do this in the first place?
I'm almost there.
She doesn't give up though.
- I'm almost there. / - You're almost there.
Grab two swings at the same time.
Here. Grab this. Grab this.
- Grab this. / - How can I grab that?
It's not like I don't want to do it.
You want to but you just can't.
It's easier said than done.
My goodness.
Oh, no.
In the end...
(Splash)
- Oh, no. / - Why did I go in?
Why is it so deep for me?
The writers told me it's knee-deep,
but it was thigh-deep for me.
Hyunhee. Hyunhee.
I'm a toad in the water.
Let me help you, Hyunhee.
It's okay. I will do it myself.
The problem is you can't climb up on the swing.
Why not just come out?
- It's too high. I'm too short. / - It's high.
Hyunhee.
I was a bit disappointed then.
If she wanted to help me,
she should have moved her body.
But she just kept saying, "Oh, no."
"I should help."
That's actually meaner.
You're embarrassed of Hyunhee.
- You didn't help. / - She's embarrassed.
- I was just an outsider... / - You look angry.
Like I wasn't with her.
- I was very embarrassed. / - She was!
- I was a bit... / - They're having fun.
- I can't lift her up. / - What are you doing?
No one's helping out.
Here's someone.
A prince turned up.
- You couldn't climb up? / - You can't.
Thank you.
Aren't you meant to marry him now?
- Such a nice person. / - We were so thankful.
When you were saying, "Help me..."
Everyone ignored you. Only he helped out.
- They all laughed. / - You ignored her the most.
Why did you say that?
Let's get dried first. Come with me.
Do we have a dryer?
I'm not sure if we do. Let's go anyway.
There were many people who fell into the water like you.
She rented the clothes and they're now all soaked.
You might be surprised to hear this.
There's a place where you can dry your clothes.
- They dry your clothes for you. / - It was great.
Don't you worry and just have fun.
Here it is.
There you go. Give him your socks too.
You can even dry your shoes.
- Really? / - Yes.
It's all for free.
You need to wait for them to dry.
- I will dry my shoes. / - Dry them in the sun.
Sohyun, there are so many young people here.
I felt like I was in an amusement park in Korea.
The important thing is whether
you will open your purse or not.
We paid for the entrance fee and the concert.
You should pay for everything.
I think she would even if it's because she feels bad.
Look. Listen to this.
It's the toad instrument from earlier.
- I will... / - It's open.
- She has to. / - But...
How much is it?
You gave me such big laughs so it's worth it.
Wait, Sohyun. This is...
The entry is 310 yuan per person.
You have to pay for me as well.
Please pay for me.
Stop trying to rip me off.
- Did you not have enough money? / - So cute.
She doesn't have enough money.
There must be ATMs here.
There are no ATMs here.
Then let's do it this way.
You go check if the clothes are now dried.
Geez.
She only paid for her own entrance fee.
Are you sure you're grateful to her?
Hyunhee, did you not bring any money?
- No, she didn't. / - I don't have money.
She didn't bring any money.
Only I brought money.
It's so much fun.
A toad that returns the favor.
Quiet and throbbing...
Toad Tour.
Whenever I did that, Chinese people laughed.
I want to be a comedian in China.
(Toad Tour, day 2)
(Hangzhou Feast)
(30 minutes from the theme park to restaurant)
Which restaurant are we going today?
We went to the theme park so we're very hungry.
- We're going to eat kaoyu. / - Kaoyu.
It's the most popular dish in China nowadays.
- So that's kaoyu. / - That's spicy peppers on top.
Spicy peppers.
You know how tender bass is.
- It's like a braised dish. / - I could eat that till I drop.
That kind of dish...
And there are pictures on the menu.
It makes it easy for us to order.
It's easy to pick and order food.
- Sohyun, come here. / - What is this?
Have you ever seen such a big cauldron?
I have never.
Is there fish inside?
They grill the fish in it
and then braise it again.
So they grill the fish first and...
First, they grill the fish and then braise the fish.
It doesn't have a fishy odor.
They get rid of the odor when they grill the fish.
It looks so delicious.
Sook, you'd really love it.
No, no.
It's here.
- That's a huge portion. / - Oh, wow.
- It's perfect for the Korean palette. / - It is.
- Peppers. / - Garlic too.
In Korea, we braise mackerel on radish.
In China, they braise fish on lotus root.
- Lotus root. / - They cook the fish on lotus root.
Lotus root adds the savory taste to the food.
It's so good.
Let me try the skin first.
I love fish skin. It looks delicious.
The onions and garlic on top...
It's just like Korean food.
Hyunhee.
My mouth keeps watering now.
This is the best fish skin I have ever had.
It's crispy, because it was grilled in the caldron.
As you know, sauces in Korea are sweet.
This isn't that sweet.
It's seasoned with chili pepper powder.
It's like homemade food.
It's so delicious. My stomach feels comfortable.
It tastes a bit like spicy rice cakes as well.
- It tastes like spicy fish stew. / - Spicy rice cakes...
It must be like spicy fish stew.
It goes well with Kaoliang wine.
It's spicy like Korean food.
You can't stop eating rice with this dish.
It makes you want rice. It's so delicious.
I love that look.
It was so easy to bone the fish.
- Is the meat chewy? / - It's so meaty.
Because it's so easy to bone the fish,
you can just eat it as if it's salmon steak.
This is a completely hot place.
I'll pay for everything.
- Even before I ask? / - Yes.
Just relax and eat.
- As soon as you ate... / - That was before you finished.
This should be a bit expensive.
No, it isn't. We ordered bass and extra ingredients.
And it was $23.80.
- Really? / - That's enough for four servings.
- It's enough food for a family of 4. / - Less than $30.
Where else will you get a family dinner for $30?
Today, we enjoyed the fancy part of Hangzhou.
Just like Hong Kong, Hangzhou also have
a light show in the middle of the city.
We must go there.
- But we should be there on time. / - A light show?
We don't have much time left.
So please eat a little faster.
(Excuse me. You should stop eating now and leave)
I don't want to waste any of this food.
- I'm hungry now. / - This is bad.
The hunger pangs are coming.
Minkyoung, are you okay?
I'm hungry.
- It's evening. / - I'm hungry now.
- It was delicious. / - This is bad.
(Toad Tour, day 2)
(Light Show)
Light show?
That show was amazing.
- That's hip. / - You can fully enjoy the cityscape.
(23 minutes by car from the restaurant to light show)
(The sky of Hangzhou gets darker)
Cityscape.
The night view there is like that of
Las Vegas or Hong Kong.
Sohyun, we don't have much time now.
We're now in Qianjiang.
- It looks like a city of the future. / - It does.
It's totally different from what we saw yesterday, right?
It's fancy and youthful.
- Qianjiang? / - Qianjiang.
There are a series of huge skyscrapers.
How do they connect the image on
a series of buildings like that?
I thought there was someone
turning on and off the lights.
You thought someone was controlling the fuse box?
(Qianjiang Light Show)
You can see the lights on the skyscrapers.
Do they have this show every day?
No, only on some days.
Tuesday, Friday and Saturday.
They set 700,000 LED lights on the buildings.
They set 700,000 LED lights on 30 different buildings.
They set the lights on the buildings.
Other people are hurrying there for the show as well.
Sohyun, it'll start in 5 minutes.
You can sleep if you want.
She started to feel tired.
- Of course. / - It was a busy day.
You must have been tired.
Today is Sungkyu's birthday.
My word.
She has a very good memory.
- You're amazing. / - Sungkyu.
You should give him a present.
- It was his birthday. / - Happy birthday.
- But he's in the army. / - He's in the military.
A birthday message from China.
- You remember your parents' birthdays, right? / - Yes.
- It's starting. / - Wow. What is that?
- It's free. / - That's right.
You can stop your car and see it if you want.
- That's pretty. / - What is that?
What is this?
- Day and night is completely different. / - It is.
- It's completely downtown. / - It's pretty.
It's really spectacular.
The city grew big as it held the G20 summit.
That's right.
Is this what it was?
Buildings become sketchpads.
Check the weather and find good days.
It'll be really great to go on a breezy day.
You can drink beer
and coffee. It's so cool.
(2.15km of buildings are lit up)
It portrayed the four seasons. It was so beautiful.
Because it's on such a large-scale,
the show is much bigger than Hong Kong or Macau.
- Is it bigger? / - I want to go there.
It's really fancy. So good.
- You've seen the laser show in Hong Kong. / - Yes.
- How does it compare? / - It's just as good.
You won't be disappointed.
Wow, over there.
They're doing fireworks here.
The fireworks are happening on the buildings.
The light show is unbelievable.
You're looking at it on TV so you can't tell,
but the length is amazing.
It's a grand show.
It'd be great to go with your lover or friends.
- Enjoying a beer... / - Yes.
It must be over.
Is it over?
Tonight is our last night here ,right?
Where are we going?
We can't stop here.
Something exciting. It's our last night,
so we'll party until we drop.
- You planned it with your style. / - Okay.
Follow me until the end.
Let's have fun.
- Which way are we going? / - Come this way.
That way?
I planned it carefully.
I found a trendy pub.
Hwijae and Sikyung have to pay attention.
- I'm paying attention. / - You'll love this place.
Is this a pub?
It's our last day, so we should drink up.
We don't really drink.
But Sikyung and Hwijae won't be able to leave.
I can't believe it's the last night already.
- I'm still stuck in that fish restaurant. / - Still?
- I can't leave. / - You'll get drunk there.
(It's already their last day in Hangzhou)
This is Nan Shan Lu.
You know the popular cafes in Garosu-gil
or Yeonnam-dong.
- They're really popular. / - Right?
- Sohyun. / - Yes?
I told you last time, right?
Every Hangzhou man that passes by you is rich.
- Hangzhou men are rich. / - Hangzhou is a rich city.
- There are a lot of rich men. / - I see.
- There must be a lot of men. / - Really?
Of course.
So what if there are a lot of men?
We can't meet any of them.
It's our last day. I'm feeling the pressure.
- From now on... / - Is this a club?
You can enjoy all 1 , 2, 3, 4 rounds here.
- All in one place. / - In one place?
- All kinds of liquor in one place. / - Really?
What?
- Is it outdoors? / - It's so pretty.
We went in there.
Snap out of it.
- Is it indoors? / - It's indoors.
The roof is open.
You can see the sky.
Look at the lights.
Everything is on a large-scale in China.
Icicles are falling from the sky.
Tonight is our last night here.
- Yes. / - It's the last night of Toad Tour.
I don't want to go to sleep yet.
Let's share our memories we made in Hangzhou
and spend the night.
I took pictures of you candidly during the trip
and prepared a gift for you.
- I prepared another gift. / - In Hangzhou?
- Ta-da. / - What's this?
- What is this? / - What is it?
Goodness.
- When did you take these? / - Toad Tour.
(Last night, when everyone was asleep)
I took Polaroid pictures of her.
- To make her good memories. / - Usually...
- Husbands do that for their wives. / - Right.
That's right.
It was as if I was proposing.
- She was like a boyfriend. / - Like a proposal.
Seriously.
All you need is a ring.
It was like a proposal.
I've never had a boyfriend like that,
but she was like the best boyfriend.
Hyunhee is so kind and considerate.
I prepared a gift for you to repay your kindness.
You even took a picture of the wallet.
- You're awesome. / - I know.
I almost cried when we named our tour
on the first day.
Look.
- Ta-da. / - Oh, my.
You probably didn't know.
We took these at the West Lake.
- At Xi Hu. / - That's right.
- You took that picture for me. / - Yes.
Oh, my.
Some pictures were taken without her knowing?
Yes.
She's so pretty.
The pictures look great.
I thought only I was taking pictures of Hyunhee.
But Hyunhee took pictures of me too.
Thank you so much.
Because you're very forgetful.
I know.
You can always look at these and
be reminded of Hangzhou.
Goodness.
I did that so she doesn't forget.
Hongbin.
She put that in to grab her attention.
It's my Hakyeon.
He loves the idols more than herself.
I did a great job by putting this picture in here.
You could've gotten bored of it.
But you have these too.
I put them in the perfect spot.
I want you to look at the photo book
and remember our trip.
Thank you so much for putting a book together.
I don't want her to forget.
We shared our memories in Hangzhou, China.
How meaningful is that?
I prepared an album hoping that she wouldn't forget.
That's why I prepared the album.
Trips with older friends really last.
That's so true.
I was so moved.
I was surprised.
I wondered why she insisted on taking Polaroids
instead of using a mobile phone.
But on the last day,
she prepared a photo book for me.
I was so touched by that.
"Hangzhou is what I miss the most."
I think I'm going to miss this time in Hangzhou
I spent with you.
We'll have to come back then.
A toad that returns the favor.
Quiet and throbbing...
Toad Tour.
Cheers.
It's already our last night.
Do you want to stay one more night?
With me?
(The toad and the princess lived happily ever after)
I miss it already.
I've been to Shanghai, Beijing,
and Guangzhou.
But I really want to go there.
- It seems really trendy, right? / - It's seems so nice.
It completely changed my idea about Hangzhou.
There was a performance that made Sohyun cry.
- That's an upgraded show. / - Yes.
It's directed by Zhang Yimou.
It's on a large-scale.
And it's something we have never seen.
They perform "Swan Lake" on a lake.
So it reminded me of my high school days
when I was doing ballet.
It was really moving.
She kept exclaiming.
Since we're on a roll, let's talk about food.
Talk about food.
Let's talk about Dongpo pork.
The Dongpo pork sauce looked so good.
You mixed it with rice and finished it.
I couldn't waste the sauce.
I wanted to mix it all up and eat it.
I love sweet food.
It was just so good.
I've never tried in Korea.
It was my first time trying Dongpo pork.
I kept thinking about it.
We'll have the audience vote now.
- Let's do it. / - My mouth is watering.
- Let's see the result. / - No, let's check the cost.
I feel rushed. Everyone is looking pleased.
I believe their expenses will be competitive too.
3 days and 2 nights on the Toad Tour.
Tell us how much your trip cost excluding the flights.
It cost $289.90 per person.
Less than $300.
- That's the most cost effective trip. / - Seriously.
That's the best.
You all enjoyed the Hangzhou trip.
Will you follow the Toad Tour's itinerary to Hangzhou?
Yes or no?
Please vote.
(Toad Tour planned a trip to Hangzhou)
(What will the judges choose?)
This week we went to Hangzhou.
What about next week?
Next week, we'll go to Kyoto, Japan.
How exciting.
- Kim Shinyoung. / - How exciting.
She's full of energy.
I'm looking forward to it.
(Next episode)
Whether you go... Kyoto! Or don't... Kyoto!
If you're going to regret, just go!
- I'll just trust you. / - Just trust me.
Ta-da.
I don't think I could forget this.
This is it.
Check out the color.
I'm salivating.
- Is it good? / - It's so good.
Right?
No way!
- Are you happy? / - I'm happy!
You'll regret it if you don't come to Kyoto.
("Eternally" by Sung Sikyung)