(Battle Trip)
(Started on April 16th, 2016)
(Numerous)
(Great tips)
(On trips)
Bravo!
This is amazing.
I've never felt like this before.
It feels like I'm in a movie.
(Battle Trip is to see)
It was the most intense moment.
Good, good.
(Battle Trip is to enjoy)
Oh, my God.
It's huge.
(Battle Trip is to eat)
It's so good.
I've never had anything like this before.
(Battle Trip's 2-year anniversary)
(The hosts have prepared a special episode)
You startled me.
You startled me!
Geez! Hey! What is this?
I have a weak heart.
That's because you're old.
What is this for?
It's our 2nd-year anniversary.
Now it feels real, huh?
That is quite fascinating.
What is?
I get surprised when I see us like this.
Don't people usually sit like this
for announcements or if they did something wrong?
Or announcing a wedding.
That's right.
What?
What are we doing?
- What is this? / - This is how it's done.
There we go.
Seriously...
- Congratulations on 2 years. / - Congratulations.
(Congratulations on 2 years Battle Trip)
Time sure goes fast.
It goes really fast.
Shouldn't we go somewhere for 2 years...
Over the past 2 years,
we were asked the most about family trips.
- Family... / - If it's a family trip...
But I live alone.
- A family trip... / - Sikyung and I...
- Dad, mom... / - Family.
- The old bachelor. / - Uncle.
It's kind of a stretch for me to be the son, right?
- It's a little hard. / - You're too big to be our son.
- You're too big to be our son. / - Then...
- You're right. / - This is good.
We'll go on a trip like this.
Korean families go on a trip to Guam the most.
- Oh, Guam. / - I went there 3 months ago.
- For me... / - How many times have you been there?
6 times.
- To be honest... / - You're a Guam native.
This means you're a native.
- Right. / - I even...
Have a family photo from Guam.
It was so good then.
Goodness.
You look so happy.
It was good then.
Seriously.
Let me tell you one thing...
There's an ice cream shop here.
I know how it tastes so I want to eat it so bad.
They'd like this place too.
Just go.
(Battle Trip's official Guam professor, Lee Hwijae)
(The ultimate girl crush, Kim Sook)
Blue is for women.
Men aren't supposed to drive.
With her...
Forget all this.
Darn it.
Help me! Help me!
(Battle Trip's official girl crush, Kim Sook)
I'm so happy.
With salmon.
One of these too.
(Battle Trip's official youngest, Sung Sikyung)
You can't!
Let's be happy for a long time.
(We'll start their family story right now)
The thing that parents like the most
is having the hotel close to the airport.
Guam is the optimal location for that.
- Right. / - How long does it take?
15 minutes.
The kids can use the pool as soon as you get there?
- That's right. / - Right.
Also, the weather's good.
You don't have to move around a lot.
- For me... / - You can plan everything then.
No, I shouldn't plan everything.
- Why not? / - Since it's a family concept.
- Should we divide the work? / - Yeah.
I'll plan the mornings.
Let's divide it into morning, afternoon, evening.
Yeah?
Can't we sleep in the morning?
What?
You can never sleep in on a family trip.
What are you on about?
You can't sleep in the morning.
You have to be diligent on trips.
Then I'll take care of the evenings.
Sikyung, you take care of the afternoons.
- Okay. / - Okay?
- Fine, okay then... / - Yeah.
What do I need to do?
Things to do in the morning and to eat.
- What to do in the afternoon. / - What you want to do.
- You decide what you want to do. / - Just decide.
- Just pick one thing. / - For me...
I can think of so many things.
In the evening?
Too much.
Let's enjoy our trip.
Yes.
I'm so...
Come on, Sikyung. Join us.
Let's have a good trip.
Let's go to Guam.
This looks like a big version of "Gangnam Style."
Try it.
This will be fun with just us three.
Good restaurants in Guam...
I'm going to eat a huge breakfast no matter what.
This looks good.
Yes, Sook?
Are you busy, Seyoon?
What time do you finish?
The radio?
I finish around 4.
- You finish at 4? / - Yeah.
Then I'll wait for you.
Hello.
To Guam.
- Guam. / - Guam expert.
I'm Guam expert, Moon Seyoon.
I'll record this.
- Do you have to record it? / - Yes.
Who do you work for?
I don't want to miss out on anything.
Okay, okay.
You know I love Korean food, right?
Why? I'm going to eat Guam food.
Restaurant "D."
Restaurant "J."
These names...
And...
The course is good.
At night.
- This is the course I like. / - At night.
Night...
"S" chicken.
At night...
- "S"... / - "S" chicken.
"S" chicken.
They have good spicy chicken.
Korea has the best chicken.
It tastes like Korean chicken.
Hafa adai.
What is that?
Hello.
- Hafa adai. / - Hafa adai.
- Hafa adai. / - At the airport...
They'll be playing music like this.
- Saying hafa adai. / - Hafa adai.
You can't just walk past them.
Hafa adai.
Hafa adai. Hafa adai.
- I learned one thing, hafa adai. / - Hafa adai.
I learned one thing, the greeting.
Sinyeong, Sinyeong, Kim Sinyeong.
Hwijae.
What should I do in Guam?
First, you have to go clubbing in Guam.
They have those adult shows as well.
You're on camera right now. I'm recording.
Oops, I'm sorry.
What about doing busking?
Busking?
- What? / - Busking.
"Say Goodbye" in an acoustic version.
It's been a while.
As you can see, I have no help.
I'll just plan it myself.
Go, go.
Seoeon, Seojun.
Why are you packing?
I'm going to Guam tomorrow.
Why?
Babies can't go.
Just me...
No...
Huh?
Did I wear sunglasses?
Take me.
How am I going to leave?
You can't go.
Why not? It's for work...
If we can't go, you can't go.
I'm going for work.
You can't go.
Can't go.
(The day of the 2-year-anniversary trip)
(Who's the first to arrive at the airport?)
Isn't anyone here yet?
(Awkward)
I can't remember the last time...
I left on a trip alone.
You're confident about Guam, right?
I'm a Guam native.
I'm a native.
I'm friends with the owner of the shooting range.
I'm friends with Chamorro people.
It's the best place for a family trip.
The airport
is close to the downtown area.
It's safe.
I'm in trouble.
(He receives a video call from home)
Seojun, I'll be back real soon.
No!
I'll be back soon.
Don't go.
Then...
Is it because I'm leaving or I'm going to Guam?
Don't go.
You don't want me to go anywhere?
Dad, don't go.
I'll call you when I'm there.
No.
(Who's arrived at the airport this time?)
It's been so long since I've been on an overseas trip.
It's nice to see you.
Oh, my.
This is amazing.
We sent people to enjoy like this for the past 2 years.
We made them happy.
Hello.
- Hello. / - Oh, my.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Hello.
It's Sook.
(Ho)
(Hahaha)
Hurry it up.
Yo!
Hey, Hwijae. Yo!
Hurry it up.
So we're actually leaving.
Seyoon recently went to Guam.
I know.
So...
But Seyoon...
Only told me about Korean restaurants.
(No help, just like Sinyeong)
Did you bring a lot of money?
No.
Why?
I have my credit card.
You need cash though.
How much did you bring?
About $100.
Lend me some money. I mean it.
Just lend me $1,000.
I don't have $1,000.
Sikyung is here.
Shouldn't I wear sunglasses since I'm going on a trip?
(Sung Sikyung now looks cool)
Incheon International Airport gives
you this sense of excitement.
He visited the salon.
Sikyung looks so cool. It's his airport look.
He's the only one looking cool.
Airport fashion.
- Look at Sikyung. / - Why are you doing this alone?
Sikyung.
You know these aren't mine, right?
- I know. / - These aren't your clothes?
- No. / - I knew it.
- Sikyung, did you bring some money? / - This...
- No. / - Talk about money later!
Don't they accept credit cards?
I want to exchange some money.
Did you bring your passports?
- Passports. / - Wait a minute.
I have my passport.
My passport was the last thing I packed.
I almost messed up bad.
Do you know about this?
They said I had to show my ears and forehead.
But now it's changed.
It doesn't matter now.
Also...
- I've ordered our meals already. / - What?
You have to order in advance, right?
What did you order for me?
I ordered a variety.
- So we can share. / - Okay then.
Let's board the plane now.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
Hey, I can use my credit card in Guam, right?
Of course.
I don't need cash, right?
They accept all cards there.
But shouldn't we bring at least $100 in cash?
$100?
I have $100.
(Off to Guam)
- Here are your in-flight meals. / - Thank you.
I ordered them in advance.
Excuse me.
I have your meal...
Yes, the healthy meal.
For Sook, who's on a diet.
I like that they gave me the right spoon for my size.
That's for Seoeon.
This is where the trip begins.
To be honest...
I wasn't going to say this because
it'll make me look old.
But the world has become so advanced.
This is so good.
This is the good restaurant.
- Sook. / - Yeah?
This is good.
I think I can eat this for every meal.
So we're actually going.
Happy trip.
I'm so happy.
As soon as we arrive...
- We sleep. / - We must sleep.
- Let's sleep. I'll wake you up. / - Okay.
I'll wake you up
then I'll sort out where we're going.
I should've brought my tablet.
(See you in Guam)
(Incheon International Airport)
(Guam International Airport, 4 hours and 25 minutes)
(Guam)
(Guam is Korea's favorite family trip destination)
(Everywhere you look)
They're so cute.
(You can have fun everywhere)
(So many activities to do)
(A paradise where you can do everything)
(We invite you to this magical island)
(Guam)
(First day in Guam)
(The hosts' rooms)
(Sikyung, Sook, Hwijae)
(Hwijae's room)
(Hwijae's room is empty)
(Where did he go this early in the morning?)
(Hwijae's swimming in the pool)
- Show us your swimming skills. / - I agree.
- We've only heard rumors about it. / - Right.
You haven't done anything so far.
You didn't even get to see the dolphins.
You couldn't even stand up on the surfing board.
He looked so pitiful when he went surfing.
(He's showing off his swimming from the morning)
(All alone in this pool)
(Sook, can you see how good I am?)
(He swam for a while all by himself)
(Meanwhile, what about Sikyung the youngest?)
(Ta-da)
(Staring the morning with news in English)
(Sikyung is an intelligent, healthy male)
(So hot)
Should I wake them up?
Such sleepyheads.
It's here.
(Silent)
Is he not in?
(Sikyung's room)
Sikyung.
Hwijae.
(Sook decides to look for them)
- Oh! / - Hi.
My goodness.
What's going on?
I thought it was my apartment.
Hello.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Such a friendly atmosphere.
Where is Sikyung?
And Hwijae?
(Spots a familiar figure 30 minutes before their trip)
Hold on. Is that Sikyung?
(Looking in)
(Staring)
Hey.
How long have you been working out?
It's been 37 minutes.
37 minutes?
You'll end up dying if you do this.
No.
I'm preparing myself to eat a lot.
What's going on?
(Sikyung did eat a lot)
(It's a good thing I worked out today)
Amazing.
Look at all this sweat.
What's up with your shirt?
You need to wear this too.
- What? / - You have to wear one too.
To be honest, we don't need to pack anything.
When they wear these shirts...
It will lift their spirits.
(Ta-da)
Don't you think about leaving the group.
We'll hang out together.
They look nice.
Smiling angel.
Can I use this to wipe my sweat and throw it out?
What are you saying?
You have to wear it.
Tell me the time and I'll be ready by then.
9 a.m.
We have to go have breakfast.
- Oh, right. / - Yeah.
We must be there by 10:30 a.m.
We have to eat breakfast...
Hurry. Run.
You can do it.
Don't wipe your sweat with this.
- Okay. / - Good.
He must be crazy.
(Sikyung ran for a long while to eat breakfast)
- Start. / - Start.
The world is your school.
Life is a journey.
Battle...
Geez.
Trip!
We've arrived in Guam!
What a day.
I don't believe it.
I feel such a sense of relief.
You're right.
When you look at Korean family trips...
This is the most popular location.
- Guam. / - We've arrived in Guam.
You're a father.
Do you agree with that?
It's even beyond that.
Last year, we stayed here for a week.
On the way to the airport, Seojun cried so much.
- Why? / - Because he didn't want to leave?
Looking at the stars.
Saying he wants to stay?
He wanted to stay here.
As you can see,
most of the people watching us here are Korean.
There are no inconveniences.
There are Korean employees.
You can ask if you don't know.
Everything is in Korean.
Today, Guam is no. 1 on
the favorite family trip destinations list.
- No. 1. / - Right.
And we're a family too.
- Our 2nd anniversary. / - That's why...
- I prepared these shirts. Dad. / - Dad.
- Mom. / - Mom.
- Old bachelor son. / - Uncle.
What are we doing today?
- Who's first? / - Today, I...
I painted the picture.
- Since you're an artist? / - Yes.
- I've planned the day... / - Where do you buy this?
With this...
There's a shop that only fashion people know.
They don't sell these just anywhere.
You have to deal privately.
There are such channels.
- Okay. / - I painted the picture today.
Morning.
Before noon.
I'm in charge.
We'll eat delicious food.
- We'll have the breakfast buffet. / - I'm hungry.
Just follow me.
How will we get there?
First off...
- Don't do things like this. / - For you two...
Don't make us do that.
I rented a car for us.
In Guam, people should rent a car
because they can rent a car with Korean license.
That's right.
Let's head out.
Let's go.
Turn around.
Battle...
Let's go.
Just do it.
Trip.
- Let's go. / - Go!
Go.
(Battle Trip 2-year-anniversary special in Guam)
(First day is planned by the hosts)
I'll be in charge of the morning.
This looks good.
Morning.
I'm in charge.
- It's so good. / - So good.
- Sikyung, you take care of lunch. / - Okay.
Hey, are you insane?
Hey!
That was scary.
Stop.
Help me! Help me!
Hey!
Stop it!
- What about dinner? / - Dinner?
(The Guam professor will take over at night)
I see the dolphins!
- Where? / - Dolphins!
Out of 5 points.
1.9 points.
3 points.
2.5 points.
(Sook is in charge of the morning)
(Sikyung in charge of the afternoon)
(Hwijae in charge of the evening)
(Battle Trip 2-year anniversary special in Guam)
(Second day is planned by the viewers)
Today, we will choose from the requests
that viewers submitted for us to try in Guam.
We'll draw them.
It's random.
(The randomly chosen activities will be carried out)
I'll lend you $40,000.
I'll go first.
Hey!
No way.
Sook, run!
You'll die once you come down.
Making me do this...
(Sook time)
(Brunch cafe)
This looks so good.
What is this?
Okay, I've chosen here for breakfast.
It's a good restaurant locals like.
Review.
"It's the best restaurant I've dined at in Guam."
They say they'd go back here if they return to Guam.
Now...
Convertible.
It's not a convertible.
Why not?
Not a convertible?
It's too sunny for that.
It's not this, is it?
- We'll go over. / - No way.
- Hurry up. / - This is ours.
What is this?
It's cute.
No convertible?
I'm in charge of the morning schedule.
- It's not a convertible? / - Come with me.
There's no convertible.
- Get in now. / - Geez.
Gentlemen.
- Get in. / - Seriously.
Thing is...
Geez.
Can't I drive?
No way.
Men shouldn't drive.
Hwijae, trust me.
Goodness.
This is new too.
- This wasn't here before. / - It wasn't.
There are tons of new shopping malls.
You're right.
If you look on the left,
there's a shopping center.
This wasn't here before.
I don't think this was here before.
It wasn't.
(Hotel)
(Brunch cafe)
(4 minutes by car)
If you look in here, it's packed with people.
It's really popular.
The locals, not tourists,
line up to eat here.
What's good at this restaurant?
At 10:30 a.m.,
we can order from both the breakfast and lunch menus.
You must come here at this time
to try food from both menus.
I heard this is a must-try dish.
The Loco Moco comes with a special sauce.
They say the sauce is really good.
- It looks delicious. / - The sauce...
Was made by accident.
They added the wrong ingredient
but it was so delicious.
That's how this special sauce was developed.
A lot of other places tried to figure out the recipe
but they won't tell the last two ingredients.
On top of that, this is a gravy sauce.
It's made from the meat stock.
Just think of it as grease.
That's a great base for sauce.
It's so good but...
To tell you in advance,
the gravy sauce is unlimited.
Unlimited.
- It is? / - Yeah.
I like anything that's unlimited.
If you have around 1L of gravy...
You could die.
Unlimited.
We're ready to order.
- Loco Moco. / - Loco Moco no. 1.
- Benedict Chamorro. / - Chamorro Benedict 1.
- And a Salmon Benedict. / - Salmon Benedict 1.
Okay.
Should we start with three?
- Yeah, that's about it. / - Okay.
Should we doggy bag the leftovers?
- Of course. / - Okay.
We must.
Will we have any leftovers?
Nope.
Serious?
There are three of us.
But...
We have two big men here.
But the size...
- An Eggs Benedict is tiny. / - It's tiny.
- It's only this big. / - Oh, really?
- It's like one bite. / - But...
First meal should be grand.
I'm looking forward to this.
Kim Sook's first meal.
(On the Jeju-do trip, she ate)
(And ate)
(And ate some more)
(She ate 5 meals in 1 day)
Can I eat all of this?
I've prepared something.
It was hard to bring this.
I took great care to bring this.
It's so funny.
Great care...
Wait...
Here.
- What is this? / - What is that?
Take a look.
Ta-da.
(Travel toppers are trending these days)
(Great for taking unique travel photos)
These are a trend these days.
How do you use them?
You take the photo like this.
Once the food is out...
I thought it was for when you tan your skin...
Then you'll have this tanned onto you. No?
Try that out.
(Uninterested)
(He's uninterested as well)
This is so Kim Sook.
You're telling me this isn't pretty?
- Let's see. / - You're telling me this isn't pretty?
It looks like he's trapped.
It's better in the sky.
- Yeah, that looks nice. / - The sky looks nice.
(Guam and the sky by Hwijae)
Here we go.
We've got the French toast right over here.
Your Loco Moco and Eggs Benedict are coming.
(Chamorro-style Eggs Benedict with ground meat)
(Eggs Benedict with plump grilled salmon)
(Hamburg patty with gravy sauce)
(A perfect combination of the Loco Moco)
What do we eat first?
Just eat the dish you want first.
- I'll slice this up. / - Yes, cut that.
Pop the egg.
First meal in Guam.
With bread.
I'll try it.
And salmon.
Sikyung.
How is it, Sikyung?
We've lived to eat this, right?
Amazing.
It's not that fattening.
This sauce isn't that fattening either.
So it's quite light.
So it's good for breakfast.
You can tell whether
the sauce is fattening or not?
My body can tell.
You'll know what I mean once you taste it.
This is the lightest Eggs Benedict I've had.
You're right.
I was very curious about this red potato.
Red potato.
This is red potato.
Red...
- Red potato. / - The red potato...
It's like...
It feels like a mix of potato and radish.
The texture.
Let me try this one.
Benedict Chamorro.
Chamorro people are the natives here, right?
- Chamorro people. / - Saipan and Guam.
(Chamorro Benedict)
(Different to an Eggs Benedict with ham and bacon)
(It's a fusion dish with a Chamorro-style sausage)
(Chamorro Benedict, $14)
Don't touch this one.
Why not?
I must take a photo.
- Hwijae. / - Stick your camera here.
It's too much work to wait for you.
- I must take it. / - Just stick your camera here.
And take photos like this.
I don't like taking food photos.
But when else will I come here?
I have to take photos.
Look how beautiful the colors are.
Upload that photo.
It's so beautiful.
When else will I come here?
I have to take photos.
Look how beautiful the colors are.
Upload that photo.
It's so beautiful.
I'll be back some time.
This dish seems very rugged.
The Chamorro sausage tastes very light.
It's healthier than you'd think.
Also...
It's really...
- Hwijae. / - Yes?
You've been to Guam so many times but never here?
Yeah.
You wasted your trips.
I had no idea this place existed.
Try that dish now.
What is this dish?
Loco Moco.
This is the must-have dish.
It's like a burger...
It's like a burger patty.
Wait. Is that rice and ribs?
It's like a hamburger patty.
It is similar to a burger.
Try it.
(He takes a good portion of the rice and the patty)
How is it?
Is it good?
It has to taste good.
Oh, this one...
This one's quite dangerous.
I should try it now?
That dish is so good.
You have to eat this.
This is the one.
It's the one.
It's so good.
Imagine a really rich mushroom soup.
Really rich. Completely savory.
Add Hamburg steak,
fried egg and rice to that.
It'd be weird if this tastes bad.
We used to add rice to cream soup when we were kids.
The kids will love this dish.
100%.
We should order extra sauce.
One sauce right here.
He's really polite.
(Adding more gravy sauce)
Let me just pour one first.
This feels like around 800 calories.
You can't bother with weight gain here.
You just have to eat.
This one is so good.
When you eat this dish,
it might get too greasy.
With this sauce,
it will refresh your palate.
Think of it as a reset button.
(Dinanche)
(Chamorro-style spicy pepper paste)
(Conne peppers are used to make the paste)
(The spiciness is piquant like Cheongyang peppers)
(Welcome to dinanche)
It's very spicy.
- Very spicy. / - Okay.
- Dinanche. / - They gave us only this much.
This smells strong.
Smells good, right?
What's good?
I can't eat this.
Did you try it?
Did you just eat it by itself?
It's spicy.
Koreans must order this.
Isn't this a punishment?
No, it's spicy and delicious.
It might be too spicy for you.
Goodness!
How much did you eat?
This is so delicious.
It's really delicious.
How is this delicious?
But with this sauce, you could finish all this.
How much did you eat?
Someone is punching the side of my mouth.
Hwijae, this is so good.
It's so good.
Isn't it so...
- You can start over, right? / - Yes.
- The sauce is... / - Let's start over.
(Looking around)
What?
You can have mine.
- Do you still have some? / - Yes.
I like dinanche.
Goodness.
It's so delicious.
It's not the spiciness that makes you angry.
It refreshes you then goes away.
It goes so well with this.
Did you come here for brunch or the spicy sauce?
Dinanche.
Seriously...
Are you going to keep eating dinanche?
Yes, dinanche.
This...
- You can't eat this dish alone. / - You're right.
You need dinanche.
You must eat it with dinanche.
Among everything in Guam, this is my favorite.
- This is only our first meal. / - The color of the sea...
The hotel, and Eggs Benedict are nothing
compared to this. You must try it.
I'm sure Koreans will love it.
This is all the sauce I ate alone, right?
(Sikyung finished 6 cups of sauce alone)
How would you rate this restaurant?
Let's make it out of 5.
I've been to Guam many times
but this is my first time trying this brunch.
Let me be honest with you.
Out of 5 points,
I give it 4.5.
Sikyung is busy eating. Don't bother.
I'll go out for a minute.
You should rate it like this.
Before and after dinanche.
How many points before dinanche?
3 points.
What about after dinanche?
4.3 points.
I'm serious.
Let me tell you why.
Eggs Benedict is common in Korea as well,
if you've tried the dish, it's a bit...
You'll be like, "What is this?" With the bread...
Just as I said, it's like a good soup
with rice and meat so everyone will like it.
But with the dinanche,
I've gone crazy. I ate everything.
Dinanche, dinanche.
The weather is so nice.
The sky looks amazing.
- Should we walk there? / - Look.
- Let me tell you something. / - What?
There's an ice cream store in there.
Let's eat ice cream on the way.
Let's go there.
Why not? Let's go.
I don't think we have enough time.
Even a short walk
makes my body sweat so much.
That's why...
- It's over there. Let's get some ice cream. / - Yeah.
Yeah.
Let's get some ice cream.
But we have to wait a bit.
No, there is no queue now.
Really? Let's go then.
Let's go then.
Are you sure?
Yes.
(They happily head to the ice cream store)
Wow. Look. It looks tasty.
- See? There's a line. / - I'm excited.
Hwijae, it looks really delicious.
- What is this? / - You must come here.
Mine is ready.
It's ready.
Thank you.
It looks beautiful.
It looks so beautiful.
(It melts in her mouth)
This is so much better than Eggs Benedict.
It's so delicious.
I don't really like sweets.
But you have to eat something like this in hot weather.
Your body sucks it up.
(Like this)
- I'm so happy. / - This is nice.
It's delicious, isn't it?
The cone is so good too.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God. / - Oh, my God.
- We're here? / - Do you see that?
That wire, Sook.
What is that?
Does this drop you into the water? What is this?
No, you ride this on the ground.
It's like a ball going straight up...
- Then coming down. / - Okay.
It's pulled back and as soon as it's released,
you spring into the sky.
No thanks for me.
- Let's ride this with me. / - No, I'm not doing this.
I feel safe only when my feet are touching the ground.
I like being held down by gravity.
(Sikyung's time)
(Slingshot of horror)
- We're here? / - Do you see that?
That wire, Sook.
Are you insane?
I'm not riding that.
(Slingshot)
(A landmark of Guam)
(You fly up 70m in just 2 seconds)
Imagine flying to the sky.
How awesome is that?
Hey, you... Are you insane?
You... I can't do this.
Forget it!
Why you...
I feel safe only when my feet are touching the ground.
I like being held down by gravity.
Hey, seriously...
You're really scared.
No, seriously...
You're so scared.
It looks fun.
I'm not doing this.
No, I mean it...
(He catches her)
Come here.
Stop trying to run away.
Gosh, look at that.
It looks so horrifying.
Look at the eyes. They look just like mine.
Hwijae, I don't think I can do this.
- You can do it. / - I'm serious.
- I can't do it. / - You can do it.
You're the host.
You won't do it for our 2nd anniversary?
Hey, that is...
Hwijae,
I'm so scared.
Are you being serious?
I'm being serious.
But this isn't scary.
I think I've wet my pants already.
- Hey. / - I mean it.
I might poop my pants.
We've introduced many rides.
- We have. / - We introduced rides in Japan...
And Daegu as well.
Do you remember Eunkwang?
(Don't forget your lipstick when you get on rides)
(Episode 16, Taiwan, aired July 30th, 2016)
(Episode 62, water activities, aired August 5th, 2017)
(Eunkwang and Changseob entertained us with lipstick)
(Forget all that, I can't think right now)
- Let's ride it. Sook, are you listening to me? / - Yes.
Do you win if you make it look pretty?
Or if you make it look funny?
- Make it funny wins. / - Okay.
Just eat the lipstick.
Alright. I will ride it.
But Sikyung, you ride it first.
- Come on. / - That's meaningless.
- It's meaningless if you do that. / - Let me see first.
- You two ride it first. / - Okay.
I'll keep my word.
What will you do if you run away?
- If you run away... / - Give me a pen and paper.
(What is he up to?)
Do you have to be like that, Sikyung?
Don't you trust me?
If she runs away, she'll have to give us all her money.
I don't think she'll give all her money to us.
Let's make it $10,000.
I will take your $10,000
and use it for Battle Trip.
- In case she runs away. / - Yeah.
Geez... $10,000 is too much.
You're so tenacious.
Use the lipstick to add your seal.
Here you are.
Please blur out the important bits.
March 16th, 2018.
If she does not ride the typhoon slingshot,
she will transfer $10,000
to the production staff of KBS Battle Trip.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
- We'll be back. / - Yeah.
Wow, you're so brave.
- What's brave about this? / - What's brave?
My heart is beating faster.
Oh, no.
(Slingshot standby)
(Shaking)
Why are they lying down?
Here it comes.
Hwijae, do we shoot out like this?
Yes, after the countdown.
- Are you ready? / - Yes, we're ready!
(Fire)
(They're shot up to the sky)
(Sook watches them from behind)
(Out of it)
(They fly towards the sun)
(Spin)
(This is the slingshot)
(Starts putting on lipstick right away)
You jerks!
Hey, you jerks!
(Hwijae can't even keep his eyes open)
You jerks!
Hey, you jerks!
This is insane.
It goes up too high even the second time.
You jerks!
This is fun.
You can't put it on now just to be funny.
Oh, my God.
Dahye, how much money do you have?
How much do you have?
How much cash do we have in total?
$50.00
$50? We have $50?
Hang on a second. Then I just need $9,950 more.
Director, how much do you have?
Please donate some money to me.
Oh, my God.
This is awesome.
- It's a great view. / - This is nice.
But I can't see anything without my glasses.
- This isn't scary at all. / - Exactly.
(Just a minute ago)
(Can't help but act like it was nothing)
Oh, my God.
Hwijae, is your nose bleeding?
Sook, I told you.
If we go first, you can't ride it.
Hey.
Sikyung, you're so pretty.
- How did you draw that mole? / - I put in the effort.
Do you know how you look now, do you?
Ride with me. I want to go on it again.
I just borrowed $50.
- I just need $9,950 more. / - Stop messing around.
Can someone lend me money?
I've collected $50.
Can someone lend me $9,950?
I'm just so scared.
- Hey, wait. / - Sook!
Wait a minute.
Someone please lend me $9,950?
(Running on the spot)
Help me!
I'm so scared.
He doesn't care. Oh, that's hot.
He doesn't even care.
I don't think I can ride this.
Wait. Sikyung.
Sikyung.
My heart's beating too fast.
- I'll be okay, right? / - Yeah.
- Where? / - I grab here, right?
Sook, your face looks really weird.
Smile.
- Hwijae. / - Are you good?
I'm so scared.
Let's go!
- Sikyung. / - Sook, don't swear.
I don't know. Goodness.
The sun is too hot.
- Will you be okay? / - I'm too scared.
- This isn't scary. It's okay. / - My eyes won't open.
It's really not scary.
Here we go.
- We're going now? / - Yes.
They're going.
We're going.
(Ready, set)
(Go!)
(It shoots up without a warning)
(Shaking)
(Screaming)
Lipstick... Lipstick...
(Though she's scared, she does what she needs to)
(Screaming)
(Sook's misfortune makes Hwijae happy)
(Sook's voice echoes in Guam)
(Sikyung puts his glasses on so he can see the view)
(He is excited)
(Can he be more excited than this?)
Are you okay? You're okay, right?
Are you okay?
- This is scary. / - You're okay, right?
(Laughing)
It's okay, right?
It's nothing, right?
- Sikyung. / - Look at the view.
Forget the view. Hey...
I'm going to hit you when we get down.
Why? Let's ask them if we can ride this again.
Hey. You...
- Don't mess with you. / - I mean it.
- My heart is up there. / - Really. Once more.
Don't mess around.
- Stop. / - Come on, Sook.
I mean it... I'll...
Can we ride it again?
Don't mess with me.
- You're insane. / - Go up right away.
Stop it. Hurry up.
- Be quiet. / - Let's go once more.
Come on, Sikyung. Hey...
Let go!
- Okay, go! / - Don't!
Help me! Help me!
Don't! Help me! Help me!
We could go again right away.
You look like "The Slave Hunters."
(Slave hunter, Sook)
Let go! Let go!
(Her fury rises)
(Good job, Sook)
I was so angry.
I got so angry when I was putting on the lipstick.
I won't hang out with you.
- I will travel alone. / - How was it?
- It was a little fun. / - See?
See? It's half-half.
But it's so scary.
It's scary and... What view is up there?
- When you go up. / - Because she's small.
She couldn't see.
It's even hard for me.
I'm seriously...
Wow...
(I'm so angry!)
I need to take this out on someone.
I'm so annoyed.
You have to give an honest review.
If you like riding rides,
this is fun, not scary.
- You two should go again. / - No...
(The viewers will choose who looks the funniest)
Out of five stars...
I give it 1.9 stars.
Well... It's fun.
I give it 2.5 stars.
Exactly half.
It's worth riding once
even if you're scared of rides like me.
I recommend it.
Now I finally feel excited since it's over.
I gave it too low a score.
You start to feel different now.
Right? It feels different, right?
After about 20 minutes, I feel different.
- Because... / - I want to complain to someone.
Now I feel happy.
- Now I feel excited. / - Really?
- I was scared before. / - That's good.
So will you rate it again?
- Yes. / - Yes, I will.
I'll give it 4.5 out of 5.
- That high? / - Yes.
It's so much fun after it's over.
I gave it 2.5 before.
Because I felt half scared and half excited.
I'll give you 2 more stars.
- It's worth riding at least once, right? / - Yeah.
(They head to the next destination)
(Battle Trip 2-year anniversary)
- Fishing, fishing. / - Fishing.
It's become popular because of Gyeonggyu.
Fishing is actually fun.
It is.
If we can catch it and eat it.
It's possible.
If the captain has a license, it's possible.
- Let's do that. / - We can make raw fish.
- Yes. / - Eat raw fish?
Since this is supposed to be a family trip,
we should think about what kids like too.
It may not be fun for us
but for the viewers...
(Brain working at full speed)
(We believe in you, Guam professor)
You're like a Guam native.
You like dolphins, right?
- I like them. / - That's it then.
You say you'd take us to see dolphins
but if we don't get to see them, I'll hit you.
If you can't see dolphins, I'll be the dolphin.
- You have to do the dolphin show. / - Yes, I will.
- You have to paint yourself gray. / - Okay.
- I'll paint myself half gray. / - Half white.
- I'll use two tones. / - Yes, two tones.
I'll transform perfectly into a dolphin.
- Water has to spurt from your head. / - Okay.
Make dolphin noises too.
- Okay, okay. / - You have to make that sound.
In Guam, you don't have to sail out too far.
You can see dolphins easily.
Don't worry.
This course is prepared by old man Hwijae.
(Fishing in Guam)
(Snorkeling in Guam)
(Dolphins in Guam)
This is amazing.
(3 things to do in Guam by the Guam professor)
(Hwijae's time)
(Dolphin cruise)
(After racing along the coastal road)
(They meet the blue sea and clear sky)
(Boats are docked at the marina)
- This is great. / - I feel like I'm on vacation.
- Seriously. Amazing. / - We are on vacation.
(She's ecstatic)
I feel like I'm in a foreign country.
Hafa adai.
- Hafa adai. / - Hafa adai.
(They get on the boat to enjoy the Guam ocean)
This is Guam.
Hwijae prepared a lot.
This course is prepared by old man Hwijae.
We'll see dolphins, fish and go snorkeling.
- Hwijae. / - Yes?
I feel like I'm on vacation now.
- This really feels like Guam, right? / - This is great.
(First, they'll have a dolphin tour)
(Hwijae is very excited)
(Here's Battle Trip's youngest)
(Glancing over)
(Sook, look at the camera)
Are you recording?
(I'm excited!)
It feels like yesterday that we were in the studio.
- But we're really here. / - This is nice.
(They get to see a great landscape)
Hwijae, look here.
(Acting silly)
1, 2, 3.
It's so beautiful.
One at a time.
What do you think?
- It does look good. / - Yes! It looks great.
Okay, it looks perfect now.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They enjoy the cool sea breeze)
(They sail for 20 minutes to see the dolphins)
Don't people say it looks pretty
when the hair blows in the wind?
(What Sook imagined)
What is wrong with me?
Actresses look pretty when their hair blows in the wind.
Hwijae, how do I look?
I heard it's pretty when the hair blows in the wind.
(Sook)
You're just "The Slave Hunters."
What's with this?
(They can't wait to see dolphins)
(One man is nervous)
If we don't see dolphins, I'll hit you.
If you don't see dolphins, I'll become one.
- You have to do the dolphin show. / - Okay, I will.
We have to see the dolphin.
(Why did I agree to that?)
Everyone, we're almost there!
Everyone, we can see dolphins soon.
There it is!
- Where? / - Dolphin! Dolphin!
Where?
(The sea looks calm)
(The video is not paused)
(Oh, no)
(1 year ago, Jeju-do host special)
All I see is seagulls.
Dolphins, where are you?
I came to see dolphins.
(Seagulls again?)
(What do we do about Hwijae?)
(Sigh)
(Solemn)
Wait? Isn't that a dolphin?
- Where? Where? / - There!
It jumped! It jumped!
It jumped!
Did you see?
- Over there! / - It's jumping!
- They're right here. / - They are.
Wow, I see dolphins here.
- Wow. / - This is no joke.
- Over here, over here. / - What's going on?
(It's unbelievable that they're seeing this)
(A pod of dolphins)
No way.
They're coming here. They're coming here.
(3 dolphins jump out of the water)
Where are they?
(Before their very eyes)
(The dolphins show their new skills)
They're so adorable.
They're playing.
I must be getting old. I'm getting teary.
You know what I mean, right?
(Sikyung, don't cry)
(Before Sikyung cries, they head to the next spot)
(Fulfilled)
(The dolphin tour was successful, 5 stars for sure)
(They head to the fishing spot)
(In the middle of South Pacific Ocean)
(They enjoy the leisure of fishing)
(The sun slowly goes down)
I'm getting bored now.
(It's not easy to catch a fish)
(They've been waiting for 30 minutes without a bite)
- Who suggested we go fishing? / - I'm Sorry.
I'm not giving you points for this.
I give -100 points for fishing.
Let's try one last time and go snorkeling.
(They try fishing one last time)
(Please bite it)
(Right then!)
I got one.
Did you?
Hey, it's a big one.
- What is it? / - I don't know.
Look at the rod bending.
(It's a sign of a big fish)
Did you catch it?
(The rod is bent)
(Hwijae, I want to eat raw fish)
(I trust you, Guam professor)
You caught a rock.
Really?
It got caught on a rock.
Rock?
(Disappointed)
What happened?
What was that? You sounded so confident.
I haven't been fishing because of the kids.
(Sikyung has one last try as well)
(Let's remain calm, it could be a rock)
(Hesitant)
- Look at this. / - Did something bite?
You've got something.
- Wow! / - What is it?
(Sikyung did it in the end)
(They finally caught a fish)
Really?
Sikyung, you did it.
Guam suits Sikyung.
Let's catch two more of these.
It wasn't hard.
Maybe I should be on "The Fishermen and the City."
Let's go snorkeling. It will make up for this.
(Snorkeling)
(The 3 of them get ready for snorkeling)
I think Sikyung doesn't have to put makeup on.
Take your sunglasses off, Sikyung.
I can't tell it's you.
This won't do.
(This is actually Sung Sikyung)
Sikyung, don't worry.
- What kind of style? / - Ray-Ban.
Okay, okay.
I shouldn't do water sports. Because...
People don't recognize me if I take off my glasses.
It will be funnier then.
Sikyung, I will draw one on your face with a marker.
I'll draw glasses on your face with a marker
so you can be comfortable underwater.
When I was in my 20s, I hated things like this.
But... I think it'll be alright to draw it on my face.
I guarantee satisfaction.
(She tries to make it look like he's wearing glasses)
Sook, those are some luxury glasses.
I think Sikyung will hit me.
Sikyung, you look better than you think actually.
Let me introduce my first artwork.
Sung Sikyung and Water Activities.
Take them off.
(He finally reveals his face)
(Amazing)
- Hey, Sikyung. / - She drew it on so well.
- I can't tell. / - She did so well.
- You can't tell at all. / - The glasses are there.
- They're just glasses. / - They're real glasses.
Do you want round glasses?
I have to do it too?
Of course, you have to take off your glasses.
Why me as well?
Let's go with round glasses.
(She tries to get away)
(She got caught)
But I don't wear glasses.
I like it.
- That's good then. / - I like it.
I'm happy.
Let's go.
Why did I start this?
(It's now time to enjoy the ocean)
(Hwijae goes into the water first)
(Sikyung joins as well)
Let's go, Sikyung.
Sikyung, I will go catch some fish.
Brother, how is it living off the grid?
I've been living off the ocean and nature
here in Guam for...
(Cracking up because of Sook)
20 some years now.
20 some years now. Living off the grid.
I'll go and catch some fish.
Can you come in now so I can get out?
(20 years in Guam but still scared of the water)
It's cold! It's so cold.
It's so cold.
(Okay)
(Everyone is in the water now)
(Inside the South Pacific Ocean)
(With crystal clear water)
(They relax and watch the fish)
(So excited)
(Hwijae is getting ready to dive)
Are you going to dive? Go on.
(Hwijae is showing off his swimming skills)
You're like a mermaid.
You were really beautiful.
(They are enjoying and relaxing in the sea)
(They head back after they complete the day's activities)
(Making raw fish with Sikyung's catch)
(Precious)
If we'd caught one each...
This is enough.
This is worthy of "The Fisherman and the City."
You'll get sick if you eat too much.
- Let's have a drink first. / - Good work.
- Good work, everyone. / - Please score generously.
It's good.
I think it tastes better than Jeju-do.
- I can't believe this. / - What is this?
It's so chewy.
- It's clean and sweet. / - Oh, my.
(Tastes clean and sweet because they caught it)
- This is it. / - I've lived in Guam for 15 years for this.
Guam is so nice.
Sir, what's your English name here?
I'm known as Nanda Kim here.
Are you okay?
I can't believe that Battle Trip came to Guam.
I'm so thankful. Please promote Guam a lot.
Tell them who good Guam is.
- Sir. / - Sook.
I heard you live under here.
You just live here.
- I'll get going now. / - She lives with the Dragon King.
(Sook is so funny)
You're enjoying it so much.
- It's so good. / - It's so good.
The fish itself is so good.
It tastes good after playing in the water.
Can't we buy some more fish?
We can buy it at the supermarket.
Sikyung, let's fish more.
Sikyung, let's do some more fishing.
How much is this course?
How much for a family of four?
$180.00
$50 for adults. $40 for children.
If you convert that to the Korean currency,
that's between 50,000 to 60,000 KRW.
That's a good price.
- It's a great price. / - Yeah.
How many points should we give this?
Sir.
For me...
The dolphin tour...
I will give it 5 out of 5 points.
But I deduct 5 points for the fishing.
You have to catch the fish to be fun.
So it's zero but then for snorkeling.
If you include snorkeling
and eating the fish we caught...
- I give this... / - Out of 5.
5 points.
Yeah!
Full score.
Sikyung.
I almost cried because of the dolphins.
- He's going to give a full score. / - The dolphins are...
Very interesting to humans.
Their existence is so grateful yet heart breaking.
For me, I think you must come here with family.
It's a must.
When the dolphins jumped,
I really thought of Seoeon and Seojun.
Even if you couldn't catch any fish...
Just being able to enjoy this sunset with your family...
This deserves 5 points.
So 5 points.
(Cheer)
If you get lucky and catch something like this...
- That's amazing. / - That'd be 10 out of 10.
Since the sun is setting, we need to have dinner.
- Aren't you hungry? / - Normally...
- Yes, after being in the water. / - You are, right?
We ate something greasy earlier.
We will get rid of that greasiness now.
- Let's go. Okay? / - Let's go.
I'll travel by water.
- Sir. / - You can ride the boat.
But you have bad knees.
I hear your Korean name is Dragon King.
I'll leave first.
Stop it, sir.
(Good restaurant certified by Hwijae)
We'll be in trouble if we go here.
We'll gain 3kg here.
- Thai? / - That looks so good.
I've been to this restaurant twice.
- Because it was so good? / - I love it so much.
- Really? / - It's so delicious.
(It's time to go to dinner where they will fall in love)
- Is it Thai food? / - Yes, it's Thai.
Do you want something refreshing?
I want something refreshing.
- Do you want it? / - Yes.
- It's salty and sweet. / - Give me alcohol.
- Why is he acting like this? / - His nose is burnt.
I thought he was a Guam drunkard.
How could my nose burn like this?
This place is really recognized
for its Thai food in Guam.
Over there. You know the review...
2014, 2015, 2016, 2017.
They won awards each year.
- Let's go in. / - Let's go.
I'm looking forward to it. I love places like this.
(Many people chose this as their favorite restaurant)
Pick one each.
What is this? They all look good.
- Here... / - How can we only choose one?
(That's impossible)
(If we had to choose one)
I want this interesting looking one.
What?
Northern Thailand sausage.
Will it be okay for you?
Northern Thailand sausage...
And spring rolls.
I'll choose the curry.
- Which curry? / - Just the standard red curry.
- Red curry. / - Okay.
Let's order this first and order more later.
No. We have to order this.
What is it?
Vietnamese fried catfish.
Hwijae.
- Shouldn't we order this? / - Don't eat catfish.
- Let's eat that later. / - Please order it for me.
- Shouldn't we have some fried rice? / - Okay then.
- Let's eat this first. / - Let's order fried rice.
The curry comes with rice.
- Let's order the fried rice later. / - Okay.
- We're ready to order. / - Sure.
Spring roll and Thai sausage...
Is this our first order?
This is for the first round.
And the second round is coming.
(Unbelievable)
(Countless food to stimulate the appetite)
(It's $69.90 in total)
(The first dish is here)
(Fried spring rolls, $7.50)
(Crispy)
She looks the same when she's scared and hungry.
- The face from the Slingshot. / - It's the same.
Same as when she's angry...
(It really is the same)
It's the same.
It's the same when she's scared and when it's delicious.
It's so good.
I'll try one too.
Want to join me, Sikyung?
(Will it suit their taste?)
(They both admire it at once)
It's fried well.
I can taste a lot of vegetables.
- What's important is... / - It tastes clean.
The skin is so thin and crispy.
(Satisfied)
What is this sauce?
It's Tom yum.
Tom yum Goong. Tom yum Goong.
(Battle Trip hosts' favorite, Tom yum Goong)
I want to boil up a load of Tom yum Goong
and bathe in it.
(It's so refreshing)
I want to order a lot of Tom yum Goong
and massage my face with it.
(Don't eat it, give it to your skin)
(It's time to eat Tom yum Goong, the best of Thai food)
(Shrimp Tom yum Goong, $14.50)
It's good.
This restaurant makes really good Tom yum Goong.
It's very sour.
(They reenacted the delicious taste of Thailand)
For people who enjoy Thai food,
they should season it stronger.
Seoeon and Seojun will like this.
I'll show you how I eat it.
I don't add the ingredients.
I just grab one shrimp.
(Cilantro)
I eat it like this.
(How will it taste with this much cilantro?)
(This is it)
Are you satisfied?
I love it.
(Sikyung also tries a bite)
(Completely approved)
This is my taste.
It isn't bad.
The red curry chicken.
(Another dish, the red curry)
(Chicken red curry, $11)
Goodness.
It looks more delicious than it looks.
It doesn't look spicy.
How is it?
Tom yum Goong.
(Sook, this is it)
We would've regretted it if we didn't order this.
Completely different from the curry we usually eat.
And it's different from Indian curry.
- It's not spicy. / - Are you sure?
Try it with some rice.
It might be difficult for you.
- It's so good. / - So good.
It's the level of spiciness that Koreans love.
Try it with rice.
I'm dying here.
It's so good.
This is a really good kind of spicy.
Why are they so fast?
The last dish is the white pepper fish.
- Okay. / - Wow.
(It's Sikyung's recommended dish, deep-fried catfish)
(Deep-fried catfish with white pepper, $12.50)
It smells great already.
(How will this unfamiliar dish taste?)
Come on.
(Just try it with no doubt)
When the meat starts to crumble...
This is the best fish I've ever tried.
Is this catfish?
- It's so tender. / - Look at the meat.
(Plump)
This is the best fish I've ever tried.
I'm sure this is
one of the top 3 dishes of this restaurant.
This isn't catfish.
It's chicken.
- It's here. / - It's the Thai sausage.
(Here comes a new challenge, Thai sausage)
(What does it taste like?)
I'll try this interesting dish, the Thai sausage.
- Will it be okay? / - How is it?
It's Northern Thai sausage.
Deep-fried squid is just common.
And skewers are just average.
This isn't my thing. Gosh, Sikyung.
(What's wrong with her?)
I told you to trust me.
Just trust me.
It's delicious.
It's great.
(This is it)
The aftertaste is a very spicy cold blood sausage.
It's more like spicy beef soup.
It tastes much like Philippine sausage.
This is amazing.
This is harmonious.
- It's not too spicy. It's just good. / - Yeah.
Imagine if we didn't order the Northern Thai sausage.
- It'd be too dull. / - It was a must.
It's really good, right?
I'm happy.
Let me focus on eating now.
What?
What did you say?
(It's time for them to eat properly)
Do we score it now?
- I already did at the start. / -  How much?
- The second I stepped in. / - 5 points?
- What about you, Sikyung? / - I think this place is Guam.
(There's no need to explain further)
This is Guam.
This place is Guam to me.
Let's calculate the expenses for today.
The breakfast we had was $64.
Slingshot was $25 per person.
And the dolphin cruise was $54 per person.
($27 per person for the Thai dinner)
(The total is $480 per person including accommodation)
I want to try other dishes.
(What? Aren't they done yet?)
It's that good.
Order green papaya salad.
(And that's how they began round 2)
Hwijae, go and enjoy the shooting range.
We'll start round 2.
Come on.
(Hwijae actually went to the shooting range)
I'm so happy.
Fathers exhausted from babysitting.
Challenge!
(Meanwhile, Sook and Sikyung finished the 2nd round)
There will be a book for our 2-year anniversary.
- So many good things are happening. / - Battle Trip?
Now that the book is out,
we should hold a special event for our viewers.
We should give out some books.
Yeah, let's give out the books.
First, please watch the live broadcast.
And upload lots of photos.
(Next episode)
It's our second day.
Today, the viewers suggested things
we should do in Guam.
We'll do a random lottery.
Check them.
(Paradise of activities)
(Clear blue skies)
Sikyung, are you enjoying your wedding shoot?
Let's be happy for a long time.
(Battle Trip)
("Blooming Day" by EXO-CBX)