Hello, I really love travel.
I'm 21-year-old, Shin Nayeon.
I've been to places that are close to Korea like
Taiwan, Hong Kong, China, Japan, Vietnam.
I want to revisit
Taiwan and Hong Kong,
and I'm wondering where I should go.
Since Hong Kong and Taiwan is already well known,
please introduce me to unique places
that people don't know very well.
It's Hong Kong but it doesn't feel like Hong Kong.
This isn't the Hong Kong I know.
Let's go!
Wow.
I just got goose bumps.
(Dynamic rides)
We'll enjoy Lantau Island.
It was so fun and fascinating.
- Yong Kong. / - Byul Kong.
Hong Kong, kong, kong.
Kong, kong, kong!
(Numerous great tips on trips)
We give you great tips for trips on Saturday night.
It's time for Battle Trip.
Last time, we visited unique places in Hong Kong.
- It was incredible. / - A new Hong Kong.
They were really exciting trip planners.
MAMAMOO's Moon Byul and Solar.
They were the definition of fun.
They were pretty.
They're pretty but Solar's mouth was too big.
I was shocked.
The scary rides were even scarier because of her.
Since you have kids,
the theme park... You must've thought of it a lot.
I went home and told my wife.
- My wife agreed to make plans. / - To go for sure.
My kids haven't heard of Disneyland.
And the fact you can meet Iron Man...
- That's the biggest merit. / - I got goose bumps.
You can't see that anywhere else in the world.
We'll be visiting when they're 6, turning 7.
You'll be looking forward to that next year?
Later on after they turn 6.
We're heading to Taiwan today, right?
Battle Trip has been to Taiwan a few times.
- Shin Dong and Kim Sinyeong went. / - Many times.
They flew the sky lanterns, ate corn at the hot spring.
- They shampooed their hair. / - The shampoo.
It was incredible.
- BTOB went to Taiwan. / - BTOB.
Eungwang with his lipstick on the ride.
That made us laugh. It's unforgettable.
That was the best.
Again, we have two lovely planners.
They went to Taiwan to show a side of it
that's not very well known.
Taiwan trip, intermediate level.
Who went where?
- I'm curious. / - I'm curious.
Let's check it out.
Taipei.
We arrived!
That's incredible.
(A place of magnificent natural surroundings)
(A city of food)
(No more Taipei)
(Taiwan intermediate course, find a new place!)
(Kaohsiung and Tainan)
(Newer and more special)
(A city beyond your imagination)
(A new city of food)
(1 week before the trip)
(The trip planners meet the staff for the first time)
(What are these two doing?)
(Serious)
(You should talk about the trip)
We're complete newbies when it comes to traveling.
Without perfect preparation,
we won't be able to do anything there.
So we prepared a few things.
- Chorong and I... / - This is a map of Taiwan.
We've divided it.
The area I researched...
Is here, Kaohsiung.
Since we're an energetic girl group...
We decided to be active during this trip.
And so we're going to tour the city.
There's a bike road that's 800km long.
We'll start from Love River to Lotus Pond...
- By bike. / - 800km?
Once we arrive, our calves will pop.
There's a theme park.
We'll drive racing carts there.
- But you don't have a license. / - Right.
You don't need a license?
Nope.
They're all difficult activities.
- Then... / - Aren't we eating anything?
We'll visit a hot pot place called Tian Shui Yue.
It's a really famous place.
You should always eat first no matter what you do.
It's a very well-planned course.
I like to go for healing.
I like to rest.
I've planned our trip to the central region of Taiwan,
called Tainan.
There's a lot to do on this side.
- Do you like hiking? / - Of course.
- Is it okay? / - Yes...
Your face says otherwise.
I do enjoy hiking...
But we won't be walking.
There's one of the top 3 high mountain train in the world.
So we'll take this train up that mountain.
- Isn't it amazing? / - Yeah.
Over here, we can see the sunrise and...
Do you know sea clouds?
- I do. / - What are they?
Floating like the clouds...
- It's a cloud. / - Right.
And it's shaped like the ocean.
We'll watch that and experience healing.
I like oolong tea.
I'm going to drink some proper oolong tea.
Then we'll do mudpacks at the hot spring.
All of mine are healing activities.
Mostly to see and feel.
(Day 1, Hayoung's course in Kaohsiung)
(Day 2, Chorong's course in Tainan, Chiayi)
We'll use these to score the places
since we're Apink.
- Like triple A? / - Yes.
To be honest, it might...
It might not go as we planned.
We'll be honest with our scores
on this trip even though we planned it.
One, since it's delicious.
I think this one needs three "A"s.
One for ambience.
3!
(Look forward Chorong and Hayoung's honest scores)
(Oh Hayoung, Park Chorong)
(Oh Amazing)
(Korea to Kaohsiung)
Where are we?
- This is the theme park. / - Amusement park!
Look. You have rides that are even famous in Korea.
As soon as we arrive...
The reason we're here
is because it's only 5 minutes from the airport.
It's only one station away.
Let's enjoy the speed
by driving go-karts.
You don't have a license.
You don't need a license for this.
(Circuit Park)
(A 10:1 replica of the Japanese F1 circuit)
(600m long, top speed of 70km per hour)
(Price of Circuit Park)
(Single seater, 8 minutes, $25, lesson fee $4)
(Double seater, 8 minutes, $30, lesson fee $4)
(Ways to enjoy cart riding)
(1, sign the agreement)
(2, input personal info, you need your passport)
(3, take a photo for membership)
(Posing for the membership photo)
Can I take my photo again?
No.
You have to use that next time as well.
I should've taken a proper photo.
Tie your hair before you put on helmets.
We have to tie up our hair?
(Hair over shoulder length must be tied up)
I put my face in here.
(Ta-da)
Let's go.
We've transformed to go-kart.
We need to do that thing...
- Bet. / - Oh, right.
What should we bet?
- Paying for lunch. / - Sure you can win?
- No. / - I have no license.
- People without licenses are the scariest. / - So true.
I'm scared.
This is to accelerate.
Wow.
- Hayoung, drive slowly. / - Okay.
(Oh Amazing battle, racing for lunch)
(8 minutes to go around the 600m circuit)
(Chorong)
(Hayoung)
(Hayoung, drive slowly)
(Hayoung speeds out)
(Screaming)
Hayoung, wait for me!
I said to wait.
(Takes a glance back and accelerates)
Hayoung, wait for me!
(Hayoung speeds on without fear)
(Hayoung 56.415)
(Chorong 54.074)
(Chorong boosts forward and catches up)
(The real race begins now)
(She's almost caught up)
(But Hayoung speeds on again)
(Speedster Hayoung is difficult to catch)
(Regretful, relaxed)
(I will catch you, Hayoung)
(Hayoung)
(Hayoung records her fastest lap)
(Driving so fast)
(She doesn't panic and drives on)
(Chorong starts her 3rd lap)
(Chorong sees something)
(Hayoung, what are you doing there?)
(She crashed after going too fast)
(Chorong, help)
(Humiliated)
(Hayoung didn't know what braking was)
(Chorong's so happy to be in the lead)
(Wow!)
(Race over)
(She gets back safe)
I drove too recklessly.
Safe driving is the best.
I won!
Free lunch for me.
- 3 for me. / - Me too.
Let's go eat. I'm so hungry.
(A noodle shop in Kaohsiung)
To tell you about how famous this place is...
They're so successful that they opened a third store.
Yoo Minsang's team mentioned 3 rules.
What is Minsang's standard a good restaurant?
What's your standard?
- They have really good business. / - Good business.
They expand their shop.
- The owner is rich. / - Rich.
Pays a lot of tax.
- And it's old? / - Yes, it has to be old.
- It's been around a long time? / - It has.
This place has opened a third store
so it passes the standard.
What's this place famous for?
It's famous for noodle soup.
(Yang Chun noodles)
(Made with noodles from Shanghai, China)
(Topped with various garnishes)
(Cheap yet delicious Yang Chun noodles and dry noodles)
Thank you.
Is this the dry noodles or the one with soup?
It's the dry noodles.
It smells like black bean instant noodles.
Really?
(A familiar smell from an unfamiliar dish)
Going to famous restaurants on trip...
- Chorong! / - Good? Black bean instant noodles?
- Yeah! / - Right?
It smelt like it.
Try it.
Right?
It's such a familiar taste.
Cook...
The thing you eat on Sundays.
It's so good.
Should we add some pepper?
Chorong!
- Is this pepper noodles? / - It's okay.
You need pepper for these dishes.
(She tastes the pepper noodles)
It's salty, right?
It tastes more like black bean instant noodles.
- You prefer this one. / - It's good.
Thank you.
This is the noodle soup.
It doesn't have a strong smell.
Radish soup!
It tastes like radish soup.
- It's good. / - This one's good.
They all taste good.
It kind of tastes like rice noodles.
The noodles aren't too strong.
I like it. It's to my liking.
Hayoung, you're eating so well.
(She's not very good with spices)
I was worried whether I'd like it or not.
I'm an extremely picky eater.
But I'm eating well today.
If Hayoung can eat it...
Anyone who's bad with foreign food will be fine.
They can all eat it.
You chose a good place, Hayoung.
I'm satisfied.
We ate all this.
- And it's not $10. / - Really?
(This didn't even cost $10?)
This and this...
- The price... / - How much is it?
Around $15.
$15.00
For these two?
It's $3 total.
Even spicy rice cakes cost $2.
All these sides are $1.
It doesn't even feel like I'm spending money.
We give it 3 "A"s.
Next course. It was so good.
(Hayoung's course in Kaohsiung)
(Bike riding)
(Love River)
(Center of Kaohsiung, dividing it into north and south)
(Longest canal in Kaohsiung at 12km)
(The greatest canal named Love River)
(A great place for dates)
- To tell you about this place... / - So nice.
It's the river in the center of Kaohsiung.
From my research...
Kaohsiung is a top 5 Asian city as rated by CNN.
There's a bike road that's 800km long.
I've wanted to ride bikes these days.
I know. And we're young.
Young?
We're youthful.
Compared to the other team....
We're probably younger thanks to me.
I'll cover for your age.
So...
What we're doing here is...
Check that out.
- Bike? / - Bikes.
This is the best possible course
for tourists.
It's free for 30 minutes.
The place we're headed to is called Pier-2 Art Center.
It takes about 10 minutes to get there.
And if we ride these bikes, it's free.
The great thing is, if you use a credit card,
it's easy.
(How to rent a bike)
Insert your credit card.
(Check your bike number and select it)
(Pull out the bike that's been unlocked)
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
Fun!
(They're racing from the start)
This is fun.
Should we play some music?
(Hayoung is currently singing "Rainism")
Hayoung is strange.
She's strange.
- Wow, what's this? / - It's so pretty here.
(They arrive at Pier-2 Art Center in 10 minutes)
What is this place?
(District B, train park)
(District C, Pier-2 Art Center and gallery)
(Pier-2 Art Center)
(Created during the imperialist era, is now abandoned)
(This was a warehouse of Kaohsiung's wharf)
(It was renovated for performances and galleries)
(It was recreated into an art space)
We're here.
It was perfect
Okay.
- Done? / - Yeah.
(Do you want to leave for somewhere?)
(It's time to leave)
(A train ride of memories)
When you watch things like "Spirited Away,"
they ride the train.
It feels like that.
(Time to get on the train)
(Ready to leave)
It's us.
Thank you.
Here goes.
Let's go.
Hello, baby.
(Heading out)
(It's a kid's train)
Hello, baby.
So cute.
(Pier-2 Art Center mini train, $9)
This is a perfect fit for me.
It's comfortable.
It's safe even if you don't hold the handles.
- It's like we're entering an unknown world. / - Yeah.
The kids would love this.
Look, dinosaur. Dinosaur.
But the people walking are faster.
It's really slow but isn't it nice?
This is very pleasant.
It's getting faster.
(It's not really this slow, is it?)
Isn't this too cute?
(Pier-2 Art Center District B)
(Renovated warehouses have become galleries)
(They're free of charge)
- We must be here. / - No, I want to ride more.
It's called the Pier-2 Art Center.
You can see modern art in Kaohsiung.
We must take photos here
and upload them on social media.
We must.
Okay.
(District C is good for social media photos)
(Trying to get a photo of their lives here)
It's so pretty.
That kid is peeing.
How about a photo of you peeping?
That's too crude.
Why would we peep?
I'm sorry. He's only a kid.
- That's a bit... / - We can't show ourselves like this.
This one.
Try it.
Take the photo when I'm in the air.
Okay. 1, 2, 3.
Did you get it?
I feel like Gulliver.
- Doesn't this look cool too? / - Let's see.
This place is cool.
(Extra close-up shots are okay)
That looks so good.
Check this out.
You need something like this to get loads of likes.
(It's not over yet)
- You can do it, right? / - Of course.
Go pose.
Okay.
Nice.
That was good.
I got it.
Check it out.
Looks good, right?
Okay, your turn.
Oh, my.
You look like a cool girl with heartache.
Okay, okay.
Okay!
That's the one.
Good, good.
Girl crush.
Check this out.
This one's nice too.
(They found their once in a lifetime photos)
My goodness.
(It was the balloon)
(Best photo no. 3)
(Best photo no. 2)
(Best photo no. 1)
We've used up a lot of calories here.
Yeah, I'm hungry.
We spewed out our passion for these photos.
Let's go to have good food.
I'm hungry.
I digest so fast.
(Their very active day passes)
It's night time.
To tell you about this place...
It's where we can eat till we pop.
It's a proper hot pot place.
Oh, hot pot!
It's been so long.
We rode so many things today
so we'll have hot pot to heal up.
Bye.
- The restaurant is huge. / - I know.
It's really classy.
The door itself is already so grand. Open...
Sesame.
Amazing.
(Surprise)
- Amazing. / - What is this place?
It's amazing.
(Tian Shui Yue Hot Pot)
(A trending place in Kaohsiung for its ambience)
(Popular among the youth for affordable prices)
It looks really fancy here
but it's all between $11 and $15.
And you don't eat as a table.
You get your own bowl.
That's so good.
So you can eat what you want.
The specialty here is sukiyaki.
It's really famous.
So we'll get a bowl of broth each.
And order sukiyaki. What do you think?
Sounds good.
We could eat till we're full and it won't cost much.
Oh!
(Surprised)
- It's a big cotton candy. / - It's coming.
Amazing.
Check this out.
It's a huge cotton candy.
Telling us to film it.
(Something you can only see here)
(The cotton candy disappears before your eyes)
It's a performance.
Oh, my God.
It's going crazy.
This must be the real deal.
There's so much to eat.
- This is the standard meal? /  - I think so.
Wow, it looks so good.
I think I have to add this now.
Do I just put it all in?
I'll add the seafood later.
Did I add too much?
(Looks delicious)
- Hayoung adds the meat first. / -  Yes.
It's so big. It's the size of my face.
It is!
I can smell the hot pot.
I want to try the meat first.
(It's finally time to eat)
I'd better try some.
In this Taiwanese sauce.
Is it incredible?
You won't be able to eat this.
It smells a bit like shrimp.
- It's good. / - Should I try some too?
(She eats the broth with no sauce)
It's so good.
I'm happy.
Hayoung, I want to try yours.
If you're a picky eater, order the original.
Everything is best in the original.
But mine has a strong flavor.
It's better without the sauce.
Just eat it as is.
Let's eat.
This is Taiwan.
(Gorging on food)
(The cotton candy sukiyaki)
(They both go for it)
We have to stand to eat this.
There's meat in here.
(Sukiyaki)
(A hot pot dish made with soy sauce and sugar)
The sukiyaki is so good.
Sukiyaki goes with egg.
(She knows how to eat it)
This is torture, right?
(Thumbs up)
I thought it'd be too sweet
because of the cotton candy.
But it's not sweet.
I think the sukiyaki is better.
The sukiyaki is so good.
(She can't stop eating)
- It's good. / - It's so good.
It's really good, right?
It's not even that sweet.
(One meat after another)
It's like we're stealing our members' food.
(An extra serving of meat)
The food's finally here.
Wow, it just came out?
- Is this that one? / - This must be the meat.
Let's taste it.
(If it's too hot, cheers)
(Bottoms up)
(Third phase of their dinner)
I'm starting to get full.
What's our overall evaluation?
1 point for ambience.
- What about price? / - Honestly, the price.
All this...
It's only because we ate a lot
but all this was a little over $50.
1 for price.
Now for taste.
The youngest prepared this with much thought.
So it deserves another "A," right?
Now it's my turn.
Into the majesty of nature...
- For healing. / - Healing.
We have to cover some distance.
We're supposed to leave now.
- It's hardcore, right? / - We have to sleep.
What kind of healing is this?
Wait. This is so tiring.
My feet hurt too much.
Hayoung's dying.
Wow.
Incredible.
(Oh Amazing Tour is full of surprises, look forward to it)
Where are we?
Zuoying HSR Station.
We have to head off on a long journey
Do you know how to purchase the tickets?
Of course.
We're at Zuoying Station.
And we're heading to Chiayi Station.
Chiayi Station.
Okay.
(Heading to the Alishan Range)
Finally, we get to see the sunrise.
(Zuoying Station to Chiayi Station, 30 minutes)
(Chiayi Station to Alishan Range, 3 hours by bus)
I feel like it's not a holiday if it's too hard.
So, I go for healing activities
since I like to rest.
(Chorong's course in Tainan, Chiayi County)
(Watching the sunrise on Alishan Range)
(So dark)
What's going on here?
Chorong?
What time is it?
It's a bit past 4 a.m.
This is Alishan Station.
We're going to see the famous sunrise and clouds.
But the thing is...
It's a bit too early, right?
We came straight by train.
- We'll get some sleep. / - I think...
Your course is harder than my course.
What kind of healing is this?
This is how it's done.
The sunrise and sea of clouds will
wash away all your stress.
Is that so?
I'm a bit anxious.
Didn't the time change?
They say the time for the sunrise
is announced the day before.
You can look it up online
so you don't miss out.
But the thing is,
there's a lot of rainfall in this region.
So there are many foggy days.
You can only see it 3 times per 10 days.
We'd be really lucky if we see it today.
- If we don't? / - It can't be helped then.
Life is just like that.
Let's hurry in.
Check out the people.
There are many people like us.
I told you. This place is famous.
(Only the diligent people can see the beauty of Alishan)
(Alishan Station to Zhushan Station, 30 minutes)
- See that electronic sign? / - Yes.
- That's the number of tickets left. / - 322.
They only have a limited amount of tickets?
Only a set number of people can ride the train.
Wow.
350 people on weekdays.
There's only one train for the sunrise.
Check that out. It's decided.
It keeps going down.
- However... / - There's no way we'll miss out.
($5.40 for tickets to Zhushan Station)
(The count is precise)
There are lots of foreigners too.
They're all foreigners.
There are no Koreans at all.
Anyone from Korea?
I guess not.
Our train leaves at 20 past but I think it's coming now.
That must be it.
It's so cute.
It's not the train I was thinking of.
It just looks like a subway station. Right?
(The train leaves for the mountain)
It's really cramped, right?
They made this during
the imperial era.
It's a little over 100 years old.
Oh, really?
- Doesn't it feel antique? / - Yes.
Like going on a trip as a kid.
Yes.
It's that old bell.
Red bean bread.
(It's so good)
It's really good.
Mom, do you see me?
Do you see me, mom?
Model?
Are you a model?
- Yes. / - Thank you.
Not model.
Why did you say you're a model?
Tell him you're a singer?
Just stay still.
No...
He'll think Korean models are all short.
He'll know when I stand up.
I see something.
(They arrive at Zhushan Station)
The last train is at,
at 7:10.
Looks like we have to get on that.
Finally, we get to see the sunrise.
So many stairs.
Oh, my legs.
Morning exercise.
(Oh Amazing are working out early)
So many people.
Hey, there's something here.
Wait a minute.
This is too hard.
Wait...
- Seriously. / - Wait.
Don't we need to get good seats?
I hope not.
(They start mountain climbing to get a good spot)
That wasn't the end.
(Hurrying to get there on time for the 6:20 sunrise)
We're here.
- So hard. / - This is nothing.
I must be really unfit.
- Here... / - Wow.
Check it out.
- Amazing. / - That's the sea clouds.
I'm a little nervous because
it rains a lot here.
So it's foggy most days.
You can only see it 3 times per 10 days.
(Seeing the clouds from higher than Hallasan)
(The sea of clouds before their feet)
- Wow, amazing. / - Wow.
We're really lucky.
It's not easy to see this.
This is higher than Hallasan.
It really is high.
So pretty.
I feel my mind clearing.
- What a sight. / - My heart feels warm.
We're higher than the clouds.
My ears are slightly hurting.
- Really? / - Yes.
I'm fine.
My ears feel blocked.
Now, if we can see the sunrise...
It'll be amazing.
(Sunrise due at 6:20)
(The clouds part as the time nears for sunrise)
It's time for the sunrise now.
Wow.
Wow...
- Wow. / - It's rising.
It's really bright.
Amazing.
It's so bright.
Hayoung...
Wow.
Wow, wow.
- Wow. / - It's rising!
It's really bright.
It's so bright.
Cellophane glasses.
What's this?
Sunglasses.
20 yuan.
Yellow.
It's really bright.
So bright.
These glasses...
They're not working.
- Chorong. / - Yes.
Your guide schedule is too tight.
It's worse than mine.
No, in the morning...
It's so leisurely since we have a lot of time.
- Now... / - Where are we?
The place I mentioned earlier.
Sister Pond.
We're going to check out the pond.
It must be called Sister Pond.
Check this out.
- It's like a door. / - Wow.
How did it grow like this?
It's a tree tunnel.
Passing the tunnel.
It's really pretty here.
(It's like a scene from a music video)
Wow, so pretty.
- Is it here? / - We should've shot our...
Music video here.
I see the pond.
Wow.
This must be it.
Seriously.
It's fascinating that a pond is here.
Oh, this.
This is the younger sister's pond.
- Younger sister. / - Hayoung Pond.
There are two ponds,
younger sister and older sister.
They loved the same guy?
It's no fun if you spoil it.
I didn't know.
I just guessed.
Did they really love the same guy?
- Yeah. / - Wow.
The sisters loved the same guy.
Why...
So the sisters jumped
in together...
That's so sad.
That'll never happen to our members.
- You can't fight over a guy. / - Yeah.
You just have to concede.
As if that's easy to do.
Just don't meet him.
The guy was the bad one.
He did that to sisters...
So this is the younger sister's pond.
The older sister's is further up.
It's such a tragedy.
Our members all like different types of guys
so this will never happen.
We really have different tastes.
Very clear.
The older sister's pond is a little bigger.
Oh, no. It's so sad.
Why did it happen?
They probably had their reasons.
But it doesn't look that deep.
This is a naturally formed pond.
Oh, my.
These ponds always...
Have such stories.
Wow. Loving the same guy...
You could make a movie or drama out of this.
We started really early today
and saw the sunrise.
We looked around Alishan Range. How was it?
The mountain is different to the mountains in Korea.
The trees are taller.
They have ponds.
It was unfamiliar
and fascinating.
Thank you for showing me this, Guide Park.
- Now we should... / - Since we're hungry...
Let's go eat.
Yes, let's go eat.
- To eat something good. / - Let's go.
(Alishan Range to eat brunch, 1 hour 10 minutes)
(A boar rock welcomes them)
This is...
Alishan...
Where the Tsou people live.
Let's go eat good food.
- Tsou people? / - Yeah.
- What do you think we'll eat? / - Soup...
Traditional Tsou food.
You'd think that but...
It'll be something totally different.
We're eating pizza.
- We're here for pizza. / - What?
The Tsou people...
(A new type of pizza in the mountains)
(Who will come all the way here for pizza?)
(Oh Amazing Tour will)
Isn't it strange eating pizza here?
Wow.
Thank you.
It's insane.
Chorong!
Is this heaven?
Barbecue!
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Thank you. Wow.
(Organic pumpkin sweet potato pizza, $14.40)
(Barbecue set, $18)
Should we try the pizza first?
Check this out.
(The pizza is deeply moving)
It's really crispy.
(They can't help but hum)
Amazing.
It's so good.
Who knew we'd eat pizza deep in the mountains?
- This is a sweet potato cheese pizza. / - Yeah.
- It's so good. / - Wow.
- It's a very Korean pizza. / - Yeah.
Pizza usually taste different overseas.
- It's usually saltier. / - But this is totally Korean.
It's so good.
It's really good.
I'm happy.
You can't not like this.
I never imagined we'd have pizza here.
(They cleared 2 pieces in an instant)
(Next is the barbecue set)
Check this out.
There's so much.
Isn't it like wrap for pork belly?
Cucumber, cherry tomatoes and paprika too.
You eat it with the vegetables.
Doesn't it really look like pork belly?
It's like pork belly.
- Is this a spicy sauce? / - Yeah.
Chorong!
Isn't it like Korean mixed paste?
It's exactly the same.
This is like a fusion Korean restaurant.
(Straight into her mouth)
How is it?
(This taste!)
Did I choose well?
I feel like I'm eating boiled pork.
This is totally Korean.
It's spicy.
It's so good
This one tastes like pork hocks.
The sausages.
What is this?
It feels like duck.
It's totally pork hocks.
It's good, right?
This is totally Korean food.
How can it be so perfect?
We're becoming silent.
You miss Korean food when you go on trips.
We can just come here.
Boiled pork and pork hock set.
Pork belly.
This restaurant really cares about the environment.
They don't allow takeout.
See the container?
You can't leave any.
I'm confident.
You can do it, right?
We have to finish all this.
It's so good.
(She adds pork and sausage on lettuce)
Good?
I think my course has been a little better so far.
- Really? / - Yeah.
The sunrise was great but...
But not active stuff like that...
What else have you prepared?
You'll find out.
- Let's go. / - Okay.
We still have a lot left to do.
(Brunch to Tsou culture village, 70 minutes)
(Tsou culture village)
(A village where Tsou people live)
(You can experience traditional Tsou culture here)
Here...
Tsou people of Alishan.
It's their village.
But here...
We've arranged to meet them.
Who?
Who are we meeting?
I called them in advance.
Someone's waiting for us?
It's them.
Hello.
Wow, what's this?
What is this?
(The traditional Tsou greeting begins)
(What's going on here?)
Thank you.
Wow.
- They gave us necklaces. / - Wow.
What was that?
Let's just follow them.
Are they looking for something?
- Wow. / - Wow, what's this?
(Alishan oolong tea)
(The high altitude provides an ideal condition)
(For cultivating for the best tea in Taiwan)
- Wow. We get to sample the tea. / - Wow.
Proper oolong tea.
- Wow. / - She lets it overflow.
What a waste.
(How Tsou people make oolong tea)
(The first batch of warm water is to awaken the leaves)
(It also acts to warm the cup)
- She keeps overflowing. / - Very generous.
The scent must infuse into everything.
It'd clean it out.
This must be to smell.
And this must be to drink.
I want to buy this.
She throws away the first batch.
The color is darker than earlier.
I'm going to drink like this at home.
Throw away the first batch.
With this...
Cover it.
It's too hot.
- Oh, it's too. / - That's hot.
That's hot.
It's hot!
Wait a minute.
How does she do it so easily?
It's hot.
So hot.
Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
This is hard.
That's my future. I'm too scared to do this.
(Hayoung succeeds at once)
You have to hold onto it tight.
Did I do it right?
It's hard.
So hot.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
It's like fresh made rice
served at a restaurant.
(The scent of oolong tea is left in the cup)
Oh, for real.
It's really savory.
The scent is so good.
We drink it like this?
(Drink tea as you smell the scent?)
(You don't have to keep that on your nose)
Oh, it's good.
It's so savory.
She's giving us more. Let's finish this.
Oolong tea is good for dieting...
You have to drink it while it's hot.
Isn't oolong tea
good for removing oils?
I drank it a lot back in the day.
To lose weight.
- We'd drink it after eating good food. / - Yeah.
- What's the use? / - Eat oily foods.
Then drink oolong tea.
It's much better after you enjoy the scent.
Can I do this?
I've improved.
This is fun.
It's different to just drinking.
Right?
It's so good.
Japanese oolong tea has a strong flavor.
This is very similar to green tea.
- Right? / - It's not bitter.
You thought it'd be bitter, right?
But it isn't bitter at all.
Is she going to keep pouring until we finish it all?
It's warm.
- Do we have to finish it to go home? / - Yeah.
- How about we drink from the bottle? / - I'm nervous.
Yeah, with a straw.
Thank you.
Doesn't it feel like the tea's digesting the food?
Now that I've digested, I feel like I need to eat again.
We definitely ate before this...
- The oil is all gone. / - You shove it down...
Then eat some more.
Let's eat again when we go down the mountain.
Since we hiked.
(Tsou culture village to lunch, 2 hours)
Since we went to the mountain,
what should we eat?
After the mountain, you need to re-energize.
Right. Normally after hiking,
people eat boiled chicken.
- So we'll eat chicken too. / - Wow.
There's a very famous restaurant here.
I looked it up.
It's this place right here.
- Wow. / - I smell something good.
Right?
(This place really feels local)
(They have a special recipe here)
What's this place famous for?
You're the...
- Right. / - Chorong guide.
It's the last dish for today
so I prepared something incredible.
And that's why I prepared chili sauce.
But I don't think you need it today.
- Really? / - Because...
We're going to have chicken.
I've ordered smoked chicken
and Taiwanese style chicken soup.
Smoked chicken dish is
skewered on bamboo and smoked.
They use a fruit tree called longan for the wood
to give the chicken fruity scent.
They salt the skin during the smoking.
And it's not just any salt. It's a secret salt.
Really? What kind of secret?
They won't say.
- A secret. / - A secret from a famous restaurant.
Wow, thank you. This must be it.
The chicken soup.
(Taiwanese style chicken soup in a big pot)
(With a variety of herbs)
(Taiwanese chicken soup, $30.60)
Let's try the chicken.
Just try a small piece.
Doesn't it look really good for you?
I'll taste it.
Oh, it's hot.
It's like boiled chicken.
It's like oriental medicine chicken soup.
The meat is so tender.
The broth itself...
They used local spices
so it's very deep.
The chicken is really firm and delicious.
It's very tender.
It's good.
I feel energized.
(They ate in silence)
(The smoked chicken is getting ready)
(It's been cooking for an hour)
(The smoked chicken is ready)
(Let's go meet it now)
Amazing!
I think I just saw something.
The head's still on it.
(Chicken arrived)
(The screen isn't on pause)
Hi.
You do look tasty.
(No way)
Hayoung.
Let's just cover its eyes.
Mommy.
It's done, Hayoung. Chicken!
I can see it's comb.
Should we just remove the neck?
Okay.
- Then you can eat it, right? / - Yes.
I'm sorry.
I think we'll lose.
It feels weird.
I think we'll lose if we do this.
Hide it.
I'm sorry.
Good-bye.
Which part do you like?
- Drumstick or... / - Drumstick.
Then the drumstick...
It's crossing its legs...
The drumstick.
(This is worse than the head)
I don't like the drumstick.
Wait, wait, wait.
Just leave it there.
- What's the difference with the neck? / - I'll remove it.
- What's the difference? / - Here.
Okay, okay.
- Should we try this first? / - Yes.
(They finally taste it after overcoming some challenges)
It's good.
It's really good.
Peace has returned.
The chicken is really big
and the meat is really firm.
It's like how Korean chicken is.
I don't like the skin...
But this is really crispy.
Hayoung, try the skin.
You don't need to season it.
Eat it with this.
Now bite off some meat.
Awesome, right?
This skin is amazing.
It's really crispy.
I thought it'd be salty.
It's not salty at all.
Since it's been smoked...
It has a pleasant smell.
If you normally don't eat the skin, you'll eat this.
The wing is good.
Now that we've had a good meal.
The final...
It's the final course.
- The course we've been waiting for. / - Yes.
It's the thing I've been looking forward to the most.
The mud hot spring.
Our legs are sore from the hike.
Let's go and relieve our fatigue.
- I'm looking forward to it. / - Right?
- Let's finish up and go. / - Okay.
- Here. / - Here.
Guanziling Hot Spring?
This isn't an ordinary hot spring.
It's where you can do a mud bath.
Since we're a girl group...
- We need to take care of our skin. / - Of course.
(Only 3 minutes away from the restaurant)
Finally we're here.
The thing we've waited for.
- We're at the hot spring. / - We're here.
This is one of...
- The top four hot springs worldwide. / - Really?
It's called Guanziling Hot Spring.
Shall we go?
Shall we?
Isn't this all natural mud?
- Wow. / - Hayoung!
- Oh, my! / - It's really here.
Mud, mud.
Wow.
It's real mud.
Should we put on some mud?
Why? Is it cold?
It feels weird.
Wow, it's so soft.
Wow.
(Rub)
Come here, Chorong.
(Some for Chorong too)
Hey, it feels weird.
Hey!
This is so...
You have to pay for this at a massage shop.
Come here, Chorong.
I'll do this for you.
Draw something cute.
(Nice and cute)
(Chorong kitty)
Chief.
It feels so good.
Put some more on.
Can we just put on as much as we want?
(Girls)
Hayoung!
Apink, Apink.
- Apink, Apink. / - Oh, Apink.
Apink...
Nice. Perfect.
Shall we go and dry up?
It's all here.
Can we just sit here?
How does it feel with the mud?
It feels weird.
I've never felt this before.
I've never rubbed mud all over my body before.
- Yeah. / - Right?
The seasons are changing in Korea
and it's so cold now.
- Your skin gets really dry. / - Yeah.
I think this will be
really good for our skin.
What is this?
(Using all her strength to reach the straw)
We're going to look so funny.
Orange juice!
Everyone, I'm Chorong of Apink.
I'm getting drunk on orange juice.
What do we do now?
Now we wash this off
and hit the hot springs.
- Amazing, right? / - Yes.
- My mouth is hardening. / - Our faces are stiff.
We can't speak properly.
It's too tight around my mouth.
Don't smile, you'll get wrinkles.
We should've left our mouths.
I know.
- Should we go wash now? / - Let's wash.
Oh, my face...
(You must remove the mud before you hit the springs)
Mommy.
We have to dip our bodies...
My skin is green.
It's so soft.
It really is.
In order to have pretty skin.
I think the elders would love this.
My mom and dad would love this.
(Excited)
This is...
Should we score the hot spring?
- Hayoung, you do it. / - From what I see...
It deserves three "A"s!
You don't just have the hot spring here.
You have a hotel as well.
You can sleep here.
The important thing is...
You can use it even if you're not a hotel guest.
So we give it three "A"s.
We're really generous with scores, aren't we?
We are.
I think the Oh Amazing Tour was good.
It was good.
It wasn't too hard.
- Healing. / - Or too tiring.
(They planned the trip hard and enjoyed it fully)
Now we have to score this place with these.
One for ambience.
One because it's delicious.
One because it's affordable.
Three for me.
Another three "A"s for this place.
I think this place deserves three "A"s.
It was perfect.
Do you realize you've scored three for everything?
We lack objectivity...
But they were all good.
We have to be satisfied
for others to be satisfied too.
We have to show them that we really enjoyed it.
1, 2, 3.
Three!
(Oh Amazing Tour)
(Oh Amazing Tour, intermediate course for Taiwan)
($348.80 per person)
(Next episode)
The Napoli of Asia.
We'll show you everything about Fukuoka.
Fuku, Fuku.
It's called the Mediterranean of Vietnam.
It's a hidden gem of a holiday spot.
Guide Kong's Nha Trang Tour.
Welcome to my tour.
Let's go.
Nha Trang. It's a hot spring course.
My skin feels good.
I don't want to leave.
A local eatery.
This is nice.
It's really good.
So good.
Nha Trang Tour.
Let's go!
(Battle Trip)
("Wolf Baby" by TRCNG)