(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
(Lee Hwijae, special host, JR of NU'EST W)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
The audience is cheering loudly today.
Today's special host
is JR of NU'EST W.
Nice to meet you.
I'm here as a special host today.
I'll work hard and try to enjoy the trips.
Thank you.
Do you like traveling?
I like traveling
but I don't have time...
- To travel around. / - Right.
Have you been on a trip before? A personal trip.
- Not for work. / - A real trip.
I haven't been on a personal trip.
- I knew it. He's so busy. / - I see.
What if...
You have a chance to go on a trip?
- You get a break. / - Where would you go?
Let's say you have a week off.
I used to work in Japan,
so I speak Japanese.
- And I like hot springs. / - I see.
- So I want to go to Sapporo... / - For hot springs?
And enjoy hot springs alone.
Do you want to go to a hot spring alone?
- He'd go with someone. / - Aren't you still young?
- Yes, I'm 24 years old. / - Wait.
- It's like a trip for treatment. / - People of my age...
- He's right. / - When you have joint problems.
He's been an idol for seven years.
I understand why he loves hot springs.
He might have joint problems.
Who do you want to go with among your members?
- If I have to pick only 1... / - Just pick 1 person.
I'll take Baekho.
- Baekho? / - Baekho.
Because he has a big build.
I think he can protect me.
As your bodyguard?
That's right. He'll be my bodyguard.
It's strange to think of you two sitting in a hot spring.
I'll tell you today's theme.
Do you have a plan for your summer vacation?
Summer vacation? Not yet.
If you don't, you should watch this carefully.
Today's theme is
the emerging vacation spots of 2018.
Oh, nice.
Emerging vacation spots.
I'm so excited to hear that.
- Hear what? / - Emerging vacation spots.
It means people don't know about the places well.
They're emerging as popular spots.
Let's meet the two teams who went on trips
to the emerging spots.
Let's bring out the four trip designers.
- Hello. / - Nice to meet you.
- Hello. / - I'm glad to see you.
We have a model team...
- And an actress team today. / - That's right.
Let's find out their destinations then.
Where did they go?
What are the emerging vacation spots of 2018?
- Please tell us. / - The place we went to...
Is like Hawaii of the U.S.
and Jeju-do of Korea.
This place is not that famous though.
It's in Vietnam.
We went to Phu Quoc.
It's Phu Quoc.
- Phu Quoc? / - Phu Quoc.
- Phu Quoc of Vietnam. / - Phu Quoc of Vietnam.
- Phu Quoc? / - It must be popular.
- Where is it? / - I've heard of it before.
It sounds like a butcher's shop.
- Right. / - Are you keeping us in check?
They're criticizing already.
Phu Quoc isn't well known in other countries
but it's very popular among Vietnamese people.
During holiday seasons,
it has a mass of local tourists.
- I can't wait to check it out. / - Me too.
Where's the emerging vacation spot you went to?
We went to Thailand.
- Oh, no. / - We've been there a lot.
I know many people have been to Thailand.
So we went to a hidden place.
Why do you think the place has been hidden?
- There must be a reason. / - Exactly.
There must be a good reason.
- Okay. / - Alright.
You'd be surprised to see this place.
- It's a hidden gem of Thailand. / - A hidden gem?
It's...
- Khao Yai. / - Khao Yai.
- Khao Yai? / - It's Khao Yai.
Khao Yai?
It sounds like Japanese.
When you said Phu Quoc and Khao Yai,
the audience was like this.
(Where is it?)
They're unfamiliar with these places.
You know what?
Traveling is all about pioneering.
Those who travel to new places are the winners.
Anyway, we're going to...
- Vietnam and Thailand today. / - Good.
They are hidden vacation spots.
If you take a photo of you watching Battle Trip
and post it on your social media,
We will select a few to give out Battle Trip books.
We look forward to your participation.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
Welcome.
(The team with more votes will win the battle)
Let's go to Vietnam first.
- Phu Quoc? / - Yes, Phu Quoc.
I'm so curious.
Alright then.
What's your team name?
Do you have a team name?
- We do. / - Yes, we do.
You'll regret it if you don't leave
for Phu Quoc now.
- Song Vacation. / - Song Vacation.
- Let's go! / - Let's go!
(Song Vacation to Phu Quoc starts now)
(10 days before the trip)
- Haena! / - Kyunga!
- Long time no see. / - Kyunga.
- It's so good to see you again. / - Congratulations.
You're going on a trip with me.
Really?
(Leading Korean model, Song Kyunga)
She looks so cool.
(She always has the aura of a model)
(Bright and innocent)
Models are so different.
What is this?
It's all the stuff I hate.
(You'll never get bored when you're with Kyunga)
(A popular model, Song Haena)
How cute!
It's warm!
It's so good!
(Feeling happy)
(Song Haena, cheerful energizer)
The theme of this trip is about
new vacation spots.
Actually, 12 years ago,
I visited Vietnam.
Vietnam is trending again these days.
I have never been to Vietnam.
- I did bring a book on it though. / - Really?
If it has to be a city that people haven't been before,
it should be somewhere we haven't heard of.
- Shouldn't there be a beach? / - I agree.
Blue ocean.
- There has to be a beach. / - Because it's summer.
- That's a must for summer vacation. / - Right.
Let's see if there's an island.
Let's see if there's a good place.
I found Cat Ba Island.
There's one more. Phu Quoc.
I've never been there or heard about it. Phu Quoc?
Phu Quoc isn't a place that
a lot of people know about.
- It suits the theme. / - Right.
I read the book and
there were only 2 or 3 pages on it.
That's amazing.
- Look at the sky. / - Isn't it nice?
- Doesn't it look great? / - That looks so nice.
It's a vacation spot you must visit
before it gets too popular.
(Phu Quoc)
It has the largest man-made safari after Africa.
We'll take the longest cable car.
(These top models showed up in Phu Quoc)
- We need a photo of this. / - Let's take one.
Does it fit?
(They dip their bodies in the beach)
(And in the mud)
This is so good.
- It's better than the one in Korea. / - Come on.
- Look at that. / - That looks so good.
(The food surpasses the usual)
It's so delicious!
- I'm hungry. / - Goodness.
- Seriously. / - Look how empty it is.
I think I would come back here.
Me too.
Right?
(We invite you to charming Phu Quoc)
So in other words...
- We can travel for two days. / - Right.
Let's make one as my day, and I'll plan the day.
And the other day as your day.
- I'd like that. / - Okay.
Since you've been to a lot of vacation spots,
we can try out the activities
at the vacation spot on your day.
I'll plan what locals do on mine.
- I like that idea. / - With that theme.
- I'll plan the day like that. / - I like that.
But since this is a battle,
don't we need a name for our team?
What should our name be?
Well...
Do you have a name in mind?
- Since we're both Songs... / - Okay.
I thought about naming it as Song Song Trip.
- Song Song Trip? / - Yes, I thought...
That's too boring.
She asked me if I had a name in mind,
and she rejected it.
- You have to do it in one go. / - I told you.
(Song)
Two Songs...
Two Songs and Song Song are the same.
How are they different?
- Song Song makes Two Songs. / - Or...
This time, we're going on a trip to a vacation spot.
Right.
Just like you suggested, we should use Song.
- How about Song Vacation? / - That's cute.
- Song Vacation. Do you like it? / - Yes.
Yes. Song Vacation. Yes!
Song Vacation...
- Let's go! / - Let's go!
(3 days before the trip)
I keep researching, but I can't find a lot of information.
Look at this. This is amazing.
(The color of the beach in Phu Quoc stands out)
(A swing above the water)
- That's Hawaii. / - I guess...
Riding this swing must be quite famous there.
Even if I don't research a lot,
Haena will cover the rest, right?
I can just trust Haena.
Our team went there on a direct flight.
That's such a nice selling point.
Since the airport was just built, it's really clean too.
It's spotless.
It was around 11 p.m.
- The airport was closing. / - It seems empty.
So we have arrived. How will we get there?
What? What is it?
- It's thundering. / - It's thundering.
- It's raining. / - The weather has to be good tomorrow.
- It will be. / - Right?
- It's my day tomorrow. / - That's right.
- Don't worry. / - It'll be your fault if it's not.
(50 minutes to the hotel by taxi from the airport)
(They arrive after 50 minutes)
- Haena, this is so nice. / - It's really nice.
It's this one. 7236.
Amazing.
This is nice.
We should do our runway walk here.
(It's a clean room just for the two of them)
(Feeling excited)
- I'm so excited. / - Are you happy, Haena?
I love it, Kyunga.
Tomorrow in Phu Quoc is my day which I planned.
Let's just pray that the weather is nice tomorrow.
- Yes. I got it. / - Okay.
- Good night. / - Good night, Haena.
I want to see the view during the day.
- Aren't you curious? / - It's thundering.
(Morning dawns as they're worried and yet excited)
(Luckily, the weather has cleared up)
We had such great weather the next day.
(Before their trip, they make a pit stop at this shop)
- It's so cute, isn't it? / - My gosh.
This shop looks more westernized than other shops.
Look over here.
We can find information on Phu Quoc.
Let's have a look since we don't know much.
There are maps here.
Since not many people know this place,
it has no information center.
So when you go to a famous cafe,
you can find information at a corner like that.
We need this to get around today.
Ta-da. You can find...
Information on a board like this.
This one is the map.
- Interesting. / - She can reach since she's tall.
You should've dusted it too.
We don't need the Jimmy Jib.
Information on traveling?
This is an upside of being tall.
Alright. Where should we go next?
(She checks the location with the map from the cafe)
Being in charge of the itinerary is a lot of pressure.
Really? No, you came up with the itinerary.
All the good beaches are clustered here.
- Good beaches? / - Yes.
Should we get going?
(Phu Quoc with Song Vacation)
(Phu Quoc beaches)
(20 minutes by taxi from cafe to the beach)
(Long Beach)
- Long Beach. / - Doesn't it look great?
- It's great. / - How beautiful.
- Is the water clean? / - It's super clean.
The sand is really white there.
- Look at the water. / - It was like a photo shoot.
What do you think? I wanted to show you this beach.
- First off, it's so beautiful. / - Right?
It might be because this place isn't well-known...
- There aren't many people. / - The water is so clean.
- It's picturesque. / - Right.
Did you see the sand? The sand is so fine.
- Fine sand is rare in Vietnam. / - Really?
Beautiful beaches like this are clustered
on the Western side,
so they're building a lot of hotels on this side.
And this beach is one of those beaches.
This is a beach right in front of the hotel.
Then can people who don't stay
at the hotel use this beach?
Everyone can enjoy the beach for free.
The hotel manages the beach...
So it's known to be clean and well-managed.
- Gosh, it's breezy. / - This is really beautiful.
(Feeling excited)
I feel like I can touch the clouds.
They are hanging so low.
Right. It feels like we can reach them, right?
- It's great since it's quiet. / - It was so quiet.
- Later, it's going to get crowded. / - Exactly.
- It'll be very stuffy. / - No one is at the beach.
Right.
- We ought to take a photo. / - We must.
There are 2 famous places where people take photos.
- 2 places? / - 1 of them is right here.
A swing!
You saw the swing on a beach in Phu Quoc
on social media.
- That's right! Yes, right! / - You've seen it, right?
- This is the place. / - It's so pretty.
I guess no one knows about this place.
- Doesn't it look beautiful there? / - Yes, indeed.
Wedding photos would look nice there too.
- Wouldn't they look so beautiful? / - 1, 2, 3.
- Gosh. / - Take my photo now.
You look beautiful. Lie back.
Hey!
- Lie back. / - Hey!
You did that on purpose. That was on purpose, right?
- No, Kyunga. / - No! My hat!
(Screaming)
That's leather!
(Everyone takes this kind of photo)
(Right before her hat falls into the water)
- Isn't it pretty? / - It's so beautiful.
- What do we call that? / - A hammock.
I'm so jealous. I want to lie down there.
- This looks so pretty. / - Amazing.
- It's hard to lie on a hammock. / - Amazing. But...
- It's really sturdy. / - Gosh.
(Wow)
- This is so much fun. / - You'll take the best photo.
(Exuding a model's aura)
She's very bold.
- It didn't flip. / - It doesn't flip.
(She's indeed a model)
(A top model never sits in an ordinary way)
You look gorgeous.
Her legs look too long, don't they?
I know another beautiful spot.
- Is it a photo spot? / - Yes, I'll take you there.
It's a little far away.
- Is it? / - Yes. You're okay with it, right?
- Well, if it's for a photo... / - It's okay, right?
- Let's go then. / - Let's go.
- Let's go. / - Where is it?
(10 minutes by taxi from Hotel "N" to "S" Beach Club)
- Where are we now? / - We're now...
- A beach club? / - Yes.
This beach is full of interesting things.
We need to pay
50,000 dong to get inside.
- About $2.50? / - Yes.
- It's cheap, right? / - It's cheap.
Remove a zero and just divide the number by half.
- That's convenient. / - Just keep that in mind.
(The entrance fee is about $2.50)
(It includes a free drink coupon)
I feel like we're going to a club.
Look! It's a shark!
- A shark? / - Yes.
This place is really popular on social media.
It's popular to take pictures with the sharks here.
There are sharks and dolphins.
- There are elephants too. / - It's so pretty.
My gosh, children will love this place.
- This place is a great photo spot. / - It is.
(There are installation artworks from various artists)
(On the beach so that tourists can take pictures there)
(It's already a famous place on social media)
- Take a picture of me here. / - Okay.
- Let me take pictures of you. / - It's so hot!
It's like a photo shoot. You look amazing.
(The sand is very hot now)
Because of the nice installation artworks,
every photo looks nice even if you don't take it nicely.
You can take pictures with the sharks too.
(She's having a photo shoot again)
The lighting is great, which makes the photos great.
Since we have one free coupon...
- Shall we get something to drink? / - Shall we?
(A glass of cold Vietnamese coffee to cool down)
- That's it. / - That coffee was so delicious.
- Vietnamese coffee is delicious. / - It was amazing.
Vietnamese coffee is famous.
(Sweet Vietnamese coffee to cool down the heat)
Thank you.
If you drink something sweet in a hot country...
- It wakes you up. / - It does.
Let's try it.
(Sucking up)
(How is it?)
It tastes like a coffee flavored candy.
- I loved those. / - It's like that candy but melted.
- Really? / - Yes.
It's like that, isn't it?
- It's delicious. / - This is so delicious.
It'd be amazing
to have a drink at sunset there.
- That sounds amazing. / - You wouldn't get drunk.
Where do you think I'm taking you now?
- I'm a little hungry. / - Right?
There's a reason why I needed sugar.
Right?
Before I came to Vietnam,
what I wanted to try the most was banh xeo.
I want to eat banh xeo.
It's like a pancake made with rice dough.
It's a wrap with ingredients in it.
- Is it tasty? / - I heard it's very tasty.
It's like wrapping with fried dough.
It's not like Korean fritters.
(What would banh xeo taste like in south Vietnam?)
My gosh, it looks delicious.
I'm hungry.
We were hungry too, so we went to eat something.
(25 minutes by taxi from "S" Beach Club to restaurant)
- Haena. / - Yes.
The place we're going for lunch is
a very famous place among the locals here.
If you ask the taxi drivers here,
everyone will tell you to go eat banh xeo there.
- Is it this place? / - It's like a transport cafe.
It's the most popular place among the taxi drivers.
There are a lot of people who have it takeaway.
I can already feel that it'll be delicious.
This must be a famous banh xeo restaurant.
- I love this kind of place. / - Right?
(She's making banh xeo on the street)
They put meat and other ingredients in.
It was my first time trying it.
- It was delicious. / - It's $1.
- It's only a dollar. / - It was very delicious.
I want to go there too.
It's so cheap.
(A happiness you can buy with $1)
(Expectant)
- What is this? / - It's banh xeo.
So this is banh xeo.
What is this?
- This is called nuoc mam. / - I see.
It's like fish sauce in Korea.
- I can smell fish. / - Right?
It's like anchovy sauce we use when
we make kimchi.
Famous chefs from all over the world come here
to buy this sauce.
- They go all the way there? / - Yes.
I don't know how to eat this.
Just add whatever you'd like to eat on the lettuce.
Then wrap it and dip it in the sauce.
It has vegetables in it.
(It's Haena's first Vietnamese dish)
I can taste flour, corn and starch.
I think they made the dough out of them.
- It was very delicious. / - It was really good.
It's like eating fritters but
all the ingredients separately.
- It tastes like green onion fritters. / - It does.
It's like seafood fritters.
It's delicious.
Nuoc mam is so tasty.
The sauce puts all the flavors together.
- That's very delicious. / - It looks so delicious.
(Everyone fell in love with banh xeo)
Nuoc mam opened my eyes.
It was so good.
If we didn't have nuoc mam, it would've been bad.
I want to try this one.
This is made with coconut.
It's like a coconut pancake.
Does it have coconut inside?
- That one was amazing. / - That was...
That was incredible.
- It's only 10 cents. / - It's 10 cents.
(One banh khot, about 10 cents)
This one is really tasty.
It has a texture I have never tried before.
- It's like sticky rice. / - It is.
- It was like sticky rice. / - It's so moist on the inside.
It doesn't have a strong coconut flavor.
I can smell coconut a bit.
I'd like to have 10 pieces of it.
- I can eat 10 of those. / - 10 pieces would be easy.
It's so tasty.
I thought flour and vegetable won't go well together.
- But they go very well together. / - They do.
They seem to be truly enjoying it.
(She looks like she would eat her own fingers)
We're eating so much, aren't we?
(They enjoy the food fully)
(Today, they won't worry about eating too much)
We paid $2.50 each.
- Really? / - And we were so full in the end.
Didn't you feel bad when you pay?
Where are we going now?
- Now... / - Yes.
- Let me explain with the map. / - Okay.
We're now around here.
We're here, and we have to go there.
We're going to a spa now.
- Spa? / - Yes.
Spa? Go, go?
Shall we get going?
If there's a spa as well, I'd love to go there.
It seems like we've won you over.
I'm kind of attracted, yes.
- You look convinced. / - I have to watch till the end.
(They take a taxi to the mud spa)
Let's go to the spa.
Alright.
- There's a taxi. / - Let's get this one.
Taxi.
- The taxi looks so small. / - It's the cheapest taxi.
- The basic fee is 30 cents. / - Yes, it's 30 cents.
We'd like to go to the mud spa, please.
It's fun to watch out the window from here.
We can see the downtown of Phu Quoc.
- Look over there. / - It's the port.
(There's a port and a beautiful sky next to city)
It's so pretty.
This town is cute.
This town is not so developed,
so I like it.
- It's so cute. / - It looks like a toy village.
I feel like it'll be very different in five years from now.
You're right.
There would be pros and cons.
- It won't be like this then. / - No.
- We're almost there. / - We're almost there.
So it's a mud spa.
Here we are.
- We're here. / - Let's go.
It looks pretty.
It looks somewhat traditional.
(What would the mud spa look like?)
(There's a lot of open-air baths)
What are they? Are they baths?
- It's an open-air spa. / - So you can bathe there.
It must be so hot to bathe outdoors.
It wasn't that bad because of the shade from the trees.
There is a cool breeze from the beach as well.
(One hour in the mud spa, about $22)
It's outside.
It's a completely open place.
People are bathing here.
Usually, the color of mud is black.
But this one is light brown.
- I thought it'd be black. / - So did I.
- Do we just go in there? / - Do we?
Can we just go in now?
(The tub is empty but they go in for now)
Can we just stay in here?
(An employee comes over after they go into the tub)
(The mud spills out)
(Wow)
(It's a moisturizing mud spa)
It's a mix of mud and mineral hot spring water.
I want to touch it.
Don't drink it.
(The mud feels very soft)
- Look at this. / - It feels really nice, doesn't it?
I'm going to sit down.
It's warm.
Kyunga. Kyunga.
Can I splash you?
This is interesting.
(Take this)
Kyunga.
(The mud fills up the tub in no time)
- They really fill it up. / - Exactly.
- Kids will like it. / - It's good for families.
Yes, it's perfect for families.
Doesn't the mud water look nice even from the clip?
Whenever there's a breeze,
I can feel the coolness.
Koreans, including myself...
- Like warm water and a hot bath. / - That's right.
- It has to be warm. / - Right.
We must heat up our bodies.
- Then our fatigue washes away. / - I agree.
(This is how models enjoy warm mud)
(Acting like they've fallen into a swamp)
Save me. Save me.
- They're weird. / - Save me.
I feel like my skin is getting soft.
Kyunga.
(Massaging with the bucket)
- Should I help you out? / - Namaste.
- Kyunga. Is it your bikini? / - Yes?
With this?
That's not cool.
I'm getting sleepy.
- Kyunga. / - I might fall asleep.
Don't fall asleep.
That must've been nice.
- After the spa, our skin got really soft. / - Right.
(They leisurely enjoy the spa)
- Haena. There's... / - Yes?
An important highlight on my itinerary.
When we were on the taxi, I said...
- We're going to a night market. / - Oh, right.
That's where we'll go at night.
- That's going to be a blast. / - Right.
- Let's dress up nicely... / - Okay.
- And head to the night market. / - Okay.
- Dress sexy. / - I'll eat delicious food.
Let's take a tour around the night market.
Should we get going now?
(They must hurry to the market)
(Screaming)
- What? / - What is it?
- What is that? / - Is that how you clean the mud?
- It's like a car wash. / - Yes.
(She strikes a pose in the midst of this)
Gosh, models are different from us indeed.
(This is how top models wash off the mud)
- Ta-da. / - When you spin, it washes off.
But if I do that, it'd wash off my makeup.
It will clean the top of my head too.
You're right.
(10 minutes from the spa to the night market)
Night markets are fun.
- You must visit the market. / - It's so much fun.
You must.
(Quirky Kyunga's day is coming to an end)
- Haena. / - Kyunga.
This is the highlight of my itinerary.
- This place is so beautiful. / - Phu Quoc's...
Night market.
(An 800m night market visited by locals and tourists)
800m long?
- It's really long. / - It was empty in the afternoon.
- Everyone came here at night. / - Right.
This place is packed.
- What's that? / - Is that takoyaki?
(The most famous food from the night market)
(It's fresh seafood)
- Seafood? / - Yes.
Since it's an island, it's fresh.
- I'm jealous about the seafood. / - Yes.
Peanuts. Free to try.
- Peanuts? / - Yum, yum.
Yum, yum.
- Peanuts? / - Peanuts.
Peanuts.
Gosh, peanuts.
- He can speak Korean. / - Yes, he speaks Korean.
A lot of stalls sold peanuts.
And look at this one.
I heard that Vietnamese pearls are famous here.
- Really? / - Everyone buys pearls here and...
Manufactures them and sells them at high prices.
- They're famous for peppers? / - Yes.
World-famous chefs personally come here...
- And buy peppers here. / - Really?
You have to buy it then.
You have to grind the peppers, right?
- Yes. Yes. / - Like a cool chef?
This one is the white pepper.
- This one is the black pepper. / - Black pepper.
Should I buy white peppers?
They're hard to come by.
(What has caught their attention?)
It's real pepper.
- I've never seen pepper leaves. / - This...
It's my first time too.
- Gosh. / - I never knew it looked like this.
- This is the pepper. / - That's the pepper fruit.
- It was my first time. / - How do you eat that?
Can I touch it?
(She carefully touches the fruit)
I don't smell anything.
It doesn't smell.
How can I taste this?
Should I just eat it?
(They taste the pepper fruit after the peanuts)
- It's spicy. / - I thought my tongue was on fire.
I thought I was a fire breathing dragon.
It's spicy.
- It's so spicy. / - No.
- It's so spicy. / - It's so spicy.
It's a different kind of spicy from chili peppers.
My mouth is numb.
It's like we tasted fire, right?
(Don't try pepper fruit without preparing yourselves)
- Should we eat something? / - What should we eat?
Do you want to try this? Can you eat it?
Chicken, one.
There are so many skewers.
(Shrimp skewer $1, chicken skewer $2)
- Gosh, they are $1 and $2. / - $1 and $2.
(Munching)
It's so good.
But since it's salty...
I think they seasoned it with a lot of salt and pepper.
(Coconut juice, $1.20)
It's good.
There's squid.
The squid looks delicious.
(Grilled squid with spicy sauce)
It looks so delicious.
The fish are huge. Amazing.
I guess seafood is famous here.
Should we eat seafood tonight?
Come on. Eat something already.
(They decide on the seafood as their last meal)
- Gosh, why is this so big? / - This one is huge.
(Massive black tiger prawns catch their eyes first)
Haena, when you come to Phu Quoc,
you must at least try one of these.
Really?
(Dinner consists of sea urchins, must-try food)
(Black tiger prawns)
(And fresh squids)
I hope it comes out quickly.
(I hope so too)
Here it comes.
This is the highlight of today.
(Sea urchin, $1.50 each)
(Squid, $3 each)
(400g of black tiger prawns, $20)
The prawn is so big.
- It's good. / - Gosh.
- It's like lobster. / - Isn't that a prawn burger?
Why is it so big?
(400g of black tiger prawns, $20)
(The whole meal costs $24.50)
It's convenient to eat there.
(Kyunga's first choice is the squid)
- Squid. / - Squid.
That must be delicious.
(The squid seems extra fresh. How would it taste?)
Try the squid.
- Which one should I dip it into? / - It's so savory.
Isn't it tasty?
The squid is delicious.
Here's the interesting point.
They didn't gut the squid before serving us.
But the innards taste really good.
- You ate the innards? / - Yes.
- Those are the tasty parts. / - Really? I haven't tried.
Should I try the sea urchin?
- I'm not good at eating these. / - Me neither.
Sea urchins look delicious.
(This is the sea urchin that we know of)
(However, it looks slightly different)
- That looks interesting. / - There are peanuts inside.
- What's that? / - Right.
There are peanuts.
- I never had peanuts with seafood. / - Me neither.
This is a new combination.
(A bite with peanuts)
(How does it taste?)
- It's not fishy at all. / - I find that intriguing.
- It's not fishy at all. / - I don't eat this because it's fishy.
Me neither. I don't like the fishy smell.
But it's not fishy at all.
They did season the sea urchin
but I can still taste its unique flavor.
I think people who can't eat sea urchins can eat this.
- Don't you think so? / - I agree.
- I want to try this one. / - Yes, let's try that one too.
It's huge.
When would we have a chance to eat this if not here?
(The prawn seems massive even at a glance)
- It's full of roe. This is amazing. / - My gosh.
(Impressed)
Isn't that huge?
That was the best out of all.
Hey, they make a heart.
- A heart. / - A heart.
A heart.
(The huge prawns totally excite them)
What's this?
Where's the red pepper paste with vinegar?
- Where is it? / - So Korean.
(How does the prawn taste?)
You need red pepper paste with vinegar to eat prawns.
(Her face tells how delicious it is)
This is it.
This is how we should end the day.
Oh, my God.
- She looks so happy. / - It was really good.
It must have been really delicious.
This is it.
There's something creamy on top.
It's the prawn's brain.
- Prawn's brain? / - Yes.
- I thought it was cream. / - This is so delicious.
It's so tender.
There was something creamy and soft inside.
- It was so delicious. / - It was so good.
(The creamy texture makes the prawns even tastier)
Shall we have a drink?
Good job today.
- I'll wrap up my tour with this. / - Good work.
I'm looking forward to your day tomorrow.
(I'm looking forward to Haena's day)
(Seafood dish and refreshing beer)
Excuse me, but there's something on your lips.
Kyunga.
- She's so happy. / - I don't think you realized that.
It's so nice. Kyunga, you're not drunk, are you?
Your face is already red.
I'm fine.
What about your diet?
I don't know. I think I will gain weight.
Seriously, I stuffed myself.
She's almost cramming the food into her mouth.
Today, you introduced me to the places...
Where I could relaxed.
Tomorrow, I'm going to bother you a bit.
Why? I'm even treating you such a great prawn dish.
Why would you do that to me?
It's a different kind of trip.
(It's going to be a different kind of relaxing trip)
Tomorrow...
I might not come out.
- Kyunga. / - I have a feeling already.
- I have a bad feeling. / - I will wake you up.
The night market looks nice.
- It was really nice. / - We had so much fun.
(Phu Quoc, a beautiful hidden island)
(With Song Vacation)
(Does Phu Quoc look like a typical vacation spot?)
(It's actually very different)
(The real trip begins now)
(The longest cable car in the world)
This was amazing too.
The world's longest cable car.
And this is the biggest safari in Asia.
It's a world-class place.
We must eat this.
(World-class dishes)
(World-class attractions)
- Look at that. / - It's so cute.
- It's a raccoon. / - It's so cute.
(World-class fun)
Would you like some mojito in Phu Quoc?
- That's the next day, right? / - Yes.
- It's Haena's day. / - Haena's day.
(Phu Quoc with Song Vacation)
- You shouldn't miss pho. / - You really shouldn't.
- Pho. / - It's southern Vietnamese noodles.
- Is it different? / - It's different from other pho.
- Really? / - Yes.
- Haena. / - Yes.
- The weather is so nice today. / - It is.
So this is the beginning of Haena's day.
Where are we going?
You said you'd like to eat...
Vietnamese pho for breakfast.
- Yes. / - So we're going to eat...
Southern Vietnamese pho.
The noodles just melt.
(Hanoi)
- That's pho. / - We tried many kinds of noodles.
- We know what they taste like. / - Nha Trang.
- Nha Trang. / - Nha Trang.
I was really jealous when they went to Nha Trang.
I heard Park Jungsoo really loved it.
(Pho)
Are we now going to see pho from Phu Quoc?
- It's very different. / - It's so different.
(It's a new type of pho dish)
The noodles are very thin.
It's similar to banquet noodles in Korea.
I already want to eat it.
(After cooking the noodles in the hot water)
You can order one with both meat and seafood in it
or one with either of them.
It's southern style, so it's a little different.
It looks so delicious.
That has to be delicious.
- It has prawn in it. / - It's really good.
They put seafood and meat in the broth.
It doesn't look that different from ordinary pho though.
As we said, Phu Quoc is close to Cambodia.
So it originated from southern Cambodian dish
and it's now become a Phu Quoc style dish.
Have you tried pho in Vietnam?
- Yes, I have. In Hanoi. / - Really?
- In Hanoi? / - Yes.
This is my first time in Vietnam
and this is also my first pho in Vietnam.
I'm looking forward to it.
- Really? / - Yes.
We just ordered hu tieu.
I've never heard of this either. I'm so curious.
Is pho we eat in Korea northern style pho?
- It's Hanoi-style pho. / - Hanoi? I see.
- It has meat in it. / - It has beef brisket in it.
You're right.
- So... / - It's here!
- Here's your pho. / - Thank you so much.
This is yours. Here you are.
(Hu tieu, $3.40)
First of all...
Goodness, it looks really delicious. Look at it.
(Sniffing)
Doesn't it smell very familiar?
Yes, I smelled this in Korea.
This is a common smell in Korean food.
You sound disappointed.
Is it because it smelled similar to Korean dishes?
- Yes. / - The broth is...
- The broth is made with meat. / - Meat broth.
The noodles are much thinner than ordinary pho.
- It's like thin noodles. / - It's very thin, isn't it?
But it's very chewy.
Isn't it usually flat?
- That's right. / - It's usually thick.
It looks and smells like banquet noodles.
- Is the noodle made of rice? / - Yes.
(Slurping)
It's so chewy.
It has a very chewy texture.
Doesn't it?
It's like half glass noodle and half rice noodle.
- Isn't it? / - It is.
And the noodle has a unique texture.
It's fresh noodles, right? Isn't it fresh noodles?
- It's dried noodles. / - It's homemade dried noodles.
I don't know if the sweet flavor is coming
from the shrimp or the squid
but it tastes very sweet.
You can choose the broth as well.
- Meat broth, seafood broth... / - Seafood broth.
You can have it mixed too.
It could have been too bland
without some spicy sauce.
You're right.
But it's already savory without any sauce added.
In the southern region, they use a lot of vegetables,
which makes the broth very sweet.
(They start to dig in)
- Look at the meat. / - That's a big chunk of meat.
The meat is so tender.
(There is a generous amount of meat)
It looks delicious.
Eunhye, you've become very quiet.
We have something to show also.
Do you? I see.
Haena, I think I'll be quite full after finishing this bowl.
It's a hearty dish, isn't it?
Even though it's just noodles.
Why do you feed me such a heavy dish?
(She winces)
Why do you keep trying to feed me so much?
You need to eat a lot.
- Do I? / - Yes.
Alright.
- To Haena's day. / - Cheers.
- Please look forward to it. / - I will.
(Phu Quoc with Song Vacation)
(Second largest safari in the world)
- Really? / - It's world's second biggest.
If you even have that...
- What about Khao Yai? / - You're so cruel.
(35 minutes by taxi from the restaurant to the safari)
- Kyunga. / - Yes, Haena.
I'd love to bring you back to the childhood.
I'm going to be a child again?
Today, pretend you're a child and enjoy.
- Okay. / - This place in Phu Quoc...
Is the biggest man-made safari
after the one in Africa.
- Really? / - Yes.
(The largest man-made safari is in the U.A.E.)
- No way. / - That's where you went?
- No. / - I was surprised.
(The second largest is in Vietnam)
It's incredibly huge.
It's the biggest man-made safari in Asia.
Is the whole area the safari?
Yes, the whole area.
It's a wildlife conservation area.
They came to greet us.
("V" Safari is the second largest safari in the world)
Isn't it amazing?
It looks very exotic.
If you stay at the resort we stayed in,
you don't have to pay for the entrance fee.
There is an amusement park,
a golf course and everything inside.
- It's so big! / - It's so cute.
It's so huge, right?
- What should we see first? / - This.
- Look over there. / - Oh, my.
Look at that.
What is it?
- It's so cute. / - They're ring-tailed lemurs.
Hello.
- She was a little scared. / - I'm scared of monkeys.
Hello, we're Song Vacation.
- What's your name? / - He's standing still.
I didn't know monkeys were this docile.
- Hello. / - Are you two on a date?
- Hello. / - We got you.
- Hey, what are you? / - Hello.
They look so cute.
They look really cute.
- They're not scared of humans. / - It's fascinating.
- Should we try feeding them? / - Okay.
I heard we can feed them.
- You weren't in Yongin, were you? / - No, way.
This is a zoo. The safari is somewhere else.
They seem to eat more than us.
They eat corns, carrots, and grapes.
Kyunga, I thought they'd run toward us...
- If we feed them. / - You can go into the cage?
- You can go in? / - Yes, you can.
- My gosh. / - You can walk inside.
- Really? / - That sounds amazing.
As soon as we walked in, they ran toward us.
But monkeys are very violent.
- I know. / - These monkeys were very nice.
They're coming after us.
(The moment she gives a carrot)
- It's jumping. / - It's following you.
(A monkey jumped to her as she tried to give a carrot)
- Oh, no. / - What happened?
It's following me!
She's being attacked.
They must've thought you were a tree.
- They thought you were a tree. / - I see.
Because you're so tall.
I've never seen that before.
(They're scary)
Can you jump?
(That's a piece of cake)
You're cute. That's mine.
- It's like holding a koala. / - I was so happy.
Hey.
(It fails to take the food)
I'll give you one.
They don't like carrots.
She's carrying three of them.
This one... Hey.
You can't just take the food.
(Corn tastes the best when I'm eating it alone)
It has facial expressions.
It's holding the camera.
- It hit your head. / - It's really gentle.
Its feet are like human hands.
They're like human hands.
It jumped.
(It takes a carrot)
(Then suddenly jumps)
That's amazing
I've never seen these lemurs in person.
- Haena, I'm a bit scared of... / - Yes.
- Feeding animals. / - Are you okay?
If we go past the zoo and go in more...
- You'll see wild beasts. / - Wild beasts?
There's a safari where you can see big animals.
They are all caged in, so you can just watch.
- It won't be scary. / - I don't have to feed them, right?
You don't have to.
You said you'd put me through hardship.
This is really hard.
- This is it. I was going to... / - It's really tough.
We're only doing the stuff I hate.
It's my day, so we'll do what I want.
Alright.
- Let's go. / - We'll go on to the safari.
- Kids would love that. / - They would.
We take this bus to go into the safari.
- Is this what we're riding? / - Yes.
We just hop in.
That was so much fun.
- Seriously, I'll go there. / - Okay.
- Zoos are really great. / - You're right.
It makes you happy.
- Here we go. / - Let's go.
Welcome to the safari park.
- It's not a jeep. / - The entrance fee...
- No. / - It's a bus.
Let's go.
You seem way more excited than before.
I've really wanted to do this.
I thought you could only go
to a safari like this in Africa.
- I know, right? / - This is so cool.
(What animal will they see first?)
- There it is. / - What? Where?
- What's that? / - Where?
- Over there. / - Where?
- Here. / - I see.
- Are they deer? / - Goodness.
They're so pretty.
- Deer are so pretty. / - They are, aren't they?
They're cute.
There are so many of them.
- I've never seen one like that. / - Antelope.
There were so many different kinds of antelopes.
I guess they don't eat each other.
They are all herbivores.
They can't eat each other. My gosh.
There are so many of them.
Is it because they're herbivores?
We're going into somewhere different.
- We're going through a steel gate. / - This is it.
- This is the real safari. / - This is where it begins.
- This is similar. / - Yes.
It's so cool.
Please show yourselves.
(We wonder what lives here)
What is it? What's there?
What is it?
(Look at that!)
- Amazing. / - Rhinoceros!
- Awesome. / - Unbelievable.
I thought they were rocks. Amazing.
- I've never seen them before. / - They're huge.
- They're like rocks. / - They're really huge.
Amazing.
- Why are they all together? / - It must be too hot.
They're in the shade because it's hot.
- Amazing. / - I didn't think they'd be this big.
They're huge.
- Don't they have cute eyes? / - Yes.
They're like buttons.
- They have a lot of wrinkles around the eyes. / - Yes.
I've been to a safari in Africa for a shoot.
Rhinoceros usually don't come out like that.
They are dangerous animals
and they don't come near people.
Look at that.
- It's a lion. / - A lion.
It's the king of the jungle.
- It hates sunlight. / - The paws look so soft.
- Seriously. / - Goodness.
They're so cute.
Haena, there is a baby here.
- There's a baby. / - Where?
There's a foal.
It's so cute.
- It's so cute. / - It's really cute.
- Goodness. / - The foal is so cute.
- So cute. / - That's a popular hairstyle.
- There are giraffes. / - Where?
- There are giraffes. / - Gosh, my nickname is giraffe.
I've never seen so many giraffes.
- Hello. / - Look.
(Bye, giraffes)
- I'm losing track of time here. / - I know, right?
The safari was so much fun. The end!
Safaris are fun.
- They are. / - They're fun.
You just stay on the bus and not harm anything.
I want to highly recommend our trip because of this.
Where are we going after this?
This time, it's world's number one.
We'll ride the longest cable car in the world.
Haena, you only deal with the world's best.
Of course.
We'll go from number 2 to 1.
- That's good. / - Let's go ride the cable car.
- Let's go. / - Go, go.
(They're off to enjoy the world's longest cable car)
- Phu Quoc has a lot to offer. / - There's much to see.
(It takes about 1 hour from the safari by taxi)
This is where we'll ride the cable car.
- I can see it over there. / - You can see it, right?
It's the longest cable car in the world.
- This one? / - Yes.
Also the apparatus...
They built this new cable car.
It's the longest in the world.
That's amazing.
It's the tallest so it is in the Guinness World Records.
- We'll pass five islands. / - Okay.
So we'll arrive at...
The cable car passes five islands.
- Hon Thom Island? / - Yes.
It goes all the way down to Hon Thom Island.
(This 7.9km long cable car passes 5 islands)
- It's endless. / - It doesn't stop.
Do you just go there and come back?
No, there are a lot of activities to do.
- You can enjoy water sports. / - On Hon Thom Island?
Then you go back.
Thank you.
(Cable car admission fee, $25)
(Let's go ride the cable car)
(The world-class cable car is right before their eyes)
It's huge.
It's really big, Haena.
(We're going on it!)
Wait.
I'm scared.
It's like an amusement park ride.
It takes 20 minutes to get to the end.
- I see. / - 20 minutes?
Yes. It's very long.
It's amazing.
Isn't it pretty? It keeps on going.
- There's a town too. / - Yes.
It's really high.
It's so nice because there's nothing blocking the view.
We can see everything.
(A panoramic view of Phu Quoc can be seen)
Unbelievable.
This is awesome.
It's like a scene from a movie.
- Right? / - Yes.
When you're up high like this,
you can see all the buildings and the rooftops.
- It's so pretty. / - If you ride it...
You can see the whole of Phu Quoc.
- It's going over the water. / - Yes.
- It's nice. / - Yes.
The view is beautiful.
Look at the color of the sea.
Isn't that emerald color?
- Amazing. / - The color of the sea is awesome.
It looks like paint is mixed in with the water.
- It's nice, Haena. / - Isn't it?
I like this course.
- This is a must-do. / - You have to do this.
- We'll see a pillar that is... / - Yes.
On the world records.
It's not a building but a pillar.
Yes, it's a pillar.
(It's as tall as a 75-story building)
I can't feel how high this is.
- That was 160m high. / - That's amazing.
(The sea looks so far away)
- It's huge. / - It looks really tall from here.
It's endless.
(It takes a while to look at the whole pillar)
It's nice. This is really nice.
The cable car was a great dating place.
(After the last pillar, they see Hon Thom Island)
We'll relax here for a bit.
Once we arrive on Hon Thom Island,
we'll enjoy water sports.
We haven't been in the water.
My feet went in the water.
My hat went in the water too.
No! My hat!
But your body hasn't gone in the water yet.
If I drown, I'm going to step on you and come out.
(Kyunga can't swim)
I think you'll actually do that.
I was thinking out loud.
- I'm just kidding. / - Even if you go far out...
Your head will still be out of the water.
Perhaps.
- It'll be fun. / - I'll believe in you.
(Let's go to Hon Thom Island for fun water sports!)
(30 minutes to Hon Thom Island by cable car)
Snorkeling in the sea is fun
but there's something I haven't tried.
You go on a board and paddle.
- A canoe? Paddle-boarding. / - I wanted to try that.
- Kayak. / - Kayaking is hard.
I wanted to try something like this.
I also wanted to try something like paddle boats.
You would look really tall if you stand up on there.
Should I plant a telephone pole there?
That's good.
I'll install the electric lines.
I'll have to see what kind of activity they will do.
You can enjoy marine sports there
if you make a reservation.
(Hon Thom Island is an activity paradise)
(The waves are quite unusual)
- It's too windy. / - What?
It's really windy.
- It wasn't good that day. / - The weather was...
- It can't be. / - The waves were too high.
The waves are really high.
You can't do any activities there.
- Gosh. / - Gosh.
The color of the water changed.
(Screaming)
The waves are too strong.
I said I prepared an activity, didn't I?
But it rained earlier...
So the waves are too strong.
- It's scary. / - Yes.
I wanted to go paddle boarding...
- Or kayaking. / - Yes.
- But we can't do it. / - Yes.
- So I prepared another activity. / - What is it?
Okay, let's go.
Let's go do the activity.
(Okay, let's go do the activity)
The activity.
This is the activity.
(She prepared a flamingo float for Kyunga)
- What is that? / - It was so nice until then.
- That was so fun. / - It looks fun.
(She prepared a flamingo float for Kyunga)
Kyunga, do you know how scary this is?
You can do this in Jeju-do.
This is on another scale.
It will be really exciting because of the waves.
Let's go. Let's get in the water.
(There is someone who is enjoying kayaking)
- Kyunga. / - This is not going to work.
- Come here. / - This is not going to work.
This is not going to work.
(Ideal)
(And reality)
Kyunga, isn't this exciting?
This is not going to work.
I want to get on the float.
(She's on it)
(But she falls)
Oh, my.
I'm a bit...
Haena, I'm a little disappointed.
(This was filmed under the guidance of safety guards)
(Song Haena doesn't know how to give up)
(Kyunga caught the float that Haena missed)
(Laughing)
(Chaotic)
(It's quite sad watching them play in the water)
We're done with this activity.
It was active for me at least.
This made the things you did earlier look bad.
That's not true.
It gets better again.
I enjoyed it.
The waves were really high.
The weather was really cooperative,
so my activity plan was successful.
Did it really go according to plan?
Is this what you wanted?
- Gosh. / - Wait for me.
(No matter what people say, it was a good activity)
The highlight of today remains.
- Really? / - Yes.
You will really like this one.
- Are you sure? / - I'm sure.
Can you tell me what the next course is?
The next course...
The sunset is really beautiful in Phu Quoc.
- I heard about that. / - Yes.
- We have to see the sunset. / - Yes.
We'll see it at a good beach.
After that, we'll eat a really delicious meal.
- Okay. / - Yes.
Great.
(It was an activity that will remain a good memory)
- If the sunset succeeds, we'll win. / - Of course.
- I was worried here. / - I was really worried.
The activity was disappointing.
I hope you succeeded in watching the sunset.
Yes, we did.
- But it was fun. / - She became serious suddenly.
- The activity was a mess. / - You must go here.
So they changed their hopes to the sunset.
(35 minutes by taxi to the sunset beach bar)
(From the cable car)
Phu Quoc is really famous for sunsets.
(Time for the red sun to set)
Will you join me at a place with a good atmosphere?
Okay.
- You have to come here last. / - That's right.
It's also better...
- At night today. Right? / - It's charming.
(They're enjoying dinner on a beach)
It's not hot at night.
It's comfortable to stay seated. It's nice.
- You can hear the waves and music. / - Yes.
Since this is the end, I don't want to go.
- I don't want to go back. / - Me too.
- I don't want to go. / - You're right.
You have to go to places like that with your lover.
- Yes. / - That's right.
(Cocktails that contain Phu Quoc's coolness)
(Fish and chips)
Fish and chips?
That place was a little exotic,
so most of the customers were Westerners.
That's why the food was like that.
(Clapping like a seal)
Would you like some mojito in Phu Quoc?
- You had a mojito. / - Yes.
(Yum)
- Thanks for the food. It was fun. / - I had fun too.
You have to have fish and chips on a beach.
It's only $9.
- Yes. / - Gosh.
You have to have fish and chips at the beach.
- That's right. / - You have to have it.
Fish and chips taste different in every country.
- That's why I wanted to order it. / - You're right.
- The seafood is delicious here. / - You're right.
(Collaboration of crispy fried batter and juicy fish)
I really like meat.
Even steaks are cheap there.
- It's delicious. / - Is it delicious?
It's greasy but it's delicious because it's greasy.
It tastes a little like Chinese, the seasoning does.
- It's like sweet and sour pork. / - Yes.
It's delicious.
The atmosphere is also really nice.
It's so nice to have a cocktail and
eat delicious food on the last night.
Right?
This place isn't well-known to people yet.
We also didn't know well.
- I think places that aren't well-known... / - Yes.
Are more charming than well-known places.
It's because it feels like
I'm the only one who knows about it.
It feels like a special place.
Phu Quoc was exactly like that for me.
It was so natural, and the people were so friendly.
The food was also so delicious.
Who knew that the second biggest safari
in the world was here?
Who knew that the longest cable car
The infrastructure is starting to establish.
It would be so nice if people came now.
There will be too many people if you come later...
You might not be able to come.
- That's right. / - Yes.
- I don't want it to be known. / - I know.
You have to come.
Should I tell people about it?
My inner conflict is so intense.
That happens. When it's so nice...
- You don't want to tell people. / - That's right.
I want to be the only one to know.
Since we enjoyed this place first,
let's tell people about it.
- I really wish people came here. / - Yes.
I really enjoyed our trip.
Me too.
In that sense...
- Let's chant one last time. / - Okay.
Song Vacation.
Let's go!
(Song Vacation in Phu Quoc, the end)
- That was fun. / - Gosh.
- First, the basic taxi rate was 30 cents. / - Yes.
- What about that coconut? / - It was $1.
- It was 10 cents. / - It was 10 cents.
Vietnam is really cost effective to travel.
You don't feel any burden from the food cost.
It's like 10 cents and $1.
We're confident of our total expense.
I don't think they used a lot.
How much did you use?
For 3 days 2 nights of Song Vacation,
the total expense excluding the airfare is...
What's the total expense?
$488.
- $488? / - Yes.
Okay.
Let's start the final vote.
Would you like to go to Phu Quoc,
Vietnam according to Song Vacation plan?
Please vote.
(They planned a trip to an emerging vacation spot)
(What will the judges choose?)
This isn't the end of the emerging vacation spots.
I heard that it will be about the grand nature next week.
We will leave for Khao Yai that boasts grand nature.
We'll come back next week with a place
that will make you forget about the summer heat.
(Next episode)
We'll enter nature.
Enjoying nature as naturalists.
It's fascinating. I keep staring.
I've never seen anything like this before.
There are monkeys on the street...
An elephant! It's an elephant!
Ta-da. This is it!
This is what you call a proper vacation.
It's the oldest and largest winery.
This tastes so good.
I'm not going to forget this.
I want to come back next time.
(Battle Trip)
(RUN by Lee Jinah)