(Battle Trip)
(Started on April 16th, 2016)
(Numerous)
(Great tips)
(On trips)
(Battle Trip's 2-year anniversary)
(The hosts prepared a special for the anniversary)
We've arrived in Guam!
(The 3 hosts left on a family holiday)
I'll be in charge of the morning.
Next.
I'll take care of dinner.
Hidden eateries in famous places.
It's our job to find hidden places.
Isn't it something you haven't tasted before?
(I want to try the Slingshot)
(Exhilarating and fun)
My heart is up there.
(The best tour courses in Guam)
They're so cute.
These guys are so cute.
We ended up doing it.
The world is your school.
Life is a journey.
Battle Trip.
Good to see you.
The second day has dawned.
We put flowers in our hair...
- We did. / - We tried it out.
That's right.
You have something else on your hat.
I prepared this for today.
(She has it in all colors)
And this isn't all.
I can pull it down like this.
Isn't it something you wear when you fence?
- Sir. / - It can be used for all things.
Hello.
Hello. I've lived in Guam for 15 years.
- You said 20 years yesterday. / - I'm Kim.
- Please enjoy. / - Okay, sir.
Today, we will try...
- A few things that our viewers asked for. / - Right.
- We received a request. / - We got a lot of requests.
We'll draw a few from those.
It's random.
We don't know what we'll get.
We don't.
(The 2nd day of Battle Trip's 2-year anniversary)
(Pick out 2 places each from the basket)
(They don't get to share what they picked)
(They're allowed to bargain and swap)
If you don't play, you lose. Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Scissors, paper, scissors)
I always lose.
If you don't play, you lose. Rock, paper, scissors.
(Sikyung wins)
Good job.
Ta-da.
Blue is for women.
Check your own.
- Oh! / - Oh.
Wow!
- Is it good? / - It's not bad.
Staying in the hotel?
It's cool.
(Shopping at the supermarket)
Mine is similar to the Slingshot.
Really?
- Is it sky-diving? / - Sky-diving?
It's worse than sky-diving.
- Space? / - What's worse than that?
I'm serious.
- Is this even possible? / - I don't know.
This can't be possible.
(Flying a light aircraft)
I picked another short distance thing.
Goodness.
I'm a regular here.
(Going to a shrimp restaurant)
That's it.
That color suits you.
(They all have different reactions)
(Sook is laughing uncontrollably)
- It's not bad. / - What do I do?
Not bad.
What am I going to do?
He says it's not bad.
(He picked another restaurant, Chamorro this time)
(Sikyung picked Flyboarding)
This is the best.
Why?
People actually think about doing this?
(Let's see now)
Let's go.
My lips... My lips...
Okay, go.
No! Don't! Don't!
(That's when I planned on revenge)
(I need to give this to Sikyung)
Swap with me.
Why?
I have two of the same thing.
What is it?
It's eating.
Are you sure that it's eating?
Yes, both of them are.
I can't give this up,
because it's cool.
But this is a different kind of cool.
Give that to me.
- What? / - Give that to me.
Both of mine are eating.
(Sikyung, swap with me)
Give me one eating one then.
Wait a minute.
This is good.
You shouldn't look.
I haven't swapped mine yet.
What is it?
- Is it food relate? / - Something scary in the air.
What about this?
This is something to enjoy.
I'm scared about being in the air.
- You don't mind it, right? / - I like it.
Since I'm on a diet,
I'll go flying for you.
- Since you can't. / - Okay, you do this one.
This is really delicious.
Done.
I'll be off then.
Hey!
Run!
Run, Sook!
Come back here.
(Devastated)
We will record the recommendations...
I can't do this.
That were given to us from the viewers.
We will capture them all on camera.
- Battle Trip. / - I can't do this.
Hwijae!
Just end it here.
Hurry up and end it.
- It's a wedding photo shoot. / - 1, 2, 3.
I didn't hear anything.
No way!
(Viewer recommendations in Guam)
(Hwijae, Sook, Sikyung)
What about that?
I want to do everything.
I'm so excited.
(After the raffle, the hosts met the staff to discuss)
(How will they carry out the course?)
The viewers...
Recommended this.
To solve your curiosity...
Even if it's difficult, we will do it for you.
You must try this.
Thank you so much, Sikyung.
This is so delicious.
Oh, it's flying.
I'm flying it.
I think I'll fall in love with Guam.
I wanted to try Flyboarding so much.
(It might be a little different from what you imagined)
(He will shoot a wedding photo if the viewers want it)
(Why are there tears in my eyes?)
I have to score it. 5 points.
I give it 5 points.
(Very satisfactory tour given by the viewers)
Let's be happy for a long time.
(Stay tuned)
We need to see this first.
What am I going to do?
- Actually... / - Why?
I was going to give Sikyung
the flying a light aircraft recommendation.
Look.
I enjoyed watching the Jeolla-do tour on Battle Trip.
You really liked riding light aircrafts.
You can fly them yourself in Guam.
Try it and l let us know
how Guam looks from the sky.
I had this and
the self-wedding photo shoot in my hand.
I told him this was an activity in the air
and I gave him the wrong one.
I gave him the wrong one.
I was supposed to give him this.
I gave Sikyung the self-wedding photo shoot.
So that's why Sikyung chased me.
I ran away because someone chased after me.
I run away instinctively when someone chases me.
I'm really sorry, Sikyung.
I thought I gave you the light aircraft.
I thought it was the light aircraft.
Let's see what this is.
What did Sikyung give me?
Oh? Chamorro restaurant.
Go to this restaurant and have a Chamorro meal.
The barbecue and dessert is really good there.
From L...
Sikyung would've loved this.
What do I do? I feel so sorry.
I'll enjoy the Chamorro food for you.
Sikyung, you can do it.
(At that time, Sikyung was)
(Losing his smile)
(Sigh)
What am I doing?
I'm going to kill Kim Sook.
It's the elder's funeral today.
They have fried rice.
It looks good.
Let's go before Sikyung catches us.
Let's go.
It's right in front of here.
(Viewer recommendations in Guam)
(Sook, Chamorro restaurant)
Let's get going.
Let's try Chamorro food.
Great thing I swapped with him.
This is perfect for me.
(Morning in Guam with a nice weather)
(Hotel)
(3 minutes to Chamorro restaurant)
It's close.
You could just walk here.
This is nice.
Hi.
Hafa adai.
There aren't any customers right now.
Guess they just opened.
This is a Chamorro restaurant.
The Chamorro are the indigenous people
and this place makes traditional Guam food here.
- Hi. / - Hi.
Hafa adai.
It's your first time?
Yeah, first time.
Recommendation?
The most popular. Barbecue.
We have a combination trio.
- Beef, pork, chicken. / - Combination.
- Combination. This one. / - Everything.
Combination.
- This one. / - One trio?
Red rice or white rice?
Red rice?
Do I understand English now?
I heard "red rice or white rice."
- Red rice or white rice. / - Red rice is not spicy.
It's famous. Very, very good.
Red rice!
Red rice! Yeah.
And...
Yeah, drink.
The most popular drink,
we have pretty good Italian soda.
You can choose mango,
strawberry, raspberry or watermelon.
Choose one flavor.
Raspberry.
- Raspberry. / - Raspberry.
Yes.
Italian soda.
- Italian soda. / - Here we have raspberry Italian soda.
Yeah, thank you.
(Italian soda with raspberries, $3)
(Eyes widen)
Soda usually
is strongly carbonated.
But this is smooth.
It's so good.
(Gulping)
(Her uvula is working very hard)
(Bottoms up)
(The main menu isn't even here yet)
(She wants more)
(Waiter is back)
I trust you.
Yeah, recommendation.
Would you like to try this root beer?
Root beer?
Root beer, no alcohol.
American soda.
- American soda? / - Yes.
Agreed.
- Okay. / - Yeah, okay.
I've never heard of root beer before.
This is root beer.
And then, this is...
Chamorro fruit punch.
Is it on the house?
Yes!
Thank you!
(You looked really thirsty)
This is Chamorro fruit punch.
This is unique.
This is really unique.
(She holds the cup and downs the drink)
(The Chamorro drink is showing off its charm)
It's kind of like tea.
So in a way...
It feels like tea.
You can taste the raspberries and strawberries...
It's between a soda and tea.
It's not a strong flavor.
I think people will like this.
This is the Chamorro fruit punch.
This is quite addictive.
This is
root beer.
(What does root beer taste like?)
(Wait a minute)
(What is this taste?)
(This tastes very familiar)
(She remembers it at last)
I didn't know you could drink pain reliever.
This is so interesting.
But this doesn't taste weird.
It does taste like pain reliever.
I prefer this one.
This one is better.
(Sook chooses the Chamorro fruit punch)
Alright, here we go.
It's here.
Check this out.
Big fella trio.
(Chamorro-style barbecue)
(The meat is marinated in soy sauce and vinegar)
(Pork, beef, chicken)
(You can taste 3 different kinds of meat at once)
(Chamorro trio barbecue, $22.95)
Let's start digging in then, shall we?
The red rice is so...
Let me taste it.
It looks like the rice is strongly seasoned
but it's just plain rice.
(Let me see, which one should I eat first?)
I'll eat the pork first.
It tastes better when you eat off the bone.
It's a very deliciously seasoned pork.
You can clearly taste the charring
and it's very juicy.
It's a flavor you can't reject.
(Sook really enjoys the pork)
(Great food makes you the happiest)
I can't put this down.
(Only the bone remains)
Let me try the beef.
It looks like...
L.A. ribs.
It tastes like a Korean dish. The dish is very familiar.
It's like L.A. ribs for the rich.
So much meat.
It's a flavor you can't dislike. It's good.
(This is delicious)
Next.
Chicken.
It'd be weird if it looks like this and tastes bad.
This has to be delicious.
The skin is to die for.
There's just the right amount of fattiness
and seasoning.
The chewy texture of the chicken is heightened.
These make up for the dryness of chicken breast.
This is so good.
If I'm on a diet
and this is the chicken breast I have to eat,
I'd definitely eat this.
I completely understand
why the viewer recommended this.
It seems to be the best flavors
you can get from a barbecue.
The chicken, pork and
beef, each have its own flavor.
Sikyung, thank you so much.
Hey, this restaurant serves great food.
(She fidgets with the menu)
(Dessert menu)
(My gosh, this is it)
This is it.
There are viewers who love desserts so...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
There are 10 desserts.
I'll just have...
No, 3.
Chocolate wasabi cheesecake.
I'll try the coconut banana...
Red velvet. I'll order these three.
(3 cakes, $20.85)
Wow, this is huge.
This is coconut.
Oh, banana.
What is this? It's so pretty.
The banana inside is so delicious.
It's so soft.
This one is
chocolate wasabi cake.
I can smell a hint of wasabi.
Hey, this is good.
The wasabi isn't tangy or pungent.
The wasabi neutralizes the sweetness
of the chocolates which can be too strong at times.
In that respect,
this is a rich chocolate cake.
(Finally, the red velvet cake)
There's a layer of cheese on top.
I have to slice it well.
(She eats it with both hands)
(She seems satisfied)
The surface seems really dry,
but it's really moist.
I will recommend the red velvet.
It's the largest serving.
It looks like it has two tiers.
This one.
The dish the viewer recommended...
Was really good.
Now, to rate this restaurant
out of 5 points...
(Thinking)
I score it 4.5.
(Sook's favorite dishes from today's meal)9
Battle.
Trip!
I switched this with Sikyung.
I really wanted to try this.
Flyboard.
(You can soar into the air using the water pressure)
(You can feel like you're Iron Man on the water)
(Flyboard, trending water activity)
I really wanted to try this.
This one caught my eyes right away.
I want to know how it feels in the air.
I want to find out how fun this is.
(Viewer recommendations in Guam)
(Hwijae, Flyboard)
I can't believe I'm doing this in Guam.
The weather is great.
The air is fresh.
I had delicious food.
And now that I'm off to do an activity,
I can't help but smile.
What's this?
Is this a factory?
It looks like the inside of a military base.
(Where am I? Am I on the right path?)
People do the water activities here?
(He's arrived at the right place but)
Are you guys...
Selling me off to a shrimp boat or something?
I didn't know it was so far away.
I've been to Guam a lot, but I've never been here.
Hello. Hi. How are you?
This place is for Flyboarding?
(You can see oil tankers and containers from here)
(It's a natural area with depth as deep as 370m)
(If you follow the suspicious path to the end)
(You can enjoy all kinds of water activities)
(Apra Harbor)
I have changed my outfit
to become Iron Man.
Ta-da.
(Flyboard, $85)
Oh, my God.
That guy's a real pro.
He's the real Iron Man.
(Can Hwijae keep his balance on the board?)
I have been...
Exercising all these years.
I have to fly.
(Shaking)
(He's practicing to keep his balance on the swing)
(Legs trembling)
Oh, my God.
- Are you okay? / - Yeah.
(He practices one more time)
What's happening?
(His lower body is too weak)
What's wrong with me?
Okay.
I want to try.
Let's go.
Okay.
(It's time for him to become Iron Man)
Okay. All the time.
Alright.
Okay.
Let's go.
(The engine's starting up)
Oh, what is this?
(He moves to the quayside)
Okay.
Alright.
(Hwijae the Iron Man, sets out)
Oh, my God.
(Oh, my God?)
It's not easy, right?
(He must keep his body up right)
(It's a sport where one must keep the balance to fly)
(However)
Oh, my God.
This is no joke.
(He couldn't stay balanced for the 1-year anniversary)
(Hwijae can't give up like this)
- Stand up first. / - Okay.
(I won't fail anymore)
(He keeps his legs straight)
(He's totally focused)
(He fails again)
(He fails as his legs lose balance)
(The sportsman faces humiliation)
(I don't know if it's water or my tears)
(Flyboarding isn't easy at all)
(Splash)
(Splash 2)
(Splash 3)
(Splash 4)
Oh, sorry.
(He's suddenly reminded of his twins)
(Yes! I can do this!)
(Motor on)
(His posture seems more stable)
(His two legs look strong too)
(Daddy, you can do it!)
(Hwijae finally flies out of the water)
(It was thanks to the cheers from the twins)
(Good job, good job)
(He successfully flies in the sky)
(Two thumbs up!)
This is no joke.
(The father of the twins prepares to fly higher)
(He looks so serious)
(The father of twins steadily floats into the air)
(He won't allow his two legs to be shaky anymore)
(The result of his effort provides a visible difference)
(I won't fail again)
(Now, it depends on how long he can fly in the air)
(Good job)
(Hwijae thoroughly enjoys flying above the water)
(Looking relaxed)
(Hwijae can fly in the air like Iron Man at last)
(He shows you that you can do anything)
(If you don't give up)
(He takes his time to enjoy the sky)
(Hwijae is utterly happy with his success)
(Let's go now)
Rather than Iron Man...
I've become a mess.
(Before Flyboarding, after Flyboarding)
Sook, I know what you're doing. Stop eating.
Sikyung, this is the thing to do in Guam.
If you enjoy the adrenaline rush and
water activities...
Out of 5, this scores...
100 points.
Iron Man.
Stark.
(Viewer recommendations in Guam)
(Sikyung, self-wedding photo shoot)
Done.
Hey!
It's a wedding shoot.
(Just as Sook did a self-wedding shoot in Jeju-do)
(Please try it at Two Lovers Point and give us tips)
This is it.
Oh, my back...
My back is too fat.
I need someone to massage my back.
1, 2, 3.
(How will Sikyung's wedding photo shoot look?)
(Current temperature, 31??
This is the worst. The worst.
A wedding photo shoot in this weather?
This is like...
Asking a beggar...
To play a rich man for the day.
(Sighing)
So I go and pick out my tuxedo now, right?
(Hotel)
(Tuxedo shop)
(8 minutes)
(A tuxedo hire shop near the hotel)
I can't believe they actually have this here.
(Posing like the photo)
Hello.
(The shop is full of fancy tuxedos)
(You can buy and hire suits here)
I'm the poor guy who needs the suit.
I'm going to be shooting a wedding shot by myself.
Okay.
- What's your name again? / - Rose.
- Rose? / - Yes.
This is Rose.
Yes, Rose.
You know that, right?
It's a beautiful name.
Right here, sir.
Thank you.
The arms are too short.
Oh, my God.
I have long arms.
I look like a poor groom.
I said the arms are too short
and she gave me this.
Yo, this is hip hop.
(He finds his swag in Guam of all places)
What's up, brother?
What's happening, bro?
What am I doing?
I'll try just one more.
Rose is doing her best.
Is there a... Aloha shirts here?
Yes, we do.
(Hawaiian shirts are commonly used in wedding shoots)
How about pink?
(Pink, if you're a real man)
Blue.
How does it look?
I want an earring too.
Thank you.
I'll live happily.
(Tuxedo shop)
(13 minutes to Two Lovers Point)
(Two Lovers Point)
(Legend states that two lovers)
(Tied their hair together and jumped off here)
(Many come here for their wedding shoots)
(Two Lovers Point)
I'm here at Two Lovers Point.
I look insane. Dressed like this in this weather.
(Where did the Sikyung from this morning go?)
If you look here,
you will realize I'm more famous than dolphins here.
Check this out.
They're Koreans.
Here on a group tour.
I must hurry to the famous spot
and quickly take the photos since it's embarrassing.
(Photo spot 1, the big heart)
(Is it our imagination that he looks pitiful?)
(Everyone's in summer clothes)
It's so hot.
(Sweating so much)
(He begins the self-wedding shoot)
(Using the remote to control the camera)
(Remote in his hand)
(Still, Sikyung does his best)
(He strikes a pose)
(Then wipes his sweat)
(The precious first photo)
I'm seriously going to murder Sook.
It's the elder's funeral today.
(Photo spot 2, bronze statue of legend)
(He's angry but still does his best)
(He makes use of the bouquet)
(With the lovers from the sad legend)
(With the elder that gave me this joy)
(Good thing you did the self-wedding shoot, right?)
There's glare.
(He looks like a groom)
(Is it your wedding today?)
(I'm just doing the wedding shoot alone)
I need the ocean in the picture.
I seriously look like a crazy person!
(He calms himself down and takes another one)
(I'm feeling good now)
(I'm feeling really good)
(A couple taking pictures for each other)
(Watching)
Would you like me to take one for you?
Would you like to borrow this?
- Aren't you Sung Sikyung? / - Yes...
Honey, it's Sung Sikyung!
- What? / - It's Sung Sikyung!
Yes, yes.
(With a tuxedo on, he takes pictures of other couple)
(He's so passionate)
I think it looks okay.
Wow, that's a great photo.
- You're so handsome. / - Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's take one here.
Take one of these for me.
(I'm not lonely at all)
Let's go!
Is it enough?
- Yes. / - I want to get changed.
- To the car. / - I want to get changed.
I want to look like a local prince.
(Ta-da)
(He looks coy)
(The earrings to make him look like royalty)
(Feeling good with light clothes on)
(A Guam prince meeting Koreans)
(Photo spot 3, ocean backdrop at the observatory)
(Entrance fee to observatory, $3)
You're so handsome.
It's because I'm wearing sunglasses.
(Heading to the photo spot)
Let me take one for you.
This is unbelievable.
Let me...
(Frozen)
It's broken.
- What do we do? / - Is the screen cracked or...
No, it's broken.
I'll send you the money for the repair.
- I'm sorry to cause trouble on your trip. / - It's okay.
I feel bad. You were only offering to help us.
Because of this bloody bouquet!
I'm so sorry.
I promise I will pay the repair bill.
You're making us feel bad.
I'm so sorry that I'm lost for words.
I'll take your photo first.
- I'll try to get a lot of sky into the shot. / - Okay.
There's a glare so...
(A photo for the price of a phone screen)
(A memorable trip for all)
(Fortunately, they later told us the phone was fine)
(It was only the case and screen protector that broke )
(The phone is fine)
Press it.
Press.
Try it.
(The bouquet that caused me pain)
(We invite you to Sikyung's solo wedding)
(You'll come, right?)
Let's live happily ever after.
(Embarrassed)
Can I go now?
(Sikyung's self-wedding photo shoot is over)
(Viewer recommendations in Guam)
(Sook, light aircraft)
Shall we go?
Gosh, I'm full.
It was a good decision to order three.
(Chamorro traditional restaurant)
(18 minutes to light airport)
It's here.
There are planes over there.
There are so many.
(Flying in the blue sky in Guam will get you excited)
(The cute light aircraft will take Sook to the sky)
I've been in one of these before.
I think the one with Sohyun was similar to this.
I'm excited.
I remember having lots of fun the time.
(October 15th, 2016, Jeolla-do trip)
(Sook rode a light aircraft during her trip to Jeolla-do)
It's so pretty.
(She rode one at the time)
(But today she'll fly one)
(Will she be able to fly it okay?)
I will fly it myself?
(She is worried)
Hello.
- Hi. / - I'll be your instructor.
- Nice to meet you. / - Nice to meet you.
My name is Nanda Kim.
- Nice to meet you. / - Nanda, Nanda.
Course G is an exciting course.
I like it.
We're flying for 30 minutes.
- 30 minutes? / - Okay.
Is this course for children?
- This is for juniors? / - Yes.
Even children can do this.
So I don't need to worry.
Okay, this is the airport. Guam International Airport.
We're going to the Two Lovers Point.
This is Two Lovers Point.
This is where Sikyung is shooting.
Seriously, I'm going to murder Sook.
So you will see the Tumon Beach.
- And? / - We'll go all the way to Apra Harbor.
This is Apra Harbor?
Here?
I can see Hwijae here. Okay.
- Alright? / - Yeah.
I like it.
(After a quick training, you can fly the light aircraft)
- No. / - No.
I'm nervous.
The aircraft is prettier than I thought.
I'm so nervous.
(The professional pilot sits next to you for a safe flight)
(You can pay for 1 and have 2 more in the back)
My goodness.
What is this?
This is amazing.
- Captain. / - Yes.
How many times have you flown?
A little over 4,000 hours of flight time.
- 4,000? / - Yes.
Okay.
(Doing a bit of slapstick now that she's relaxed)
(Ready)
(They're ready)
(This is awesome)
(It's time to fly the light aircraft)
It's moving.
Here we go.
(As the engine gets louder, she looks nervous)
You have the controls now.
I'm actually in control?
(She has to make the aircraft take off)
(She's excited and nervous at the same time)
(Now pull it yourself)
(As she slowly pulls the controller)
(The aircraft starts to fly like magic)
(Sook successfully flies an aircraft)
I made it fly. I made it fly.
Did you see? I made it took off.
(Feeling exhilarated about taking off the aircraft herself)
(A beginner pilot's exciting first flight)
(As she calms down, she sees the beauty of Guam)
Look at the color of the water.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
This is incredible.
- We'll take a left now. / - Left.
(Trembling)
(Turning)
(She successfully made a left turn)
Oh, here?
Go this way?
(First up, Two Lovers Point)
It looks amazing.
I bet Sikyung's there somewhere.
Sikyung, I'm here!
I'm here and you're there!
Are you having fun taking wedding pictures?
You're dead once you get down here.
How can you make me do this
and have fun on that?
It's so pretty.
(The second course, Tumon Beach)
I think I'm going to like Guam a lot.
(The third course, Apra Harbor)
Wow, isn't that Hwijae?
Hwijae!
Hwijae, good luck!
Left turn.
(She mastered how to turn now)
(After Apra Harbor, Sook's plane returns)
(Slowly, you'll fly lower)
(What's going on?)
(Wobbling)
(Landing is the most difficult part in flying a plane)
Can I do a good job in landing?
(Nervous)
(Both novice and experienced pilots are nervous)
(The airplane is shaking violently)
Please maintain the balance.
(The novice pilot is preparing to land)
(Can she succeed in one try?)
Good landing.
Good, good, good.
(She must've been scared)
My heart was racing when I was landing the plane.
Good flying. Very good.
I'm still alive.
I'm sorry, I'll get out a bit later.
I think I peed a little.
The landing was scary.
But when I was up in the air,
I felt touched because I was
flying the plane.
There's an enormous difference in looking at Guam
from the ground and from the sky.
I have to give it a score, right?
So the score is...
I have to consider the cost.
If you're rich, it's worth 5 points.
(If you're rich, it's worth 5 points)
Well, what I've chosen is...
An eatery.
This restaurant specializes in shrimp dishes.
We have to go there.
Do you go there often?
I go there at least twice whenever I come to Guam.
And I noticed they have
a branch in front of our hotel.
The head restaurant is in downtown
and you have to line up to eat there.
The head restaurant is small, but this branch is big.
You have to go here
and try the shrimp.
(This is the shrimp you must eat in Guam)
(The shrimp will be revealed soon)
(Viewer recommendations in Guam)
(Hwijae, shrimp restaurant)
We'll go taste some shrimps.
There are shuttle buses everywhere in Guam
so you can go anywhere in downtown for free.
But this shrimp restaurant is
right in front of our hotel.
It's right in front of it.
That's our hotel.
And there's the shrimp restaurant.
(He's very excited about shrimp)
Let's go!
(The restaurant is full of customers)
(Inside is decorated with shrimps everywhere)
(There are couples)
(There are friends)
(And there are families)
(Hwijae, try the shrimp)
(Hwijae is ordering)
One garlic.
Coconut shrimp.
- This is also one of our favorites. / - This is my favorite.
My favorite.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
I'm salivating.
(Coconut shrimp is being cooked in the kitchen)
(Nicely fried)
(Placed in a bowl and it's done)
(Coconut shrimp, $17.99)
Let's go.
I have your favorite.
Yes, it's my favorite.
This is the coconut shrimp.
- Thank you. / - Please enjoy.
Everyone.
You may doubt how good this is
but this is beyond your imagination.
Drench it.
It's not that spicy.
Then you eat it right away.
(His nostrils are widened)
This...
I want to sell this at baseball stadiums in Korea.
(Fantastic)
It doesn't have a strong flavor,
so the kids love it.
The meat in here is fresh.
So rather than it being plump, it spreads in your mouth.
It's fried evenly and so crunchy.
Also, it's so savory
because of the coconut powder on the outside.
As you chew it,
you can taste the coconut.
That's the highlight.
Someone has to be next to you...
To restrain you.
(Otherwise you won't stop eating it)
(Please someone stop me)
(Here comes the waiter who will stop him)
(What's the next dish that will stop him?)
(Gambas cooked in Guam style)
(Gambas, $16.99)
Don't just eat the shrimp.
Take a piece of bread
and dip it in sauce.
(Yes, this is it)
This isn't just delicious.
You'll think, "What is this?" It's that good.
It's a bit different from Korean gambas.
It's both spicy
and sweet.
Spicy and sweet.
Then you mix rice in it.
(You mix rice in the sauce)
(He faints because it's so good)
It has a mild garlic flavor
and the sauce is perfect for Koreans.
And this is what makes the garlic shrimp complete.
First, you take a spoonful of rice.
Dip it in the sauce slightly.
Just a little bit.
Then you place a shrimp on top.
It's a combination of sauce, rice and shrimp.
This is Guam's triple combo.
(His nostrils only tell the truth)
I'm feel bad because I'm eating this alone.
(He wants to share this with the others)
This is crazy.
Thank you.
Viewer G, recommended this place.
I can't help it. This restaurant...
I give it 5 out of 5.
This is a place you must visit
in your schedule.
Please come here and enjoy it.
(Like me)
(Viewer recommendations in Guam)
(Sikyung, supermarket shopping)
(A viewer recommended a supermarket tour)
There's a place Sikyung would like.
There's an American supermarket in Guam.
It's enormous.
People shop there...
And post the pictures on social medias,
bragging about what they bought.
(In Guam, one must shop at the supermarkets)
(10 minutes from Two Lovers Point to the supermarket)
These are suggestions the viewers sent in
about things that you can only buy
here in Guam.
It feels like America.
This is America...
But they have wooden chopsticks.
(Korean writing)
(Fascinated)
If you look over here,
there's kimchi flavored popcorn.
One of the viewers recommended this. Only sold here.
It's kimchi flavor.
This might actually not be that bad.
This is something you can't find in Korea.
You can spray it on chips.
To satisfy our viewers' curiosity...
And, everyone.
Whenever you go abroad, always buy potato chips.
They never eat it alone.
They always dip it in all of these.
These are all dips.
They're always displayed together.
I think this is the difference between them and us.
(What is he buying next?)
This is low-fat.
They have a "golden" flavored Oreo.
This looks good too, right? Red velvet.
This looks good.
Maybe I should send this to Sook.
Okay. No, wait. Kim Sook! Wedding!
Kim Sook! Wedding!
I sowed the wind and reaped the whirlwind.
(Mommy)
(He didn't know back then)
(I'm sweating from my eyes)
What is this?
(Just like the phone, he had a mental breakdown)
I'm so sleepy because I sweated so much.
I should buy ham.
(Thinking of buying ham makes him happy)
Let's go find ham.
You have a variety of hams when you're overseas.
Let me buy a few of them.
This one is good too.
This one looks delicious.
American hams are very salty.
That's why they're delicious.
This is Portuguese sausage flavor.
That is oven-roasted turkey flavor.
This one is bacon flavor.
Chorizo flavor.
I found an interesting one.
Black pepper sounds good.
This doesn't sound bad.
Teriyaki flavor.
This and rice is going to be my dinner today.
Even the color of the packages are so pretty.
I want to collect them.
(He heads to the next section)
This is the drug section.
Interesting, right?
Chocolate stimulant laxative. What does this mean?
It relieves your intestinal problems.
And it tastes like chocolate.
One of the writers of Battle Trip said
they had intestinal issues and this fixed them up.
So we will take this as well
since you can only buy it here.
Since we found something that is good for you,
now we are going to find something that harms you.
Let's go to the beer section and get cold beer.
I've tried Guam beer.
Banana flavor.
Apple ale.
This is normal.
If you like different kinds of beer,
you should try these.
This is how Americans
visit their friends.
Like, "Let's drink till we drop."
With a bottle of tequila under their arms.
Let's go.
(When did he buy so many?)
(So much stuff)
Let's go.
(He will try these soon and review them)
(The long day is almost over)
- Hwijae. / - Yes.
I can feel freedom here.
- Right? / - This place is inner peace itself.
It is indeed.
- The weather is so nice. / - Look at the beach.
- Look at the families. / - Boys are running around.
- They're hanging out. / - This is great.
This is how you have fun.
(Ypao Beach)
(With rest areas, barbecues and other amenities)
(It's the biggest park and a popular beach in Guam)
This is how life should be, right?
Sikyung said he's going to cook something.
- At the cliff... / - I wonder if he got good photos.
- Also, Hwijae... / - Over there...
- That pink shirt... / - Isn't that his manager?
Is Sikyung wearing a pink shirt?
Let's take a picture.
Let's take a picture of Sikyung.
Sikyung.
Hey, Sikyung.
You don't have to do all this.
- Sikyung, are you trying to impress? / - Sikyung.
Sikyung.
Go away.
- Sikyung, are you trying to impress? / - Sikyung.
(Huh?)
Sikyung, are you okay?
- Why are you suffering, manager? / - What is this?
(The manager is the sous-chef)
(Fries and fries some more)
(He fries meat as well)
- We'll help you. / - It smells good.
- We'll help. / - Nothing to help.
Having you here is confusing me.
Why?
Please have a seat and drink beer.
That's great news for us.
Is there anything you want to eat?
They say we can do barbecue on the beach.
That sounds amazing. Let's do that.
- Sunset barbecue. / - Would you like me to cook?
- We can just order, can't we? / - I like everything.
- Oh! / - Let's go grocery shopping there and...
- Could you make steaks for us? / - Make us steaks.
There must be a local way
to grill steaks there.
What I did before was pan-frying.
I'm sure the locals are better than me.
I'm asking if you'd like something else on the fire.
Could you make us stir-fried glass noodles?
Alright. I'll make it for you.
- You can cook that? / - You can?
Yes, it's just a bother...
You want to eat that with the sunset in Guam?
You want to eat glass noodles in Guam?
- I feel like we need it for a feast. / - Shrimp for me.
We need to take it from Korea.
- Gambas. / - Shrimp.
Please grill shrimps.
- You want me to grill shrimps? / - Yes.
- You said it's a barbecue. / - Just grill it yourself.
- That's just... / - He wants to cook something.
- Oh, on the fire? / - Yes.
- Just on a gas stove... / - Something with seasoning.
(Cooking?)
(That's how Sikyung ended up)
(Preparing a meal for the 2-year-anniversary special)
Since I have to cook there,
I will take some basic seasonings.
Barbecue
has a high likelihood of failure.
It's not a time to brag about my cooking skills.
I should show something that the viewers can do.
What should I cook then?
I should cook something that can never be bad.
So this is what I'm going to cook.
(Sizzle)
(It's beef and shrimp with Sikyung's special sauce)
(On a lightly toasted tortilla)
Sour cream, green guacamole, salsa.
I'll buy the red, green and white sauces.
(Deeply impressed)
It's Mexican food.
What are you going to make?
What are you making?
This is so hard.
(Cooking at a barbecue place)
Don't we have electricity?
Come out already.
The knife is so dull.
Is there anything you can't do, Sikyung?
You're good at everything.
(Sikyung's table)
(First dish, Sikyung's taco)
(He will make guacamole first)
(Take out the seed)
(Add salt and pepper)
(Let's make Sikyung's taco now)
(Prepare the vegetables and meat)
Now, let's make the sauce.
(Add garlic, peppers, and various spices in olive oil)
Looks delicious.
I'll make it not too spicy.
(It's quite good)
(Marinate the meat in Sikyung's special sauce)
(Stir-fry the marinated meat)
I can't wait to try it.
(His cooking went on until it became dark)
- Please say it tastes good. / - Of course.
It smells incredible.
(They're very excited)
Please show us how you eat it.
Take one piece of tortilla.
- Put some meat on it. / - Add meat.
- Add some meat. / - Three slices of meat.
Next, add the shrimp.
- Then the onions. / - Onions.
(With fried paprika)
It looks good already.
Add plenty of each sauce.
- Plenty of... / - You don't want too little.
Oh, my. It looks so good.
You have to be able to wrap it though.
- I think I put too much. / - Let's try.
It's supposed to be eaten in big mouthfuls.
- Okay, let's go. Wrap it. / - Let's go.
The three colors are so pretty.
(Mmm)
Oh, yeah!
- It's so good. / - It's good.
- Not bad? / - Not just not bad.
I think this is the best food I ate in Guam.
(Sikyung feels proud)
Sikyung...
Let's open a restaurant in Korea.
It's really good.
Avocadoes are cheap and good here.
Just scoop it out and season with salt and pepper.
Every supermarket in America sells this.
Salsa sauce. And this as well.
So just add cumin to this and marinade it...
- Add what? / - Cumin.
You know at lamb skewer restaurants,
they give you red seasoning and seed-like things.
They sell that like this here.
This and cilantro, garlic and pepper.
Fish sauce.
Add it all and let it marinade.
But I didn't have time to marinade this.
- This is so good. / - This is so good.
It's good for your health. Eat some more.
I don't usually like to eat food like this,
but this is good.
I usually can't eat onions.
- Really? / - Yeah.
But this is so good.
I really shouldn't eat so much.
Thank you for enjoying it so much.
This is amazing.
Since we don't have a lot of time,
I'll make the pasta right away.
- You're going to cook pasta? / - Yes.
I don't think you'll need to.
- Isn't this enough? / - It won't even take 10 minutes.
All the preparations are complete.
(Sikyung's table)
(The second dish, rice cake pasta)
(Fry rice cakes in a pan with meat grease)
(Add the onions you've fried pre-hand)
(Then add cherry tomatoes)
When the tomatoes start peeling,
season it with balsamic vinegar.
Then add some mozzarella cheese.
(Add mozzarella cheese and season to your taste)
(When the cheese starts to stretch, it's done)
(Confirms the cheese before serving it)
Sook.
- What is that? / - I need two dishes.
Gosh, what is this?
Rice cake pasta?
This is amazing.
This is insane.
What did you do to the rice cakes?
Does Guam have rice cakes?
- I brought it from Korea. / - Oh, my God.
(I need to eat this first)
Is it good?
What is this?
It's insane. Sikyung, this is insane.
- Isn't it delicious? / - What is this?
This is so...
I learned this from Chef Kim Sohui.
The one that uses the Busan dialect.
- She has her hair up. / - From Austria?
Yes.
You can't get this wrong.
It's really delicious.
(I forgot)
I add
the pork rinds from earlier.
Eat it together.
Chef Kim Sohui taught you this?
Yes, the base is soy sauce.
Yes, I thought I tasted soy sauce.
(Everyone will like this)
My kids will love this.
Yes, the kids will like it.
Sikyung will be loved when he gets married.
It tastes different with the rinds.
This is really good.
I'm glad you like it.
(Sikyung is satisfied)
How does rice cake tastes like this?
It's great as a snack with drinks and as a meal.
Why do the tomatoes go so well with this?
I love rice cakes.
I've never seen you eat this much.
I usually eat a lot.
- Really? / - Yes.
- This is the finishing touch. / - Good work, Sikyung.
- Good job. / - Thank you for enjoying it.
It was so good. It was perfect.
I really worried about what to cook.
This is the best food
I've had in Guam.
I'll give you 5 points.
- I didn't know taco tasted this good. / - 5 points.
- Taco... / - I didn't know...
You could cook all this here.
The reason I made these...
If you cook meat outside...
You can buy these three here.
Anything tastes good in this.
Eat it with seasoned meat.
This is healthy and delicious.
Okay.
I'm so happy.
What did you do today? Tell me.
- Sook? / - Yes?
I have to put something straight with Sikyung.
Why did you run away earlier?
I'll fly in the air for you.
Okay, you take this then.
Done?
If I go here... We're done.
(Sikyung saw it)
- I'll get going now. / - Hey!
No way!
Sook, run! Run!
I didn't run away.
- To be honest... / - Why are you so fast?
It was so annoying.
I thought she was a bullet.
All animals...
No.
All animals become real fast when
they're in danger.
I thought I gave him the light aircraft one.
But he chased after me, so I ran away.
It was funnier
because you didn't get caught.
That's such a relief.
If I had caught her...
It wouldn't have stopped there.
Sikyung did a self-wedding photo shoot today.
I went to rent an outfit.
I tried it out and bought it.
I also bought some earrings. I wore earrings.
- No way. / - Why did you buy earrings?
I wanted to feel like Guam royalty.
I had a bowtie, an aloha shirt and earrings.
I wore the tuxedo...
I sweat so much as I was getting changed.
I couldn't take off my pants.
- It was stuck to you? / - Because of sweat.
I know what that is.
- But I had to cook for you. / - Yes.
There were products the viewers were curious about.
They wanted me to buy them and show it to them.
They wanted reviews.
We just need to try these and leave reviews.
Who wants to go first?
I see "kimchi" written in English.
It's kimchi flavored popcorn.
- What is that? / - We don't have it in Korea.
- Is this only in Guam? / - Yes, it's only in Guam.
What will it taste like?
Kimchi flavored popcorn?
It's so unusual.
It doesn't smell like kimchi.
Not at all.
1, 2, 3.
(This taste)
Isn't this just plain popcorn?
I think we should eat some kimchi with this.
Will you buy this or not
on your way to Korea?
1, 2, 3.
- I won't buy it. / - I won't buy it.
I won't.
I'm sorry. It's out.
This doesn't taste like Kimchi at all.
They just added a little spiciness.
I think it's a little spicy.
But it's not enough for us.
It might suit the taste of foreigners.
What's next?
There was so many dried fruits.
This is mango coated in dark chocolate.
Oh, my God.
This is my specialty.
Chocolate is for me.
- You said you wouldn't eat things like this. / - I'll buy it.
(She hasn't had a taste yet)
You said you wouldn't eat it.
- I'll buy it. / - Try it first.
How can you not buy this when it looks like this?
You have to buy this if it looks like this.
Will you buy it?
It's a sweet thing covered in another sweet thing.
Doesn't it look so pretty?
How about the taste?
It doesn't taste like mangoes.
It doesn't taste like mangoes at all.
The chocolate is this thick.
You can't taste the mango.
Let's just eat a mango.
Plain mangoes are better.
- Plain mangoes are better. / - Yes.
Will you buy it or not? 1, 2, 3.
- I won't buy it. / - I won't buy it.
I'll buy it.
But the part without the chocolate is real good.
You have to buy this when it looks like this.
I think we still have a lot left to eat.
Do you have more left?
They said this was delicious.
Isn't this whipping cream?
This is...
I'll buy this.
(I'm the fairy of consumption)
You have to buy things like this.
Would you like American or sharp cheddar?
- I'll choose American. / - I'll also choose American.
This is like jelly.
This is amazing.
Can't you feel it?
This tastes like it will stick right to your veins.
I mean it.
It makes your tongue curl up.
It's because the crackers taste so strong.
This is good.
This is cheddar.
Let's try half each.
The cheese is good.
How do you eat this?
Foreigners dip chips in everything.
There are so many varieties of dipping.
They must have invented this after dipping everything.
Between the two, I recommend this one and I'd buy it.
- I won't buy this. / - I also won't buy this.
It's too salty.
I'll buy it if it looks pretty.
- We have one more left. / - What?
It's constipation medicine with chocolate flavor.
You can get it only in a drug section.
- Are you constipated? / - I'm not constipated.
Me neither.
I don't have constipation but should I try it?
- Just a taste? / - Just a slight taste.
It worked for one of our writers.
Really? Her constipation...
Gosh, what is that?
She was constipated?
Eat the whole thing. How much of it should I eat?
Read the instructions.
Is it chocolate?
It looks just like chocolate.
Two chocolate pieces for adults.
Once or twice a day.
It just smells like chocolate.
It really does.
- It's just chocolate. / - Let's taste it.
- It's a medicine, right? / - Yes.
I'll buy it.
It's a perfect gift.
- It's not so delicious though. / - It's not.
- It's a little bitter. / - It's bitter.
- But it's chocolate. / - Just chocolate.
If it really works, I'm willing to buy it.
- Me too. / - I'll buy it.
1, 2, 3.
- Buy it. / - I'll buy it.
It's great as a gift.
It's so good. How much is it?
Around $9.
- It's not cheap. / - $10?
There are 4 blocks though.
Chocolate...
So there are around 20 doses.
- Alright. / - This is unique.
This is very unique. It's interesting.
I'm willing to buy
more than half of the items.
(Guam shopping list)
And I got something when I had some time.
You went shopping.
You went shopping!
Take a closer look.
Nanda?
Nanda!
- Nanda. / - Hwijae! I love this.
I chose all the colors.
This is so pretty.
You can choose the color combinations
and make your own flip-flops.
This looks so pretty.
B.
(Hwijae's DIY gifts)
(Custom sandals, $30)
(Price may change depending on the design)
I chose all the colors.
This is so pretty.
- Something that doesn't stand out. / - Amazing.
Not to stand out.
Yellow and red doesn't stand out on women.
(She tries them on immediately)
- Don't expect too much. / - Of course.
Just...
- What's Sikyung's name? / - Something you can wear.
Does it say Sikyung?
No.
- What does it say? / - This looks like a designer label.
That's a fake.
- Balla? / - How can I wear this?
Just wear them at home.
- Thank you, Hwijae! / - Treasure it.
I think I'll have a good sleep tonight.
The air was so nice.
I felt really good.
It's been amazing. Thank you so much.
(They made great memories here)
(And)
(They spent the past 2 years together)
How was the past 2 years?
- I didn't even know it's been 2 years. / - Me too.
I host other TV shows for longer...
- Time really flew for Battle Trip. / - You're right.
It's all thanks to the viewers
that show us lots of love.
I'm very grateful.
We've worked so hard to make
a meaningful and interesting show.
It's easy to say but difficult to achieve.
This isn't our last episode, is it?
- We will continue, right? / - We have too.
The new hosts will come from there.
Don't say that.
Three of them will come.
- Oh, so it's you? / - Who are they?
It's a junior.
Don't say that. I want to keep going.
It'd be so funny if three people walk in.
Right?
Thank you so much for the past 2 years.
Please continue to support us.
I guess this is the end of our
2-year-anniversary special.
The world is your school.
Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
(Please continue to love and support our show)
There will be a book for our 2-year anniversary.
- So many good things are happening. / - Battle Trip?
How about we have an event to give away the book
as a gift to the viewers?
Yes, let's give them away.
Please tune in to the broadcast
and upload a photo of it.
(Next week)
I turned 20!
It's great that I'm going with you at this age...
- Yoo spring. / - Na spring.
Spring is here!
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
??Spring, spring, spring is here ??
It's like we're on a time travel.
No way.
(A new challenge at 20)
It feels like it's snowing.
Amazing.
(Battle Trip)
("Scentist" by VIXX)