- Kota Kinabalu. / - This is nice.
This is our 30th anniversary...
Let's have a wonderful trip.
I want to travel as a woman.
It's our 30th anniversary...
Like a model...
1, 2, 3.
- This is painful. / - Smile.
We'll remember this for a long time.
You're the best, Yangrak.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Paeng Hyeonsuk, Choi Yangrak)
(Kim Hyungkyu, Kim Yuna)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Continuing from last week,
we're with the trip planners who have planned
romantic getaways for married couples.
- Welcome. / - It's nice to meet you.
Also, we have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trip.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
Hyejung, how was the Balu Tour from last week?
They took commemoration wedding photos...
- In the last part of the Balu Tour. / - Yes.
When I saw that, I realized that it's best...
- To capture memories with photos. / - That's right.
- Only photos remain later. / - That's right.
It's not common for married couples
to go on a trip alone, right?
There are times when a married couple would...
- Go on trips with their married friends. / - Together.
- They don't go by themselves. / - Not by themselves.
- So I think it's more meaningful. / - That's right.
When I saw their trip last week,
I thought it would be nice if they went on more trips...
- Since they're young and healthy. / - That's right.
- That doesn't only apply for you. / - Thank you.
- That's right. / - I think every...
- Korean married couple's like that. / - That's right.
- We should enjoy more. / - Yes, we should.
- I wish that would happen. / - It must've been ages...
Since Hyungkyu and Yuna went on a trip
without their child, right?
- Yes, that's right. / - How long has it been?
Our child is 12 years old.
- It's been 12 years. / - Is he already 12 years old?
- You never went by yourselves? / - It's the first time.
No.
- Aren't you curious how it will be? / - We're better.
- Really? / - We went 4 years ago.
My wife went through a lot when we moved.
So we left the kids and went to Singapore.
- That's nice. / - He complains but he's good.
- That's right. / - We had...
- A big fight there though. / - Gosh.
- A big fight? / - Yes, a big fight.
- That happens. / - What do you usually fight about?
There are certain things you shouldn't say on a trip.
- What are those? / - "Hey."
- "You said you knew this place." / - That's the worst.
- That's the worst. / - You're right.
- "You wanted to come here." / - That's the worst.
- "You said you knew this place." / - The worst.
- After all that work. / - "I knew this would happen."
- Things like that. / - Yes.
- You have to be careful. / - That's the worst.
- That's annoying. / - What's so funny is that...
- When married couples fight... / - Yes.
They forget why they fought the next day.
- They fight over trivial things. / - It's that trivial.
- Really? / - What do you fight about?
Like I just said, I don't remember why we fought.
- That's right. / - Really?
- Love fights. / - Maybe you just have a bad memory.
- It's trivial. / - Do you have to remember that?
- That's right. / - Not yet...
Have you ever fought on a trip?
- I don't think they will fight. / - We have a similar tastes...
- When it comes to traveling. / - They won't fight then.
For example, we like to find good food.
- You like comics. / - We like to drink alcohol.
- We also like comic books. / - No reason to fight.
We have similar goals.
- So we don't fight on trips. / - That's important.
Some people don't like good restaurants.
- That's right. / - They don't like to wait in line.
"Do we have to wait in line for 2 hours to eat this?"
- "Let's just go somewhere else." / - That's Yangrak.
We knew where the past trip planners of Battle Trip...
- Went in Hokkaido. / - You knew.
We took care...
- To make it feel fresh. / - Did you avoid those places?
We chose things that will make you feel interested
and brought them here.
- We took time. / - What if you're the only one...
- Who thinks like that? / - No.
I'm not the only one who thinks like this.
- Maybe we both got it wrong. / - He picked on me before.
Is there a reason why Hokkaido is voted
as a good place to travel for couples?
The natural environment's amazing.
- That's right. / - The land is very big.
There's a lot of places to go.
They even have a plain...
- The sea... / - They even have mountains.
And also mountains. You can also taste all sorts...
- Of delicious food there. / - Everything tastes great.
- I'm looking forward to it... / - Yes.
Because she likes eating shows, and she likes to eat.
I do.
- She doesn't look like that. / - She's very thin.
- No. / - When I pick a destination...
I exclude places where the food doesn't seem good.
- Food is the most important. / - It's important.
We usually talk about how the trip was
before we start shooting.
I asked them, "How was it?"
They kept saying, "The food was so delicious."
- And "I want to go there now." / - All about the food.
I had the best ramen of my life.
I usually don't like vegetables.
I prefer meat.
I was shocked by the vegetable dishes...
- Were you surprised? / - And other dishes I ate there.
- The best vegetable of his life? / - It was the best.
Since we're talking about the best vegetable of his life,
I ate the best seafood of my life.
It was my first time eating this.
I want to appreciate it again by watching the video.
- The best seafood of your life. / - The best seafood.
- I'm looking forward to it. / - And...
We will reveal a little more.
There are 3 best night views
in Japan that are well known.
We'll introduce the night view.
The lavender garden...
- Is really famous in Hokkaido. / - That's right.
- We went there. / - You will see a better...
- Flower garden in full color today. / - Gosh.
- I'm looking forward to it. / - Your tour name is...
- Man Man Tour. / - That's right.
- Man Man Tour. / - What does that mean?
It means that we're confident...
- And relaxed. / - That's nice.
Also, we both like comic books.
Man Man Tour also means
"Comic books are the best."
That's perfect.
Goodness.
- Let's see it. / - Let's see the Hokkaido trip...
Of Man Man Tour.
(20 days before the departure)
- Should we start? / - 1, 2, 3.
- Hello, nice to meet you. / - Handsome and pretty.
I'm Kim Yuna of Jaurim.
I'm also Kim Hyungkyu's wife.
I'm the husband of Kim Yuna of Jaurim.
I'm also a dentist,
an entertainer and Yuna's manager.
I'm Kim Hyungkyu, nice to meet you.
(Dentist, entertainer, manager and husband)
That's right, he's her manager.
- That's right. / - Yes, that's me.
- It's been 12 years. / - We did a photo shoot...
- Before we got married. / - That's right.
(June 2006, Yuna and Hyungkyu became one)
Not many things changed after the wedding.
Except the fact that we live together.
Thankfully, we have similar preferences
in movies, music and comic books.
They are almost identical.
That's why...
It feels like I got married...
To the most similar friend to me.
It's fun because of that.
It's always fun.
I can't rest even when I sleep while
I'm working on an album.
- I keep thinking even when sleeping. / - The melodies.
When I spend several months like that,
I need something to liberate myself.
So I endure by thinking
that I can go on a trip after this.
We went to Tokyo in Japan for our first trip.
- We went to Gangneung in 2007. / - In summer.
It was the last trip we went by ourselves. After that...
- We never went by ourselves. / - Not once.
After Minjae was born, we went on a lot of trips...
- With him. / - If the child is young...
It's hard to go by yourselves leaving him behind.
- That's right. / - It's not easy.
It's good that you went on this trip.
We enjoyed it thanks to you.
We're going to leave...
- Minjae behind for this trip. / - That's right.
If the destination is too far...
- And we move too far... / - The time...
I think it will be hard to choose as a destination.
What place is cool and near?
A cool place would be...
Hokkaido in Japan?
(A cool and near place, Hokkaido)
- Wait a minute. / - Hokkaido.
We love Hokkaido but
we've only been there in winter.
- People usually go in the winter. / - We went in winter.
I think it will be charming in the summer too.
(Yuna really loves Hokkaido)
We went there a couple of times with my family.
- With the family. / - We only went there in winter.
(You can enjoy the white beauty of winter)
(And the freshness of summer in Hokkaido)
- We have a lot of memories there. / - Wait a minute.
- You've been there twice already? / - Yes.
Only in winter though.
I heard that...
Corn is delicious in summer.
Is corn the best vegetable of your life?
You'll find out when you watch it.
They have different kinds of corn from Korea.
They say it's really good. Also, the dairy products.
- That's right. / - Dairy products are famous there.
Ice cream is delicious there.
- Butter is also delicious. / - Yes, butter.
- I can only think about corn right now. / - Corns?
- I want to eat corn. / - In my case...
And potatoes.
- Hokkaido potatoes are really delicious. / - I heard.
- So... / - There's the Sapporo Beer Festival.
(Let's celebrate the Sapporo Beer Festival)
- Yes. / - Yes.
Let's drink in the daytime.
- In the daytime? / - Is it time for the beer festival?
- It's around this time of the year. / - It's around now.
- It's over now though. / - It's a summer beer festival.
You have to eat a lot of fresh seafood
when you're in Hokkaido.
You have to eat seafood.
We must eat seafood...
Go to the beer festival in the day.
There is so much to eat.
We're coming up with a schedule.
In some ways, my wife...
Always came up with a trip plan until now.
For this trip...
I'll try...
Planning the schedule.
Do you think you will do a good job?
I'll try.
Would you like that?
- Yes. Alright. / - Trust me.
- Good. / - Please plan a good trip.
- Good. / - They're not like a married couple.
- They're not. / - They're like friends.
They're like really old friends.
- Are those comic books? / - Yes, it's my room.
- Are they all comic books? / - Yes.
- He really is an aficionado. / - He really is.
I'm the trip planner of Man Man Tour,
Kim Hyungkyu.
I lost all the data I had.
I'll update the information...
From the comic books.
- Comic books? / - I picked...
The books I'm going to bring...
To the trip.
I got information from the comic books.
He really loves comic books.
Ta-da.
It's a travel guidebook to Hokkaido.
It's from spring, 2015.
Let me cook something delicious.
- Why is he suddenly cooking? / - What is he doing?
Minjae asked me to cook some dumplings.
So I was cooking dumplings.
- Now... / - He looks different in the gown.
- This is your clinic. / - Yes.
You weren't working in the clinic but doing that?
- It was after I dealt with the patients. / - Right.
I was having a break.
Based on the comic books we like,
we're going to have some farm experiences.
These are all 5-seater and 7-seater cars.
On the first day, we'll go drink beer.
I have a feeling that he's plan will be so good.
After drinking beer, we'll go to an observatory.
(During the break at work, he plans the trip)
After the observatory,
if we have enough time, we'll go to a bar.
It sounds like it's mostly about alcohol.
It's perfect. On the second day...
On the second day, we should rent a car.
Did you plan the whole trip alone?
We agreed that I plan the trip this time.
Since you're meticulous.
We'll observe the nature and...
(This is beyond perfect)
It's perfect. It's perfect.
(Man Man Tour, Hokkaido specialty)
(Beer festival)
(Night view)
(Robatayaki)
(Visit to a farm)
What's that? Was it a picture just now?
(Top 3 ramens in Hokkaido)
I want to go back.
When you want to go back,
it means you really had a great time there.
- Ta-da. / - Yes!
We're here.
- We arrived. / - It's Hokkaido.
I'm a little worried
the clothes I brought are not warm enough.
- Was it 21?? / - Will it be cold?
- It was very cool there. / - It was sweltering hot here.
- It was 40??here. / - There was a heat wave here.
It's cold there. It was so different there.
- Let's take the JR Train to the downtown. / - Good.
- I like the JR Train. / - Shall we?
- Let's go. / - Go, go.
That'd be better than taking a car. It takes 1 hour.
- It is. / - There's no traffic jam either.
There's a transportation card called Kitaca card.
You travel faster with it.
After the trip, you can keep it until the next trip.
You can also use it in convenience stores.
We take this JR Train for about 40 minutes.
- That's a quick trip. / - It is.
Let's go.
(It's their first trip alone in 12 years)
It must be nice to ride a train with your partner.
- Right? / - It was really nice.
After 40 minutes, you arrive at Sapporo Station.
- Sapporo. / - Sapporo Station.
We arrived at Sapporo Station.
The weather is so nice.
(The nice weather makes them feel good)
I shouldn't be like this.
- Anyway... / - The weather is nice.
- We're hungry, so... / - Mr. Planner. Yes.
Today, we're going to have a romantic day...
- And eat many different things. / - Romantic?
We're going to have a romantic day while eating a lot?
- Because we love food. / - We do.
- How romantic. / - First, we'll eat corn.
- Corn is the specialty here. / - The reason for our trip.
(Man Man Tour, Hokkaido specialty)
(Sapporo Station)
Do you see that thing on the left?
- It's so cool. / - There's a tower there.
It's the television tower.
It's the television tower of Sapporo.
Do you remember we once took a picture here?
We took a picture in front of the tower.
- We took a picture here. / - We did.
We took that not long after we got married.
- In winter. / - It was winter.
That was early 2007.
You guys look frighteningly the same as now.
You haven't changed.
There's a reason why we came here today.
- There's a reason why... / - Corn.
- Right. / - Corn.
One of the most delicious foods they have here is...
It's corn.
- Corn. / - Corn.
- So... / - There's a corn vendor.
- Hello. / - Hello.
It's somehow...
There are so many tasty-looking things. Look.
There's even a half and half deal.
(She orders in Japanese without any problem)
She looks like a Japanese.
(Half and half, $3.50)
(Potato and corn, $3)
(Grilled corn, $3)
(Total, $9.50)
I actually didn't understand why you would
travel all the way to Japan just for this.
However...
- It looks so good. / - It looks delicious.
- Look at this. / - Let me put this aside.
- Look at the color. / - It looks delicious.
You can tell it's good by the color.
In Korea, we also grow Chodang corn in Haenam.
I think Chodang corn and this corn are related.
It's sweet and crispy.
Let's start with the steamed corn first.
(Steamed corn first to taste the natural flavor)
- This one. / - Let's try...
- The steamed corn. / - We have...
- One each. / - Good.
I think we can make this into one. Hang on a second.
- Hang on. / - She started first.
(I'm already eating)
Is it good?
(She's expressing how good the corn tastes)
- Is it good? / - This is not corn.
Hang on a second. I haven't started yet.
- His face got bigger. / - He's feeling rushed.
Oh, my. I thought he was a squirrel.
- I was... / - My goodness.
- It was so good. / - Really?
I couldn't take my mouth off.
My gosh.
(He's falling because it's so tasty?)
It's amazing.
You can taste the juice of the corn.
It's crispy.
I can't take my mouth off it.
It's like a fruit. The skin is thin and it's crispy.
It's sweet.
Once you start eating it, you can't stop.
- You really like it. / - You spin it like a squirrel.
I don't think I'll be full after eating two of these.
(It's so good that one must eat at least two)
Where is your corn?
This corn is...
It's so shocking. It's a culture shock.
We have something that is called,
"sweet corn" in Korea as well.
But this is so delicious since it's fresh and local.
Shouldn't it be illegal to sell this?
- I want to eat more. / - He thinks it should be illegal.
Let's try this one.
- It's time to try grilled corn. / - Grilled corn.
Is it better steamed or grilled?
It looks so good.
I wonder what sauce they put on.
It's so good by itself.
The thin layer of soy sauce brushed on the corn
makes it nice and salty.
(What is that?)
What is that?
(What?)
Excuse me? Hello?
(She successfully stole the corn)
How is it?
It tastes like scorched rice.
Why?
- His eyes might pop out. / - He can't stop.
It's good, isn't it?
This one tastes different from the one we just had.
(He's enjoying the corn with his whole face)
- It's so good that his face is messy. / - It was so good.
When you eat something really good, you can't speak.
You're right.
It's a shame
you can't experience the taste through the screen.
The corn itself is so good.
When you bite it, it explodes in your mouth.
- Which is very refreshing. / - Exactly.
The burnt flavor from the sauce,
the flavor of scorched rice.
The flavors from the charcoal are combined together.
The sweet corn and the savory sauce...
I see why this is famous in Odori Park.
Since we had food, now we need to drink.
- Something cold. / - Something cold.
- Beer. / - We should drink beer.
- Something cold. / - Beer.
There's a beer festival in this park.
That sounds great.
It's so delicious.
If I travel there, I'll buy corn as soon as I get there.
(They walk to the beer festival from the corn vendor)
(It's the perfect weather for a walk)
The weather is perfect today.
It's the perfect weather for a walk.
(The weather is perfect for a summer walk)
It was really hot yesterday.
- I know. / - And now, I'm here...
Walking in a quiet park with my partner.
- How nice. / - It's so nice.
Look. Can't you feel it?
- Let me see. / - Can't you feel something?
This is where the snow festival
always takes place in winter.
Now there's a beer festival here.
It's become a beer festival now.
- If you take a look... / - It's beautiful.
Starting from here, there are beer companies...
- On each block. / - There are different companies.
- Exactly. / - Yes.
The Sung Sikyungs are all there right now.
I see Yangraks as well.
People who are like me and Yangrak.
(Sapporo Beer Festival, from mid-July to mid-August)
- We were there early... / - It's a different view.
- Right. / - That's the middle of the day.
- It is. / - It feels like a rock festival.
Hi.
- Beer brings peace to the world. / - It does.
- Beer is the best. / - It brings the people together.
- People are drinking a lot of beer. / - You're right.
What a beautiful and heartwarming scene.
I'm suddenly wondering what I've done with my life
instead of going to these places.
- Right. / - I'm getting angry.
We should have gone there.
How nice. The menu is written on the table.
There are...
- Many different kinds of beer. / - Before we begin...
As you know, this is Man Man Tour.
- Yes. / - So...
I've brought comic books.
- What? / - I've brought comic books.
Can't we order first?
Let's talk about...
- Why we have to drink beer. / - Can't we order first?
Look at her eyes.
There's a story about beer here.
- Take a look. / - Okay.
- Alright. / - I...
- Will order our menu. / - What?
- I don't get to choose? / - No.
Trust me.
I said I'd choose our menu,
so I went to order.
- She's doubtful though. / - She can't trust him.
- Make sure you order all of them. / - Trust me.
Don't worry be happy.
Hyungkyu's never once
ordered the food.
I usually do it for him.
She has...
- A developed palate. / - I seek out good food.
So I tend to trust her.
- I see. / - He just has to trust her.
If I trust her, delicious food is served.
(All he's doing is looking)
But I didn't know.
(He even asks for a recommendation)
(Oh)
I ordered it wrong.
- Oh, no. / - Why?
I ordered...
Two glasses of beer.
What?
Two glasses of this one.
Two glasses of this one too.
I got too worked up.
He should've ordered one each.
What's the problem? Just drink them all.
- I know. / - Tell me about it.
Why would he be concerned?
Just drink them up quickly.
- Right. / - It's not wrong.
- Just drink more. / - He placed the right order.
He did a good job.
- He'd have to make extra orders. / - Right.
(He's looking for the booth to pick up his order)
(He asks a festival staff member)
(Confused)
Extra...
(Isn't this the place?)
He looks very confused.
It's here.
(He finally finds the pick-up booth)
I ordered two glasses of this beer
and I was supposed to pick them up over there
but they didn't give me any.
(Will they be able to drink beer within today?)
(Waiting for her husband and beer)
It's taking long.
There he comes.
Just the sight of it...
It's beer.
How much are you going to drink? This is huge.
I brought these first because they were heavy.
- Right. / - Hold on a second.
- You'll come back quickly? / - Yes.
Do you always talk politely to each other like that?
Yes.
- We sometimes talk casually too. / - See?
They look good when they talk politely to each other.
By mistake...
I ordered four glasses of beer.
- By mistake? / - Yes, by mistake.
- Or did you want to drink them all? / - Not sure.
Drink some of this first.
Good.
- First. / - This one is...
- Just draft beer, right? / - Yes, it is.
- I ordered ice beer too. / - Ice beer.
Did I do a good job?
Good job.
Let's drink now.
It's good.
(Drinking together)
It's so amazing.
It has to refresh your head just like that.
- How refreshing. / - I know.
- It really was good. / - I bet.
(It's time to eat now)
- Are they bar snacks? / - Yes.
They look delicious.
- It's fried chicken. / - Is this chicken and beer?
Fried chicken is a must when you drink beer.
This one is my favorite.
- French fries. / - French fries.
French fries.
- Yuna looks a bit... / - French fries.
- Look at this. / - What do you say?
Half-dried squid.
- She approves of the squid. / - And...
- Your favorite, cucumber... / - Seasoned cucumber.
You also like vegetables.
That one's delicious.
It is.
It's amazing.
- It is. / - It has its own unique taste.
- It's good. / - It's quite addictive.
- How exciting. / - These are...
- Beans. / - Beans. Good.
- That's basic. / - Right.
- Good spread. / - What do you think?
- What do you think? / - Actually...
It's my first time having you serve a beer meal for me.
- Right. / - Because normally...
- I order food. / - Right.
You're not so satisfied with the snacks, are you?
I prefer non-fried ones
to the fried ones.
Most of them were my preferences.
I'll give you a score this way.
There are six kinds of dishes.
Out of six...
Out of six.
(Nervous)
(What's the score of Hyungkyu's first beer course?)
Out of six...
I'll give you 5.5.
5.5!
- That's a high score. / - Good.
You gave him a high score.
- In that sense... / - If this...
Had been sausages...
- Oh, right. / - Sausages.
- I'd have given you 10 out of 6. / - Sausages.
I missed the sausages.
Cheers.
(The considerate they are, the better the mood gets)
(Her husband's favorite)
It's delicious.
(She takes a bite of her favorite too)
I usually like vegetable bar snacks
but this seasoned cucumber is truly amazing.
It tastes savory like sesame oil and a bit salty too.
- It goes well with beer. / - I know, right?
- I highly recommend it. / - I love that dish.
- The cucumber is good. / - It's really good.
By the way,
aren't you reminded of someone?
- Our son. / - I'm reminded of...
Our son so much.
I'm reminded of Minjae.
- That's right. / - Of course...
- He must be doing fine. / - I know.
But it's our first time drinking beer together
in the daytime...
- Ever since our son was born. / - Especially on a trip.
Totally.
I'm envious of that.
Whether they have a child or not,
everyone is busy taking care of their lives.
But we have...
Created an unusual space within our daily lives
to do unusual things.
- It's... / - That's why traveling is good.
I know. That's what's good about going on a trip.
- I love it. / - Me too.
What do we do now?
(What's the next schedule of the Man Man Tour?)
- Mr. Planner. / - Yes.
I've searched on the books...
And this city is famous...
For its sparkling night view.
- It has a wonderful night view. / - Observatory?
There's an observatory on the 531m-high mountain
which is located in the southwest side of Sapporo.
- Do we have to climb the mountain? / - No.
Let's head to the observatory.
Good.
(She loves it)
- Let's finish the rest. / - Let's drink.
Let's do that.
Cheers.
Here's another interesting thing about the beer festival.
You get to have certain kinds of beer only sold there.
- It's limited. / - It's really fun...
- To try that limited beer. / - How refreshing.
It's so nice.
(Man Man Tour, night view)
(They travel about 20 minutes from the park)
We rode a shuttle bus...
And headed to the observatory.
- Alright. / - Gosh.
We've arrived here on the shuttle bus.
The air feels different here.
- It's refreshing. / - It really is.
It has the coolness
which you can feel in forests, don't you think?
This place is called,
Mt. Moiwa observatory.
Moiwa.
- Let's go. / - We've eaten a lot today...
So let's have a romantic time.
It's one of the three new best night views in Japan.
- Where did you hear that? / - I memorized it.
I picked it up from others.
- Let's go. / - Don't ask me for details.
Let's go in.
One of the three new best night views in Japan?
(And)
They do a vote on night views once every 3 years.
It was Hakodate instead of Sapporo
until the last survey.
But the night view of Sapporo placed 2nd
at the survey taken in 2015.
That's how it became the new best night view.
The survey is taken once...
- Every 3 years. / - Right.
Let's ride a cable car
and head to the top.
Okay.
- We must buy tickets for it. / - Tickets.
Usually, you have to pay $17 for an adult ticket.
But there are discount promotions.
You can find discount promotions via the app.
- Here's the discount for the cable car. / - Top three.
You can save 340 yen with this coupon.
- You should prepare it beforehand. / - Exactly.
It has different destinations.
- One goes to the mountain top. / - I know.
The other stops in the middle.
The price varies depending on the destination.
(Roundtrip ticket, $13.90 per person)
Thank you.
Nice.
It's so nice and wide.
It's here.
It's so roomy inside.
It's nice. Let's...
- How exciting. / - It's here.
(The back side has a better view)
If you go up...
It feels like you're going to a dreamland.
(Such a view lies ahead of you)
You know that feeling when
you're relieved of indigestion?
This makes me feel that kind of relief.
It's nice and refreshing.
(Living the moment and the view in pictures)
The cable car was taken in the photo.
The cable car.
(Man Man Tour in Hokkaido)
(Current location)
We've gotten off from the first one.
We have to wait here a bit...
And get on a mini cable car.
- You're transferring. / - You have to take...
- 2 cable cars. / - You take 2 cable cars.
It's so high up.
It must be pretty high.
I've never been to such a place before.
Me neither.
You've planned well.
Good job.
(They're fascinated by the scenery)
Look.
We're here. We're here.
(They're finally on the top of Mt. Moiwa)
It smells different here.
- It smells refreshing. / - I love this smell.
It's cool.
It's quite chilly up here.
(As the sun is about to go down, it's quite chilly)
It's really nice here.
Look at that.
(Fascinated)
There aren't as many people there as I thought.
We went there deliberately early.
- In the evening... / - It must be crowded then.
- Locals queue to go up. / - That's how it looks.
Look at that.
(Fascinated)
It looks so surreal.
Look over there.
It looks really amazing.
(The clouds slowly sail in the sky)
(The ridge touches the sky)
It's pretty nice in the daytime as well.
It has a clear and nice...
Panoramic view.
It's amazing.
(When the sun sets, Sapporo's night gets bright)
- We went there one hour ahead. / - It's so beautiful.
It looks so pretty.
It looks so romantic.
- It's romantic. / - What a great night view.
(The stars of Sapporo light up the entire city)
It's stunning.
We've seen the night views of different places.
- Since you like going to observatories. / - I do.
We always visit observatories, right?
Certain towers of different cities.
The one in Fukuoka is the most recent one we visited.
This place is much better.
We've also been up to the observatory of Sapporo.
- You're right. / - It was beautiful there too.
I totally get why this is
one of the three best new night views of Japan.
- It's wonderful. / - It's so colorful...
- And vivid. You see many colors. / - You're right.
It looks like twinkling stars.
- It's so shiny. / - This is amazing.
It's so sparkling.
The city lights shine like the stars in the night sky.
They're so shiny.
I love you more than all the lights.
You know I do, right?
(I love you more than all the lights)
Let's make a heart.
We should let others see it too.
Let's move on to our next spot.
It's so beautiful. It must be way prettier...
- In reality than on the screen. / - It was very beautiful.
(Man Man Tour, robatayaki)
They're our team
but it's all about eating and drinking.
- That's correct. / - Maybe you should've...
Taken Yangrak with you.
My mouth is watering so much now.
(His mouth is filled with saliva)
I wonder where they went among
so many good restaurants.
There must be a lot of good restaurants there.
(This is where their last schedule takes place)
It's so crowded here.
- We're back to reality. / - We're back to reality.
We're back down to reality. Ta-da.
(They're back in reality from the dreamy observatory)
I think people would come here to go to bars.
We're here alone without Minjae.
So...
- Where we can drink alcohol. / - Where we can drink.
Alright. Actually, the beer here is very delicious.
Does the place we're going now have good beer?
- It has seafood. / - We can't miss seafood here.
And crabs.
Crabs?
- Let's go eat crabs. / - Crabs?
- Is it this way? / - It's this way.
Let's go.
I searched the restaurants that the locals like.
- So it's popular among the locals. / - It's local.
- It looks delicious. / - I'm worried this restaurant might...
Get too famous after it's aired.
It will be.
This restaurant looks fancy.
This is the fantasy of every mom and dad.
The fantasy of every mom and dad.
Having the children go to bed and drinking alone.
Drinking alone abroad.
- And with a lot of great dishes. / - I know.
The grill looks amazing.
- It does. / - Look at that.
It looks so delicious.
It looks delicious.
I'm nervous.
You're nervous to see how delicious it will be, right?
Yes, I am.
Here it is. We've been waiting.
(Cold beer is served first)
It looks beautiful.
I'd like to take a picture.
Are you going to take pictures before we drink?
Can I take one picture?
You have a disagreement on this.
One wants to take pictures
while the other wants to drink first.
Let's clink the glasses and let me drink first.
I changed my mind. I have to drink too.
(Beer tastes the best right after it's served)
It's very creamy.
- It was a good idea to come here. / - It was.
How was it compared to the beer from the festival?
It was a little different.
Could you not drool when you speak?
- It was amazing. / - Really?
Stop rooting for their team.
The first dish must be sashimi.
- It's squid sashimi. / - Squid sashimi.
Squid.
- It's squid sashimi and innards. / - It's squid sashimi.
This must be squid innards.
- You can eat that? / - When we were there...
Squid was in season.
And this is grilled crab innards.
- The price... / - It was beautiful.
It was about $7.
It was 720 yen.
It has crab meat on top.
- It has a rich crab flavor. / - How do you like it?
It's savory and rich.
It has the taste of the deep ocean.
- I love crab innards. / - I love it too.
- It's served with crab meat. / - That costs just $7.40?
It looks delicious, doesn't it?
- It's a little... / - Look at this.
- I know. / - It looks so delicious.
- It does, doesn't it? / - Let's warm it a bit...
And before it's too late..
- Shall we turn off the stove? / - Let's turn it off.
It looks wonderful.
It smells so good.
She looks so happy.
- It has to be delicious. / - I know.
How is it?
(He doesn't like innards)
It tastes delicious!
Does it taste delicious?
It's good.
(He plucks up the courage and tries it)
Now is the time to drink beer.
(So this is how it tastes)
(This is what I wanted)
Squid sashimi.
Squid was in season then.
- It was sweet. / - Look at the cuts on it.
- It's really chewy, right? / - It is.
- Look at that. / - I can see...
The delicate touch of the chef.
This is mountain wasabi.
- It's white. / - Yes, it's white.
- It's a different kind of wasabi. / - I see.
- That wasabi was delicious too. / - How is it?
(She tastes it with a little bit of wasabi)
Are you thinking?
- How many points would you give? / - It's sweet.
It's the best squid sashimi I've ever tried.
Is it that good?
- Was it the best one you've tried? / - It was so good.
What's important hasn't...
- Come yet. / - It must be the innards.
- It's sweet. / - It is, isn't it?
Let me try the innards.
The innards are slightly frozen.
I'm a little scared to try the innards.
Let me put a little more wasabi on it.
The innards are the best.
I've never tried that.
(Surprised)
Her face tells how good it is.
- Suddenly... / - It tastes great.
- It's so good. / - I know.
- I love this dish. / - Do you?
The squid innards is amazing.
- Is it good? / - It's the king.
- King of kings? / - King of kings.
- This was served frozen. / - You're right.
It's tasty when it's thawed.
When it's thawed, it's creamy.
It's creamy.
- It's like the foie gras of the ocean. / - It is.
That's a great way to put it.
It's not fishy. It has a very rich flavor.
How is it?
You're dancing suddenly.
It's so good.
- This is so good. / - So it's tasty.
It was very tasty.
(Steak and grilled onions are served)
Onions.
I want to try that.
- It looks good. / - It's beautiful.
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
- So it's tasty. / - It was very tasty.
It looks delicious.
(Steak and grilled onions are served)
Onions.
- Onions are just onions though. / - Look at the butter.
- That onion was... / - Onions taste all the same.
- Awesome. / - It looks beautiful.
(Grilled onion, $5.40)
What should I start with?
(Steak, $20.30)
- That looks delicious. / - It looks good, doesn't it?
- That looks so good. / - This is why you get fat there.
That meat...
- You can't help it. / - Was very tender.
That butter...
- You love meat. / - I do.
It's tender and juicy.
It's so juicy.
- People with bad teeth... / - I want meat now.
It's good for old people who don't have good teeth.
You can even cut it with your teeth. It's well cooked.
This steak is...
One of the best three steak dishes I've ever had.
- Really? / - Yes, it's that good.
I could lose myself when I eat this.
It's delicious.
I'm curious about this onion.
- The onion. / - I wonder if...
- The onion tastes good. / - You got shocked, right?
- Why? / - You'll see.
- That tastes good? / - That's the onion.
The butter on the onion melted. Look.
- It did. / - Where did it go?
It's inside the onion.
I have a feeling that this onion will be so tasty.
This is not an onion.
- It's not an onion? / - It's not, right?
What is this?
Does it not taste like what we imagine?
- No, it doesn't. / - No.
It's like I see an onion in a forest...
And it's harvesting itself.
Saying I should eat it.
"Eat me!"
- "Please eat me." / - The two of them...
Have the same sense of humor.
She must like his jokes.
I guess it's not funny to others.
- What made you laugh so hard? / - I don't get it.
Was the onion joke so funny?
It was so delicious. You'll feel the same.
You're so meant to be.
- I don't like vegetables. / - You don't. You hate them.
This onion is the best onion I've ever eaten in my life.
(It's the best onion he has ever eaten in his life)
- What's so funny? / - It's still funny for me.
- We'd like to laugh too. / - You guys are weird.
Tomorrow...
We're going to meet them.
- Is it far away? / - We'll rent a car.
- A rental sounds good. / - We'll rent a car...
And truly experience Mother Nature.
- That's our plan. / - I'll be looking forward to it.
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
- Man Man Tour. / - It was such a fun day today.
Let's do this.
It looks so delicious. They are delicious.
If we mostly ate yesterday,
today is about experiencing Mother Nature.
It'll be even cooler.
I can't wait.
This is the farm.
So pretty.
(Fresh air, beautiful views)
- Wow. / - What is that?
(With the soulmate)
The rain...
It's nice when it rains.
It's nice when it doesn't too.
But with this wonderful rain...
I love it that it's raining today.
I liked the trip plan.
And I like my trip partner as well.
Plus the weather was great.
Everything was great.
I want to come back on a clear day.
(Their perfect trip continues)
(Day 2 in Hokkaido begins early)
This is the second day, right?
- Yes, it is. / - We rented a car.
(Near Sapporo Station, 8 a.m.)
It's a great morning.
- I'm sleepy. / - But I'm a little sleepy.
Yesterday, it wasn't a Man Man Tour...
- Food Food Tour. / - It was a Food Food Tour.
It was all about eating yesterday.
Today, we're going to nature.
- Nature? / - We'll freshen our eyes.
In order to do that,
we can't walk.
That's why we will rent a car.
It'll be confusing driving on the opposite side.
- You can easily get used to it. / - It's confusing...
In the beginning but you get used to it soon.
- So this is... / - This is a beginner sign in Japan.
It's magnetic and you can attach it here.
- Beginner! / - Good.
- Right. They have that in Japan. / - Yes, they do.
This is for beginners and there's a sign for seniors.
- There's a senior sign. / - A senior sign.
It's okay to get lost...
- When you have that sign. / - That's right.
At first, I was surprised
to see different signs on the cars.
One of the things you've wanted to do here is
to go to a farm in Hokkaido.
You can see and feed
the animal in nature.
You can milk the cow yourself too.
There's a cheese workshop you can participate in...
With the milk you got.
It sounds like there are many activities to do.
It looks nice.
First, we went to a farm.
There were many people who brought their kids.
It must be a great place to go with children.
- Yes. / - Yes, it'd be very nice.
(Here, you can feed animals and make dairy products)
You can feed the animals there.
Yes, you can make butter and ride horses there.
There are many activities you can do with your kids.
It's a great place to visit with children.
(Man Man Tour, visiting a farm)
We traveled quite a long distance.
It was about 300km.
She's right. We traveled a long way.
- Now... / - We're almost there.
We're almost there. Now, I can see a forest.
Look.
- Look at this road. / - I know.
It's so nice.
You come out of the city...
- And there are wide fields. / - It's completely different.
- It's like a picture from a fairytale book. / - I know.
- This is... / - It's just like how we imagined.
- An amazing view. / - It's the nature of Hokkaido.
Such a place reminds you of your children.
- It did. / - It totally did.
It doesn't look like it at all.
It's just the two of them.
(After a long ride on the endless road)
We've arrived at the farm.
(They arrive at the farm in nature)
I think we should go this way first.
Let's see what's here. You can see small animals.
- It's a baby goat. / - Look, it's following him.
- Nice to meet you. / - Hello.
- It must be hungry. / - Look at it wag its tail.
It's a goat but it's like a puppy.
You're right. It's so cute.
(Yuna gives milk to the baby goat)
It's so cute.
It must be really hungry.
It was drinking very fast.
It was wagging its tail while drinking.
- My gosh. / - It's almost...
- There you go. / - It's like a puppy.
- It drinks really fast. / - Look at it wagging its tail.
It's like someone drinking a glass of beer bottoms up.
- It's drinking really fast. / - It has a big appetite.
You should try too. There's not much left.
Alright. Is it sleeping?
It's wagging its tail.
They feed it 4 times a day instead of its mother.
- It finished it. / - It finished it.
- It's so cute. / - It's going to him.
(The baby goat goes back to the instructor)
Thank you. Would you like to try holding it?
- Really? / - It's really like a puppy.
I want to try holding it too.
- How adorable. / - It's so cute.
It's well-behaved.
- It's so nice. / - It's very...
- Friendly to people. / - I can feel its heart.
- Its heart beats. / - Does it?
What is its name?
- It's Meme. / - Meme?
- Meme. / - Hi, Meme.
Meme.
- Meme. / - Meme.
All the goats there are called Meme.
- All the goats are Meme? / - Yes.
When the goats grow up, they graze the goats.
Then it's hard to call every one of them if they have
different names.
When they're all called Meme,
you can call all of them at once.
- So this one is Meme no. 187. / - You're right
- It's so cute. / - Meme, nice to meet you.
- It was so cute. / - It's looking at him.
It's amazing that it's so calm in his arms.
My goodness.
(It's time to say good-bye to Meme)
Thank you.
- Bye, Meme. / - Meme.
- Meme. / - Meme is wagging its tail.
- It was so cute. / - It's so well-behaved.
I'm so jealous.
Gosh, look at this.
It's a cattle shed.
This is where the milk cows are.
- You can milk the cows here. / - Milking.
You can experience cow milking here.
The cows look so cool.
- Look at its eyes. / - The cows look great.
Its eyes look just like Hyungkyu's eyes.
I felt like it was my family. I couldn't help but feed it.
- They look so similar. / - These are goats.
They are a bit...
They're so adorable.
Meme, let's go.
Oh, my.
You don't lead the goats
but you follow the goats.
- You follow the goats. / - Is that the rule?
That's the rule. You have to follow the goats.
Come this way.
(Following Meme, they ended up somewhere)
- Look at that. / - Meme.
- It's amazing. / - We climbed up here.
There are people flying kites.
- There are so many kites. / - Shall we go that way?
(They have a good view of the whole farm here)
(The whole world seems to be colored green)
- Look over there. / - It's amazing.
- It's really nice. / - That place looks really nice.
- It does. / - You'd find inner healing there.
How do you like it here?
- Honestly, it was fascinating. / - What was?
I can't believe I took a walk with a goat.
- I couldn't believe it. / - You have never...
You have never done that in your life, right?
We took a walk with a goat.
Now...
- Kim Yuna of Jaurim. / - Yes.
You said you were going to yodel for me.
You're good at yodeling.
(On their way to the farm this morning)
- Yodeling equals Kim Yuna. / - Is that right?
Let's think about it when we get to the farm.
Really? Will his wife sing for him?
It must be nice that his wife is a singer.
(Yodeling)
(Surprised)
Shepherds yodeled on top of the mountain
in order to communicate with people.
(Yodeling)
That's so nice.
(Please hurry and sing after me)
You have to raise your voice higher.
(The new students of the yodeling class)
(Yodeling)
She sounds so different to us.
You have to raise your voice higher.
I shouldn't have asked to do this.
You have to put an emphasis on this part.
It feels like she's the boss and you're her employee.
(I will teach you with love and care until you succeed)
(Loud)
You're so loud.
It seems like he's sleepy.
- My eardrums. / - I'm sorry.
That's good.
(He tries it again properly)
(Whatever)
I don't think that alcohol was the only thing they had.
(As long as we're happy, nothing else matters)
(They leave the farm with memories of yodeling)
Let's go.
- Yuna is driving now. / - That's right.
(She looks uncomfortable)
This is uncomfortable.
(Revving)
I'm at the stage where I'm getting to know the car.
Honey...
Don't drive too fast.
I think Yuna drives more roughly.
(Takes a look)
This is scary.
Maybe I should have driven.
(Anxious and restless)
My wife and I are similar in many ways.
One thing different is our driving styles.
I keep safety first enough to make people...
- Frustrated. / - You put safety first.
Even if we are tight on time...
I say, "Safety is the most important thing."
I don't change lanes.
I think there isn't a big difference
if we drive on this lane or that lane.
But my wife drives roughly.
She drives like a rocker, just a bit.
I didn't know he said this.
- Singers are rough. / - That's right.
- We always have a lot of schedules. / - That's right.
(Yuna drives without hesitation)
- It's raining slightly. / - Yes.
It's raining slightly.
It's so nice that it's raining slightly.
It's nice.
Do you know the song, "Come Rain or Come Shine?"
Of course, I know it.
Nobody's loved you
(Her sweet voice is added to the rainy scenery)
(Looks at her sweetly)
- It's nice. / -  Happy together
I love it so much.
Is she also singing for you when she's driving?
That's really nice.
- It was coincidental. / - That's right.
(Come rain or come shine)
(High as a mountain, deep as a river)
It was perfect for that day.
(The wife who couldn't help her musician spirit)
It is a song saying that I will love you come rain...
Or come shine.
(She was reminded of "Come Rain or Come Shine")
There will be happy and unhappy days while we live.
It could rain or sun might shine.
The song is about that.
Turn right after 400m.
(Embarrassed)
- I'll just be quiet and drive. / - It's okay. It was nice.
We were creating a nice mood
and the GPS suddenly shouted at us.
(He's blaming the GPS for no reason)
- Like, "Focus on driving." / -  Days may be...
Cloudy or sunny
- Turn right. / - Yes, ma'am.
(Laughing)
The GPS stopped us...
When we were in the middle of singing.
- It told us to drive. / - It must have been listening.
(It was a good interjection to focus on driving)
I want to see a beautiful garden or forest.
They prepared thoroughly.
- The lavender season is over. / - Yes.
The lavender season is over in July.
- We covered the lavender season. / - Yes.
- Lee Gookju went there. / - That's right.
They went there to take the best photos of their life.
They made videos.
It's not a lavender garden...
- But we'll see a flower garden. / - If it's possible...
I want to see a garden with flowers in full bloom.
Won't there be a farm nearby there?
(Man Man Tour, Shikisai No Oka)
(2 hours and 20 minutes by car to Shikisai No Oka)
It takes 2 hours and 20 minutes by car?
- We drove for long. / - Yes.
We drove over 2 hours that day.
The way there was also nice.
We're here.
You went through a lot.
We're here at...
- Shikisai... / - Shikisai No Oka.
- We're finally here. / - Yes.
I researched about it.
It says flower garden view here.
The flowers bloom...
- Starting from May to October. / - Yes.
There are several kinds of flowers.
- I researched it. / - Good job.
Tulips start to bloom...
- In May. / - Let's go and check it out.
It seems like she's your boss
and you're her employee.
I'm looking forward to what kind of flowers there are.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Wait a minute.
I need to take these.
- That's right. / - Why don't you take it after?
Are you taking these right now?
I have to take it with me right now...
- To get information. / - That's right.
I always take pamphlets with me of a certain spot
whenever I go to another country.
I keep them.
If you collect those...
- lt's nice to see them later. / - It's fun.
- You feel proud, and it's nice. / - Of course.
Look at this.
It's a travel guide.
I brought the one from 2015.
I still have it.
The 2015 travel guide is useless now.
It only takes up luggage space.
We don't need
old pamphlets.
The information changes.
The roads change.
It doesn't help at all.
He's just collecting them.
- It's a personal goal. / - That's right.
- They're memories. / - It's to satisfy my own desire.
I think there's a flower garden here already.
I don't think...
These gardens are special.
Of course, we have already seen a lot of...
- Flower gardens like these. / - In our neighborhood.
- In our neighborhood? / - In our neighborhood...
- Apartment building. / - Is that true?
There are gardens like these in our apartment.
I was a little disappointed at the entrance.
Do people come here to see this?
It feels like a failure
seeing just this.
Failure?
- The weather isn't nice. / - That's right.
Let's go in.
This is interesting.
This is interesting. This is a little interesting.
(He's showing interest in other things)
This is a little...
I want to take photos but I don't have any hands.
- Let's get on the bus first. / - Okay.
- It's because... / - He wanted to take a photo.
Yes.
- Yuna is cold at times like that. / - Yes.
- She didn't take photos. / - I had a lot of stuff.
So I couldn't take photos for him.
We're on a bus being pulled by a tractor.
I like things like this.
Did I plan wrong?
We don't know yet.
Look at the top of that hill.
That looks beautiful.
We'll go up there on this bus...
Where we can see it properly.
We're moving.
The tractor bus will lead you there
if you pay around $5.10.
There must be something.
I'm looking forward to it.
- I'm looking forward to it. / - Wait a minute.
I know what you're talking about
since we're on the hill.
It's so big.
(What does the flower garden look like?)
Look at that.
It's so pretty.
How did they make that?
(Located in Biei with flowers for every season)
- There are sunflowers. / - You can take the best photos.
- Photos of your life. / - Yes, of your life.
This is the amazing part.
It's so pretty.
(Impressed)
This is really amazing.
(A vast flower garden is spread endlessly)
- It was a surprising view. / - It's like a picture.
- The colors are amazing. / - Isn't it amazing?
(Happy)
- How did they make this? / - This is my first time...
- Coming here. / - That's right.
It's a very surprising view.
Different flowers are planted...
- According to their rows. / - There are lavenders.
- I think it's really big. / - It's really big.
(The big carpet is embroidered with flowers in line)
- It's a giant's carpet. / - You're right.
Different flowers bloom for each season.
They also take care of different flowers.
- They have different sections. / - That's wonderful.
(They arrive at the viewpoint of the flower garden)
Have you ever seen flowers planted
on this large a scale?
This is my first time.
- Right? This is also amazing. / - What I said earlier...
- I would like to apologize... / - Apologize quickly.
About it being like my apartment.
- It feels like my eyes... / - It's colorful.
Are wide-open.
It feels exactly like that.
(You can't forget photos in front of an amazing view)
(Focused)
I think it will be nice to go with your lover.
A married couple special is surely filled with love.
(We've never seen a more beautiful garden)
(We'd like to apologize for enjoying this alone)
- I can't explain what I'm seeing... / - Yes.
- With words. / - We can't capture it in photos.
- For this trip... / - Yes.
I rented out the whole place.
(They are the only ones there in the large garden)
I rented it. No one is here.
- That's right. / - Yes.
- No one is here. / - We rented the place.
- No one is here. / - Yes.
No one is here except us.
It was raining a little bit,
so we were the only ones there.
- That's so amazing. / - It was so surprising.
I liked the rain.
- Yes. / - It's like a painting.
- It's so pretty. / - It's unbelievable.
The weather helped them to enjoy the place.
- How is that possible? / - It's so beautiful.
This looks like it's CG.
- Isn't it strange and unrealistic, right? / - Yes.
I think you wouldn't want to leave this place.
This is amazing. It's a spectacle.
It really is a spectacle.
It's nice when it rains.
And it's still nice when it doesn't rain.
But it's amazing since it's raining.
I like it so much because it's raining.
Everything is so nice. It's nice when it's sunny.
The view and the colors would have been brighter
but you wouldn't know the view when it rains.
I think it felt different that way.
Honestly, I think it's better because of the rain.
- It's more picturesque. / - Yes.
Since we took a walk...
- We're hungry, right? / - I'm hungry.
Let's go to the next spot.
- Will we eat something? / - We will eat something.
- Good. / - We'll eat something we like.
- Let's go quickly. / - What could that be?
- Since we're going there... / - He's not working again.
- Patients are waiting for him. / - No, that's not true.
I was doing that during my spare time.
I don't think that's true.
I think it will be okay if we ate ramen.
Yuna doesn't like ramen or instant noodles that much.
But we have a unique memory...
About ramen.
I think it will be okay...
If we ate ramen for one meal...
For my own personal desire.
A course for you? That's dangerous.
My wife doesn't like ramen.
But you went to a place where they only sold ramen?
- Yes. / - He likes that kind of food.
(Man Man Tour, 1 of the 3 best ramens in Hokkaido)
- It's quite far. / - Yes, it's far.
It was a little distant from where we were.
The distance is quite far.
(Darkness has come to Asahikawa already)
Asahikawa is the second biggest city in Hokkaido
after Sapporo.
That's why this place...
- Is getting popular. / - That's right.
I saw that there was a...
- JR line here in Asahikawa. / - Yes, it's here.
- We could come here by the JR Train... / - Right.
- From Sapporo. / - Right.
- It's nice. / - It's perfect.
- It feels so nice... / - Yes.
(The chilly weather reminds you of warm soup)
Since it's raining.
- I like it better this way. / - Yes.
It's raining. This is the place.
- Is this the place? / - That's right.
It has 70 years of tradition.
I'm really looking forward to it.
- Let's go inside. / - Okay.
- Let's go inside. / - Let's go inside.
Excuse me.
Yes.
- Hello. / - Hello.
That place must be delicious.
- This place was really delicious. / - Sikyung knows...
- When he sees the entrance. / - I know.
(A meal of ramen for Hyungkyu)
(The noodles are so firm, it can't be compared)
(This place has a special secret broth)
(1 of the 3 best ramens, Asahikawa ramen)
What's the signature dish?
That's why I brought a comic book...
- About ramen. / - Can't we order first?
We have to see this before we order.
- He's starting again. / - We have to see this.
- They're going to fight here. / - We have to see this.
We have to see this.
(Why did he take out a comic book suddenly?)
Let's see.
(Hyungkyu's study, before departure)
- There are so many comic books. / - That's right.
This is a very important book.
- "What is Ramen?" / - What kind of book is that?
- There is. / - That's so interesting.
It's a comic book about ramen.
It has a lot of good information.
I really should take it with me.
- If you see here... / - Yes.
(What are the 3 best ramens in Hokkaido?)
There are three best ramens...
- In Hokkaido. / - Yes, there are three best ramens.
Miso ramen in Sapporo.
Shio ramen in Hakodate,
and shoyu ramen in Asahikawa.
These 3 ramen are
the 3 best ramen in Hokkaido.
They also have shoyu ramen.
- Let's order that. / - That's famous.
- Is that famous there? / - Yes.
- I did some research. / - Yes.
There's a point to focus...
On this Asahikawa ramen.
If you see here...
Can't we order first and talk while they cook?
Can't you order quickly?
Yuna should have made a fuss.
It tastes better when you do this.
Can't we order first and talk while they cook?
- Okay. / - My stomach is making sounds.
I'll order shoyu ramen.
- Should we order one each? / - That sounds nice.
Shoyu ramen and shio ramen.
- Shio ramen? / - Yes.
- Is he cooking in front of you? / - Yes.
Is that the kitchen?
Asahikawa shoyu ramen...
Doesn't have one type of broth.
- They don't use just one ingredient. / - Right.
They mix meat broth and seafood broth...
- And make it. / - Do they use double ingredients?
In other words,
it's a combination of meat and seafood.
- It's like the combination of us. / - That's right.
- The noodles are important. / - You have to slurp it up.
They make the noodles by hand there.
- With two types of broth... / - And soy sauce.
They use meat and seafood like for Jinju cold noodles.
- That looks good. / - It was really good.
(He smacks his lips)
(Shoyu ramen, $7.70)
(Shio ramen, $7.70)
Usually, there's 30% moisture in noodles
but they have less than 20% here, so it's chewy
and the broth is absorbed by the noodles.
- Thank you for the food. / - Thank you for the food.
- I'm going to try the soup first. / - That's right.
(You should try the soup first when you eat ramen)
It has a really refreshing taste.
(Refreshed)
- The weather is a little chilly... / - It suits the weather?
Because of the rain.
It would be perfect for a hangover cure.
This one is good.
- This one is good. / - Yes.
I heard that there was a secret method to the broth.
(Shoyu ramen is the best dish)
They made the soup with seafood broth,
pork broth and pork fat.
It has a deep taste.
They must have done a lot of research.
- Let's try the noodles now. / - But...
- I'm going to try the noodles. / - Okay.
(Slurping)
(I can't believe this taste)
The flavor has depth.
- The noodles are also delicious. / - Yes.
(He sucks it in without even breathing)
- It was really good. / - I'm hungry.
- Shall I make some instant noodles? / - Yes.
You're saying that the noodles are firm, right?
- That's not enough to explain it. / - It's bouncy.
- Is it bouncy? / - Yes, it's bouncy.
Noodles should be chewy.
You can only eat those noodles...
- When you're there, right? / - You're right.
- It's raw noodles. / - You can't imitate that.
It has great texture.
Is it good?
- It's really good. / - Thank you.
It's really good.
(They're really into it)
Isn't it delicious?
Hokkaido, Asahikawa shoyu ramen.
They put meat and seafood broth
and added fat from meat.
- Is that in Korean? / - They understood.
Bravo.
(What's he doing?)
- They're saying different things. / - That's too much.
(Did he understand?)
I got complimented because of a comic book.
It wasn't a waste to bring the comics.
I'm going to eat again.
I thought you didn't like it.
This was either the best or second best ramen...
- I ever had in my life. / - Is this the best again?
It's really good.
Why did they experience so many bests?
- This is interesting. / - Yes?
When we eat noodles in Korea,
we learn that it's rude...
- To make slurping noises. / - Yes.
But in Japan,
you have to make sounds when you eat noodles
to express how good it is.
- You're doing a good job. / - You're doing well too.
- Is it good to make sounds in Japan? / - Yes.
(The standard of the standard)
We did a lot of non-daily experiences today.
How is this restaurant objectively?
Don't make me talk right now.
He said, "Don't make me talk."
This is the last.
(He takes the last sip)
- Put it on your head. / - Goodness.
(Just like Sikyung did)
(He takes the last sip)
The soup...
He finished to the last drop.
After I finished it...
- "Gratitude" was written on it. / - It does.
You can only see that if you eat everything.
- It's not salty. / - No.
- This is different. / - Yes.
It's different from other ramen.
Stop showing us. What is this?
I'm having a hard time because I'm drooling.
(It's as if his salivary gland is broken)
The Man Man Tour is really something.
It's a culinary tour.
That was great. Thanks to you, I had a great ramen.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
- See? The sign looks delicious. / - Does it?
- The sign looks tasty. / - Yes, the sign does.
How do you know just by looking at the sign?
- Alright. / - Before we go back to the hotel...
Since we ate a lot,
shall we take a walk?
- What do you think? / - Are we going for a walk?
Are we going to one more place?
Well, you know...
You're acting really suspicious.
- It's a surprise. / - She got you.
- She noticed. / - Goodness.
- I guess he hasn't done it a lot. / - He's unskilled.
(Toward the end of their Hokkaido trip)
(The final destination of this trip is Asahikawa River)
Where is this? It looks so nice.
We're at a riverside where you can see
the Asahikawa bridge, which represents the area.
(It's a quiet parking lot where they can be alone)
- Riverside. / - It's so...
- It's wide open. / - It's nice.
Exactly. It's...
If the weather was nice,
I was going to take you to a place
where we can see the stars.
- But it rained today. / - I see.
- Why see the stars so suddenly? / - Well, you know.
Hyungkyu prepared something. Goodness.
- This reminds me of the Hangang. / - Exactly.
- We had dates there. / - We did.
- At night, after my radio show... / - It wasn't the radio.
- After the show... / - Yes.
- We'd meet at Hangang. / - Yes, we did.
- Then go home. / - We did.
- So about that... / - Yes.
Why isn't he giving her the gift?
(Hyungkyu opens the trunk carefully)
(Goodness)
- He prepared something. / - No.
Awesome.
What is it?
Ta-da.
(Her eyes are wide open)
- What's this? / - This is...
(Hyungkyu turns the light on)
- Gosh. / - What is it?
He prepared something cute.
(The trunk is full of their memories)
- When did you prepare this? / - Pictures?
I printed some pictures.
That's fantastic.
(Their memories from their old trips)
(And the new memories from this trip)
Thank you.
(Before they departed from the ramen place)
- I'll go use the bathroom. / - Okay.
(While she's waiting for Hyungkyu)
You did it then.
I have to decorate.
(He prepared a small event)
She didn't know that was in the car?
She didn't know because it was in the back.
You wouldn't look there.
Gosh, he's taking it again.
He loves taking photos.
- He loves taking pictures. / - Yes.
What should I do?
- What do we do? Here? / - Let's go in.
- Should I take my shoes off? / - No, keep them on.
- Go in like this. / - I'm so touched.
- It's like they're playing house. / - But she likes it.
(Yuna claps because she's embarrassed)
- What do you think? Isn't this fun? / - It's so cozy.
- It's a lot of fun. / - I feel like a kid.
We don't like surprises.
So even on our wedding anniversary...
We just go out to eat.
That's what we normally do.
Thinking that he put up all the pictures
and lights...
I found him really cute.
- Awesome, right? / - Look at this.
What's this picture?
These are our old pictures.
These are...
- From this trip. / - This is from yesterday.
- This is Sapporo. / - Yes.
Goodness. This is Sapporo.
It's nice to have the old and the new pictures
together.
- Yes. That's very pretty. / - That's early 2007.
- Early 2007. / - We went on a trip...
- With our parents. / - Right.
- That's why we went there... / - This one.
- Yesterday. / - That's why we took this.
- Here. / - It's fun.
Even though we don't have the same composition...
- But it feels the same. / - It's nice.
Yes, that's nice.
You can go back on your 20th anniversary.
- Yes. / - That's right.
Like I mentioned before...
This trip was so great...
And also it was a different experience.
I thought it was weird because
we haven't been on a trip together...
- In over 10 years. / - Over 10 years.
This was the first time...
- After Minjae was born. / - Right.
We drove and talked
for an hour and a half to two hours.
I think this trip will be...
- A very memorable one. / - Right.
From now on, Man Man Tour...
Yes, Man Man Tour. Can we do this often?
Yes. For all our lives.
- That's good. / - We'll do it.
- Let's do well. Let's go. / - Let's do it.
(A trip with a partner like a friend and like a lover)
I realized again that
there is a match made in heaven.
Because you two share jokes,
you have the same sense of humor,
and that looks so great.
- I want to ask you something. / - They're all married...
Except us two.
- You're right. / - You two should get married.
- Get married. / - You can marry each other.
(Don't look far for your fate)
- Goodness. / - I became a bit envious.
- I'm a little jealous. / - Yes.
- You look good together. / - We'll have you get married...
As we end this show.
Actually, I didn't feel jealous last week.
But I feel jealous this week.
You must've felt really great about Hokkaido.
- Because it's been 12 years. / - Yes, it did.
This place is really great for couples
because it is an area with vast nature.
Standing before nature, humans seem very small.
Though we are small,
when we're with our partners and family,
we can rely on each other. We can realize that.
So I think it's a great destination for married couples.
You can taste delicious food and you can relax.
- I highly recommend it. / - Yes.
Hyungkyu, you married a great woman.
When you were taking a selfie,
she left without taking one for you.
Weren't you angry?
No. Because...
That happens so often.
- He's used to it. / - Yes.
He took a selfie after
getting the surprise ready for his wife.
The look on his face.
After 5 years, she's going to say, "I don't believe this."
- No, she'll understand. / - I don't believe this.
Let's check out the cost.
This is what we want to know.
- It's that horrific time. / - The total travel cost...
Excluding the airfare.
Hyungkyu, how much was it?
For 2 nights and 3 days in Hokkaido,
the Man Man Tour spent...
- A total amount of... / - Total amount.
- Per person. / - Per person.
$313.
- That's similar. / - $313.
- That's less than we thought. / - It's not as expensive.
- That's right. / - You even rented a car.
- We spent only on food. / - Right.
We spent money on nothing else.
- That's right. / - We looked at nature.
A couple of 30 years received luxury spa treatment.
- That's what they did. / - Yes. And the snap tour.
But this couple is younger and they were economical,
so they saved money.
Alright. Please stand up and say your last words.
Sook, why don't we...
- Open our eyes together? 1, 2, 3. / - What?
(Scary)
- There. / - They look the same.
- That was great. / - Hokkaido will make your eyes...
Pop with its food and nature.
Visit Hokkaido that's like a place in a cartoon.
Are you ready to vote?
Those who will go to Hokkaido
and enjoy a trip according to the Man Man tour,
please vote.
(A romantic getaway for married couples)
(What will the judges choose?)
Will it be the Balu Tour in Kota Kinabalu?
Will it be the Man Man Tour in Hokkaido?
What will the judges choose?
(Kota Kinabalu vs. Hokkaido)
The difference isn't much.
I think the first digit will be the same.
(What will be the result?)
- I'm nervous. / - Goodness.
- Why am I so nervous? / - It's making me nervous.
Why am I nervous?
It's the same first digit.
- It's 70... / - The first digit is the same.
- No! Go up. / - Come on.
(Which team will be the final winner?)
(Kota Kinabalu wins)
What a shame.
- It's okay. / - So close.
- Good job. / - Yes.
I was so surprised.
Please tell us how you feel.
It was a meaningful trip for our 30th anniversary.
- Yes. / - I was happy to see...
That Hyeonsuk enjoyed it more.
It was only...
- A two-vote difference. / - They did a good job.
- They must be upset. / - No.
Thank you.
They're so happy.
- You're the best. / - I'm serious.
They went through so much trouble and all...
But you didn't do anything special.
All you did was eat corn.
- We did a lot. / - All you did was eat corn.
- They drank beer and gave milk... / - We prepared...
To goats. It wasn't memorable.
- Congratulations. / - Hyejung, how was it?
- Don't you want to go on a trip? / - Honestly...
It made me really want to go on a trip
after watching the videos.
- I will sit here next time. / - That's right.
- You should be a trip planner. / - I want to plan...
A trip that people would really like to go.
We will go to Jeju-do after a long time next week.
- Jeju-do? / - I'm so excited.
For the past 2 weeks,
we saw the trip of a 31-year couple...
- And a 13-year couple. / - A 13-year couple.
- We're 30 years! / - It will be a match between...
- Idols of 21 and 7 years. / - They must all know.
Please look forward to the Idol special.
We will come back next week.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
Thank you.
(Next episode)
Wan Jun Tour!
It's a stream that old people enjoy.
We're eating such good food.
I know this neighborhood really well.
(Baekho Tour with JR)
We have to eat this.
Oh, what am I to do?
This is my first time planning and going on a trip.
I was so happy.
(Battle Trip)
("HANN" by (G)I-DLE)