(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Hwijae, Jooe of MOMOLAND)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Nice to see you again. The special host for today
is Jooe.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
Hello.
I'm Jooe of MOMOLAND.
I'll be a great host with the spirit
of a 20-year-old girl.
How are you going to show that spirit?
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
("BBoom BBoom" by MOMOLAND)
Great!
- Whatever she does, she's cute. / - So cute.
- That's what 20-year-olds are like. / - 20s...
She's energetic from the start.
That's good.
A special trip is prepared today.
Yes, it's very special.
What is it?
We prepared an event for this special trip.
Battle Trip has a book now.
- We published a book. / - We have a book now.
We will...
- Finally. / - Randomly select those who...
Watch the broadcast and award them books.
From last week's 30-second preview,
Battle Trip was reported in the most number of articles.
- That trip is today's... / - Why was that the case?
It's because...
- Special people are here today. / - So fresh.
They're fresh 20-year-olds.
Jooe is also 20 years old.
Yes, I was born in 1999.
She was born in 1999.
Guess what year was I born?
I was born in 1979.
Nice to meet you.
- Excuse me? / - Wait a minute.
Then...
Why are you saying this?
They're exactly 20 years apart?
Exactly 20.
Father?
- What? / - Father.
As for me...
- Were you born in 1972? / - I won't say what year.
Year of the Rat.
I was born in the Year of the Rat.
These days, people don't talk about
their Chinese zodiac sign.
They won't.
If someone talks about it...
- That shows you're old. / - That's right.
Instead of Year of the Tiger...
- If you say it like Year of the Panthera. / - Panthera?
"Where did you go?"
"Europa."
You're really old if you say that.
That's such an old word.
It's a really special trip today.
Today's theme is,
Spring flower trip at 20.
It feels so fresh.
I feel the flowers budding.
(Fresh)
How old are the
100 judges today?
20 years old!
We have 100 people who are 20 years old.
That's right.
Let's hear how our youngest Sikyung was
at 20 years old.
During our time...
In "My Sassy Girl,"
Gianna Jun and Cha Taehyun
show off their ID cards after turning the legal age.
They do this.
They enter a bar.
That was a scene in the movie.
It was a dream for 20-year-olds.
That's right. When you enter a place...
Did you do that too?
No, no, no.
What's your dream then?
For me, when I'm stressed,
I want to go to the karaoke room after 10 p.m.
Whenever our schedules are over,
we couldn't find the right place
to relieve stress.
- When you were underage? / - Yes.
- But now... / - Did you go when you became 20?
I did!
- Really? / - I burned it up.
In the karaoke room?
Yes.
- Where else did you go? / - It was crazy.
Other things I've done are like,
with the members at the dorm...
- Just... / - Did you drink beer?
Did you drink beer?
How was it?
You drank so much your hair is beer color.
Right. Old people used to
dye their hair with beer.
Don't say things like that. It's so sad.
There must be so many things
she'd want to do now that she's 20.
It's the start for you.
Today, it's a trip for fresh youth
that just turned 20.
They went on a spring flower trip.
I'm curious about where they went.
First, our 20-year-olds...
- Trip planners, please come out. / - Come out.
(Park Jihoon, Park Woojin of Wanna One)
(Mina of Gugudan, Yoojung of Weki Meki)
Seeing them like this, it's...
- Wanna One and I.O.I. / - That's right.
- I.O.I vs. Wanna One. / - Wanna One.
- That's the battle today. / - That's right.
20 years old...
You'll all be adults soon.
- Yes. / - Yes.
Is there something you dreamed about doing.
- The thing you want to do most. / - Something...
You want to be able to do now that you're an adult.
I want to do this.
- Where? / - When we go to after-work dinners...
I want to be able to
drink with the older members.
- You want to drink alcohol? / - Yeah.
Also, I'm into cars.
Driver's license?
Yes, I want to get my license.
That's right.
What about Mina and Yoojung?
For me...
I want to watch soccer with my parents
and have chicken and beer.
Or...
Clink glasses with my parents
when they drink soju.
- I'm hoping for that. / - It's all about alcohol.
We could only drink after our birthday.
- That's right. / - Now you can drink from January 1st.
- They must have drunk a lot. / - Of course.
Really?
- You can do it now then. / - Yes.
When do you feel like you're really an adult now?
Recently,
I bought a transportation card because I needed it.
I went to register and
I couldn't register as a teenager.
That made me realize
I was 20 now.
It hit me.
When I say hello
to the driver when I'm in a taxi,
The driver used to say,
"Where are you going, kid?"
But they ask me,
"Where are you going, young lady?" these days.
It surprises me and makes me think,
"Does it show?"
- It makes me think like that. / - "Does it show?"
Do you like to be called young lady?
- That's cute. / - It feels new to me.
- Before... / - Since it's the first time you've heard it.
- Young lady. / - That's right.
Let's start Battle Trip now.
Today's special is a spring flower trip at 20.
Where did you go for your flower trip?
We went to Suncheon, which is currently having
a spring flower festival, then went to Gwangyang.
- Suncheon and Gwangyang. / - Right.
This team...
Must have a lot to eat.
Suncheon has delicious food.
Suncheon has a lot of good restaurants there.
You can't leave Gwangyang out.
Gwangyang as well.
Gwangyang is amazing.
Can we look forward to an eating show?
- Of course. / - You can look forward to it.
Mina, can we really look forward to it?
I gave up being on a diet on this trip.
Did you eat a lot on this trip?
Yes, on this trip,
we just ate, ate, ate, ate and
then took photos in between.
That's what the tour was about.
Did you see flowers?
Yes, we saw 100 million flowers.
- 100 million flowers? / - Yes.
- 100 million? / - Not 1 million?
- 100 million flowers. / - 100 million flowers.
We went to a park where
100 million flowers were in bloom.
Right away...
She started singing
when she heard 100 million flowers.
2, 3.
♪ 100 million flowers are in bloom ♪
♪ Without holding back... ♪
My daughter.
Our daughter.
Nice.
Jihoon and Woojin,
where did you go?
We started from Jinju and
went to Hadong,
which has the most beautiful flower path in Korea.
- Jinju... / - Don't we have something impressive?
They have 100 million flowers.
Of course we do.
We went to the 10 ri flower road.
Do you know of it?
- 10 ri? / - Cherry blossoms all the way?
- Oh, 4km? / - 10 ri as in 4km.
Have you ever showered in cherry blossoms?
- A shower? / - With cherry blossoms?
That's how many petals there were?
You'll be shocked when you see.
- Enough to take a shower? / - Seriously.
Okay then.
Flower trip of 20-year-olds.
It's Hadong vs. Suncheon.
People might think that
it's an unexpected place
for 20-year-olds to travel.
These places are known as
the hottest places on social media.
A lot of young people like these places.
That's why we went there on Battle Trip.
Let's check out the map
and see where they went.
You have to keep going down.
It's much faster nowadays.
It's quite far.
Jinju, Hadong. Gwangyang, Suncheon.
Isn't that Hwagae Market?
- That's right. / - It is.
You're right.
Between Gyeongsang-do and Jeolla-do.
Looking at the map,
I think you could go to Jinju, then Hadong,
then Gwangyang, and Suncheon in one trip.
Right, if you have the time.
If you have enough time, that's the best way.
Jinju is famous for cold noodles.
Of course, it's famous.
- Do you know? / - Of course.
Honestly, I didn't know.
I was searching for good restaurants in Jinju...
- I found it was famous for cold noodles. / - Very famous.
So we went there right away.
What's in Hadong?
We spent a lot of money
in Hadong.
- Did you spend some money? / - Yes.
We ate Korean beef
in the end.
I can't wait.
- Everyone will get excited by the beef. / - But...
Since we're talking about food...
Once we complete our promotions,
our reins are removed.
We eat like it's an eating show.
You don't have to show your midriffs anymore.
That's right. Look at me.
So I'm really looking forward to their eating show.
Did you know that Suncheon,
where Yoojung and Mina went,
is a pilgrimage for Rail-Ro train travelers?
Rail-Ro?
It's for Koreans under 29.
It's an unlimited train travel pass
that can be used in any train in Korea.
- Is there something like that? / - You can't use it.
There are dates for that.
- That's right. / - They have specific dates.
You can choose either 5 days or 7 days.
You can plan according to...
- Your travel route. / - If you buy that pass...
Can you ride a train anywhere?
You can ride to anywhere.
The entire country.
Think of it as an unlimited pass for 5 days.
That's right.
Also in Suncheon...
You can get free accommodation.
Or you can hire a bus.
- There are many services. / - It's a service.
It's very nice.
That's good.
- Anyway. / - First off...
Let's go see the 100 million flowers first.
We'll go to Suncheon.
Do you have a tour name?
1, 2, 3, 4.
♪ Spring is here ♪
- Yoobom... / - Nabom...
Spring is here.
You also prepared an event, didn't you?
Before we started the trip,
we prepared a small event.
When you post a photo of yourself
watching our trip on TV,
we will choose one of the viewers
and give you the photos we took.
- That's great. / - It's really an idol special.
It's a 20-year-olds' spring trip.
This is Mina and Yoojung's trip.
Why don't we shout out your name to start us off?
Spring flower trip at 20.
- Yoobom. / - Nabom.
- Let's check it out! / - Let's check it out!
I'm already feeling excited.
My excitement is up to here.
Planning a trip is when you're excited the most.
(Hehe)
Goodness.
Hello,
I'm Mina of Gugudan.
Hello, I'm Yoojung of Weki Meki.
(They were part of I.O.I from Producer 101 Season 1)
(They finished their time with I.O.I)
This trip will be meaningful.
How beautiful.
So, we...
This time...
For the first time...
We're going on a trip together.
Right?
- So cute. / - We...
Just turned 20, you know.
- Right. / - Now...
We have no limitations.
- They're gone. / - We're a bit more...
- Free. / - That's right.
It's my first time going on
an overnight trip with a friend, without my parents...
It's a first for me too.
We only had beach, pension, beach, pension.
We didn't plan anything.
- We only went to play. / - Right.
- This was your first time? / - Yes.
I've never spent a night out.
It's our 1st trip as 20-year-olds,
I want to do this
when we go on our trip.
I have a wish.
At a roof top bar.
I want to try the cocktails there.
- At a fancy bar? / - While listening to music...
A glass of cocktail.
Your mind is already at the bar.
I want to
do something like
riding a bicycle with you.
But I don't know how to ride one.
Huh?
- Huh? / - If we ride a 2-man bicycle...
I can only go straight.
You can drive the bicycle.
Right...
You can enjoy the view while I drive the bicycle.
I got it.
Also...
In junior high,
the twin look was trending.
That's right.
I've never worn a matching outfit with my friend.
And I want to...
Go drinking...
I want to drink.
It must be fun just imagining it.
From a long time ago,
I've wanted to go backpacking on a train.
That's a great idea.
Since it's spring now,
we must go see the flowers.
- I've been thinking about it. / - Really?
If we're going to see flowers,
we have to see a field that's
covered with flowers.
While we're at it.
Let's go to a place with a whole field of flowers.
I've done my research.
Suncheonman National Garden's spring flower festival.
The festival lasts from April 6th to May 22th.
Are there a lot of flowers in Suncheon?
- For that long? / - I really want to go to a festival.
This proves that the flowers over there
are so strong.
Are you saying the soil there is fertile?
Yes, because of that,
you can see flowers until May.
The flowers will still be in bloom...
- Even after this show airs. / - Right, right.
The festival ends on May 22th.
- I really want to go see flowers. / - Right?
- We can take photos. / - Flowers like this.
There are a lot of tulips.
Look at that.
And this place is...
This is where you can take the best photos.
- This place is really nice. / - Right?
Flowers are everywhere.
I read that Suncheon is
a must visit place to go by train
for travelers who are in their 20s.
That's what you were after.
- Yeah. / - That's what you're after.
- You were. / - At first...
I planned a train trip from the start.
There's also that.
It's a place that's set up to show
what Korea was like in the 1960s and 1970s.
So...
It's like going back in time.
You and I
can go back in time too.
This is nice.
The Yoobom Nabom Trip.
You feel like crying again, right?
Anyway, we can try that.
We can take a lot of photos here.
I only picked
the destination which is Suncheon
and the transportation, the train.
Next to
Suncheon,
Yeosu and Gwangyang are located.
- That's the whole itinerary. / - Yes.
- Yeosu, Suncheon and Gwangyang. / - Yeosu is nice.
- Yeosu is great. / - But...
Yeosu has been introduced on Battle Trip already.
But they showed a tiny part
of Gwangyang that time.
Like a brief preview.
We can introduce the city thoroughly this time.
- We'll be thorough. / - Yes, thoroughly.
Gwangyang is famous for bulgogi.
Bulgogi.
Gwangyang bulgogi.
- Yes, we have that. / - We can introduce that.
- We can... / - You look so happy.
We can try the bulgogi too.
Let's find a lot of fun things to do there.
Let's make our trip amazing.
You find out more about Suncheon.
I'll find more about Gwangyang.
Okay.
Should we clap?
We have a great plan.
Right. Then...
Let's name our trip.
My name is Yoojung and you're Mina.
And it's spring or "bom."
Mina, Yoojung...
Yoojung. Yoobom, Nabom.
And Yoo sounds like "you."
So it's like your spring, my spring.
- Like you and me. / - Yes, like that.
- Sounds great. / - Yoojung, Mina.
- Yoobom Nabom. / - I like it.
You and me.
- Your spring, my spring. / - My spring.
Yoobom Nabom.
Let's go!
- So natural. / - They sound different.
♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ I'm ready ♪
♪ Spring, spring, spring, spring is here ♪
- Yoobom. / - Nabom.
Spring is here!
Looks so fun.
(Fascinated)
It's a swing!
Want me to push you?
(She steps on the flowers)
I stepped on the flowers.
- So cute. / - Cute.
- Cute. / - I love this place.
It smells like tonic.
(Smell of the herbal tonic)
It's like adult spicy rice cakes.
I like the taste of jujubes.
- So pretty. / - Finally...
- She's drinking. / - Is that wine?
I've always wanted to try this.
With friends...
We haven't seen that dance in ages.
It's different when the originals do it.
(Yoojung's spring)
(Mina's spring)
(Current time, 4:30 a.m.)
- 4:30? / - 4:30 a.m.
- Yes. / - We are at Yongsan Station.
We're in Yongsan now.
Yes, this is Yongsan Station.
Don't you think we should visit
many places in Suncheon?
That's why
we will get on the first train
and get moving.
Understood?
- This way, we'll visit many places. / - Right, right.
Yoojung said
I need to trust her and follow her lead today.
That's right. Let me handle today's itinerary.
We'll take a good look around Suncheon
and take a rest.
Okay, okay.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
Let's go.
(They set out to Suncheon)
What's this?
Why?
What's going on?
What is this? Is this a train station?
- You've only been to Seoul Station? / - Wait...
I'd never been.
- You've never even been to Seoul Station? / - No.
Yoojung is fascinated by our station.
What is this place?
- I've never seen this before. / - This is Yongsan.
- So many firsts for you. / - Yes.
It feels so strange.
Why?
It's like...
I still can't believe it.
We're really going on this trip.
Unbelievable.
We have an important matter on our hands.
The much anticipated...
Ta-da.
Ta-da!
We made these the other day.
You must take those on trips these days.
If you take a photo through those...
- They turn out great. / - Right.
It'd be great if you make one
before going on your trip.
When you take a photo with that at the beach,
it looks so good.
This is how they turned out.
Isn't this pretty?
Ta-da.
So pretty.
Then...
Let's take this out...
- Yeah. / - And take a photo here.
Right here.
This is the spot. This is it.
This looks good.
So it shows.
(Toppers are the focus)
(Yoojung sleeps on the train)
(Yongsan Station, Suncheon Station)
(2 hours and 40 minutes)
(Suncheon Station, 7:50 a.m.)
We've arrived at Suncheon Station.
This is Suncheon!
Was that your first time there?
- Yes. / - Yes.
My gosh.
We have to do this thing.
- What is it? / - A photo with the station name.
We need to take a photo with the sign.
- People take photos like that. / - Isn't that pretty?
Suncheon.
Where are we going now?
- We will... / - You told me to follow your lead.
After I.O.I, this is the first time...
- We've gone anywhere together. / - That's right.
Doesn't it feel like...
- We've gone back to that time? / - Yes.
To really travel back in time...
Are we going?
We will take the bus to travel back in time.
- It must've been a great trip. / - That way.
- Let's go. / - Were you in high school in I.O.I?
- Yes. / - Yes.
We first met when we were 17.
Oh, my.
Besides, you were so busy when you were in I.O.I.
- You didn't have time to travel. / - That's so true.
That's right.
Even at this point,
it kind of...
Feels like...
We're in a drama set.
Is that the bus stop?
I think this is it.
Yes, this must be it.
Here it is, drama set.
Then from here...
I bet it's been a while since you took the bus.
- Yes. / - It's been a while.
- Right? / - Walking around to celebrate us being 20...
I think it'll be memorable.
The bus is here.
My gosh, the bus!
- Ta-da. We'll take this bus. / - 77.
Here we go.
When we go to Gwangyang tomorrow,
we will take the same bus.
Is that so?
Yes, we'll take the same bus.
You can visit almost all of
the tourist attractions with Bus 77.
- We should remember that number. / - Yes.
This slightly looks like Jeju-do.
Really?
Everything about Suncheon looks interesting to me.
It's different taking the bus to go to school
and taking the bus on a trip.
You're right.
Your faces look different.
On days like this, even the weather's nice.
Right.
You're right.
The dramas
that were filmed here
are all shown here...
Like this.
Amazing.
"Bread, Love and Dreams".
Of course, I know. I know Kim Takgu.
- "Gangnam Blues." / - They filmed dramas here.
- Many dramas were shot here. / - 47.
"East of Eden."
- We're here! / - I see murals.
1970s, 1980s, 1960s.
Divided into eras.
This is so interesting.
It's a TV-shaped entrance.
Hello.
Two tickets, please.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
I'm going to attach this to my diary.
It's a scene from the past.
Restroom.
This is Suncheon.
Goosebumps.
Why?
I saw that
in "Lights and Shadows."
- Really? / - That theater.
- A domestic theater! / - That's right.
- It was so fascinating. / - Yeah.
It's that place.
- So fascinating. / - It was really fascinating.
When people come here,
everyone rents out school uniforms.
Boys and girls uniforms.
Everyone does.
We can wear them here?
You must try that out.
People must rent school uniforms.
- Taking photos... / - You must enter that time.
- So many. / - I really want to try it.
Coming here with friends,
wearing uniforms and eating lunch boxes.
Experiencing these things.
- Hello. / - Hello.
No way.
This is a school.
Isn't this adorable?
Those green desks!
It was so interesting.
I hate that wood.
Right.
You get all these splinters.
That's right.
If you touch the wrong spot. Right.
If you see in movies...
Right.
The character in "Black Rubber Shoes" wears this.
What kind of uniform is this?
They have props.
Student president.
They had that there.
Kang Daniel?
- Why is that there? / - What's Kang Daniel?
You can borrow name tags.
It was there as an example.
- Ta-da. / - Ta-da.
They did this.
That's so outdated.
No, no. We have to own it.
We must look confident.
(Confident)
Hey, you said we have to look confident!
(Cute)
If you take photos in uniform here, they'll look great.
- There were many spots for photos. / - Looks good.
You can take those photos
and compare them to your mom's.
- You're right. / - Of course.
Doesn't it feel like
we're students of the old days?
- What do you mean? / - It's so...
Isn't this 1988?
(Sunyang Cinema in 1988)
That's right. I saw this theater in the drama.
This theater showed up a lot in "Giant."
And "Lights and Shadows."
Ah!
Right?
You remember that, don't you?
(Oops)
(What is this?)
We can now watch...
Erotic movies.
I'm so embarrassed.
They were...
They only had those type of movie posters.
What is that?
Adult movies...
Why didn't they have things like "Rambo?"
Should we go in?
(Embarrassed )
(We're 20 years old, we can watch all movies)
Here...
- Wow. / - Pretty photos.
These photos will be memorable.
- Later on. / - You take photos with your phones...
And they print them on wooden frames.
Just like from the old days?
- A place that suits our uniforms. / - That suits...
We should take a photo in such a place.
(Poor hillside village in the 1970s)
The weather was great that day.
- This is it. / - You're right.
No.
Lean on me.
Everyone took photos on their sides
in the 1970s.
- That was so nice. / - Great photo.
I haven't looked yet.
Me neither.
- Let's look on the count of three. / - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
This one turned out great.
This is awesome.
It's like a movie.
- Doesn't it look like it? / - This one's no joke.
Thank you.
- Bye. / - Thank you.
- It's a photo of a lifetime. / - So pretty.
You're right.
When it comes to Battle Trip...
You can't leave out food.
You're known to be a picky eater.
That's true.
You can't eat a lot of food.
- You can't eat all of them? / - No, I can't.
You can't eat any of the dishes on the list?
Something that suits your tastes.
- Restaurant. / - I found a course.
- Right, right. / - A course meal?
Okay.
(Drama set)
(Suncheon eatery)
(30 minutes by Bus 77)
Traveling by bus...
- You're dressed the same. / - The twin look?
We kept going with the twin look.
A trip to Suncheon is so...
I feel like we can do everything here.
So what are we eating?
Today, we will
eat the famous dish everyone must
try in Suncheon.
We'll eat spicy fishcake.
My gosh.
Spicy fishcake?
Fishcake?
Seriously...
This is like asking a cat to hold on to a fish.
Looks good.
That looks so good.
Amazing.
- Hey. / - Amazing.
What is it?
This is...
We have a place this in my neighborhood.
Should we write something too?
We love spicy rice cakes.
- Right. / - It's lucky that it wasn't the busy hour.
The students would go crazy.
It'd be insane.
It really looks cute.
It'd be fun to go and look for that.
At that restaurant.
(They write for each other)
Actually...
Suncheon is famous for cockles.
- Cockles? / - Yeah.
She can't eat cockles.
But cockles aren't in season now.
So...
We love fried foods, right?
We love it.
While we were promoting, we had spicy rice cakes...
- Hey, hey, you're right. / - Yeah.
We only had spicy rice cakes or cup rice
in our green room.
- Or chicken. / - We ordered it at the dorm.
You're right.
We ordered spicy rice cakes a lot.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
This is how it's served.
Hey, but for the price,
the serving is huge.
Do you cook it on the spot?
I like it when there's more fishcake than rice cake.
I recommend it for people who like fishcakes.
- Thank you for the meal. / - Thank you for the meal.
(I'll eat this up)
(She's focused)
(Blowing)
I only blew lightly.
(Slurping)
This is so good.
(Blowing)
- See? See? / - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mina.
This...
I get why it's called spicy fishcakes.
Is it spicy?
Spicy rice cakes are normally sweet.
It's...
Spicy.
It's spicy.
Like really spicy seafood noodles.
- Yes, it's like that. / - It's really spicy.
Taste like really spicy noodles.
Too spicy for Yoojung.
She can't eat spicy food.
It's like adult spicy rice cakes.
Yoojung...
She eats like a kid.
- She's cute. / - Look at her face.
I can't eat spicy food.
I can't eat hot or spicy food.
- It's exactly this. / - You're right.
But I like spicy rice cakes.
The portion is huge though.
There are dumplings too.
Yes.
It was a generous serving.
Try the fishcake. The fishcake.
It's seasoned well because it's thin.
I like that it's cut into
bite-sized pieces.
- Isn't it spicy? / - No.
This is my type of food.
That's good.
- We already finished half of it. / - Looks so good.
This is like volcano rice cakes.
It's strong but...
It's not heavy.
- Isn't it light? / - It's not the spiciness that hurts.
Isn't it light?
(This is my kind of food)
- Today, it's so... / - Mina eats so well.
Mina.
I can take small bites
but I can't take big bites.
- It looks... / - It looks delicious.
How long has it been since you
ate as much as you want?
- It's been a while. / - Right?
We’ve been promoting our albums these days.
I see. You can't eat much then.
(If it gets too spicy, a sip of drink to ease down)
Let's turn off the stove.
Shall we?
We might end up scorching it.
I was boiling it down so we can mix rice.
You're a pro.
The sauce is...
We fried rice with the sauce.
This is it.
That's so...
It was really delicious.
Koreans always do this at the end of a meal.
I need to do that to finish a meal.
- That's how to end it. / - It's hot.
It's really savory.
I could immediately feel the aroma of the cheese.
Woojin has fallen for the mixed rice.
- You have to eat that. / - Right?
Actually,
I don't really like
cheddar cheese because it could be
a little too greasy.
But this is not greasy at all. It's really savory.
- It's like a cheese pancake. / - We finished it.
It looks so delicious.
When you go on a trip, you should eat a lot.
Of course.
(Mmm)
It's delicious.
What are we doing now?
It's spring, so we're going to go see flowers.
Let's go see flowers.
It's okay.
You can act like that at your age.
We're going to a spring flower festival.
The one you showed me before?
- That... That... / - Yes, yes, that's right.
100 million flowers.
That's right.
- There? / - We're going there.
Shall we go?
- Thank you for the food. / - Thank you for the food.
(Suncheonman National Garden)
(30 minutes on Bus 66)
I'd like to see 100 million flowers.
(Spring is when everything is in full bloom)
This place is really huge.
We're here.
We're finally here.
Well, this is where I've been
looking forward the most.
- Me. / - Me too.
Right? Right?
- Let's check it out first. / - Hurry, hurry.
I think we should hurry to see a lot.
Let's hurry and check it out.
We have to walk around a lot.
Right.
I really wanted to look at flowers.
(It's the size of 150 soccer stadiums)
150 soccer stadiums?
- Yes, it's really big. / - It's huge.
Healing forest.
By the way...
I was wondering how 100 million flowers
could fit in one place.
But it's so huge.
We should check the map.
There's a lake too.
1-hour course, 2-hour course.
This one starts from East Gate to Rose Garden,
Maze Garden, Lake Garden, German Garden,
Dutch Garden...
Let's take
the Yoobom Nabom course.
Okay.
- Shall we go? / - Okay.
You might not be able to see the whole thing in a day.
Some people stay there overnight
just to visit this place.
There are a lot of people here.
It's so...
The tulips are so beautiful.
(Flower path from the entrance)
How pretty.
♪ The world ♪
♪ Is a little cold ♪
♪ Compared to ♪
♪ When I was living inside you ♪
♪ Without anything lacking ♪
The tulips there...
- Are just the beginning. / - Right.
This is just the beginning?
- This is just the beginning. / - Tulips are the start.
How many flowers are there that this is just the start?
That's how big it is.
I can't believe I'm here.
Amazing.
- There's a lake as well? / - Yes.
I can't believe there's such
a big national garden.
- It's so fascinating. / - That path is so beautiful.
- Right. / - I can't believe such a place exists.
It's really nice there.
Many people said that we had
to visit the Dutch Garden,
so we added it to our course.
- ♪ I like ♪ / - It's so pretty.
♪ You ♪
This is so beautiful.
It looks so pretty.
It was really pretty.
It's a perfect place to take nice pictures.
Any random photo turns out nice.
It'd be great for photos.
This is so pretty!
This is too much.
I think this is my first time seeing tulips
since I was a little girl.
Right?
We don't often see tulips unless
you're in an amusement park.
It's so pretty.
Are we in Korea?
- So pretty. / - I love this color.
- This? / - I'm really into...
- Lavender these days. / - Lavender?
This?
- Can I sit down? / - Yes.
1, 2, 3.
- So pretty, right? / - That's so pretty.
It's all flowers in the back.
The flowers are so nice.
Seriously
Like this.
- Pretty. / - That's how it's done.
Is it a trend to close your eyes
when you take photos like this?
They do that these days.
Like this.
To make you seem fresh.
Fresh?
Right.
So it's a trending pose, right?
- Closing your eyes. / - Right.
Now, we're going to see canola flowers.
After seeing canola flowers,
we'll see animals.
There are so many things we need to see.
So first, let's go see canola flowers.
(Everything that is yellow is canola flowers)
(My goodness)
- Seriously. / - Amazing.
How many flowers are there?"
How many canola flowers are here?
This is just...
Like Jeju-do.
This is amazing.
- It's so pretty. / - Seriously, it is.
Make sure you come here.
It was so pretty.
I...
I wanted to take pictures of
the good memories here,
so I brought soap bubbles.
- You brought these for pictures? / - Yes.
Will it work?
But it should be windy...
You need a lot of wind...
- Huh? / - Goodness.
They'll fly out now.
So pretty.
- That's like... / - I thought it was photo-shopped.
They look like manga characters.
Here we go.
- God? / - Ready...
(Swing)
- Hey! / - Did it come out okay?
- Did we get a good one? / - I think I did.
Oh, wow.
- That was really fascinating. / - That was good, right?
I think it is.
How did you get the slow-mo right here?
Right?
That's awesome.
- Good job. / - Please pat my head.
- Good job, good job. / - I did so well.
Right?
Let me take a video of you this time.
Cue.
- That's a good one. / - I can tell it's good.
- It turned out well. / - It did.
- She smiled. / - She did well.
She smiled.
It was good when she smiled.
This is where it starts.
This is how it turns out. Isn't it pretty?
Then the bubbles fly out.
You did well too.
- Hey. / - I know how it works now.
- Nice. / - Okay, okay.
- Then... / - Yeah?
Let's go see the flamingoes you wanted to see.
Flamingoes!
I heard there are other animals as well.
Let's go see animals.
Let's hurry.
- Let's go! / - Go!
- I want to see. / - How do you feel right now?
My heart is racing!
- This place is really nice. / - It is.
- Wow. / - Wow.
The first time in my 20 years of life seeing flamingoes.
Unbelievable.
It's like they're wearing stockings.
Look at their bodies.
They're forming a heart.
I wish I could touch them.
Two flamingoes make a shape of heart together.
They can be standing with only one leg.
Yeah. Behind the one that's sleeping.
You're right.
Amazing.
They have such thin legs.
It's really interesting that they sleep on one leg.
They hide the other leg.
Look.
This is so fascinating.
- Everything's a first. / - Right.
- Seeing flamingoes for the first time. / - All firsts.
- First time in the Dutch Garden. / - First trip.
There's more inside?
Yes, in that building over there,
there are other animals.
Bye, guys.
We're leaving.
- They're very flexible. / - They are.
They can bend like this.
- What are you doing? / - She's good at that.
She's good at that.
- Good at bending her body. / - Yeah.
At times like this, you just have to move along.
I'm not going to respond.
(The next friends after the flamingo are)
- Prairie dogs? / - Oh, my.
Oh, they're so cute.
- So cute. / - Aren't they too cute?
So cute.
Do you want to be on Battle Trip?
They eat a lot.
What is that? They make it look so good.
I know.
- They were so cute. / - Eating so well.
- Goodness, fennec foxes. / - Fennec fox!
- They're so pretty. / - Aren't they pretty?
I want to raise them.
Oh, my. They're so cute.
People say I look like a fennec fox.
- That's right. / - You do.
- You look like one. / - You like alike.
So cute.
They're so cute.
- Meerkats! / - Seriously.
It was so amazing. They were standing up like this.
They're on the lookout
for large predators.
That's why they stand on their feet and look around.
Please stand for us.
- Just once. / - That's what I'm thinking too.
They want to take photos.
- Zoom. / - Just once.
- Please just once. / - But they...
Do it just once.
They must be going inside.
We wanted to take that so bad.
Did you wait for ages?
Like this...
No, like this.
Let's walk and then do this.
Got it?
Walk and 1, 2, 3.
- That's what happened? / - What's going on?
Cute!
How pretty.
Zoom.
They actually gathered.
- Oh, my. / - So cute!
It was fascinating...
- That they actually stood up. / - Wait a minute.
How did you call them?
It was so amazing.
They must've been aware.
Try it when you go there.
It might work.
So cute.
They know how to act on TV.
Look at that.
They actually put their hands like that.
- So cute. / - They're so cute.
Their noses are red.
Are they trying to pretend to be bigger than us?
(I'm not going to lose)
I'm so happy.
I become happy when I see cute animals.
Thank you.
Bye.
- Bye. / - Farewell.
1, 2, 3. Step, step, step.
Are you a meerkat?
- Cute. / - They're so cute.
From Suncheon to Gwangyang...
We'll have to sleep a night, right?
- Right. / - We have to sleep.
- We do. / - At a guest house.
That sounds good.
I didn't know this was a guest house.
(Suncheonman National Garden to guest house)
(Automatic reflex)
- Let's go this way. / - Here it is.
The guest house. Shall we go inside?
- Let's hurry. / - Let's go.
(A place to rest for a short time today)
- Hello. / - Hello.
(Guest house, double room for $50)
(They enter the guest house)
It smells so nice.
So nice.
- $50 for 2 people is cheap. / - Yes.
- This bed. / - Yeah.
Isn't it similar to the ones in the I.O.I dorm?
- These rails? / - Yeah, the rails.
- But this place is better, right? / - Yeah.
You know why?
- It's two single beds here. / - Yeah.
It's good to sleep there together and make memories.
- You can talk and sleep. / - It's so good.
It reminded of us of the past.
True.
Don't you love that time?
- Right before you fall asleep and talking. / - Yes.
What are you thinking about?
I'm just... Sad.
That this will end tomorrow.
I've always wanted to travel
without my parents and I'm glad that...
- I'm doing this with you. / - Right?
That's what made it better.
We wore school uniforms and took photos.
- We also ate vintage snacks. / - That's right.
Being able to travel with
just you and me was so good.
I realized we received so much love back then.
I feel like I'm experiencing that again.
That's such a classic dance.
So many people cheered for us.
I feel so thankful for that.
(Memories more precious because we can't go back)
We have to get up early and have the breakfast buffet.
That's right.
Whatever you've prepared...
- Just trust me. / - I'll just follow that course.
Sounds good.
Let's hurry up and sleep.
- There's lots to eat tomorrow. / - Let's sleep.
- "There's lots to eat tomorrow." / - Turning the light off.
They're so cute.
I didn't tell you the highlight.
- We're going to eat Korean beef. / - What?
- Korean beef? / - That's why we have to sleep now.
I'm so excited.
Let's go to sleep. We have to wake up early.
- I'll see you in my dream. / - Do we have to?
You don't have to.
- You can't stop talking. / - Sleep well.
The sun will rise at this rate.
♪ The sun is up ♪
♪ Get up now ♪
- What do they have? / - Let's eat breakfast.
- Take two pieces of toast. / - Is that in the guest house?
- Guest house breakfast? / - Yes.
- In the basement. / - It's for free?
Yes.
- Part of the accommodation fee? / - Yes.
(Pop)
- Is it working? / - Isn't it working?
We've never used a toaster before.
(It must be working since it's warm)
(They try the cereal)
That's so cute.
This is new.
Is this all we get?
It's too little.
Nice.
- Stop, stop. / - Stop? Okay.
(Let's eat now)
It's so cute.
- Let's eat. / - Let's eat.
(They are filling their stomachs before they leave)
She hunches so well.
She eats while hunched.
- She always hunches over. / - When she eats...
She's really into it.
If Yoojung planned the day in Suncheon...
Today is my plan.
- Mina's spring. / - Mina, Mina, Mina.
♪ Mina, Mina, Mina ♪
Don't you think Gwangyang will be really fun today?
I really want to try Gwangyang bulgogi.
They have a bulgogi street in Gwangyang.
The street is filled with bulgogi restaurants.
That's right.
- We must specialize bulgogi. / - I like that.
We must specialize bulgogi.
If Yoojung planned the day in Suncheon...
Today is my plan.
This is so good!
(Captivating 20-year-old's hearts)
- We're finally going. / - It just passed by.
- I'm looking forward to this. / - Looking forward to it.
It's so pretty here.
Seocheon Riverside.
So nice!
I love it.
Goodness.
Yoobom Nabom, spring is here.
Bye.
(We'll start Mina's spring in Gwangyang right now)
(Mina's spring)
We're looking forward to it.
- Will they start with bulgogi? / - It's Gwangyang.
This weather makes me want to hum.
♪ I'm a banana allergy monkey ♪
(Excited)
This must be the bus stop.
It must be.
Bus 77 will arrive soon.
Bus 77 is here.
- Hello. / - Hello.
It's meat.
There is a special combined tour ticket
between Suncheon and Gwangyang.
It's cheaper if you visit more than 3 places.
Really? This is amazing.
We're here.
- This is the Gwangyang bulgogi street. / - Right.
- It's Gwangyang bulgogi street. / - It says it right here.
(Gwangyang bulgogi street)
- Wow. / - So many bulgogi restaurants.
Right.
We're going to a Korean beef bulgogi place.
- The Korean beef that kept me up last night? / - Right.
- You like pickled plums, right? / - Yes.
You can eat it with pickled plums.
- Plums and bulgogi. / - That's right.
It's destiny.
- What did they say? / - Destiny.
Oh, destiny.
The other places cost over $20.
But for us...
The owner raises cows.
- Really? / - Yes.
That's why it's cheap.
It's perfect for the early 20s.
- How do I put it? / - Very cheap and delicious.
- Very satisfactory. / - That's right.
- Trip without money pressure. / - You're right.
♪ Let's go eat Korean beef ♪
(They finally get to taste Gwangyang bulgogi)
- The bulgogi was so delicious. / - It looks so good.
It really looks good.
Plum? You eat it with plums.
- That looks so good. / - That is delicious.
- It was so good. / - Show us quickly.
Here... At other places,
they marinate the meat beforehand.
- That's right. / - It's that common brown color.
Here, they marinate it before it's cooked...
- So the meat is read. / - Really?
You know that pretty raw meat color?
- Pretty color. / - Gwangyang bulgogi doesn't have soup.
- They cook it like that. / - That's right.
And you cook it.
- It's different to the bulgogi we know. / - Right?
It looks delicious.
That was so good.
Thank you.
There are so many side dishes.
The meat looks so nice.
(Make some noise!)
The meat is red unlike the meat they serve
in other restaurants.
It's so red.
This is the pickled plum.
I've had chili pickles before...
- But I've never tried this before. / - It looks good.
- That's really good. Pickled plum. / - It's good.
It's sweet and sour.
It's so sour.
- Can I just have this instead of pickles? / - Right?
So good, right?
- It was so sour. / - It's great for digestion.
- True. / - Indeed.
I'm excited.
(Falling for the meat)
Yoojung's starting to hunch up now.
She's hunching.
It cooks fast.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(What does Gwangyang bulgogi taste like?)
Her reaction doesn't let us down.
(I did it because it was so delicious)
We apologize to the waitress.
Our girls react so loudly.
I get now why people said
you have to try the bulgogi in Gwangyang.
I know now.
There's no point coming here if you don't try this.
I thought the meat would be dry because it's so thin.
- But it's juicy. / - Yes, and it's very chewy.
Is there any way to make it even more delicious?
Wrap it in lettuce and perilla leaf.
Like this.
This is unfair.
You shouldn't do this.
That tastes amazing.
Is it for me?
(She takes a big bite)
(Do you like it?)
It hit you.
You just chewed on the pickled plum, didn't you?
I can see that.
In Suncheon, Gwangyang, you must eat this.
- This? / - It's game over with this.
I want to go back just to eat that.
- Really? / - Me too.
- Is it that good? / - Okay, I fully get you now.
I get what you're saying.
The pickled plum is so fresh and sour.
(She also opens her mouth wide)
I like how it pops in your mouth.
The pickled plum has a distinctive taste.
That's what makes the whole thing delicious.
- It's delicious. / - It's so delicious, isn't it?
Try the meat fresh from the grill.
Try the meat.
(It's so hot)
- She's so funny. / - Look at her face.
It tastes so good.
You have to eat it fresh from the grill.
That's right.
You shouldn't let it rest on the plate.
You have to bring the meat straight from the grill.
- You shouldn't use a plate? / - You have to eat quick.
- As if you're fishing. / - That's right.
Woojin, are you convinced?
I'm kind of jealous.
It looks so delicious.
That's...
(They're enjoying the really hot food)
This is amazing.
It's different.
- This is why we came here. / - Right.
This is so... If you didn't eat this,
you shouldn't say you've been to Suncheon,
Gwangyang.
You must try this here. Okay?
This is incredible.
I don't think I will eat any other bulgogi from now on.
It's so delicious.
I think Yoojung can be a great actress too.
- So many faces. / - Such a variety of expressions.
They eat so well.
(They keep eating)
(They finished the food)
We'd like to order 2 more portions of meat.
That's it.
- They need to eat more. / - More plums too.
- Thank you. / - You need to get more.
Thank you.
- Shall we begin? / - Shall we begin?
- Actually... / - Is this a beginning?
(I'm done)
(I'm just getting started)
(Even when Yoojung left, Mina kept eating)
I want to go to Suncheon.
- For the bulgogi? / - Yes.
- Gwangyang. / - You said you wanted to ride bikes.
Right.
How about I teach you?
I've learned before
so I can ride it.
But I can only go straight.
Let me teach you.
Where can we ride bicycles?
Near Seocheon Riverside and Seomjin River.
- There are a lot of canola flowers. / - Canola flowers.
It's covered with the flowers there.
- All covered. / - Really?
We have to ride bikes now.
I'm so happy.
Do many people ride bicycles at Seocheon Riverside?
I think so.
- It's right next to where you were. / - Yes.
- That looks nice. / - Perfect course.
- You eat bulgogi then... / - You don't get that in Seoul.
- Exactly. / - This is Seocheon Riverside.
- Seoul is too artificial. / - Really?
- It's so pretty here, isn't it? / - Yeah.
The flowers are beautiful here.
Doesn't it make you feel good...
- To see the open view here? / - Right.
Just watching the river flow makes me feel good.
They're all cherry trees but no blossoms.
This place must be beautiful with cherry blossoms.
- It must be really beautiful. / - Right?
This place must be colorful all the time.
I love the colors here.
Riding a bicycle here must be nice for sure,
but walking must be nice as well.
(They play with each other)
Now let's go ride bicycles.
This is so nice.
Hello.
We'd like to rent bicycles.
From April 6th...
You can rent bicycles for free
in Gwangyang.
- Really? / - Yes.
If it's free, you should ride it.
They just started this service.
The weather is great today. It's so sunny.
- Let's go! / - Let's go!
Hey, Mina.
There are only...
This many canola flowers.
That road is supposed to be covered with flowers...
But we were there too early.
(It wasn't like this when I looked it up online)
It's supposed to look like this.
Yes.
There might be more canola flowers by now.
Yes, by now, it'll be in full bloom.
It's okay. We can enjoy this subtle beauty.
You're right.
"Subtle beauty."
She's right. There's subtle beauty.
As you push the pedal, put the other foot on the pedal.
You're good.
I can do this.
Okay. Come here.
How do I?
Turn around.
Be careful.
She can't turn corners.
(You can just turn corners with your feet)
Actually, I can't turn corners either.
What the?
You two are a great team.
(They're excited)
Mina, I love this.
Mom, dad, I'm riding a bicycle.
This is nice.
The weather is so nice, isn't it?
It would've been nice if there were canola flowers too.
- It'd be so beautiful with the flowers. / - Right?
I'm sure they'll make it look like it with CG.
Canola flowers!
(Yoojung and Mina ride along the flower path)
(Mina rides the bicycle with only one hand)
I want to do that too!
No, I can't.
Choi Yoojung, you're a fool.
Kang Mina, you're a fool.
(Although there are no flowers, they enjoy the ride)
How was it?
Although there were no flowers, it was very nice
with the cool breeze and everything.
The weather makes the ride even more enjoyable.
- Let's go eat plum blossom macarons. / - Okay.
Let's go.
Macaroons?
- Plum blossom macarons? / - Yes.
I heard Gwangyang is famous for plum blossoms.
But around the time we visit the city,
there are no plum blossoms.
It's sad to miss it though.
So we will see the plum blossoms through food.
- They have plum blossom latte. / - Really?
- Goodness. / - It looks pretty, doesn't it?
And these are plum blossom macarons.
They come out like this.
- Isn't that pretty? / - It's so pretty.
I'm really worried about my team now.
- Their reactions are so bad. / - That's a real flower.
When guys eat bulgogi and it's really good,
they go...
The end.
(The famous plum blossom shaped macarons)
(They look super cute)
(Plum blossom macarons, $2 each)
We took so many pictures.
They're great for photographs.
(She's taking pictures again)
They're so pretty.
It's perfect girly photos to upload on social media.
- That 20s feel. / - What does it taste like?
This is raspberry cream cheese and
this is cream cheese.
(Yoojung takes a bite)
(Mina takes a bite too)
They say it's the best macaron
if it doesn't crumble...
- When you bite into it. / - It didn't crumble!
That didn't crumble.
- That macaron was so soft. / - Yes.
- It went in slowly like this. / - Like this.
- Isn't it really chewy? / - Yes.
It goes in like this.
It goes like this.
I've never had a macaron this chewy.
I highly recommend this.
(Cream cheese macaron this time)
(Mmm)
It's so delicious.
Some people don't like sweet stuff that much.
I don't think this is that sweet.
It's not that sweet.
Now, we have to drink milk tea right after.
It's so pretty, I feel bad eating it.
(What's this flower?)
It's a real flower!
Hey, it's a real flower.
She has a great reaction.
- That milk tea is so pretty. / - Hey, it's a real flower.
(Spray rose means "I can't stop admiring")
(I have to taste it even if it's pretty)
Wow.
Why?
It's so good!
(Smiling brightly)
What kind of milk tea is this?
It's a mix of earl grey, assam
and English breakfast are blended.
I knew it.
I love milk tea so much,
so I tried many different kinds but this tastes new.
It has a flowery aftertaste.
It's so good.
Three kinds of tea are blended together,
so unlike other milk teas, it tastes more like a flower.
This milk tea is so good.
I'm quite shocked by this.
We had plum blossom macarons,
so now we'll have a latte.
One dessert after another. Nice.
Let's go have some latte.
Let's go.
(She packs the leftovers)
It's a great set. Macaroon and milk tea.
It's a perfect combination.
(They're on their way to have plum blossom latte)
This place is 5 minutes away from the macaron shop.
- Really? / - It's really close.
It's right here.
- Hello. / - Hello.
It's pretty.
- The cafe is so pretty. / - It is.
We're going to have this.
Plum blossom...
- You have to have that. / - It's so pretty.
(Adorable plum blossom latte)
(Plum blossom latte with pink whipped cream)
It's really pretty.
Did you hear that?
"It's really pretty."
That was from the bottom of his heart.
Right?
It was.
It's so pretty.
Won't it look pretty if we take pictures with these?
- Shall we? / - Since they're all plum blossoms.
Good, good.
This is perfect for taking pictures,
when you come with a friend.
It's so pretty.
Take them right away.
(She takes pictures with all her heart)
(Burning it up)
(Plum blossom latte, macaron)
You can use a straw to drink this...
But it's better to drink it like this
so you can drink in with the cream.
It's really delicious that way.
It's not the cream you think.
It's not whipping cream.
It's really so...
How should I explain?
I was taken aback.
When I drank it, the cream didn't go into my mouth.
That's "Secret Garden."
You have a mouthful of cream
and coffee suddenly goes in.
The condensed milk cream was really dense.
- The cream is so good. / - Yoojung.
(They drink it one more time)
You can even chew the cream. It's that dense.
- Condensed milk. / - Condensed milk...
- That's cheating. / - Cheating.
Really?
- That's cheating. / - Do you want to try this?
Try this.
This one has a strong coffee smell.
People who can't drink coffee
can drink this.
This feels like eating...
- A pink cloud. / - You're right.
I've never tasted a pink cloud...
- But that's how you'd describe it. / - Right.
- It's sweet. / - The cafe is very cute.
(I finished it)
- One more plum blossom latte. / - She had two.
You said you don't eat much.
Thank you.
(They enjoy spring as they drink plum blossom latte)
I looked, but there is no rooftop bar in Gwangyang.
But I found a better place.
- Really? / - Yes.
- We don't need to go to a rooftop bar. / - Really?
- We don't need to go. / - Really?
I found a really great wine bar.
So we...
I don't know. I really like that place.
Look at her. She's happy just thinking about it.
What a great time.
We've gotten changed again.
We're dressed up nicely.
We'll take a cab
to the wine bar.
Hello.
I'm really excited. I've never been to a wine bar.
Are you taking a cab to the wine bar?
But you take a bus everywhere else.
- Cab for the wine bar... / - They got changed too.
- They're spending money. / - They got changed.
- Our clothes... / - You need that black cab.
I feel like we shouldn't be here.
No, we have to hold our heads up.
- We're 20 years old. / - Right.
- We can go in. / - That's right.
I understand why you want to dress up.
- I'm scared. / - Let's not show that it's our first time.
They don't want to show that it's their first time.
- Hello. / - Having your first dress shoes...
At age 20.
You can never forget. I still remember too.
Hello.
This is weird.
(They're given a menu)
(What does this mean?)
- But we don't know about wine. / - Of course not.
It was too difficult.
- It's difficult. / - What do we do?
I still don't get wine.
Can you recommend us something?
We don't know much about wine.
The bestselling wine at our bar is
(Ca'Bianca? What?)
(What? I have no idea what he's saying)
I'll tell you what to do as an expert.
Take recommendations and keep
drinking different ones.
Then once you find one that you like,
memorize the name.
Memorize what it's called?
- Memorize the taste. / - Once you memorize that...
That becomes your standard.
Wine starts from there.
- He's Muhammad Ali of drinking. / - Seriously...
You should learn how to drink from Sikyung.
(The bartender leaves)
I can't remember the names.
All I remember is d'Acqui.
Even if I pretend to be an adult, I can't fake it.
It bubbles up a little bit.
So it's easy to enjoy.
It's pretty.
- It looks tasty. / - It's affordable too.
It looks good.
Thank you.
This is awkward.
I feel awkward.
- I feel weird. / - This is too...
That's a pretty sound.
(Stiff)
It's good.
I like how it tickles my nose.
Why does it tickle my nose?
That's the wine bouquet.
- This is the bouquet? / - Yes.
(Yoojung learns about wine bouquet)
You look good with wine.
She seems mature when she's drinking wine.
- It suits her. / - She didn't hunch when she drank wine.
- You're right. / - She sits up straight.
She hunched over when she ate spicy rice cakes.
(Wait, this looks like it's for grownups)
What?
- Gosh, this is weird. / - I know.
- Thank you for the food. / - Thank you.
Eat then drink? Or drink then eat?
- You're such beginners. / - Whichever way you want.
I'll try this first.
(Yoojung and Mina are playing grownups)
It suits her.
- Like she's experienced. / - It suits them.
Mina looks good too.
(Staring at Yoojung)
(What's wrong?)
It feels so weird. I can't believe you're drinking.
I feel the same.
They think it's funny.
Now I can feel
that we're 20.
- This is the last day of our trip. / - Right.
The trip will end after we see the rainbow fountain.
- Don't you feel sad? / - I don't want to go back.
Don't you feel sad? Right?
But the fountain will be great.
- Is it good? / - Yes, it's huge.
Is it?
You can look forward to seeing it.
Can I look forward to it? Alright.
(Darkness falls over Seocheon)
This is the last course of our trip.
Such a shame.
What's that?
That's the Rainbow Bridge.
The lights come on at night.
It's beautiful.
(Jaw-dropping)
They have the best reactions.
- The best. / - Such good reactions.
Isn't it fascinating?
They go up so high.
It feels refreshing to see the fountain in front.
So pretty.
- Wow. / - Wow.
Music, lights, fountain.
- All in sync, right? / - Yes.
It's high enough to reach for the stars.
(The first song is over)
(The next song continues)
("On a Spring Day with Cherry Blossoms" by J-Cera)
Yoojung.
Mina.
It feels somewhat touching.
It feels so good to watch it with your best friend.
(The words "You and Me" appear all of a sudden)
(What's going on?)
Is that possible?
Congratulations.
Wait a minute.
- What's going on? / - I prepared this.
I just got goosebumps.
Ta-da.
- You did this? / - Yeah.
When did you do this?
- Can you make a request in advance? / - Yes.
You can upload words or photos on the homepage.
- Congratulations on being 20. / - Mina, you're so clever.
We're 20...
I feel sad.
You can also display a photo.
Isn't so pretty.
This is so touching.
I can't believe we're 20.
I think we had...
Some time for inner peace. It was so enjoyable.
- You both became 20 this year. / - Right.
She organized it and cried alone.
This is so nice.
When you're with a good friend, you get emotional.
You really do.
It feels so special that we're on
a trip to celebrate the age of 20.
(Yoobom Nabom enjoy their trip to the last moment)
- I bet you'll remember this trip forever. / - Yes.
Right?
We were a team, so we spent a lot of time together...
- But it was our first trip. / - First time.
I came on the first trip of my life after turning 20.
I'm glad that I came here with you.
It feels more special and meaningful with you.
We'll go on a trip together again when we become 30.
- 30? / - That's nice.
It was amazing.
Yoobom Nabom, spring is here!
- Bye. / - Bye.
(The end of Yoojung and Mina's spring)
I feel so bad for Jooe.
- Suddenly? / - Yes.
Because I saw Jooe feel envious
watching their trip.
Which part were you most envious of?
- The bulgogi. / - I knew it.
The macaron and latte.
Food is the best.
I think the bulgogi was the highlight.
- I agree. / - It's true.
The meat is very juicy.
When you eat marinated meat...
- You only taste the sauce. / - Right.
But this one is fresher.
He's right.
When we had the bulgogi, we kept saying
that the meat is so thin but it is very juicy.
- We said that so much. / - Right.
- It just melts in your mouth. / - Yes.
It just melts away.
I was impressed to see so many kinds
of flowers in Korea.
The Netherlands, various countries, Germany...
There were all sorts of countries.
I've never seen such things before.
I have a vague recollection of being there.
You should leave plenty of time for it.
- You're right. / - Yes.
It's a huge place.
Which place was the prettiest?
Our favorite was the Dutch Garden.
There was a huge windmill.
And we could see many other gardens on the way.
So you can enjoy as you go.
Alright.
This is the most important moment.
The total cost of...
- The Yoobom Nabom Tour. / - The cost.
- This is important. / - How much did you spend?
For the overnight trip of the Yoobom Nabom Tour
in Suncheon, Gwangyang, we spent...
How much?
Excluding the KTX fare.
- Per person... / - Per person!
$162.85.
That's very cheap.
- That's including accommodation, right? / - Yes.
- And the entry fee earlier? / - Yes.
- Two cups of latte. / - That's right.
- You ate too much. / - We had too much bulgogi.
Wine...
Would you go to Suncheon and Gwangyang
according to Yoobom Nabom Tour's plan?
Please vote.
(They planned a spring flower trip at 20)
(What will the judges choose?)
The first trip in their 20s isn't over yet.
Right.
It's time to head off to Hadong,
a place you can visit all year round.
(Next week)
It's a first with you.
It feels like we're in a movie here.
Like a pink fairy tale.
I'm so happy right now.
Save in my heart.
Let's go.
(A new spring in the sky)
The view is amazing.
Good view, nice wind.
Let's go.
Will this day ever come back?
(Battle Trip)
("That Day" by Lovelyz)