Let's go!
We're heading to the winery.
There is wine in every one of these?
There is no end.
- Ta-da. / - Wow.
Each island is owned by someone.
- Are we in the U.S. now? / - Yes, we are.
This is cool.
This place has an unexpected charm.
I love it.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Seo Hyorim, Lee Honggi of FTISLAND)
(Wendy and Seulgi of Red Velvet)
(Special host, Lee Teuk)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip.
Continuing on from last week,
we have the trip planners that went to countries
that we'd want to live in.
- Nice to see you again. / - Hello.
You're the winner of the 100th episode.
Stop it.
We have our 100 impartial judges in the audience
who will vote on today's trips.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
To celebrate our 100th episode,
we've been on a same theme for 4 weeks.
Today, we're going to small cities of Austria.
Which cities are there other than Vienna?
- I've been to Austria before. / - You went there.
- Sook. / - It was about 10 years ago.
Every place in Austria is nice.
All the cities are beautiful.
And I liked Hallstatt the most.
Hallstatt is the name of a lake.
- A lake? / - Yes.
The lake is beautiful.
As you walk on a street,
you'll see rambling roses there.
- Right. / - You can see them along the windows.
And it is very leisurely
because there are benches around the lake.
So you can take a rest there.
We mostly think of Switzerland with the Alps.
But the Alps actually lays across many countries
including Italy and Switzerland.
And Austria has more mountains than Switzerland.
There are twice as many mountains in Austria
than in Switzerland.
Two-thirds of Austrian territory
is covered with the Alps.
A lot of the movies have the scenes
where people run as the camera moves back.
I bet you did that.
It's a beautiful country anyway.
Many Austrian sites are listed as
UNESCO World Heritage sites.
- But that's no easy task. / - Right.
Korea also has a lot of UNESCO World Heritage Sites.
- We have Gyeongju. / - Historic district of Gyeongju.
And the Jeju Volcanic Island and Lava Tubes.
Dolmens in Gochang, Hwasun and Ganghwa.
What places do Austria have?
There's the Old Town of Salzburg.
- And Hallstatt that Sook mentioned. / - Hallstatt?
And Graz is the second biggest city in Austria.
The city still has a lot of medieval buildings,
so the whole city is designated as a
UNESCO World Heritage Site.
And there are Melk and Krems
located along the Danube,
and Wachau Cultural Landscape that's
located between those towns are
also listed as UNESCO World Heritage Sites.
And we've been there.
- Did you go there? / - Yes.
Let's look at the map.
- I don't know where they are. / - Let's.
In that area with those cities including Krems,
people have lived for more than a thousand years.
So the places look just as they did in the old days.
That's why they're designated by UNESCO.
If it has a thousand years of history
and listed as a UNESCO World Heritage Site,
everywhere you went probably looked amazing.
There are a lot of villages with grape vines
and popular restaurants in Krems.
You can also visit a beer factory there.
No problems if we have a beer factory.
- Beer factory. / - Whoo!
The city has almost everything.
When you went to Hungary,
the trip designers went to the Danube in Budapest.
- Right. / - They did.
In front of the National Assembly building.
That river starts from Germany
and it passes through Austria to Hungary.
And we crossed the river on a cruise ship.
We'll see the beautiful night view then?
Yes, it will be amazing.
When you are in Austria, you must go to Salzburg.
- Salzburg? / - That's the Santa Clause village.
Salzburg is where Santa came from.
- That's right. / - Really?
- What's her job? / - I didn't know.
Seriously, what is her real job?
She's like a travel writer who does part-time acting.
Acting is her hobby.
- So, they went to Salzburg. / - How did you get there?
Hyorim and Honggi rode in a helicopter.
What did you do in Salzburg?
Did you enjoy activities?
- You should've rode something. / - Of course.
- Tell us. / - We enjoyed the Alps...
And the downtown of Salzburg at once.
- We went paragliding. / - Paragliding?
Please look forward to it.
I want to try paragliding.
Alright. It has "The Sound of Music" and the Alps.
Digidigidip Tour's trip to Austria.
Let's check out the small city trip.
We're going to the small cities of Austria.
It looks different from Canada.
It's pretty already.
(The everlasting medieval city that loves art, Vienna)
We're going really deep today.
Wow, this is huge. I had no idea.
Now this is Europe.
It's like our time together is just ours.
I feel like a local.
(They leave behind their romantic trip in Vienna)
Today is my day.
- It's so pretty. / - The colors are so amazing.
- This is so nice. / - Why is that house so pretty?
Wow, it's so nice here.
I'm so happy just to be walking here.
I remember the scenes from the movies.
We're visiting the places in "The Sound of Music."
Everything is just perfect.
(Their trip becomes even more thrilling)
The world I see is even more beautiful.
- You like? / - I love it!
(Their trip in Austria begins now)
(It's the 3rd day of Digidigidip Tour)
Oh, Bahnhof.
Is that the train station?
Bahnhof means train station.
It's my day today.
You planned today, right? You planned it well, right?
Since it's my day...
I'm getting nervous.
My hobby is discovering songs
that people don't know about.
- That's right. / - I want our trip to be different.
I wanted to find hidden spots
that people wouldn't know about.
- Krems. / - Krems?
And the port in Salzburg.
(Cities for Wendy's Day tour)
(Krems)
(Salzburg)
Krems and the Danube.
- It's so pretty. / - The color is so...
It's so pretty here.
- Hurry over. / - Check out that village.
Right?
They have beer there.
We'll drink some beer at the beer factory.
- I know about Salzburg. / - You do?
- Mozart's hometown. / - It's Mozart's hometown.
Salzburg is famous for "The Sound of Music."
I can't wait to see this.
Wendy looks like a local.
- I totally agree. / - Right.
(Digidigidip Tour, day 1 of Wendy's Day)
(Krems, Salzburg)
(Day 2 of Wendy's Day)
(More activities in Salzburg)
"The Sound of Music" tour sounds good.
It's nerve-racking but still...
- For our... / - Fun trip.
- Wendy. / - Seulgi.
Digidigidip!
Let's go.
I guess you went there by train.
- Yes, we took the train there. / - Yes.
From our hotel, the one-way ticket was $23.
We're in Krems now.
- Krems? / - Yes.
It's the hidden spot I told you about earlier.
The buildings here are pretty and famous.
- It's enlisted on UNESCO too. / - Really?
Didn't I tell you earlier?
Didn't I tell you about the river? The Danube.
- The Danube? / - Yes, this is the Danube.
- Really? / - The second longest river in Europe.
- Seriously? / - Yes.
("The Blue Danube" by Johann Strauss)
(The Danube runs from Germany to Romania)
- This is beautiful. / - Look at the village.
- Oh. It's so picturesque. / - We'll take the cruise...
And admire the scenery and surroundings...
- Of Krems. / - You can go through the river?
You can go around on the cruise.
The villages are on the way.
Since many historical buildings
are well-preserved in Krems...
- It's enlisted on UNESCO. / - Really?
It's so beautiful.
Let's go. Let's go.
- That's great camera work. / - The Danube.
It's a boat.
- Should we go buy our tickets? / - Sure.
I think this is where we go in.
The cruise ticket costs $27.
There's a cruise that leaves at 10:10 a.m.
10:10 a.m.? We can get that one.
I really wanted to try this.
We're in Krems.
(Hopping)
Let's go, let's go.
I think there's a restaurant on the cruise.
Really?
Doesn't that look like a restaurant?
This place is so nice.
(Wow)
(Round ticket from Krems to Spitz, $53.80)
(The view calls for a song)
(Her sweet voice goes well with the scenery)
- It looks peaceful. / - Right?
- Austria looks peaceful. I agree. / - I agree.
I wonder how long this river is.
I think the river runs for about 3,000km.
3,000km? That's huge.
It starts from Germany and ends in Ukraine.
- It's connected all the way there? / - Yes.
That's how long it is.
Many people know it as Donau, its German name.
- In English, it's called the Danube. / - The Danube?
- In Czech, it's called Dunaj. / - Dunaj?
- The names are all different. / - Yes.
Since it's so long,
they must've named it differently in different places.
The view from this spot is so nice.
It's so picturesque.
Ladies and gentlemen.
We are now approaching the most famous town.
Famous town.
Wachau.
I think he's explaining about the town.
Is that so?
(You can see the Wachau Cultural Landscape)
(From up close when you pass Durnstein)
Look over there. Do you see the castle over there?
It's over there. Can you see it?
King Richard was held captive in that castle.
Really?
How did they manage to build a castle there?
It hasn't changed.
That means it's really old.
So cool.
We're getting close.
- Durnstein Castle. / - It's so pretty.
This isn't the monastery, right?
- It's really pretty. / - Aren't the colors beautiful?
When we were facing it, the colors were beautiful.
- Right. / - Seriously.
The footage doesn't do the justice. In person...
- The colors looked so pretty. / - Hey.
Look at that.
(They move onto the next town)
This is wonderful.
Wendy, how long does it take...
- To Spitz on the cruise? / - 1 hour and 30 minutes.
- You can take your time with it. / - Yes.
Every corer was so pretty.
This town is called Spitz.
- Spitz? / - Yes.
Doesn't it look cute?
I can see the fields right away.
Right? The houses are so pretty.
(The scenery that reminds them of a fairy tale)
I love the sound of birds chirping.
Listen to the chirping.
What will we do now?
We should look around this town since we're here.
- That's why we'll rent bicycles. / - Bicycles?
(Bicycle rental in Spitz, $32 per day)
Is that it?
Segway...
We're not riding that, right?
- That's not a bike. / - I want to ride that.
I want to try that too.
It'd be nice to try it out since you're on a trip.
- That was sudden. / - Hey.
(Zoom)
Seulgi, you look so cool.
Let's go.
(Why is Wendy envious of Seulgi?)
I didn't know I would fall like that.
- I wanted to ride a bicycle. / - You can't ride it?
I don't know how to ride bikes.
- Really? / - Yes.
Then did you ride it after learning how?
- Yes. / - The rental shop gave me a basic lesson.
You look cute.
My eyebrows are pushed down.
Hey, you look a bit angry now.
Her eyes have been drawn together.
Let's go.
(They finally set out)
You're pretty good.
♪Ring, ring ♪
Hey, this is great. This feels so relaxing.
??Out of my way please ??
Since this is an electric bicycle,
it doesn't require a lot of energy.
- That's right. It's electric. / - That was electric?
- Yes. / - This is beautiful.
- This is so nice. / - Why is that house so pretty?
Hey, aren't these houses so beautiful?
What's that?
That flower is beautiful.
That doesn't look like a house.
I feel like I'm in a fairy tale. A world in a fairy tale.
There are a lot of pretty flowers here.
(When they pass through the hill between the houses)
- Gosh, this is nice. / - The town was so pretty.
Wendy is floating like a ghost.
- With a white robe. / - Standing upright.
(A ghost at the vineyard?)
Gosh, she looks so scary.
- This is hilarious. / - Behind her...
The downhill is slightly scary.
She's a ghost.
She does look like a ghost.
Please film her whole body.
- You only filmed her upper body. / - This is nice.
- She's chasing her. / - She keeps following.
- I love how fresh the air is. / - She's the ghost.
I've never seen anyone...
- Create laughs with a Segway. / - So funny.
(Currently, they're on an uphill at the vineyard)
- You're following me, right? / - Yes.
- My legs are getting tired. / - Look at her face.
- That bicycle... / - She looks totally exhausted.
I'm not good at riding a bicycle.
- Her legs are giving way. / - I love the smell here.
I'm tired. I'm so exhausted.
(Argh)
(You said it was easy earlier)
(In the midst of her struggle on the uphill)
- Are you keeping up? / - Yes.
Am I the only one struggling here?
I'm not tired.
My eyebrows are getting tired.
Her eyebrows are getting tired.
They've come down too much.
Her eyebrows have sunk.
It must be hard to keep your eyes open.
That's cute.
(At last, it's a downhill)
Come on.
Be careful.
(Wendy successfully climbs down too)
- Great. / - Gosh, that was scary.
- You did well. / - But that was fun.
The colors are beautiful.
This is like a movie set.
(This small town looks like a movie set)
Hey, this part looks so pretty.
Come quickly. Hurry, hurry.
(They want to stop for a moment and look around)
Hey, look at this.
This is like a movie set.
(The scenery turns them into the main characters)
How pretty.
I'm jealous that the residents here get to see this
every day.
- Aren't you getting thirsty? / - I'm thirsty.
- I prepared some drinks. Yes. / - Really?
- What is that? Why is it so big? / - Radler.
Radler means cyclist.
A lot of people here ride bicycles.
- Right. / - It's a light beer.
- It smells like beer. / - People always drink that.
They drink it after biking around.
- They drink it like a beverage? / - Yes.
It quenches your thirst.
It's like mixing lemonade with beer.
- It's lemon beer. / - 2%?
- A light beer with only 2% alcohol. / - It's nice.
- Isn't it refreshing? / - Yes, it is.
And I love the sound of the flowing water.
Everything. Did you hear that?
- Impeccable timing. / - It's 1 o'clock.
The bell is ringing for us.
- It looks like a commercial. / - It looks so beautiful.
- It's a commercial. / - It's a sports drink commercial.
I love the sound of the bell.
- But I'm hungry. / - I was about to say that too.
Let's go and have our lunch.
(Depart from Spitz, arrive in Krems)
Aren't you hungry?
That's why I found a restaurant...
- Where we can eat right away. / - Right away?
- This one? / - Yes.
It was next to the ticket booth.
That's right.
This is a restaurant not that many people know about.
- Really? / - We eat as we watch the Danube.
The location is prime.
We can enjoy the romance
while enjoying a good meal.
- Let's get a glass of beer outside. / - On the terrace.
That's a great shot.
What's that doing there?
- Exactly. / - It was really good.
This is the place, Seulgi.
This is nice.
We'll be eating on the terrace.
With a river view.
- I'm starving. / - Right?
You must eat at a place like that.
- Burger. Vegetarian. / - What's famous here?
- I want to visit there. / - We had this yesterday.
- The short rib soup? / - Yes.
But we've had too much meat.
I want to eat something different.
What is this one?
Sea bream?
Is that some kind of a fish?
- If it is, let's get that. / - Right?
It is fish.
- lt's a blackhead sea bream. / - Blackhead?
- Let's get this one. / - Isn't that expensive in Korea?
The prices are about the same.
- Then we should order this. / - Let's get one of that.
This one. What about this one?
Wachau Breaded Chicken Burger.
It's local bread...
We saw a cathedral on the cruise.
It's made there.
This comes with pumpkin seed mayonnaise.
- Apricots again. / - The mayonnaise sounds good.
- Pumpkin seed mayonnaise? / - That sounds good.
This is apricot jam.
- That's right, they ate apricots then. / - Apricot jam.
Austrians eat a lot of apricots.
Really?
This is so good.
They add apricots in many dishes. I saw this earlier...
- There's an apricot festival. / - Really?
Let's get that.
And the one from earlier.
We should get a glass of beer.
What is this?
Here you are.
Does the head normally looks like this?
How can it look so pretty?
- Is it cream? / - You can tell it's good from the glass.
- What is this? How? / - I learned to enjoy beer...
- After drinking that. / - You need to gulp that down.
Check out the bubbles.
(A sip of draft beer feels cooler on a hot summer day)
- Amazing. / - Cheers.
- Prost. / - Isn't the foam really firm?
(Surprised)
(This is the swag of draft beer)
- What's that? What is it? / - How can that be?
- We just clinked our glasses. / - Is that baking soda?
Is it fake?
- Prost. / - Did someone raise the foam?
- No, no one did that. / - Don't get the wrong idea.
Both of us didn't know how good beer could taste.
- Well... / - That's when we found out.
- You can only taste that there. / - Right.
This is good.
- Does draft beer taste this good? / - Draft beer.
This is how draft beer is supposed to taste like.
It's clean.
It's not that bitter, right?
Some plates to share. Here you are.
Thank you.
I feel like something amazing will be served.
Will a whole sea bream be served?
To share, we have the Mediterranean vegetables.
Even the potatoes look good.
- Enjoy your food. / - Thank you very much.
Hey, I think this will taste great.
At last.
- We'll finally get to eat a fish. / - It's a whole fish.
The sea bream is here.
We can separate it like this.
Can you see this?
- See how milky white this is. / - It's milky white.
This looks really delicious.
- Look at the milky white fish meat. / - It's plump.
But you know how sea bream is expensive in Korea...
Try it. Hurry up and try this.
- It's expensive in Korea. / - Yes.
I didn't know they'd serve us a whole fish.
The grilled sea bream was $22.
- But it's huge. / - $22?
We only have sea bream raw...
- Because it's expensive. / - Right.
But steamed or grilled sea bream is really delicious.
- It was really good. / - I didn't know.
It's so good.
It's not fishy. It's tender.
- That looks amazing. / - It was so tender.
- White rice goes well with that. / - White rice?
It's not fishy at all. It's very tender.
To be honest, food from overseas might be a bit salty.
- It's not salty. / - Yes. Isn't it perfectly seasoned?
They put something on top. What could this be?
- It's like the spinach from yesterday. / - Right.
It taste like thistle and spinach.
That makes the dish fragrant and
enhances the flavors.
We should eat the skin too.
- You like skin. / - I like skin.
- Let's keep eating. / - They finished the whole fish.
Yes, like that.
(Feeling excited)
- That's a waste. / - It must've been really good.
- I'll hold this. / - It was really good.
We can't let even a piece go to waste.
- They thoroughly finished it. / - If only they had rice.
- Honggi keeps asking for white rice. / - Yes.
Hey, we have to eat this too.
- You had the burger too. / - Yes.
But the fish is so good.
- Let's try a bit of this too. / - Sure.
That looks delicious.
They added apricot jam in it.
- It's fried chicken Honggi likes. / - But the apricot...
- A chicken burger. / - That burger looks really tasty.
They added apricots in it. Isn't this apricot?
Try it.
- It's served with the burger. / - Wasn't it good?
Yesterday, when we had the meat dish,
we ate it with ground apples and radishes.
It was refreshing.
And we had the raspberry sauce with schnitzel,
it was refreshing.
Wouldn't this be somewhat similar?
Fried chicken is tasty everywhere.
Look at this. Can you see it?
(So filling)
Homemade bun.
I'm going to try it.
You should've squeezed it.
- It was too big. / - I couldn't. It was too big.
I couldn't press it.
- Press it. Press it hard. / - Don't get all riled up.
- Bite it as you suck in the air. / - Like that?
It's really unique with the apricot jam.
- It's good. / - That must be...
The pumpkin seed mayonnaise.
It's huge.
- I can taste it. / - The pumpkin seed mayonnaise.
If it has mayonnaise in it,
it's game over.
- Watch the roof of your mouth. / - Can't not like it.
You have to try the meat with the apricot.
Isn't it good?
This makes you smile like a mom.
The fried chicken patty is salty. It's well-seasoned.
The apricot is refreshing.
The mix of these two balances out the flavors.
It's sweet and salty at the same time.
- Seriously. / - That's right.
How can the chicken be this good?
Yes, the fried chicken is so good.
(She has another bite of the crispy fried chicken)
No.
Don't spill out.
(Chomp)
(Great reactions even when she eats)
(This needs no words. It's truly delicious)
I'm almost done with mine.
- This is good. / - They eat really well.
- Right? / - Right.
It's the apricot from earlier.
(She finishes the last bite without any hesitation)
(Licking)
- Plus the beer. / - Look at her close her eyes.
The meal tastes better on the terrace.
It's cool too.
(She gulps down her draft beer too)
Wasn't it good?
- Yes. / - Wasn't it tasty?
Earlier, you seemed to really like this beer.
- So we'll go to a beer factory. / - Really?
There's a famous beer factory in Austria.
- It's a beer factory. / - It's a beer factory.
- That looks good. / - Wow.
- It's the same beer we drank. / - That's awesome.
- How does Austrian beer taste? / - It's that beer.
(The charm of Austrian beer we didn't know about)
How is it? Is it good?
- It's so good. / - It tasted so...
- Was it amazing? / - It was different.
(21 minutes from Krems Station by shuttle bus)
We have arrived at the beer factory. We're here.
A beer factory.
- My first time. / - Isn't this your first time?
It's my first time too.
Will we be able to watch the process of making beer?
Yes.
We'll be able to taste it too.
Taste it too.
- Is this right? / - By the way...
??Taste, chew, enjoy ??What was it?
It's "Eat, chew, taste, enjoy."
- Are you going to be like this? / - "Eat, chew..."
"Taste, enjoy?"
Can you do it with me?
2, 3, 4.
??Eat, chew, taste, enjoy ??
(It's embarrassing)
(She's immersed)
You're good.
It's this way.
Is this the entrance?
Let me escort you.
Welcome to our brewery.
Before we enter,
we kindly ask you to wear our safety vests.
- Okay. / - Ah, yeah.
(They put on safety vests to be spotted easily)
I like the color.
She likes the vest.
So, let's go upstairs.
Yes. Okay.
(They take off to have a tour around the factory)
(When you go up the stairs)
It's pretty hot.
It was really hot.
- Like a sauna. / - Why is it hot?
(It's the beginning of the beer making process)
- What? / - Because of the fermentation.
They ferment the raw ingredients at over 100??
- They ferment it here. / - Yes.
They do that here.
There's a certain law in Europe
that regulates people to use only malt,
hops and water to make beer.
Add something else, and it can't be called beer.
What's that?
Hop in a crusher.
Crusher?
It's ground hops.
They mix the ground ingredients with water
and boil it in heat.
Then they use the one next to filter it.
They add the hops and boil it again.
Then they filter it again.
And the state it's in just before completion...
Which we call original wort.
It's called wort. They call it beer wort.
Next step is that we want to have alcohol.
- So we start the fermentation. / - Fermentation, okay.
(They pour some beer right after fermentation)
(The fresh taste will be revealed soon)
(What's the next spot?)
(Her jaw drops)
I smell the beer.
- Is this the smell of the beer? / - Beer, yeah.
I've never seen a factory up close like this.
(They can see the process of packaging beer)
- I can smell the beer. / - It's no joke.
(Amazed)
- Is that the one? / - Canned beer.
The machine can produce
50,000 cans of beer in 1 hour.
- Wow. / - It's really fast.
- Awesome. / - Really fast.
(Next is where the beer gets the final fermentation)
It's cold in here.
(It's freezing)
Now, you'll try it.
Drink beer...
- Directly from the tank. / - It must be delicious.
Is this the tank?
It's where we can taste the beer
directly from the tank.
It's real draft beer.
It's coming out from this tank, right?
He's pouring beer directly.
- Really. / - Wow.
Look at the froth.
- The froth is like whipped cream. / - It contains...
- All kinds of minerals and proteins. / - You ready?
You know all the nutrients.
It's all in here.
Really?
- Look at its color. / - It's murky.
- You're right. / - It's very soft too.
It's murky because everything is inside that beer.
- It's pretty yellow. / - There's a lot of froth.
- As we say in Austria, prost. / - Prost.
- To your house. / - Prost.
(Cheers)
It's really good.
(Gulping)
(Her eyes know the taste of beer)
It's delicious.
(Cheers one more time)
(Beer is going down their throats)
It tastes like I won't get drunk.
You want more?
Just a bit more.
(Seulgi can't lose to her)
You want more too?
(Yes, please)
It's delicious even if I keep drinking.
(Brewery tour, $12.30 for 2 glasses of beer and a bread)
(It's open for tours 3 times a week)
(More details are written on the website)
(Exclaiming together)
Drinking it directly out of the tank...
It doesn't taste like beer I used to know.
It's really good.
It was sparkling.
- It was amazing. / - I bet it's delicious.
- Its taste depends on distribution. / - I see.
I think I should drink beer at a beer factory from now.
There isn't any beer factory in our country.
People can go on a tour around the factory like that?
- They can make a reservation... / - So they can.
Through the website.
- You need prior reservations. / - Right.
Shall we leave with an excited heart?
Let's clink before we go.
- Wendy. / - Seulgi.
Digidigidip.
- Di. / - Gi.
Dip!
Seulgi, let's leave for
the city of music, the hometown of Mozart now.
- Let's go... / - To that place.
Let's go.
(On a train to Salzburg)
A train ticket to Salzburg costs $63.
- It's one-way. / - Okay.
I can't believe we're in Austria.
I just can't believe it.
Now that we're on a train,
I'm reminded of "Before Sunrise."
Their love starts on a train.
I remember that.
(Their coincidental relationship starts on a train)
(It's a romantic love story of European train trips)
I don't know about this movie but
I feel like I should watch it.
I highly recommend it.
Let's say you met a guy
by accident like the movie.
You talked to each other for a short period of time.
Then he suddenly suggests you should get off.
Would you get off then?
I think I would.
If I was really attracted to that guy.
I think it'd be too short of a time
to get to know each other.
- I wouldn't get off. / - But what if...
What if you two were so compatible?
What if you guys got along so well?
I might make a plan to see him.
- Oh, later? / - Yes.
I think I'm a bit spontaneous.
We're heading to Salzburg right now.
What are our plans there?
Our plans?
(They soak deeply into the city of music)
Wow, it's so pretty here.
- It looks delicious. / - What's that?
It looks really tasty.
I'm so happy. What do I do?
I love just walking here.
I'm reminded of the scenes in the movie.
These are the places in "The Sound of Music."
Everything here is just perfect.
The world seems even more beautiful.
(They fly in the sky of Salzburg and Alps)
We're flying.
(Wendy's Day in Salzburg)
(Salzburg)
(Tasting Austrian dessert)
- We arrived in Salzburg. / - Right.
What is there that we like?
Aside from sightseeing and shopping?
- Of course, eating. / - Right?
There's something...
- We must try in Austria. / - What is it?
It's the must-try dessert
and the must-try coffee.
- It's Sachertorte. / - You know that?
- Is it famous? / - It's also sold...
At Hotel Sacher in Vienna.
It's really famous.
- What's that? / - Is that cake?
It's only sold in Salzburg.
- It's only sold in Salzburg? / - Yes.
It only exists in this region.
It was so rare in the past.
Only noble people could have the chance to eat it.
- Are you ready? / - I am.
Let's walk in like sophisticated ladies.
- Like noble ladies. / - Okay.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Didn't you say there are only two...
- Of this cafe in the country? / - Yes.
A lot of global celebrities visited this place too.
It is this place.
It's the evidence that many celebrities visited here.
There's the name on the picture. Hugh Grant.
- They recorded all the celebrities. / - Hugh Grant.
Yes.
- All the celebrities visited there. / - Cameron Diaz.
There's a picture of Tom Hanks too.
- Tom Hanks. / - He looks young in the picture.
She's Maria.
- Heroine of "The Sound of Music." / - That's right.
- ??Do, re, mi ??/ - Seriously.
I really want to hear that.
This place used to serve to the royal family.
Right, I heard that too.
It seems like an art museum.
Right, museum.
The interior of this place
makes me feel like I'm really in Europe.
I can sense the old European-style in the interior.
It must have a really long history.
(Its antique beauty from 150 years of history)
Places in Austria have 200 to 300 years of history.
100 to 200 years at least.
Our first dessert...
- Is called Nockerl. / - Nockerl?
You can't find this dessert anywhere else but here.
- It's sold only in Salzburg? / - Right.
The meringue symbolizes the three mountain peaks
surrounding the city.
- The dessert looks like mountains? / - Right.
(It has the shape of 3 mountain peaks)
- It looks so good. / - Did they make the meringue...
And torch it?
- A little. / - They torched...
- The top part. / - Right?
It's served with jam.
(Nockerl, $25)
It looks delicious.
(It makes the girls excited)
It looks so pretty.
That's one huge dessert.
- It looks good. / - They serve it for you.
It's so soft.
She serves it like that.
- It's a bit like... / - I'd like to put it in my mouth.
It's like cheese cake.
- Do you have a sweet tooth? / - Yes, I do.
It'll melt away in your mouth.
(She scoops some strawberry cream as well)
It looks like you eat them together.
I forgot to take a picture of it.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Enjoy.
(Wow)
It's hard to make meringue like this.
Really hard.
I've always wanted to do this.
Seriously, it's hard to make meringue like this.
It looks like a baby's bottom.
It's so hard to make meringue like this.
Did you hear that?
Did you hear the sound of the meringue?
I want to record the sound.
- It's amazing, isn't it? / - I heard it.
- Good job, me. / - Well done.
- I heard it. / - Good job, Wendy.
(Here it goes again)
It smells like a tasty pancake.
It does. I smell eggs. Let's try.
- I don't know. / - It must melt in your mouth.
- It melts, doesn't it? / - Yes, it melts like foam.
It melts away in my mouth like foam.
- It just melts away. / - When you feel down...
- This will cheer you up. / - I'm sure it will.
It feels like a fluffy pancake
that melts in your mouth.
- There's nothing to chew. / - You're right.
It just melts away.
Do we have something like that in Korea as well?
- No, we don't. / - We don't, right?
I like the outer part.
- The baked part. / - That baked part is...
- It must be delicious. / - It is.
I'll try it with the cream.
That alone can be a bit too rich
but the strawberry cream
makes it taste refreshing.
(Mmm)
I think I get why they eat it with the cream.
Just this alone can be a bit too rich.
But the cream helps with it.
(Their coffee is served)
Yes. I needed coffee.
- This is Einspanner. / - Einspanner.
That's Viennese Coffee.
- Viennese Coffee. / - Exactly.
- This is Melange. / - Melange.
You know how we rode in that carriage?
I heard people used to drink coffee
while riding carriages.
It's shaky on a carriage.
But Einspanner doesn't spill.
- Oh, really? / - Because of the cream on top.
Because the coffee spills on a carriage,
they put cream on top of it.
- The cream keeps it down. / - Yes.
Also, it keeps the coffee warm.
It doesn't spill. What comfort.
Are you talking about a bed or what?
(She's tries the Einspanner)
- Drink it up. / - All you get is the cream.
- You'll only taste the cream. / - That's true.
You have to finish the cream first.
- Then drink the coffee. / - It might go into your nose.
You look so cute.
The coffee doesn't taste that bitter
because of the cream.
(She tries the Melange as well)
This is Melange.
It's delicious.
It's really soft.
It's a bit nutty.
It tastes like Job's tears tea.
- Job's tears tea? / - Job's tears tea?
Suddenly that place looks like a Korean tea room.
It was very nutty.
(Finally, Sachertorte is served)
- Sachertorte. / - Sachertorte.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
This is the most famous dessert here.
I heard this was a must-try.
Torte means cake.
- Torte means cake? / - Yes.
Back in the old days, sugar was rare.
Chocolate was a delicacy only for the nobles.
It's a fancy cake with apricot jam in it.
- It's a very fancy cake. / - It has apricot jam in it.
- They put apricot jam in there too. / - Always apricots.
Which part should I eat first?
However you like.
They're well-known for apricot jam.
- Is this apricot jam? / - Is this apricot jam?
We just had the same thought.
Is this apricot jam?
Try it. Try it already.
Please try it.
Let me try it without the cream first.
(How does it taste?)
I can taste the apricot jam.
My friend said it tastes like a fancy Vic Pie.
My friend said that.
- A fancy one. / - Vic Pie?
A fancy Vic Pie.
My gosh.
It tastes very rich.
It's good, isn't it? This is delicious.
Is she going to say something else?
Why did she compare this to that?
I can't understand that at all.
My friend said that. Don't you think they taste similar?
Who is this friend?
- Who is this friend? / - Who is it?
I think I need to talk to her.
Why would she compare this to that?
It's really tasty with the cream.
I haven't gone to many restaurants
nor am I a gourmet...
But the chocolate is chewy and soft.
As you see, there is a very thin layer of apricot jam.
- But it tastes so strong. / - How is it possible?
- It's so thin. / - It's so thin.
But it's perfect with the chocolate.
What's important is the combination of
the sweetness and the freshness.
- You're right. / - It's moderately fresh...
- And moderately sweet. / - And moderately sweet.
When the balance collapses,
it will taste like nothing.
She sounds like an expert.
You sound like a gourmet.
(Proud)
(She takes a sip of coffee after eating the cake)
They taste perfect together.
They enhance each other's flavor.
- You really like sweets. / - It's made of raspberry...
Normally, Seulgi and I...
- Don't eat a lot of dessert. / - We don't eat desserts.
We don't like cakes and don't eat them often.
That's the first time I had so many desserts in my life.
They must've been a perfect match.
(She takes the last bite)
(Happy)
Save it in your stomach.
(She's really enjoying it)
It's delicious. This is so good.
I think I will miss this in Korea.
I didn't know we would eat two desserts.
I'm looking forward to our upcoming schedules.
Are you ready to have fun?
- Wendy. / - Seulgi.
Digidigidip.
Go.
(The first day of Wendy's Day was successful)
(Second morning in Salzburg)
(Wendy's Day, Salzburg)
("The Sound of Music" tour)
- They're finally going there. / - Finally.
This seems to be the perfect weather
for what I prepared.
What did you prepare? What's with our costumes?
- It's a dirndl. / - A dirndl?
Yes, it's the traditional Austrian outfit.
I like colors that stand out, so I picked red.
When we think of traditional clothes in Austria...
This comes to mind.
I'm wearing something from the Middle Ages.
The Middle Ages?
Are there people walking around in those clothes?
- There are. / - There are a lot of them.
A lot of children wear them too.
(I'm wearing a dirndl)
Where are we going in these costumes?
Where are we going?
"The Sound of Music."
- Have you seen the movie? / - No.
But I remember that scene on the Alps
where they sing the "Do Re Mi" song.
It's the famous scene.
That was the most impressive scene.
(A movie based on the true story of the Trapp family)
(Filmed in Salzburg, a lot of tourists visit the set)
The movie makes me well up even now.
The music is so great.
I prepared a tour for you.
There are two kinds.
There's one where you ride a big bus
with others and look around.
There's an actual "The Sound of Music" tour.
- Yes. / - Yes, there is.
There's another one that's more private.
You can see things in greater detail.
The private tour is limited in time.
After the first 4 hours,
you have to pay extra every hour.
Nice to meet you, I'm Wendy.
Nice to meet you. Good morning.
- I'm Seulgi. / - Nice to meet you.
So, first we start by looking around
the Mirabell Garden.
- Follow me. / - Okay.
(Seulgi and Wendy's Digidigidip Tour)
(Mirabell Garden)
(It's in front of the palace that was built in 1606)
(It's a famous spot for a dreamy, romantic wedding)
("The Sound of Music" tour begins here)
- It's nice here. / - It's beautiful.
Mirabell means nice view in Spanish.
From here, the stairs...
It's a nice view.
- Ready? / - It's very nice.
- It's very broad. / - It is.
- Where is... / - People have weddings there.
- Perfect spot? / - Nicest spot is right here.
- Right here? / - Right here. Turn around.
You have a nice view of the garden.
(Doesn't this remind you of a scene from the movie?)
- Is this it? / - Yes.
It looks exactly the same.
(It's exactly like in the movie from over 50 years ago)
It hasn't changed.
We built a fortress.
I wonder what fortress it is.
What's the name of the fortress over there?
It's called Hohensalzburg Fortress.
It's the big castle on top of the mountain
to protect the city.
- It was never seized? / - No.
- It looks cool. / - It hasn't change since back then.
- Yes. / - It looks exactly the same.
(It's where Maria gets close with the children)
(The musical staircase)
The "Do Re Mi" song. This is here.
The children walked around here during that song.
If you want to, you can step up here
and walk along there.
Then you feel like the children.
Look at that.
(It's Wendy's favorite scene)
(After being educated in a strict military style)
(The children gain their innocence through this song)
It's a very old movie.
It's amazing the places still remain the same.
It's been 50 years.
Everything there is older than me.
Look on your left, there's Dwarf Garden.
They're also shown in the movie.
(Dwarves with comical expressions)
(Especially, this dwarf)
I have a picture taken right here.
- Really? / - Yes.
(Wendy's nick name is Fun Wendy)
He has a lump.
The look on her face is so pretty.
It looks like this.
- I can do this. / - Honggi looks the same.
I can do this.
(Scanning)
She gives it a try.
- Look at that. / - It won't be easy.
- I look the same, don't I? / - She's so cute.
(She's good)
This is fun, imitating the dwarves.
It looks so beautiful.
- It's well-maintained. / - It's a beautiful country.
(Mirabell Garden)
(Leopoldskron Palace)
This place was beautiful.
It's like a picture.
(Leopoldskron Palace is a rococo style building)
Rococo style.
(Located next to a small lake named Lake Weiher)
(In the movie, it was Captain Von Trapp's mansion)
(The huge mansion has a beautiful lake at the back)
(Except for the exterior, all the scenes were shot on set)
It's so beautiful.
- I want to live here. / - Me too.
- I heard it's now being used as a hotel. / - Yes.
It'll be great to stay in that hotel.
You can see the lake as you open the window.
Even if don't stay in the hotel...
- I'm just happy to walk down the road here. / - True.
It reminds me of the movie scenes.
- They were riding on a boat. / - That's right.
You should watch the movie again before visiting.
It looks even better with the sunshine.
I want to live here.
The clouds and mountains.
- The hotel is reflected on the lake. / - It's beautiful.
- And the sky is reflected too. / - It's the sky.
- It was beautiful. / - It looks amazing.
It's lovely.
It looks like a painting.
- The weather is so nice. / - It was so beautiful.
It was seriously so beautiful.
(Mirabell Garden, Leopoldskron Palace)
(St. Gilgen)
(They drive an hour to the lake)
Isn't this the song that plays at the start of the movie?
(It's the best opening scene in the history of cinema)
The music keeps playing in the car?
Yes. He keeps playing the songs for each place.
- Songs for each place? / - Yes.
- It's part of the tour package. / - That's so nice.
Welcome to the countryside.
(Wow)
(The blue sky and fairy-tale houses)
- It's just so... / - It just makes you applaud.
That's right. It just makes me clap.
It'd be great to live in a house like this.
This is the place of my dreams.
I know.
- It looks like a picture. / - It seems like a fairy-tale.
Look at the color of the sky.
It feels like I'm dreaming.
I think nature is the most beautiful thing.
If you find a husband, you can start a family.
I don't want to go back to Korea.
(Looking around)
Are those the Alps?
- All the Alps. / - He says they're the Alps.
It goes from France to Vienna.
The Alps.
- You know Mont Blanc? / - Mont Blanc? Yes.
Mont Blanc.
Here, the highest mountain
is Grossglockner. Almost 4,000m.
And one here next to...
(Grossglockner, 3,798m above sea level)
This place makes women become girls.
That's how it feels.
(They pass a small church)
- The first... / - It's so small.
It's tiny.
Wow.
(The last course of "The Sound of Music" tour)
He told us to close our eyes...
- And open them then? / - Yes.
And this lake spread out before our eyes.
It was beautiful.
It looks the same.
This is the last course of today's trip.
- You prepared a lot. / - You're hungry, aren't you?
Yes, I'm a little hungry.
We should have a picnic at a place like this.
Women love that.
At a place like this. We should spread a mat.
- Shall we eat? / - Yes!
- Let's enjoy. / - Okay.
Okay. Let's eat. I'm hungry.
She brought a lot of fruits.
I'll eat it enjoying the view.
Admire the beautiful scenery.
Take a bite of the pear.
She planned a great day.
It looks like a picture on the calendar.
It's sweet.
It tastes like a jujube.
- Is it a pear? / - Right. It's a pear.
The pear is like a jujube apple.
It's more like a jujube than a pear.
It tastes good anyway.
The lake behind me had the color of emerald.
- You must've loved it. / - It looks amazing.
- It was lovely. / - My gosh.
I didn't know I'd have a picnic here.
It looks like a composite picture.
- I think so. / - I know.
With a chroma key green screen.
- That's the scene. / - Right. I remember the scene.
I'm so happy that I can have a picnic
with such a beautiful view.
I really want to live here.
It looks wonderful. I really want to go there.
I don't know why but it feels like
I'll sing better if I go there.
With the fresh air and pretty view,
I feel like I'll be able to sing better.
Thank you for preparing all this.
- You know the "Do Re Mi" song. / - Yes.
We can make a song of our own.
Okay. Let's do that.
We should come up with a word about do.
Seulgi always tries things like that.
"A city we'd want to live in."
??A city we'd want to live in ??
- Re, Red Velvet is here. / - Because we're here.
Red Velvet came to this beautiful city.
Mi is...
- Mi that means beauty. / - That sounds nice.
Mi for beauty.
(Mi for beauty)
They are covering their faces again.
- It doesn't sound right. / - When did you sing it?
We even recorded the song.
(Fa for the pretty blue sky)
(Sol for the scent of flowers)
(La for a humming song)
(Ti for the beginning)
(Our Battle Trip)
My goodness.
Oh, no.
(Do, re mi, fa, sol, la, ti, do)
(Cringe)
Honggi, please help me out.
I need help myself.
Seulgi is having a meltdown.
They keep shooting a movie.
- Di. / - Gi.
Dip!
(Digidigidip Tour, Wendy's Day)
(Grain Lane)
Seulgi, this is the Grain Lane.
It's so beautiful.
I was surprised as soon as I got here.
The signs are especially beautiful here.
They are very old.
- At least 200 years old. / - 200 years?
Yes. About 200 years.
Really?
Some are like 300 to 400 years old.
All the signs are specially made...
- For each shop. / - Right.
- There's nothing of the same. / - That's 400 years old.
I heard Mozart's birthplace is on the street.
(It's the main street of the old downtown of Salzburg)
Designers go there and take a lot of pictures.
They take pictures of all the signs there
and study design with them.
It's interesting that the signs have pictures.
In Korea, we only have letters.
The illiteracy rate was high in the past.
So they added pictures to help people
recognize the signs.
"This is a shoe store
and that is a clothing store." Like that?
Big pictures.
They used pictures instead of letters.
(The signs made for utilitarian purposes)
(They are now the brand that represents the street)
Every sign is so pretty.
They're like Christmas tree ornaments.
They are so pretty.
- It feels like Christmas. / - Right?
This place must be amazing during Christmas.
It must be beautiful.
Seulgi, aren't you hungry?
- I'm very hungry. / - There's a sausage place.
Let's go to the famous restaurant and eat.
Okay.
Let's go.
??Shall we enter to eat sausages? ??
This is the place.
- Is this it? / - Yes.
- It's such a random location. / - Right?
- Is it a famous restaurant? / - They sell hot dogs.
(Take a byway on the main street)
It's hard to find the restaurant.
It's so hidden.
It's inside the alley.
(A takeout hotdog stand that opened in the 1950s)
Look at the long queue.
- This has to be delicious. / - It was so good.
- Look at the bread. / - It looks so good.
Let's sit here.
Cheers.
(Crispy)
(It sounds appetizing)
(They like it)
The bread looks like a baguette,
so I thought it would be hard and chewy.
Honestly, I thought it would hurt my teeth.
- I thought it'd be too chewy. / - But...
It's so soft. It breaks so easily.
Can you see it?
It's like a very soft biscuit.
- The crust is... / - It's like a biscuit.
It's so soft and warm.
- It looks so delicious. / - It was really good.
- I love this. / - Me too.
(They eat)
(And eat)
It's so big. Two people can share one.
You made up for not eating much there.
The sausage is not a normal sausage.
- It's a bit spicy. / - This spiciness...
- Is it because of the powder? / - I think so.
Is that turmeric powder?
- It's curry powder. / - What I like the most is...
That there are two sausages.
You like that there are two sausages?
I'm so moved.
I'm so moved that there are two sausages in it.
Seriously, this is moving.
They give you two sausages.
They know that one isn't enough.
She's so happy to have two sausages.
I love hotdogs.
- You love hotdogs? / - Yes.
You haven't tried it, have you?
Overseas it's...
- She eats so well. / - She's so cute.
She keeps eating at a moderate speed.
She does.
She quietly goes hard.
It must be so delicious.
You're so fast.
Make the last bite look really delicious.
(I'm already finished)
I'm finished.
Paragliding.
Can you do that?
I'm thinking whether I should add it to the list or not.
But there...
Korea and Europe have different sceneries.
So I think it'll be fun.
- This seems like a must-try in Salzburg. / - Really?
Then how about we try it?
Let's just go like that.
What?
- We're doing something harder. / - We are?
(Screaming)
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
I'm flying.
Oh, my God.
(Paragliding in the Alps)
(Look down Salzburg and the nature of the Alps)
(Flight lasts about 20 minutes, $158 per person)
Why did I bring you here?
- Why did I bring myself here? / - You planned this.
Do you think you can do it?
You look more scared than me. I'll go first.
If you don't do it, I won't either.
Is that how it works?
Yes. If you don't do it, I won't.
- Hello. / - Hello, hello.
- Paragliding? / - Yes, we are.
Are you excited?
- Nervous. / - Nervous.
Everybody is.
It's super easy.
As soon as you're in the air, you'll enjoy it.
Are you sure?
Are you sure it's easy?
Today, we will take off on the other side.
Do you want to have a more challenging take off?
- More challenging? / - Yes.
- What is he saying? / - The smallest takeoff...
At the steepest part.
He's saying we're doing something more difficult.
We are?
- It's our first time. / - It's our first time.
- That's okay. / - Just kidding.
Just kidding.
(His joke scared them)
There's always people who make jokes like that.
They're laid-back.
I don't know. Let's just jump.
It shouldn't be that hard.
Let's just go like that.
(Spaced out)
- It won't be scary. / - It won't.
You can put this on here.
You do this...
This one looks okay.
Can you hold this for a second?
I feel good now.
Don't we have to tighten this more?
They will do it for us.
I can't believe my life will be left to that rope.
That rope looks so weak.
In flight, we're connected with these carabiners.
Okay?
(Seulgi gets trained)
Pull it.
- I practiced that too. / - You have to run hard.
You have to run hard indeed.
- You will see. Everything will be fine. / - Okay.
- Perfect. / - It'll be okay.
Seulgi, you can do it.
- You can do it. / - She's so cute.
(Wendy is ready too)
Wendy looks...
She looks better with a helmet now.
It looks better than her original hairstyle.
With her eyebrows pressed down.
- Yes. / - Pressed down.
That way I can recognize her.
If I never come back,
please remember me.
(Laughing)
(She wants to cry)
Here I go.
I'm going.
- She's scared. / - This is hilarious.
- Always this direction. Okay? / - Okay.
- It's so beautiful. / - Seulgi is good with these things.
I'd love to fly there.
Seulgi is good with these things.
I was not nervous earlier but now I am.
(Her mouth is dry)
This direction. No fear.
- Yeah. / - 3, 2, 1, go.
We just go like this?
Heading to the other direction.
Heading the other direction.
- What? / - Like this.
- And go, go, go. / - Run, run.
We suddenly started running.
Go, go, go, go!
(She flies in the sky)
Go, go!
(Screaming)
(Shouting)
Wow. What should I do?
- Having good time? / - Yeah, it's nice.
- It's perfect. / - Perfect but...
Where we go?
We're just flying around. We're next to the mountain.
To the next mountain?
I'm flying!
(She flaps her arms)
Here we are!
That's right!
Scary.
(She's scared and happy at the same time)
It was amazing but scary.
Good.
(She feels free in the sky)
It's 1,300m above sea level.
(After Seulgi took off)
Oh, my God. Oh, no.
- Me? / - A bit forward.
I run and then I just put my feet in the air?
- Just keep going. / - Keep going?
Don't sit down. Just keep going.
I run in the air?
- Ready? / - Yes.
He told me to keep running in the air too.
- Run? / - Yes, run.
Keep going.
Very well done.
(She runs in the air)
She's running in the air.
It looks strange.
He told me to keep running.
(Wendy flies)
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! This is so good!
(Wendy is excited again)
I love it!
Oh, my God!
Wendy was really scared at first but...
But now she's not.
It looks like she's enjoying it more than Seulgi.
She suddenly sings.
(Her voice is stable even 1,000m above the ground)
This is beautiful. Oh, my God.
- It was indescribable. / - Amazing.
It was different from what I see from the airplane.
- It's different. / - Of course it's different.
It's different to be in the air, feeling the wind myself.
Look. It's surrounded by the mountains.
(She can see all of Salzburg)
(Behind that is the Alps)
(Unless you're in the sky, you can't see)
(Such beautiful scenery)
Right now...
I'm so happy.
No matter how high a building is,
you can't feel such a wind on it.
This is so much fun.
When you paraglide,
sometimes, birds come and fly with you.
- They fly next to you? / - Yes, they do.
(Seulgi looks more relaxed now)
- Really nice. / - Really nice.
Do you want to try flying on your own?
No. No.
- Really? / - No, no, no.
- Okay. / - No...
(He surprised me)
It looks so scary down there.
I will hand you the camera.
No, no, no.
You have to.
Every time... You can't lose it.
Every time a red light flashes...
Sorry, I can't speak English.
It's all good. No worries.
Everything is good.
This is...
- This doesn't feel safe. / - He kept laughing.
(Chris kept playing jokes)
He was being too mean.
It's really scary if you let go. It swoops down.
Go straight. Go straight.
(What is she doing?)
- She's so cute. / - That's survival English.
- She's cute. / - Your English is getting better.
Calm down.
He's having so much fun.
Oh, my God.
There are the other ones coming.
- I'm so jealous. / - It was so nice.
It must've been so good because of the weather.
I'm eagle.
- "I'm eagle." / - She's an eagle?
- I'm eagle. / - I'm an eagle.
Now we have to... Shall we do a roller coaster?
Roller coaster? No, no, no.
No. You're scared.
- I know this. / - They will spin now.
- It is so dizzy. / - It will make you vomit.
- I was so dizzy after that. / - Don't do it.
- You have to do a small roller coaster. / - Okay.
Roller coaster.
(Screaming)
I'm flying.
- Very good. / - Oh, my.
Your voice range must have become higher after this.
It became really high.
Touchdown.
- You did a good job. / - She really landed well.
I'm not afraid of anything anymore.
Seulgi, you did a good job.
I think Wendy will be shouting out
exclamations of surprise in English.
Wow. Oh, my God. That was amazing.
Her voice is really loud.
This is amazing.
Wendy, I can see you're super-talented.
- She's controlling it herself. / - Yes.
It was so fun to do it.
- We go left, right, left, right. / - Okay.
You went round and round.
It was really fun.
This was fun.
(Welcome back)
(Lands lightly)
- She landed well. / - She did a good job.
- She really did. / - Didn't she do a good job?
So, Wendy.
- How was it? / - I was so happy.
I'm shaking right now.
- Are your legs shaking like this? / - Yes.
I'm shaking.
Little bit. That's normal.
- I loved it so much. / - It will be gone in a minute.
I loved it so much.
Great memory. Thank you.
I think she enjoyed it the most...
- Yes, she enjoyed the most. / - Out of everyone.
I was so happy.
- It's so beautiful. / - I'm so jealous.
He kept saying something in English.
- I couldn't understand him. / - I did this.
I kept saying, "Yeah, it's good."
He let me control it.
I didn't know he was asking that.
He asked me but I just said, "No, no, no."
Really?
I was so happy. I just loved it.
There's no other way to express it.
You won't know unless you experience it.
She makes us happy to watch.
I felt like I was born again.
I felt like a new born bird
that was walking for the first time.
- Really? Did you feel that? / - Yes.
- I feel like I was reborn. / - You will start from zero.
Waah.
(Happy birthday)
Yeah. Let's learn how to talk again.
Waah, waah.
They had a good time. Is this their last course?
It's the last course.
The night view of your life.
It's not a plain night view, it's the best ever.
Austria with the setting sun is also really pretty.
- The color is so pretty. / - It's pink.
It's pink and purple.
Look at the clouds. They're also really pretty.
Yes.
There are a lot of locks.
I think this bridge is a meaningful place.
It's really pretty because it has various colors.
Hyorim, did you also put a lock there?
- Of course, I did everything alone. / - Did you do it?
- Good job. / - Yes.
I can't believe there are so many people
wishing for happiness.
(Makartsteg Bridge is very romantic)
You'll be really surprised if you know what time it is.
It's 9:06 p.m.
- It's 9:06 in the evening. / - It's so bright here.
It's 9:06 in the evening...
- But it's so bright outside. / - It's so bright outside.
It's so bright outside. This was from a Korean.
It's Hyorim's lock.
Isn't it Hyorim's lock?
Did Hyorim write someone else's name?
Hyorim and who?
They are surprised after seeing a man's name on it.
- That's why they just left. / - It got edited.
- It got edited. / - That's why.
That's very considerate.
(Where they will see the night view)
(They arrive at the observatory)
- Observatory? / - There must be a place to see that.
- Yes, there is. / - They didn't use to have one.
- We have to go back and forth. / - For two people?
(Monchsberg observatory, downtown Salzburg )
It's automatic.
- Is there an observatory? / - It's faster...
- If you use the elevator. / - Yes.
It's high.
It operates until 11 p.m. during July to August.
For the other months, it only operates until 9 p.m.
It only operates until 11 p.m. for the summer
and 9 p.m. for the other months.
Let's see how pretty the night view is.
Seulgi, don't look yet. Wait, don't look.
Just go to the right. Don't look.
Come down. Continue to come down.
- Come down. / - Can I trust you?
Trust me. Come down.
Continue to come down.
Are you ready?
1, 2, 3.
(Wow)
How is it?
- It's so pretty. / - If you come here...
Slowly after crossing the bridge at 9 p.m.
while enjoying the sunset...
You will be able to see this amazing night view.
I really want to go there.
The buildings are low. I can see the castle over there.
It feels like I've gone back in time.
There's one more thing.
Do you see the red light on top over there?
No way.
- Is that where we did paragliding? / - You're right.
Good job. That's the answer.
- Did we jump from there? / - Yes, that's right.
We jumped from 1,280m.
We came back alive.
There's nothing we can't do.
That's the best.
It was so nice.
- I admit that it's nice. / - The course was so good.
- Including the observatory. / - Yes.
Do you see the two towers?
The opposite side is the Mirabell Garden.
It's there?
It's everything we did today.
- You can see everything. / - Yes, everything.
They are all the places we went today.
- We went everywhere. / - Yes.
It summarizes the whole trip when you go up there.
- Isn't that right? / - Yes, that's right.
It has only been 4 days
but I think we had such a meaningful time
while visiting all the hidden...
- And famous places in Austria. / - That's right.
I was happy.
I think this is the first time I've ever felt alive.
This place was so nice.
If we come here again later, I don't think...
- It will feel like this. / - It won't feel like this.
- We won't be able to experience this. / - Yes.
I really want to live here. I was so happy.
That's what we should've done for our last day.
- Good job. / - Yes.
- You did a good job, friend. / - Good job.
Should we just enjoy the view?
(They were happy because they were together)
(Digidigidip in Austria)
It's pretty.
Lee Teuk, how was it?
- I was really jealous. / - Right?
I didn't think the paragliding would be special,
but I wanted to jump after seeing this.
- Right? / - I want to see the night view.
I even want to hang a lock there.
"The Sound of Music" tour was detailed and fun.
- Right? / - I really like that movie.
- I really want to go there. / - Haven't you been there?
I think I watched the movie at least 30 times.
I listened to the music enough to memorize the lyrics.
- Go there. / - You have to go there.
- I really want to go there. / - You should go there.
- I was so surprised. / - It feels very different.
Wasn't the tour so nice?
There are cheaper courses and more expensive ones?
Yes, for people who want to enjoy a deeper tour,
there's a longer course that goes to
the Salzkammergut,
that is located in the outskirts.
So I think it will be nice
if you chose the tour according to your situation.
It was so nice
that both of them were really happy
instead of pretending to enjoy it for the show.
- That's right. / - I could tell that they were...
Really excited and happy.
- That's right. / - Yes.
- Isn't that right? / - Yes.
That's what it must feel like to be a bird.
That's right.
Do you have any tips for paragliding?
You can go higher when the wind is stronger.
- So go in the morning. / - Is the morning better?
- Yes. / - Avoid doing it when it's cold.
I tried it once in Switzerland.
If it's too cold, it's hard to endure.
- That's right. / - Seulgi and Wendy.
When did you think you wanted to live there?
After "The Sound of Music" tour,
I automatically kept saying
I want to live here without thinking about it.
I kept saying that I was happy.
For me, it was when I saw the night view.
- When you saw the night view. / - Yes.
I really wanted to live there where
I could make so many precious memories.
Okay, let's find out the final expense.
How much did they spend for 5 nights and 6 days?
- I'm a little nervous because... / - Yes.
The cost of activities and everything is expensive.
- Yes. / - Things are expensive in Austria.
- That's why we took the helicopter. / - That's right.
Let's see it.
For 5 nights and 6 days,
the final expense of the Digidigidip Tour...
What's the final expense?
- Excluding airfare. / - Excluding airfare.
- Per person... / - Per person?
$1,306.40.
- It's less. / - It's similar.
- The difference isn't big. / - I think we spent $5 less.
- Is it a $5 difference? / - Yes.
- A $5 difference. / - Yes.
A 5 vote and $5 difference.
Please say your last words...
To persuade the hearts of the judges.
If you prepare your trip
according to our tour,
you will be able to feel like you're born again.
Austria has a lot of delicious food
and many places to see.
So I wish you would vote for us.
Are you ready to vote?
If you want to go to Austria according to
Digidigidip Tour...
Please vote.
(A trip to a country where you'd want to live)
(What will the judges choose?)
Will it be the Realistic Sibling Tour to Canada?
Or the Digidigidip Tour to Austria?
What did the judges choose?
- Yes. / - Okay.
We must win, otherwise our loss
will be mentioned on the 200th episode.
- The first digit is the same. / - The first digit.
It's a 1 for both teams.
- The first digit. / - That's it.
- The first digit is shown first. / - It's a 1.
- Okay. / - This is okay.
- The last digit? / - What's the last digit?
(Real Sibling Tour, Digidigidip Tour)
(Which team will win?)
What is that?
(The final winner is Austria)
It's a 16-vote difference.
- It's a big difference. / - We won.
(Bitter)
- By 16 votes... / - The gap got bigger.
- Digidigidip Tour won. / - They got 11 more votes.
Lee Teuk said he would
come on the show until he wins.
- You've been on several times... / - Yes.
- But you've lost 3 times. / - 3 consecutive losses.
You lost whenever you came here.
I believe that I should keep the promises I made.
There's nothing I can do about it.
I should come back since we lost.
- You'll win one day. / - Of course.
If you haven't been on summer vacation yet,
don't give up.
We'll be back next week with locations
you can visit last minute for a short period.
- Isn't summer vacation over yet? / - No.
- Is it another special? / - Is it another special?
- Yes. / - Please look forward to next week.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
(Next episode)
Sichuan and Chengdu...
- Pandas. / - Oh, my goodness!
I see it, I see it. I saw the rock.
Wow, this is it.
I'm too much in the front.
- Over there! / - Where?
- There they are. / - Whale sharks.
- The view is amazing. / - Right?
What is this?
(Battle Trip)
("Now or Never" by SF9)