We have finally arrived in Bandung.
Follow, follow me.
It's simply amazing.
My prince.
This is just what I like.
So pretty.
It's so awesome.
Everyone, have a Bandung day!
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Suji, Song Daeun)
(Jooe and Yeonwoo of MOMOLAND)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip!
Continuing on from last week,
the theme is Hidden destinations
you must visit before everyone finds out about them.
We have our trip planners with us again.
- Welcome. / - It's nice to see the four of you.
- Hello. / - Hello.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
Actually, it was our first time to hear about Bandung.
- Bandung. / - Bandung, Indonesia.
I didn't expect much because it was unfamiliar.
But it was very fun and interesting.
- I really want to go there. / - Right.
If you visit our blog, you can find...
All the details and addresses there.
You can refer to it before going on your trip.
This is a battle between special hosts.
Suji and Jooe were here before.
I think that's why they could plan perfect trips.
So I was hoping to be here again
after winning today.
Where do you want to go? You have a kid.
- Sometimes, I need to leave home. / - Watch your kid.
That's not it.
Sometimes, we have a married couples battle.
- Married couples? / - You should do that.
Must I go with my wife?
I think it's a good idea.
That's how married men are.
I mean, I just want to go on a trip.
Anyway, today, we're going to places you should
visit before everyone finds out about them.
- And there are a lot of places. / - Yes.
There are a lot of destinations we don't know.
It's a little far but there are a lot of places in Africa.
- That's right. / - In Tanzania...
There's a place called Zanzibar.
It's the best vacation spot loved by European people.
Zanzibar in Tanzania.
I want to recommend one.
I heard rural areas of France are so nice.
- France. / - Right.
Not Paris.
If you go to the country,
there are good restaurants and wineries.
The people are really hospitable.
- They're hospitable. / - And much cheaper.
And they have...
- A tour around ancient castles. / - Right.
They're not famous castles
but you can sleep in there.
You can rent the whole castle.
Yes, and it's not so expensive.
But what about a trip to the equator?
- A trip to the equator? / - The equator?
- In Ecuador... / - I really want to try it.
There's a city called Quito.
You can do some scientific experiments there.
- The egg. / - It's very interesting.
You can stand an egg on end of a nail.
You go all the way there just to balance an egg?
- It's just one of the experiments. / - I see.
You can experience many things there.
I heard there are so many interesting things.
Alright. Remember those places.
It's the hidden trip locations.
- You should visit. / - They're our opponents...
But I'm very curious about Sakhalin.
- I'm so curious. / - It's because...
We have to talk about the history regarding Sakhalin.
We have the tragic history in Sakhalin.
There are people who couldn't come back home.
That's right.
When we went on a trip to Mokpo,
we learned this term.
- It's called dark tourism. / - Roh Chunghun said that.
It's traveling around
historic or disastrous sites.
A trip for fun is also good,
but it is also very meaningful
to go on a trip where you can learn and introspect.
- That's right. / - To be honest...
I didn't know much about the place either.
When we got there,
there was the Monument at the Mountain Pechali.
which was built in remembrance of the history.
We heard about the history
and had some time to think about it there.
- I could understand how they felt. / - It's so sad.
- Right. / - When we go to a place like that...
- We feel like crying. / - Right.
It felt strange.
- I know. / - It was weird.
There are second and third generation Koreans.
They speak a little Korean.
- Oh, that's true. / - I guess the food there is...
- Also sort of Korean. / - Right.
- Is that true? / - Yes.
It was like something I had for breakfast.
- It was like home cooked food. / - Really?
- Seriously? / - Home cooked food?
You can look forward to it.
Before we start, let's take a look at the map.
It's Sakhalin.
It's closer than Bandung.
- It's so close. / - It's close.
- How many hours? / - About 3 hours.
- 3 hours? / - Vladivostok was also very close.
- Is there a direct flight? / - Yes.
There are direct flights on Tuesdays, Thursdays,
Saturdays.
- There are? / - Three direct flights a week.
Sakhalin has a small population
for its large land mass.
- It is about 500,000. / - 500,000?
They mostly live in the center area...
- Called Yuzhno-Sakhalinsk. / - Okay.
All the restaurants and landmarks are not too far.
It was very convenient.
- I see. / - They are concentrated in there.
- It's a good thing. / - It has easy accessibility.
I heard a lot of Russian people...
- Go to Sakhalin for a trip. / - Right.
- There are a lot of reasons for it. / - Yes.
- But they mostly go skiing there. / - Skiing?
- Yes. / - They go skiing there.
- The quality of snow is good there. / - Right.
So national ski teams also go there for training.
- Really? / - To Sakhalin?
And the weather is relatively warm.
So many people visit there.
There's one thing I'm worried about.
Crustaceans like lobster or king crab...
- Are very famous there. / - That's true.
When crustaceans and instant noodles are aired,
the viewer ratings soar.
Once we slurp the noodles,
the viewer ratings go up.
I hope it won't happen.
People who love fishing visit there as well?
I was so surprised to see that.
Did you go fishing?
You will see.
- Anyway... / - Where do you go fishing?
Out the sea.
- Out to sea? / - There's the Sea of Okhotsk.
You can actually go to the Sea of Okhotsk.
I'm worried about fishing though.
A lot of trip planners have tried fishing on Battle Trip.
But they rarely caught fish.
- But we... / - Wait. Don't tell. Don't tell.
- It's a secret. / - A secret?
What's your team name?
We came up with something cute.
- Cuter than ours? / - Sure.
Start.
(Cheerful and bubbly)
(They're the cutest ones)
Moa Moa Tour!
Let's watch it.
2, 3. Get your ticket!
Hello, we are MOMOLAND.
- I'm Jooe. / - And I'm Yeonwoo.
So fresh.
(MOMOLAND is on Battle Trip)
(Human vitamin, Jooe)
(Pretty jewel, Yeonwoo)
Have you been on a trip before?
Of course.
Unlike you, I have.
- A homebody. / - I love staying home.
It was the first time she got on a plane this year.
- Really? / - Yes.
- Because of work. / - She's 23 now.
Let's decide where to go first.
You should do it systematically.
I want to go to Russia.
- I've heard so much about it. / - Let's go then.
Really? You're very decisive.
- What should I put in? / - Russia.
Map.
Blagoveshchensk?
Khabarovsk.
- The names are so difficult. / - They are difficult.
Is this an island?
Yuzhno-Sakhalinsk?
It's too big to be an island.
- It's Sakhalin. / - Sakhalin?
I've heard of it before.
But it doesn't sound familiar.
I saw it in a documentary.
(They heard it in a documentary)
Right, it's a city we'd see in a documentary.
It's about 88% of Korea's total land area.
It's huge.
- Is it that big? / - Yes.
It's the biggest island.
It's beautiful.
- It was so... / - What's that?
- It's so beautiful. / - What's that?
- It looks so pretty. / - It's huge.
It's the biggest island in Russia.
But the population is only 500,000.
- It looks beautiful. / - I didn't know it was that big.
- It was so... / - What's that?
- It's so beautiful. / - What's that?
- It's a beautiful island. / - It looks amazing.
We don't need to go to Switzerland or Vancouver.
What's that?
(Russian and Korean people live together in Sakhalin)
(It's a place with a painful history)
It takes only 3 hours.
- Oh, no. / - It looks so pretty.
What's that?
- I can't believe this. / - It looks white.
It looks great.
I'm so surprised.
Alright then.
- Shall we go to Sakhalin? / - Sakhalin?
Let's go there.
- Yeah! / - Oops.
- Let's go to Sakhalin. / - Let's go.
I've been to Russia before.
So I'll plan our trip
around the downtown on the first day.
You can...
- Plan a trip to the outskirts. / - Yes, the outskirts.
I'll look into the outskirts.
It's hard but I'll give it a try.
- Moa... / - Moa...
- Tour! / - Tour!
Bandung was very nice but I was disappointed...
- You didn't show us the ocean. / - Right.
We can finally see the ocean now.
It's so cool in winter.
- It's beautiful. / - It's Moscow.
We didn't go to Moscow.
We went to Vladivostok.
There are a lot of famous destinations.
(It's a place where culture, history, nature coexist)
What's that?
- It looks like Greece. / - It's amazing.
(The biggest island in Russia, Sakhalin)
(And there are two mysterious girls)
It feels like fall.
(They are cheerful at every moment)
I love it.
I think I can go alone.
Follow me.
(The energetic girl, Jooe)
(She's whimsical at every moment)
What was that?
Hi.
I'm spaced out.
Let's order one more glass.
I'm No-Face.
Oh, my God.
(The whimsical girl, Yeonwoo)
So Yeonwoo is a little eccentric.
That was my secret.
- Sakhalin. / - It's so pretty.
- Is it a cathedral? / - Yes.
- What's all that inside? / - It's a cathedral.
Oh, my God! Don't move!
That looks so scary.
We went to the outskirts.
(It's Mother Nature time)
- That's the Sea of Okhotsk. / - Wow, I feel so good.
(Living and breathing nature)
- Oh, no. / - They caught a fish!
I'm sure they set it up in advance.
What are you talking about?
- I love it. / - This is so good.
To be honest, I'm satisfied.
(There will be familiar looking foods as well)
Wasn't it Korean food just now?
- This is so good. / - This is it.
Cheers.
Moa Moa Tour! Bye!
- There's so much land. / - I like that they're so cheerful.
That's a Russian doll.
Russian doll.
Moa Moa Tour!
Yeah!
- Lie down. / - Lie down, lie down.
(Wriggling)
They're so rowdy.
They're so cute.
- I have to make them look bad. / - At that age...
- That's how you travel with friends. / - That's right.
- You crawl around. / - Exactly.
Crawl around?
(Moa Moa Tour, Jooe's Downtown Tour)
(Moa Moa Tour, Yeonwoo's Outskirts Tour)
(Incheon International Airport, 8 a.m.)
Yeonwoo! Finally, the two of us...
Okay.
I didn't finish my sentence yet.
- They're in comfortable outfits. / - Here we go.
We're going on a trip.
- We're going on a trip. / - This is my first trip.
I've been abroad many times but...
This is almost your first time flying, isn't it?
- Hello. / - Hello.
It's a direct flight.
At 8:40 p.m. Oh, I'm sorry, your photo...
That scared me.
- Let us see the picture. / - I just saw a nightmare.
Please go to gate 45.
- Thank you. / - Have a nice trip.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
We will have a nice trip.
- She's a pretty stewardess. / - Thank you.
Bye.
(They keep bowing)
- See you later. / - Bye.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
It was a direct flight.
- It's a direct flight. / - It took only 3 hours.
- 3 hours. / - It sounds really nice.
- I know. / - It took only 3 hours.
(Sakhalin)
(Yuzhno-Sakhalinsk Airport, 2 p.m.)
- Is that the airport? / - That's the airport?
It looks so unique.
- I thought it was a gymnasium. / - Me too.
It's nothing like Sakhalin I've been imagining.
Oh, my! This is...
Sakhalin!
- Yeonwoo, this is Sakhalin! / - Is this Sakhalin?
Finally, we safely arrived in Sakhalin.
After flying 3 hours from Korea.
- We flew here. / - We're in Sakhalin.
- That's right. / - By the way, it's not so much...
- Colder than in Korea. / - I checked earlier.
- The weather in Korea. / - The weather is perfect.
- Korea is 23℃ now. / - 23℃.
And it's 18℃ here.
It's not that different.
It's the warmest time of the day.
18℃? That's...
- Like how it is here these days. / - It's not that cold.
The weather was not so different from here.
I've always thought it'd be freezing there.
- They even have foliage. / - It must be that time.
We need to get a ride from here.
Would you like to take a taxi or a bus?
I'd like to take a bus and...
- Enjoy the area. / - You want to feel Sakhalin.
I want to feel that I'm in Sakhalin.
(Where is their first destination?)
Where are we going, by the way?
We're going to the landmark of Sakhalin,
which is a cathedral.
- A cathedral? / - Yes.
We're going to a cathedral.
- The cathedral from before? / - In Yuzhno-Sakhalinsk...
- What's going on? / - There's a big cathedral.
What is this?
I recorded it.
- This is newly built. It was built last year. / - New?
It's a new building, built last year.
It's the landmark of Sakhalin.
It's the Russian Orthodox Church.
I think we should go check out this place.
(Moa Moa Tour, Jooe's Downtown Tour)
(Cathedral of the Nativity)
- Now, let's take this white bus. / - Bus no. 3.
We'll take bus no. 3.
- Let's take the white bus. / - Yeonwoo.
Let me tell you something interesting.
- Yes. / - In Russia...
You get on the bus through the back door.
In Russia, you get on the bus through the rear door.
- You're right. / - And you pay as you get off...
Through the front door. Interesting, right?
It's been a long time since I've ridden a bus.
- Me too. / - Right?
It's been 2 to 3 years.
Haven't ridden one since I debuted.
There are a lot of trees.
The air must be clean here.
(Sakhalin, Yuzhno-Sakhalinsk)
Where are we going?
Just follow me.
We arrived much earlier than expected.
- It's worth coming here, isn't it? / - It is.
It's so pretty here.
It's amazing.
It's shiny.
- It's beautiful. / - It's so pretty.
- It's so big. / - It was built last year.
- It's magnificent. / - What's that on the top?
- It was very shiny. / - It was so clean and beautiful.
The white color...
- Represents purity. / - Purity?
Yes, purity. The gold color represents light.
- Light. / - It's shiny like light.
- It does look very shiny. / - It has a sense of nobility.
(White for purity and gold for light and nobility)
It was really beautiful.
I can imagine it looking really beautiful in winter.
- Yes. / - With a white backdrop.
The weather looks really nice.
- Shall we go take a closer look? / - Shall we go in?
- Let's go. / - It looks so cool.
Doesn't it look like something in a movie?
I want to take this home.
- The cathedral? / - Yes.
I really wanted to take it home.
Can anyone go in?
Anyone can go in,
but you can't wear revealing clothes.
If you're a woman, your head should be...
- Covered? / - Yes.
You have to cover your head with something.
- You have to be respectful. / - I see.
(How does it look inside?)
- It sounded very scary. / - It's scary.
(You have to be quiet inside and enter with hats off)
- Gold door. / - What's all that?
(The inside is filled with colorful paintings and gold)
- It was really beautiful. / - It was so beautiful.
- It looks like a museum. / - It's very flashy inside.
Here...
Women have to put on a veil to cover their heads.
Women have to cover their hair.
- Men have to take off their hats. / - Right.
It seems like you can borrow the veils for free.
- So you can borrow them. / - Like that?
I think this will work.
Like this.
- There you go. / - She looks so pretty.
Now help me.
There you go.
It's pretty nice.
- It makes me feel reverent. / - I know.
The ceiling looks so beautiful.
How did they paint on the ceiling?
I know. It's amazing.
How did they paint on it?
- It's very big inside. / - How high is it?
(The entire walls are filled with paintings)
- How high up? / - It's 77m.
- 77m? / - 77m.
I want to hold this sight in my memory.
(Yeonwoo and Jooe can't take their eyes off)
It's more splendid inside than outside.
- It is. / - You're right.
There are only two colors on the outside.
Blue and gold. But the inside...
- It's very colorful. / - It's more beautiful...
- Because there are more colors. / - That's right.
It has very different colors from outside.
- It looks like a crown, doesn't it? / - You're right.
- Now... / - We're hungry.
Exactly. We should go eat.
I found a really...
- Good Russian restaurant. / - The weather is amazing.
A really good restaurant?
Who am I today?
I'm the trip planner today.
- Let's go. / - Okay. Let's go.
Even if you say this is an escalator...
- I'll believe you. / - This is an escalator.
Really?
What were we saying?
(Moa Moa Tour, Jooe's Downtown Tour)
(Russian food)
(3 minutes by car from the cathedral to the restaurant)
- It takes 3 minutes by car. / - It's so close.
- Are you looking forward to it? / - It's nearby.
There aren't many people on the street.
The population density is not so high
compared to the size of the land.
They have really lovely colors.
- The buildings are so colorful. / - Red, green, yellow.
- The buildings look so pretty. / - It's very relaxing.
- Green, blue... / - Isn't this the place?
How did you know it?
- How did you know it? / - Obviously, it's crowded.
Hi.
- I'm so hungry. / - Me too.
Let's go eat.
I'm going to eat a lot.
(The restaurant is full of matryoshka dolls)
- It feels like Christmas. / - It has a Christmas vibe.
It's very unique.
I'm curious about Russian food.
- Me too. / - I know.
I love the ambiance here.
I love the tables too.
I love it here.
It'll be perfect if they have great food too.
I'm sure it'll be great.
- I think it'll be great. / - Seriously...
I only ordered their most famous dishes.
How famous are they?
They're as famous as Yeonwoo.
Then they're not so famous. There's a long way to go.
As famous as Yeonwoo.
"There's a long way to go."
I'll work harder.
(Jooe prepared famous Russian dishes)
- Are you drinking beer? / - Yes, we are!
That's the best.
- The beer is better than expected. / - Looks tasty.
Really?
(A Russian salad, Olivier)
- What is that? / - Isn't that canned food?
- Isn't that so cute? / - You're right.
(Rump steak)
(Pelmeni, Russian dumplings)
(With cherries!)
- What's inside? / - Cherries.
- Cherries are stuffed inside. / - What is that?
- Why would they do such a thing? / - It has cherries?
(Including beer, the whole meal costs $27)
Thank you.
Honey was added. Honey.
- Honey? That sounds good. / - Was their beer good?
- How was it? / - It was so good.
(How is the famous Russian honey beer?)
She's completely won over by the honey beer.
- I guess it's really good. / - I really want to try it.
So cute.
You have my trust now.
- Really? / - Yes.
I'm going to...
(Jooe is getting excited)
A glass of beer before food is served.
- That's the best. / - She's getting excited.
I told you to just trust me.
(A glass of honey beer excites her to the fullest)
- I love it. / - I thought it would be just sweet.
- It's sweet and sour. / - It's sweet and sour.
- It's fruity. / - This is...
This beer is light. Even light drinkers can...
- Enjoy this beer. / - That's right.
- You drink well. / - You don't get to travel often.
Since Russia is a cold country...
- What's that salad? / - They eat a lot of canned food.
So they've just designed this dish like that.
If you lift this, it'll pop out.
You should lift it since I prepared this meal for you.
- Okay. / - Yeonwoo...
- Do whatever you want to do. / - Let me try it.
Let's see. There you go.
- Have a taste. / - What is this?
(How does this unique salad taste?)
Russians eat this dish on the New Year's Day.
It's one of their common salads.
This has a familiar taste.
- Really? / - Yes.
It's like a home cooked meal.
Right?
- This is just like... / - Tastes like mom's cooking.
They eat that for the New Year.
It's like that vegetable salad at the school cafeteria.
Do you know it? The one with mayonnaise.
- The thing that tastes bad. / - It tastes good!
- It's delicious. / - Why are you being like this?
Don't you eat a lot of salad buns?
- It's bad for you too. / - That's not true.
It's the salad in the salad buns.
- It's like that salad. / - You're right.
I can tell that it's high-calorie although it's a salad.
- Since it's a cold country. / - I want to eat it with bread.
- I don't usually eat salads. / - You don't eat it at all.
(Feeling embarrassed)
Don't try to embellish it.
I only eat flour for my vegetable fix.
But this is delicious enough for me to eat this salad.
(This salad is perfect for Yeonwoo who hates veggies)
(The familiarity of the taste makes them keep eating)
(Aggressively eating the appetizer)
They finished the salad.
The flow can't be cut off. Hurry and give us food.
I'm hungry.
(The main dish is served at last)
Let's give it a warm welcome.
- Should we have a bite of this? / - Yes.
Rump steak.
What's the sauce for? It's to dip it, of course.
- It looks like pork cutlet. / - Is it fried?
It looks like a fried meatball.
(Big dip)
I normally don't eat meat with sauce.
Maybe we shouldn't have dipped then.
(How does the steak taste?)
- What is it? / - What? What is it?
What is it? Is it horseradish?
(This is Russian horseradish)
This wasabi is really strong.
You put too much sauce on it.
Horseradish is spicy.
They should have tasted it first.
What is this? Seriously.
It was really spicy.
- You should've tasted the sauce first. / - Exactly.
- I thought it was a sour sauce. / - I know.
(Attacked by horseradish without warning)
You thought it was the sauce for the French fries.
- Yes, precisely. / - I'm crying now.
- What is this? / - I have a runny nose.
- This is nice. It's tasty. / - Yes.
- This is good. / - It's good.
(However, the steak tastes good)
- This is pretty good. / - Yes, it really is.
This is just like the meat pancakes.
It's chewier and plumper than that.
What an interesting dish.
It tastes different with the wasabi sauce.
I want to eat that.
I think I can cook this.
Isn't that a Korean dish?
- It looks like Korean pancakes. / - That dish...
Is a really popular food in Russia.
(We ought to eat meat)
Meat is always good.
- It's meat. / - People should enjoy eating meat.
We have more food. Yeonwoo, we have another dish.
(The next dish is served right away)
- The cherry dumplings. / - Thank you.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Yeonwoo, you try it first.
- What are you saying? / - Hurry.
- I'm curious about that dish. / - Cherry dumpling?
- I'm not sure about this one. / - It's red.
(Will the cherries and dumplings go well together?)
(She's half curious and half worried)
- That's bad, right? / - She tried it.
- That's not good, right? / - What is it? What?
- What is it? / - Is it too sweet?
(Laughing)
Well, this dish isn't for me.
And the one I chose was particularly red.
It was particularly red.
- The outside looked red. / - The cherries...
Geez.
- It pops like this. Look. / - Why? It looks unique.
- I can't eat hot food. / - The cherries smell nice.
But the cherries are warm.
- Can't we think of it as a cherry pie? / - Right.
No, it's more like...
A steamed dumpling stuffed with cherry isn't of meat.
- Steamed cherry dumpling? / - Yes.
(Jooe tries one too)
I prefer cold food over hot.
(Showing approval)
I like it.
Really? Everyone has a different preference.
This is more of a dessert.
I really like it.
- Are you serious? / - Yes, I really like it.
Then I'll eat this steak.
Hey, here it is. Here it is.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
- Guess what it is. / - What is this?
This is a special dish for you.
You can only find this in Sakhalin.
These are dumplings with crab meat.
Actually, it's either a hit-or-miss.
- I chose this dish just for you. / - Salmon roe.
- I remember that. / - That looks delicious.
Pelmeni is dumplings.
These are similar to dumplings in Korea.
- That one looks good. / - That was to die for.
After observing Jooe's face, this dish is really good.
Yes, it was.
I'm just going to trust you. I'll trust you.
- This is really good. / - I won't taste cherries, right?
(She's doubtful at first)
You can really taste the crab meat.
It has cream pasta sauce.
It's a crab dumpling with cream pasta sauce.
- That one looks really good. / - That looks tasty.
It was really good. That dish was divine.
It's not as heavy as I thought.
Right when you think it's going to get heavy,
it has a clean taste.
You have to try this in Russia.
People of all ages will love this.
It was really tasty. After that, I could trust Jooe.
- It was that good? / - Yes.
(They eat all they want without worrying)
(The food has disappeared instantly once again)
- That must go well with beer. / - I could trust her.
- Yes, it went well with beer. / - Yes.
She emptied her beer.
- Suji. / - Yes?
I think you just got won over.
No, no. Not at all.
The beer was so good.
- Yeonwoo, we just ate. / - Yes.
We should set out again.
- Is that why you fed me? / - We're MOMOLAND.
Right.
- We'll go to the amusement park. / - MOMOLAND.
Let's move.
That sounds great.
There's an amusement park in the city center.
- An amusement park? / - Wow, amazing.
- This is pretty. / - They have the Viking as well.
Are you good with rides?
I'm really good.
I'm good too. I'm a master.
- I'm no joke. / - I'm an adult.
(Moa Moa Tour, Jooe's Downtown Tour)
(Gagarin Park)
- Gagarin Park. / - Gagarin Park.
(12 minutes from the restaurant to the park by car)
- A walk in a park after drinking... / - That's so pretty.
- Honey beer is nice. / - The ground is spinning.
- Yeonwoo, this place... / - I can't run. I'll feel nauseous.
- It's called Gagarin Park. / - Okay.
The locals in Sakhalin visit this place a lot.
- It's a park. / - It's huge.
It's so beautiful.
Actually, the park was originally named
something else.
They changed it.
(Locals often enjoy a walk among birch and fir trees)
Unlike the colorfulness of Bandung...
- This offers a different vibe. / - It's very tranquil.
- It's romantic. / - Right.
This is a great place to come with kids.
Absolutely. Or with pets.
- I'm a companion animal. / - Companion animals.
Happy, run.
Happy.
What are we doing?
The trees here are birch trees and fir trees.
The trail is made up of these trees.
Do you know how to massage your back?
(Showing perfect teamwork)
Birch and fir trees emanate a lot of phytoncides.
- That's true. / - It must be so aromatic.
(They're enjoying the short Russian autumn)
- We can try... / - Okay.
Many different things here. Just follow me.
The park is huge.
It is huge indeed.
The amusement park is superb.
- We're at the amusement park! / - Yes!
It's an amusement park for Yeonwoo!
The rides only operate from May to October.
- They don't operate in winter? / - No.
This park somehow...
Seems desolate.
Exactly.
There are almost no people.
Only a few things operate
during the weekdays.
I don't think we need to wait in line.
I'll ride something scary.
- Because I'm a grown up. / - A scary ride?
Yes, because I'm a grown up.
- I'm not interested in kid's rides. / - Not interested?
- Let's ride the Viking! / - Okay.
We should ride a Russian Viking.
That's right. A Viking is a must.
That looks cute.
(They seem excited about riding the Viking)
Are you talking about that children's Viking?
Are we getting on that one?
Are we getting on that children's Viking?
- Hello. / - Hello.
- I'm excited. / - We thought nothing of it.
- Doesn't it look cute? / - Gosh, it was scary.
Isn't that for children?
I don't think it'll be that scary.
(Viking ride, $3.20)
(This is the only safety feature)
The safety bar only goes down to here.
(Looking at the safety bar, it must not be scary)
- I don't think it'll be scary. / - I don't think so either.
What? Why is it starting so suddenly?
- It scared me. / - It makes a scary sound.
What's that noise?
- It sounds like it's really old. / - What?
It's the sound of the rubber tire underneath.
- It's like a haunted house. / - It sounds terrifying.
- Wait. Isn't this really old? / - What's wrong with it?
(It sounds horrible)
I hate it.
I haven't been on a ride in so long.
Look at the height.
It goes up really high.
That looks pretty scary.
- That tree has been cut. / - Really?
- Like in the shape of the Viking? / - Yes.
It couldn't grow because the Viking kept touching it.
Goodness.
Jooe, you don't seem scared.
(They start enjoying the Viking)
(Jooe is super excited)
Yeonwoo, was that scary?
It was really scary.
- I kept asking to stop. / - She can't open her eyes.
- That tree is hilarious. / - It is.
That tree has a straight line.
(Struggling)
It tickles.
(Her heart tickles)
Jooe, were you happy or scared?
I felt ticklish.
Ticklish?
- Ticklish? / - That tickles a lot.
- I've never... / - What's that?
- Ridden one for so long. / - Me too.
This was the first time.
He kept it going because there were no other people.
He kept laughing.
(They enjoyed the Viking in an empty park)
Stop!
- Stop! / - Let's go for a different one.
Can't we take a break?
She's being dragged.
When I was little,
I dreamed of being in an amusement park alone.
It's nice because that's what they experienced.
Is there something else you want to ride?
I want something scarier.
- Scarier? / - Because I'm a grown up.
- I found something scarier. / - You can't even ride it.
This looks scary.
This is it.
This is it!
This ominous feeling is never wrong.
- Move! / - This is really scary.
This drops down at once.
- What's this? / - This is really scary.
Isn't there one in Korea too?
- I was really shocked to see that. / - No, it's not.
- Isn't it the same one? / - It's not?
This one spins.
(What is this?)
- This looks super scary. / - That's too high!
(This tower is higher than the Ferris wheel)
- What's this? / - This is really scary.
This drops down at once.
It's higher than a Ferris wheel.
Isn't there one in Korea too?
- I was really shocked to see that. / - No, it's not.
No? It's not that one?
This one spins.
- This looks super scary. / - That's too high!
(It's a swing ride)
- You feel like you might die. / - Really?
That was really scary.
That looks like a swing...
- At a playground. / - That chain looks too thin.
Compared to the height...
My heart is racing like crazy.
(Jooe is waiting comfortably)
It's going up.
(The swings take off)
Unbelievable!
- It's so high. / - It keeps going up.
It's really scary.
It's so scary.
(Meanwhile,  Yeonwoo)
No.
I hate this. Let me off.
I want to get off.
(She starts screaming as soon as it takes off)
- What? / - What was that?
- I want to get off. / - What?
That was like some horror film.
It seems that your pupils were...
Let me off!
Your eyes have lost focus.
I think you can see everything.
I think you'll see the whole city when it spins.
(Yeonwoo lets go of herself)
I'm drawing a blank.
It's scary! Let me go down!
I know how that feels.
Open your eyes.
(It's not okay)
(Shivering)
I hate that.
(It's spinning slowly at 35m high)
I want to try it. It looks nice.
You're lying.
- It's higher than the Ferris wheel. / - It's slow.
The view is so pretty.
It's spinning slowly. It's not that scary.
- Yes, it's really scary. / - Come on.
It's really scary but it's really beautiful.
I feel like my shoes are going to come off.
I'm holding tightly onto my shoes. They might fall off!
(She's gotten used to it and is taking pictures now)
Gosh.
She's taking pictures.
How can you take pictures?
(It speeds up as it comes down)
- It's going faster. / - Gosh.
(The swing goes out farther)
Oh, my God.
Birds! Why are they coming here?
(Birds fly by)
Even the birds avoid it.
That's funny.
(Jooe's video)
Birds!
- Why are they coming here? / - So close.
The birds are greeting you.
I was so surprised.
I'm scared!
Look at the beautiful foliage.
That's scary.
It must be scary.
(It's so scary)
I'm scared.
My shoes are going to fall off.
(It lands after 4 minutes)
(She's totally out of it)
What is this?
(Jooe must've been scared too)
That...
She's crying.
The ride was too long.
I think you should ride it even if it's scary.
Women can ride it.
- Right? / - Yes.
(Legs give out)
(Her legs too)
I'm sorry.
Your legs give out when you ride something scary.
- Yeah. / - I think I lost my voice.
I screamed too much.
I'll take you to a place...
Where we can calm our excited and scared feelings.
- Worse place than here? / - You can trust me.
You can really trust me.
I'm sorry.
(I sincerely apologize)
I haven't heard you say sorry
so sincerely in 3 years.
Let's go.
(Sun sets in Sakhalin)
That's beautiful.
The red sunset.
(They go to their next destination)
(Moa Moa Tour, Jooe's Downtown Tour)
(Korean fusion cuisine)
It's quiet and empty.
- I felt like I was there alone. / - I see.
That's very charming.
(11 minutes by car to the restaurant)
Seriously, it's really special.
- How is it special? / - We had...
- A Russian style lunch. / - Yes.
This time,
it's a combination of Korean and Russian food.
It's a fusion cuisine.
I'm so excited.
Let's go in and eat.
It's called Leto.
- It means summer in Russian. / - It's beautiful.
(It looks like they wouldn't serve Korean food)
It's a fancy restaurant.
It doesn't look like a Korean restaurant.
- What's that? Is it kimchi stew? / - Kimchi stew?
That looks familiar.
Sakhalin people came up with
their style of fusion Korean food.
(The locals enjoy it)
The locals eat it too.
Sakhalin people like it a lot.
He really seems to be enjoying it.
(He eats from the earthen pot)
- In Russia... / - Vodka!
They always serve the alcohol first.
- Russia serves alcohol first. / - Of course.
- To warm you up. / - That looks good.
- Cheers. / - It's cheap.
Cheers.
(A glass of vodka, $2.90)
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
(Slurping)
It's good.
(She doesn't look happy)
They say it's not good if the alcohol is sweet.
She doesn't look happy.
Isn't it sweet?
What's wrong?
- She's only 20. / - The alcohol was too strong?
Too strong?
(23-year-old Yeonwoo likes it)
You're good at drinking it.
I think I'm drunk.
- You can get drunk on Battle Trip. / - It's a work dinner!
- Yes! / - I'm buying!
Everyone has to order two dishes.
Make sure everyone orders seasoned bracken only.
(Clattering)
Who just...
- Who made that clattering sound? / - Dropped the fork?
(Who made the clattering sound just now?)
Who just coughed right now?
I'm in the middle of mind reading.
- "I'm reading..." / - They have great teamwork.
- "Your mind, right now." / - "Your mind, right now."
How do you know this? You're young.
- This meme is famous online. / - Of course, we know.
- "Who made that clattering sound?" / - "You fool."
(This is how good MOMOLAND's teamwork is)
"It was me."
Wow.
What's that?
This feels weird.
A Russian waiter is serving Korean side dishes.
- This is an honor. / - It feels weird.
What are the side dishes?
That would feel strange.
(You ought to shake the rice bowl first)
- Do you know what this is? / - What?
- Hey, this is white rice. / - Did you see that?
What?
Did you see that?
- That was amazing. / - Did you see that? Try it.
If you do this at a dinner party,
everyone will love you.
- That was cool. / - She's had many dinner parties.
- Seriously. / - Hey, we won.
- We won. / - We won the battle.
- That's what the managers do. / - We won.
- She just flipped the bowl. / - How did you do that?
- That was hilarious. / - Jooe is so hilarious.
- What was that? / - Seriously?
I want to learn that.
- This is the seasoned bracken. / - In Sakhalin...
- Seasoned bracken? / - Bracken grows so well.
But since they hadn't eaten or cooked this before,
they had never eaten this. They didn't know how.
When the Goryeo descendants
began to put down roots in this region,
this dish suddenly became popular.
They learned to eat it.
The seasoned bracken is delicious.
There must be many dishes
Koreans established after going over.
Yes, there are a lot.
This reminds me of my mom.
This bracken tastes softer than the one in Korea.
It's not tough at all.
- It's really soft. / - It is.
- How did they cook this? / - It's the softest I've had.
- This restaurant is good. / - It's pretty good.
The bracken.
(Even picky Yeonwoo eats more)
Next up is raw fish.
- No, it's not. / - Raw fish?
(They'll try raw fish next?)
(They marinate raw fish with vinegar in Sakhalin)
- Is it spicy raw fish salad? / - They have that?
Yes, it was made by the Koreans there.
(Plate of raw fish, $4.80)
This is delicious.
It's to die for.
How is it? Is it similar to the dish in Korea?
- It's even better. / - Really?
Seriously?
They cook with fresh fish they catch that day.
Raw fish is fresh there.
It differs from the Korean dish.
- It feels like that. / - It's so good. How should I put it?
- The oil. Yes. / - The chili oil.
That's a bit unique.
- Koreans must eat Korean food. / - Yes.
- Absolutely. / - This is very good.
Let's eat the meat now.
- When you travel, you crave Korean food. / - Right.
This is a great place to go
when you crave Korean food.
That'd be perfect.
(But it doesn't look like regular bulgogi)
(Munching)
(Yes, meat can never go wrong)
- Does it taste like bulgogi? / - Yes, just like bulgogi.
- It's the same. / - It is bulgogi.
It's like braised short ribs.
This is very different.
They serve it like it's braised short ribs.
I should eat bulgogi with kimchi.
(She eats it with kimchi)
(Bulgogi is tastier when you make a lettuce wrap)
This is delicious.
- It's just like Korean rice. / - Yes.
I'm so happy.
Is this the clam stew?
- Clam stew. / - Is this the clam stew?
A meal needs stew.
- You need soup. / - Koreans ought to have stew...
For their meals.
- The clams were huge. / - Great.
(Did the flavor impress her?)
- This is delicious. / - What is this depth of flavors?
This is so good.
It's like cheese instant noodles.
Exactly. This is like vongole pasta.
Some add butter in kimchi stew.
- That's a lot of butter. / - Some people add butter.
I think that's right.
I thought this would taste like soybean paste stew.
- It was very creamy. / - I see.
- This is good. / - It's so delicious.
It's so good.
- I guess it's not spicy. / - It's not spicy. It's...
- Like a Western dish. / - Suji.
You look like an audience member.
This is getting me hooked little by little.
I really want to try the clam stew.
When I heard they went to Russia...
- We didn't expect good food. / - Right.
- That looks really good. / - It was really good.
This restaurant is awesome.
(Eating with gusto)
(Their hands are moving ceaselessly)
Kimchi, thank you.
(It translates to "more kimchi, please")
Can you get a refill?
- No, you pay for kimchi. / - You have to pay for it.
You have to pay extra, right?
- It's 8 cents to get a refill. / - What?
- 8 cents? / - Yes, 8 cents.
(They keep on eating after getting more kimchi)
Yeonwoo, what did you think about today's trip?
I really enjoyed my time today.
- Really? What was your favorite? / - Yes.
The honey beer...
(They're still thinking about the honey beer)
You don't mean that. You finished the vodka too.
Exactly. Let me order one more.
Tomorrow, we're going to travel far.
We'll go to the outskirts to experience Mother Nature.
I love it.
(She smoothly takes Jooe's vodka)
Time out. I think Yeonwoo is drunk.
She's drunk.
- Yeonwoo's future seems promising. / - Drunk.
(He looks forward to Yeonwoo's future)
- Is that so? / - She's a drinker.
- They're going to the ocean now. / - She can't drink.
(Today, it's the outskirts of Sakhalin)
I'm going to head out to the outskirts.
I can't make you wait.
Let's go.
Yeonwoo, you look cool today.
I'll trust Lee Dabin today.
(Racing hard)
It's the ocean!
The ocean looks amazing.
It's so pretty.
We caught these without any bait.
- We caught some! / - Yeah.
I can't believe that!
What is that?
- We caught some! / - Yeah.
(Every line they throw, they get a catch)
Feed me! Feed me!
(This crab is on a whole new level)
Give me one more crab, please.
- We did it. This is it. / - No, no.
(This crab is on a whole new level)
- We did it. This is it. / - One more crab, please.
- No, no. / - We won.
- It's really delicious. / - We won. It's over.
- We did it. We did it. / - Today was incredible.
- Yeonwoo's Day! / - Moa Moa Tour!
It's Yeonwoo's Day!
We're going to the outskirts.
I can't make you wait.
- Let's go. / - Go!
Yeonwoo, you look cool today.
I'll trust Lee Dabin today.
It's the ocean.
That's what we expected.
- We fished without bait. / - Caught them!
We caught them.
I can't believe that!
What is that?
- We caught them. / - Caught them!
(Every line they throw, they get a catch)
Feed me! Feed me!
(This crab is on a whole new level)
Give me one more crab, please.
- We did it. This is it. / - No, no.
(This crab is on a whole new level)
- We did it. This is it. / - One more crab, please.
- No, no. / - We won.
- We won. It's over. / - King crab.
- Today was incredible. / - We did it. We did it.
- Yeonwoo's Day. / - Moa Moa Tour!
(The second day of Moa Moa Tour)
Good morning.
- Good morning. / - Good morning.
(They're already in a good mood this morning)
We have to travel to this place first.
We're heading to the outskirts.
- We're going to the outskirts. / - Okay.
In Russia, people carpool like a taxi.
You have to call the vehicle with an app
but I already did that.
I can't let you wait. You mean so much to me.
Where are we going via taxi?
We're going to a place with a rich...
- And long history. / - History?
(This place comes with historical significance)
This comes up first when I look up Sakhalin online.
Monument at the Mountain Pechali.
I think we must go to this place.
What is that?
It represents the longing for one's hometown.
(Mountain Pechali Monument)
Let's go!
Let's go.
Other than historical sites...
Where else are we going?
I prepared something exciting for you.
- Something exciting? / - Yes.
We're going to the outskirts and see Mother Nature.
Mother Nature.
(The view from the car changes to nature)
(50 minutes by car from hotel to the monument)
We're now in nature.
We are. It's Mother Nature.
Where are we? What is this called?
- It's a port. / - A port.
A long time ago, during Japanese ruling,
Koreans were forced to come to Sakhalin through
the Port of Korsakov.
They had a chance to go back to Korea.
But because of the bad situation,
a lot of them couldn't come back to Korea.
So that's where it is.
A monument is built here to remember the sadness.
It's called Monument at the Mountain Pechali.
Let's go.
I didn't know about this.
Is this the monument?
Yes, it is.
(The monument is right next to Port of Korsakov)
(The ship won't come)
(They waited for the ship)
(That will take them back to their home country)
(Full of the feelings of longing and resentment)
From here, you can see the whole Port of Korsakov.
It must be very sad to be there.
(It was built to honor the Koreans missing home)
The name of this monument...
- It's very sad. / - Is so very sad.
I'm sure both of you will never forget this experience.
- For sure. / - You're right.
(The ship won't come, they waited and waited)
It's such a sad story.
So they kept waiting here.
Exactly. They kept waiting here for the ship to come
but the ship never came.
(They waited for the ship that will take them home)
We almost didn't know that this existed in Sakhalin.
- That's true. / - I hope after our visit...
More people take interest and
remember the sad history and mourn together.
Although we're on this trip to have fun,
I thought it would be nice to
learn about the history too.
That's why I brought you here.
You're...
So cool, Yeonwoo.
You're so cool.
Should I trust Lee Dabin today?
It was a good idea to take you to this place first.
- I can rely on you. / - I made you trust me.
(Where is the next destination?)
(Moa Moa Tour, Yeonwoo's Outskirts Tour)
(All-terrain vehicle)
- ATV! / - I want to try that too.
(10 minutes from Monument at the Mountain Pechali)
It was only a 10-minute ride. It was very close.
- I love the proximity. / - It's really close.
It is.
It's a sports center?
It kind of feels like Jeju-do.
- It really does. / - Don't you think so?
- So many activities. / - I wanted to ride a light aircraft.
It's a shame we didn't get to ride one.
We're very used to this vehicle.
We've ridden it before.
I wanted to do something I've done before.
We're going to ride an all-terrain vehicle.
It's not a regular all-terrain vehicle.
It's a monster all-terrain vehicle.
- Monster? / - It's a 550cc ATV.
- 550cc? / - 550cc?
That must be really fast.
(Russian activities are on a whole different level)
(A monster ATV)
It was really big.
It was very fast as well.
(You can see the landscape of Sakhalin)
(It's the best activity to properly feel Mother Nature)
550cc?
It's almost as powerful as a car.
- It's like a car. / - It was very fast too.
- A small car is... / - About 600cc.
- Right? / - Most all-terrain vehicles are 125cc.
It's really big.
It must be very fast.
- You should learn properly. / - It sounds different.
(They get thorough 1 on 1 lessons)
- It sounds grand. / - It was very safe.
Can you ride it without a driving license?
- Yes, you can. / - Without a driving license?
Anyone can ride it after a safety course.
(They're ready)
(For safety, a guide will be driving with them)
(Finally, they take off)
(The two drive into Sakhalin's nature)
Men would love this.
Men would go crazy.
Since it's big and powerful, it's fun riding it.
- I can imagine. / - It feels really good.
- I'm a genius. / - It was really nice.
It feels so nice. I want to keep driving.
(Jooe on the other hand)
I'm scared.
(She's driving as slow as possible)
(A very big puddle)
You should drive on it and splash the water.
You have to just drive through that.
- Yeonwoo was such a good driver. / - Really?
(Jooe is slowly getting used to it)
It's a big road.
(It's an open road that is nice to drive on)
My gosh. It feels so good!
This feels awesome.
This part was the best.
Go, Yeonwoo!
There are a lot of open places here.
- We could feel nature. / - Go, Dabin.
(They aren't afraid of puddles anymore)
Let's go!
(They speed up)
(They speed along the road, overcoming the fear)
- Jooe! / - You're driving to the ocean?
- Yes. / - Yes.
(They stop at the highlight of the place)
It's so pretty. It's beautiful.
- What is this? / - Is it a lake?
A lake?
- It is a lake. / - A lake?
Yes, it's a lake.
It looks gorgeous.
Behind the lake is the sea.
(Sakhalin's nature down the mountainside)
It looks amazing.
It's really beautiful.
(A satisfying and clear view)
Thanks to the long, straight road...
- And the flat land... / - You're right.
We could leisurely
see the beautiful view of nature.
- I loved it. / - I loved it too.
- I mean it. / - I think...
- I should buy one back to Korea. / - What?
I think I should buy one.
Yeonwoo, now that we've seen this beautiful sight,
where are we going next?
We just saw the ocean from a distance.
Now we're going to see it from up close.
I'll show you the ocean.
Up close like this?
Yes, it will be right before your eyes.
- Like this? / - Yes, like that.
I'll take you to the place. Just follow me.
Let's go.
- Let's go. / - Let's continue Yeonwoo Tour.
- Bye, Moa Moa Tour! / - Bye, Moa Moa Tour!
(Moa Moa Tour, Yeonwoo's Outskirts Tour)
(Fishing)
(It takes 40 minutes by car to get to the fishing place)
(Okhotskoye)
(It's a seaside village right next to the Sea of Okhotsk)
- The Sea of Okhotsk? / - So this is where you'll fish.
- There must be a lot of fish there. / - At the beach?
There were a lot of fish.
How many fish will you catch?
I'll catch 3 fish in 10 minutes.
- Here... / - How is that possible?
Of course it's possible. I...
You what?
- I... / - Nothing to say?
My fists are on fire.
- What fist? / - I catch fish with my fist.
Will you punch water like this?
Exactly. If I punch the water like this, fish will pop up.
Let's go. You'll see once we get there.
(Screaming)
You scared me.
(What did she see?)
What's up?
There are so many fish.
- What are they? / - There are so many of them.
- They are... / - They're salmons.
- Are they salmon? / - I've only seen this on TV.
- Are the black things all fish? / - Yes.
- They're swimming upstream. / - Oh, my.
The water is so clean.
Is it a river connected to the Sea of Okhotsk?
- They're coming from the sea. / - I know.
They're going to lay eggs.
It's breeding season, so they're swimming upstream
to lay eggs.
(They're salmon from the Sea of Okhotsk)
- You're now watching salmon... / - Salmon!
Swimming upstream to lay eggs.
(The salmon swim back to the river they were born in)
I can feel their maternal love.
Go, mothers!
- Go, mothers. / - Keep it up.
Let's go fishing now.
You can't see this anywhere.
(They get on a boat on the beach)
Here I come!
I wonder how much the boat ride costs.
Boat rides are usually expensive.
(They sail toward the ocean)
It feels nice.
A half day boat tour is $100?
- Yes, it's a half day tour. / - Per person?
- Actually, I've fished before. / - Have you?
I don't have much experience in ocean fishing.
- But I went fishing with my dad. / - Really?
- So I wanted to do it with Jooe. / - I see.
- It's perfect weather, not too cold. / - Yeah.
I like the sunshine.
- It's getting warmer. / - This is beautiful.
This is great.
(The captain tells them something)
(He points at something)
- Why? / - You can swim in the ocean in summer.
- My gosh. / - Gosh, this is amazing.
- What is that? / - Gosh, this is amazing.
- Why? / - It's a seal.
- What? / - A seal?
- Seal? / - Seal?
- Seals were looking at us. / - It's seals.
Where?
- They were so cute. / - So cute.
- Look at that. / - They are seals.
They all are seals?
- They are true seals. / - True seals.
My goodness.
They are true seals.
Spotted seals?
They're so cute.
- They look so cute. / - So cute.
That's so funny.
- They're so cute. / - They are watching people.
- They are seals. / - They're watching you.
- They were watching us. / - Right.
This is amazing.
It's so cute.
They are so adorable.
I got goose-bumps.
They are really cute.
The seals are watching us.
They all are like this.
It feels like I'm watching a documentary.
It looks like a documentary. This is amazing.
We're seeing a lot of rare sights today.
- Thank you. / - I'll remember this forever.
- This is amazing. / - It's a wonderful experience.
- It was so nice. / - They were really cute.
- We don't get to see seals often. / - Right.
I've never seen a true seal before.
And they were watching you like this.
- That was so cute. / - Dozens of seals did that.
(The boat stops slowly)
Are we fishing here?
(They arrive at the fishing point 10 minutes later)
- Fish. / - Fish.
(The captain is setting the fishing rods)
This is my first time fishing.
(They fish without bait)
- What? Only with a float? / - Without bait.
I've never seen this before.
- You're fishing with a lure. / - She's holding it.
Fake bait.
(They get the fishing rods)
Yeonwoo, you know what?
- Let's make a bet. / - A bet?
It might be hard to fish then.
You'll be surprised.
Yeonwoo seems good at this.
Look at her form.
(They make a bet on fishing)
(But their fishing rods are so calm)
Are they sleeping?
(I heard the fishing is good here)
(Peaceful)
(Jooe's rod, Yeonwoo's rod)
(Surprised)
(Yeonwoo's fishing rod is bending vigorously)
- It's here. / - It feels heavy.
(It looks quite strong)
(The captain helps her)
You failed to catch it because it's too heavy?
It got stuck on a rock.
(She feels dejected)
- It can happen. / - Please edit this out.
It can happen when you fish.
- The fish were very strong. / - Jooe is reeling in.
- What kind of fish? / - At this moment...
I did a great job.
Oh, really?
- Is it fish? / - Did I catch it?
- I was... / - The sea helped her.
- I think you caught it. / - I got it!
- Did you catch it? / - I got it!
You're afraid of fish though.
I overcame the fear...
After fishing.
I got it!
How long did it take?
- About 5 minutes. / - She caught a sea-perch.
- Only 5 minutes? / - Sea-perch tastes good.
She caught a sea-perch in 5 minutes?
(She's catching it again?)
(It feels even heavier)
I got it!
- Who is it? / - It's Jooe.
(She caught two fish at a time)
I got it!
I got it. I got two of them.
- Did you see that? / - Yes.
- See? / - That was so cool.
See? My bucket is full of fish.
Do you see it?
This isn't easy.
(Yeonwoo tries hard to lure fish)
(Yeonwoo's fishing rod shakes heavily)
The important thing is that they don't have bait.
- Right. Without bait. / - They're fishing without bait.
Look at her face.
- Because of the sea breeze... / - Yeonwoo got it.
It's like half fish and half water.
(She finally caught one)
- How many? / - Two fish.
(Yeonwoo caught two fish)
The place offers the best fishing.
And there are various kinds of fish.
- Right. / - They are very big.
- Without a bait. / - You caught 5 fish in 10 minutes?
We went there in September.
It's even better in July and August.
I see.
I got it again. I caught fish.
One fish.
See? My bucket is full of fish.
If you cast it, you can catch one in 3 minutes.
Yeonwoo, I caught one more.
(Jooe 5, Yeonwoo 2)
(Yeonwoo caught two more fish)
It's big.
I caught two again!
(They catch fish every time they cast their rods)
- I got it. / - Gosh, what's going on?
Already?
- It looks so fun. / - It's been less than 30 minutes.
- How many fish? / - It's the best fishing we've seen.
Really?
Gyeonggyu would love this, Yeonwoo.
(Gyeonggyu would love to go fishing with her)
(They caught 13 fish in 30 minutes)
We have bait now.
It works even better with bait.
(They try fishing with bait now)
We released the small fish.
- I guess there's a rule. / - The babies.
(She gets a bite as soon as she casts the fishing rod)
I hope it will be a big one.
Gosh, what's that?
- What? I guess it's big. / - Maybe it's four of them.
She can't reel it in.
It's so strong.
(It's not easy to reel in)
(Jooe's rod, Yeonwoo's rod)
The fishing rod is bent.
(It's not easy to reel up the fish)
What? What did she catch?
I got it.
(The fish is finally coming up to the surface)
Don't you need a scoop net?
My goodness.
- What? / - That's amazing.
- This is unbelievable. / - My gosh.
Five fish?
It looks gross.
It's not gross. It's beautiful.
Gosh, this is amazing.
Are the fish stupid?
It was amazing.
We caught 20 fish in an instant.
Please take a picture of us.
I can't believe this.
(Jooe is a little afraid of fish)
- It looks so fun. / - Oh, my goodness.
- She's afraid of fish. / - Gosh, wait.
- She caught sea-perch again. / - Sea-perch.
It's so big.
Jooe's very lucky when she fishes.
- Right. / - I think I'm lucky.
(You can catch various kinds of fish at the right time)
(Captain)
- Fillet the fish. / - What are you talking about?
I'm not done yet.
- Yeonwoo, the bucket is full. / -  Give me 2 hours.
It's not full yet.
I have a lot of fish.
Gosh, they caught 20 in total.
- Fillet the fish now. I'm hungry. / - Are you serious?
I'm hungry.
(How can we eat this?)
Director, can you please help us?
(We want to eat raw fish)
We will give you one fish.
Right. We will give you one for free.
(Okay, I'll fillet the fish for you)
(The director fillets the fish)
The captain is supposed to do this.
In Russia, they don't eat raw fish.
Oh, that's right.
They don't know how to fillet the fish.
The director seems good at this though.
- It looks delicious. / - He looks skilled.
- Cold sea fish taste good. / - The director...
(Jooe finally tastes the raw fish)
(It's so delicious)
(Yeonwoo tastes it too)
It's good.
It's delicious.
- It was really good. / - It was so delicious.
I've never tried fresh-caught fish.
Thanks to you, I finally get to eat fish in Sakhalin.
It feels like this sea-perch is moving in my mouth.
By the way,
it's not easy to get sauce in Sakhalin.
There are a lot of Korean products there.
They sell hot pepper paste with vinegar there?
Yes. In the supermarket.
We went to a supermarket,
and there was everything.
They sell everything.
(They're enjoying the raw fish)
We ate it all.
To be honest,
I'm not full yet.
Of course not.
Most people won't get full on this.
We can have crabs...
At the captain's place.
Really?
We have to eat crabs in Sakhalin.
Now that we tasted raw fish,
we should eat crabs now.
We will just taste some crabs?
No, we will eat a lot.
(Moa Moa Tour, Yeonwoo's Outskirts Tour)
(Sakhalin king crab)
- It's here. / - Crab.
- Gosh, this is a problem. / - It looks weird.
- What's that? / - This is too strong.
Those are all horns.
You should be careful when you eat it.
- Look at that. / - You can't find...
- That crab in Korea. / - I've never seen it before.
How... How...
You can't even freeze it?
- No. / - Is it a natural monument?
- You can eat it only in Sakhalin. / - Natural monument.
- It's from the Sea of Okhotsk. / - Sea of Okhotsk.
- You can find it in Korea... / - It's only $20?
But there are not many.
- How much is it? / - It's $20 per kilogram.
(It's the best dish in Sakhalin)
It's right next to the ocean.
The captain's house is right there.
He also provides lodging for tourists
who come here for fishing.
This is a special course I prepared for you.
(They have the last meal at the captain's house)
There's nothing though.
- I want to eat. / - It'll be served soon.
It'll be served live.
Live?
We will eat a live crab.
- It's here. / - The captain's wife serves it?
(What's that?)
It'd look scary.
- It fills the whole tray. / - It looks so scary though.
You choose which one to eat?
- You should choose. / - This type of crabs...
Are very valuable here.
- You have to try it. / - Right.
This is what we usually eat.
I want the red king crab over the other one.
Sounds good.
(The red king crab goes straight into boiling water)
They cook it in boiling water instead of steaming it?
It looks good.
That's why it's so moist.
- They didn't steam it. / - It looks delicious.
They don't just steam it.
- They steam it and boil it. / - Yes.
(The red king crab boasts it's red color)
That was really amazing.
- Gosh, look at that. / - That looks good.
It really looks big.
(She takes a big bite of the claw first)
(The size of the red king crab is surprising)
- It is full of meat. / - That claw alone...
- Would make you full. / - Yeah.
It costs only $20 per kilogram.
It is really full of meat.
(Jooe also takes a bite of the red king crab)
It's really meaty.
It tastes a little different from average king crab.
Average king crabs feel like crab meat.
This is chewier. It's almost like squid.
Nice and chewy.
The texture is amazing.
The reason why it's good is because...
It's not only fresh but also well-seasoned.
(It's more flavorful because of the natural saltiness)
- They need wine. / - Champagne or white wine.
- White wine. / - Beer.
They don't sell alcohol.
You can bring your own drinks.
That's amazing!
- That's even better! / - That's even better!
- Even better. / - You don't have to pay for drinks.
- That's right. / - Of course.
I should go to Sakhalin.
(The plain red king crab tastes amazing)
- It's so good. / - This is it.
Aren't crustaceans beautiful?
There is soft flesh inside these hard shells.
I was so surprised. I thought it was a facial spray.
How is it different?
Compared to ordinary blue crabs.
- It's a little chewier. / - Chewier?
- The texture is like squid. / - Really?
- It's really chewy. / - The meat is kind of like...
- Red king crabs are like this. / - It's very firm?
It's very firm.
You can feel the chewiness when you chew?
(They eat it up in no time)
(They feed each other)
(This is the result of them eating and eating)
I think we ate it clean.
(There aren't any legs left)
Can't you eat this in front of you?
We will eat the body now.
(Take the shell off)
It's filled with a lot of things.
This also has a lot of meat.
(The meat from the body is revealed)
You have to dip it with what's inside there.
- That's right. / - Gosh.
You have to dip it with...
- What's inside there. / - That's right.
You have to eat it mixed with white rice.
It's chewy.
(They both take a big bite)
This part is really delicious.
It's really delicious. It's really delicious.
It's really chewy.
- She's showing it for us. / - It was really moist.
The legs taste better for crabs like this than the meat.
The captain recommended the body for us.
(Jooe takes it and bites it off)
Everyone, you must hurry.
In a month, that place will be packed with Koreans.
(They focus on eating without talking)
It's really good. That was amazing.
(Only the shells are left!)
2kg is too little.
You should order one more.
The flow shouldn't be stopped. Hurry!
- 1 person should eat 1 crab. / - Yes.
- We did a refill. / - That's right.
Oh, my God.
You should eat quickly.
(They attack the legs as soon as it came out)
I want to live in Russia.
She's not even putting the scissors down to eat.
She knows the taste.
She forgot about the camera.
We didn't respect the food by showing good manners.
- Why? / - We didn't take photos.
- Photo. / - They forgot to take a photo.
We were distracted.
(They already finished eating everything)
(They've already cut the legs)
Such bad manners.
- Let's put them back. / - Okay.
There are people like that.
I can't understand people who pull the crab apart
and make it whole again just for a photo.
We wanted to go that far because it looked so good.
- You're cruel. / - The legs are all apart.
(You can see the cut leg here)
That's enough. Let's eat.
- Cheers! / - Cheers!
(Can't get sick of the red king crab)
It's good.
- Gosh. / - That looks really delicious.
They ate a lot.
It's cheap. You should eat like that when you're there.
- It's cheap. / - Yes.
Today is really amazing.
We fished and ate something that's only in Russia.
It's so nice but I feel sad.
I feel really sad.
We ate a lot
but there's so much we haven't tried.
- Let's come again next time. / - Okay.
Let's come to eat.
- Let's come to eat. / - Let's come to eat.
- Not for other things. / - Let's come to drink Vodka.
I'm really happy.
(The last night in Sakhalin came before they knew)
Where is this place?
- It's right there. / - In front of the captain's house.
- The captain is working hard. / - It's our last night.
- The last night came. / - Yes.
To be honest, I always went...
On trips with my family.
It's my first time going on a trip with a friend.
We had lots of fun today.
We went on rides yesterday.
It was really fun.
We shouted together
without worrying about anything else.
I think I was the only excited one.
- Yes. / - As you said...
This was also my first time going on a trip like this.
I was worried a lot,
but there was no need to be worried.
I had so much fun.
- That's right. / - It's not easy to go on a trip...
To Sakhalin but we came here.
- That's right. / - It's so full of charm...
And it's so beautiful.
I think it will become a good memory.
It was more meaningful and fun than I thought.
I really liked it.
Thank you for having fun with me.
- Okay. / - Thank you.
I went through some trouble to play with you.
I played with you today.
- You know that, right? / - We had fun together.
That's right. We had fun together.
Cheers.
(The end of Moa Moa Tour's Sakhalin trip)
That's enough.
I think it's enough for us.
I think we really reached the highest point.
- That's enough. / - How did it feel to catch 5 fish?
- That's right. / - It was your first time fishing.
She was even afraid of fish.
I had so much fun.
It felt so nice to catch 5 fish at once.
- That's why people fish. / - That's why people fish.
She opened her eyes to fishing.
It was so fun. More so because I caught more fish
than Yeonwoo.
You can't fish if you go there right now, right?
It's October. It will become winter soon.
- No, in the wintertime... / - Yes?
- You can do ice fishing. / - You can do ice fishing.
- Can you fish on top of ice? / - Yes.
- Can you do ice fishing? / - Yes, you can do it.
I need to go there.
There are so many good things to eat.
If you like to fish,
July to September will be perfect for you.
If you go on time, you will have a lot of fun.
You ate 4kg of crab. Wasn't that too much...
- For a girl group? / - We refrained ourselves a little.
- Did you refrain yourselves? / - Really?
We even had dessert.
- Could you eat more? / - Of course.
Can you eat red king crabs anytime then?
Or do they have a specific season?
- They have a season. / - You must eat it.
- It's not frequent. / - Yes.
It depends on when they're caught.
You can only have red king crab there.
- Red king crabs. / - Red king crabs.
Both of you are like the audience.
We need to make plans.
- We're holding hands. / - We were planning.
- We should go there. / - Everyone, make plans to go.
Let's check out how much they spent.
- Our Moa Moa Tour... / - Should be a lot.
Spent 3 days and 2 nights in Russia.
- The amount we spent in Sakhalin is... / - It is?
- Please. / - Excluding airfares...
- And per person... / - Per person.
$382.
- We were much cheaper. / - Thing is...
It wasn't cheap.
The boat ride was $100 per person.
- That's right. / - There was boat ride.
- The activities. They add up. / - The ATV.
- They also ate one crab each. / - That's right.
- You ate a lot. / - Yes.
- Okay, let's vote. / - Let's vote.
Will you take Moa Moa Tour
and travel to Sakhalin? Yes or no?
- Please vote! / - Please vote!
(They designed a trip to hidden location)
(What will the judges choose?)
Okay, will it be SuDa Signal's Bandung trip?
Or will it be Moa Moa Tour's Sakhalin trip?
What did the judges choose?
- Here we go. / - Moa Moa Tour to Sakhalin.
- SuDa Signal to Bandung. / - Bandung.
Bandung, Sakhalin. Sakhalin, Bandung.
The result?
The result is...
- Zero. Six. / - Oh, no.
- Six! / - I'm nervous!
- No, no. Moa Moa! / - Why am I scared?
Come on nine! Show me a nine!
Show me a nine!
(Bandung wins)
(Sakhalin 76 vs. Bandung 90)
What's going on?
Our trip was really cost-effective.
- That's right. / - It was about $200.
- That's right. / - They were close to $400.
They spent more money with the boat...
- To show us more things. / - That's right.
They can't beat us because of the cost.
Alright, everyone.
Hwan was here as the special host today.
You almost fainted because of Sakhalin today.
- I lost again today. / - Will you come again next week?
Can't I just come next week?
Since I lost?
- Above all, it was so meaningful... / - Yes.
- For the Sakhalin team. / - It was so nice.
- I felt really proud. / - Thank you.
- We have an amazing project... / - It's amazing.
- Coming up next week. / - Yes. It's a special.
Sikyung, I heard you two went on the trip!
(Host special, Hwijae vs. Sikyung)
It's a host special.
It will be a gourmet trip next week.
- They sent us to gain weight. / - Must tune in.
Guess where they sent us?
(What country did they design for a gourmet trip?)
Sung Sikyung went to Italy.
Lee Hwijae went to...
Spain!
It really suits both of them.
They weren't the only ones who went on a trip.
We weren't the only ones.
We each went with the best chefs in Korea.
- I'm really looking forward to it. / - It's a real battle.
- To Spain? / - Please look forward to next week.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
(Next episode)
I'm here in Catalonia Square!
We have to watch Flamenco.
It has history.
It's called the kitchen of Europe.
It's the largest food market.
They have fire and tapas...
This is incredible.
It's weird doing this with a guy with a mustache.
Why?
This is amazing.
How are we in an alley right now?
If you don't stay focused here, you'd eat 900 calories.
This is the Salute.
- It's nice. / - It's really so cool.
(Battle Trip)