Hello, I live in Jinju.
I'm Gwon Minseong, 33 years old.
I'm planning a hot spring trip for the winter.
Please plan a unique hot spring trip
that will refresh my mind and body on Battle Trip.
(Nha Trang, Vietnam, hot spring trip)
This is nice.
Can't I leave it here?
Vietnam.
There's a legend that's similar to one in Korea.
I'm so scared.
It's all good but
they don't give us napkins.
Darn it!
Milk!
You insane?
It's a mud hot spring with an egg theme.
It's good because I like things like this.
Since prices are so low...
You can order whatever you like.
It's really good.
- It's so good. / - Yeah.
- Nha Trang Tour. / - Nha Trang Tour.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
(Numerous great tips on trips)
It's time for Battle Trip where we give you
great tips on trips.
We're continuing on with the hot spring trips.
Today, we're heading to Fukuoka.
We're back with our four guests.
Long time no see.
- It's been a week. / - Oh, welcome.
Nha Trang...
- It was so... / - It was so good.
So good.
We accept that their food and prices were good.
Please add that...
Add dark circles under her eyes with CG.
- Why, ma'am? / - Us?
- Yes. / - What do you mean?
- We're so healthy. / - We're fine.
- You're okay, right, Jungah? / - Yes.
- For us... / - You looked tired from the first day.
But...
When it comes to traveling...
Being cheap and having good food is important.
- But who you're going with is also important. / - It is.
And how well you spend your time there as well.
- That's right. / - That's important.
One of the beauties of traveling is
the short distance trips.
- Short distance. / - That's right.
If you have to travel too far...
- But Fukuoka is too close. / - Traveling far by car...
- It's like Jeju-do. / - It wasn't that short.
- It's true. / - It's too close.
- It wasn't that short. / - It's a good thing.
It's like an overseas trip in Jeju-do.
No... You should go far for a trip.
- A bit. / - That's not true.
Fukuoka is a better place to go with children.
It was a short trip but we used our time wisely.
- It was nice. / - Let's watch it then.
- Okay. / - Shall we?
Is there anything special about Fukuoka?
There have been many trips to Japan so far.
You can forget about all those other trips to Japan.
- Was it that good? / - It was that fun.
There are more than 20 hot springs.
In the village?
Yes, in the village.
- It's a hot spring village. / - Right.
It's like a hot spring village.
You get a medal at the entrance.
- With it, you can go to any hot spring. / - Any?
If you don't have time to go to each one,
you can hand over the medal to someone else.
You can pass it on?
- That's right. / - It's a unique system.
- It's like clubbing culture. / - That's right.
- Like on club day. / - That's right.
Is there a time limit?
- You can use it for 6 months. / - 6 months?
- Yes. / - If I can't use it...
You can take it home and use it again?
Yes. If I can't use it...
- I can give it to someone else. / - Sounds expensive.
Each place has a distinct feature.
So you can choose the hot spring you want,
experience it...
- Then you can experience another one. / - Right.
- It's really diverse. / - It's like Hot Spring Day.
- That's right. / - Exactly.
- Tell us about one dish. / - You can't leave food out.
- In Fukuoka... / - When it comes to Fukuoka...
- Pollack roe is famous there. / - Pollack roe?
Pollack roe tastes the same everywhere.
- That's right. / - It's nothing special.
We brought some back because it was so good.
Yeah.
- I'm sorry, but... / - Unlike the Korean type...
Can you turn off Jungsoo's mic?
She keeps butting in.
"Pollack roe tastes the same everywhere."
How are we to make a living?
- The saltiness... / - Let us be on her dramas then!
When it comes to Fukuoka...
- The seafood is great there. / - Right.
I heard there are a lot of beautiful women in Fukuoka.
- Fukuoka beauties. / - Really?
- The water's good. / - The women...
- The food is fresh. / - Because the water is good.
- I know. / - That's why their hot springs...
and food are famous.
Is the pollack roe eaten as a side dish?
They eat it topped on rice.
Unlike Korean pollack roe,
they ferment it in kelp broth.
It has a deep flavor.
- It's tasty, but not salty. / - It's subtle.
Pollack roe is popular in Fukuoka.
When people go to Fukuoka...
- They always buy them as gifts. / - That's right.
- Did you buy it? / - Of course we did.
Pollack roe mayonnaise...
- I couldn't miss it. / - I bought pollack roe tubes.
What about pollack roe mayonnaise?
- I bought it as well. / - We bought that too.
- I love pollack roe mayonnaise. / - It must be good.
- It must be delicious. / - With the roe I bought...
- I cooked pollack roe pasta... / - Coffee's better.
- And many other dishes. / - Jungsoo keeps saying...
"Coffee is better. Pollack roe isn't that good."
Ma'am...
We have plenty of good coffee in Korea.
I'd better never see you eating pollack roe!
Just you wait.
Lee Hwijae...
Lee Hwijae, you insane?
You insane?
Fine, I am!
Okay, everyone.
Let's check out the first half
of the Fukuoka trip.
(How far did you go in Fukuoka?)
It's beautiful.
It looks pretty.
The flying time is about one hour.
So nice.
(There's plenty of cheap and good food)
It's a foodie's paradise.
That's the one.
(Hot springs)
(Healing)
(Food tour)
(Shopping)
(Let's go to Fukuoka)
Did you eat?
I just ate whatever at home.
Right? You had some brunch?
- Just whatever. / - Right.
What does this place remind you of?
A hot spring.
- It does, right? / - Isn't it a hot spring?
- That's why I prepared this. / - You're right.
Right.
Isn't it a bathhouse?
That was the concept...
- Of that cafe. / - Since the theme is hot spring...
We went to a cafe with a hot spring theme.
Is it a cafe?
It feels like...
- We're at a hot spring. / - I know.
This is like a warm up. Then we'll head to the
hot spring and enjoy a hot bath there.
Haven't we been to Japan twice?
- Only once? / - No.
- I went for a drama. / - Oh, once for a drama...
- And it's been about 10 years. / - Right.
The thing is...
I heard Jungah
recommended me.
So I...
I was so happy to hear.
A trip can change depending
on who you go with.
- That's so true. / - I'll make it fun.
So
- I wanted to go with a close friend. / - I know.
Even if we meet after a long time,
we can go out for a cup of coffee.
- And it feels like we met yesterday. / - Right.
- Even if we don't meet so often. / - That's important.
So I gave her a call.
And Haeyeong was like,
"Okay, Jungah!"
That's how...
- We ended up here. / - Make sure you take me.
Do you often go to
public bathhouses?
We live near each other.
- We live in the same neighborhood. / - Neighbors.
Right.
The thing is...
It's kind of like a freestyle trip.
- Have you been to Fukuoka? / - Never.
Have you been there?
Yes. I stayed in a ryokan.
Hot springs are famous there.
For me...
- It's so beautiful. / - In Fukuoka...
- Yufuin is beautiful. / - Yufuin.
- Beppu. / - Yufuin is really nice.
We're best friends going to Beppu.
- She just made a pun. / - That's lame.
You said you'd make it fun.
We're best friends going to Beppu.
You mean Beppu.
Best friends.
Yufuin.
Yoo-hoo.
Those places are famous but...
Are we going there?
- Not this time. / - We're not?
This time, we're going
to someplace new.
- It's a secret. / - Not somewhere famous.
That's right. You should go deep.
Exactly.
It's like a secret we can reveal
on Battle Trip.
- That's what I prepared. / - You know about it?
- I prepared. / - You know about it?
I don't know if she actually knows or...
Right now...
It's just...
I bought this!
Oh, my!
- Check this out. / - Wow.
It tells you where to go.
- I can't believe this. / - She made a list.
- Haeyeong prepared everything. / - So nice.
- She did? / - I went to Japan several times.
Fukuoka is famous for seafood.
Do you like seafood? Would you like some...
Would you like some seafood?
I love seafood.
Is there anything you want to eat?
So much.
- I love seafood. / - So much to eat.
I like meat.
And I like alcohol.
I like hot springs.
- There's so much. / - Desserts are famous there too.
You know, desserts are sweet.
So we might come back with extra pounds.
That's alright. I can afford to gain some weight...
- If I can be satisfied 120%. / - Right.
- Right. / - I can lose weight afterwards.
I guess your metabolism is still fast enough.
You go.
Just go.
- 20s? / - Yeah.
You're in your 40s.
The original.
If you just have this...
This is cheaper.
(Bubbly guide with dad jokes, Yun Haeyeong)
Why are you so slow-witted?
Think before you speak.
Intimidating ladies.
It's my first time in Fukuoka!
So...
This is so pretty.
(Heart of a girl but intimidating, Yang Jungah)
Hi!
Was that a private pool?
- Yes. / - And you had an ocean view.
They are having yakiniku too.
Open air hot spring too.
- Japanese yakiniku... / - Yakiniku is so good.
Fuku, Fuku, Fukuoka!
Let's go warm ourselves up.
How many years has it been?
I know.
- Being on a trip. / - I know.
I'm happy to be on a plane.
(Even boarding the plane gets them excited)
Fuku, Fuku, Fukuoka.
- Fuku, Fuku. / - See you soon.
- Fuku, Fuku? / - Fuku, Fuku.
To Fukuoka, the warm city.
Destinations with short flight times.
- They're the best. / - You're right.
With the hotel close to the airport.
- That's right. / - I prefer those places.
(Fukuoka's weather is fairly warm the whole year)
Since it's in the south, it's warm.
It's ranked as the 7th best city to reside in the world.
- It's ranked 7th? / - It's a sister city to Busan.
(The city has beautiful sea and beaches)
(Fukuoka)
- We are finally here. / - Is this it?
Fuku, Fuku.
- The weather is amazing. / - Fukuoka.
The weather here is excellent.
Hey, is it summer here?
- It never goes below zero. / - That's right.
- It feels like we're in Jeju-do, right? / - Yeah.
Since Japan is an island,
the air is bound to be fresh.
It's my first time in Fukuoka.
Are you happy?
If you're happy, I'm happy too.
We need to take one of those buses.
- Do you know where we're supposed to go? / - Sure.
This is called...
SUNQ Pass.
For three days...
1, 2, 3.
North Kyushu...
You can use this in Kyushu
for all your transport.
If you buy one of the passes...
You can use public transports without a limit
throughout the trip.
When did you prepare these passes?
It's cheaper in Korea.
If you buy it here, it's too expensive.
Did you buy them in Korea?
Yes, I looked for them online.
You should have told me then.
Fukuoka has the shortest distance from
the airport to the city in Asia.
- Is that so? / - Yes.
That's really short.
- Jungah. / - Yeah?
- Since we worked hard, we must feed. / - Right on!
Let's go. Go!
They're going to "feed" themselves.
We worked hard for this.
Hey, it's in Korean?
There are a lot of signs in Korean.
It's really nice that Korean is written on the bus.
- That way, you won't get lost. / - You're right.
They announce it in Korean too.
- Chinese, Korean, English, and Japanese. / - Really?
- Let's get on. / - Where do I put this? Here?
Maybe not.
This is not it.
(Get on the bus from the back entrance, take ticket)
(When getting off, show ticket and pay or present pass)
(This is where you pay the fee)
Come on over.
We're on a bus.
Have you ridden a bus on a trip?
- I haven't been on a bus in ages. / - I know, right?
I don't have to take the bus in Korea.
Good-bye...
Airport.
The weather is really great.
It's so good.
Oh, the sun.
It's 10 to 15 minutes.
You can get there in 20 minutes.
- The visuals... / -  I remember that!
I love pollack roe.
It's so good.
It's famous for pollack roe.
I can't wait.
- I read that it's really popular. / - I know.
We're going to a famous restaurant in Fukuoka, right?
Pollack roe topped rice.
You can look forward to it.
- It'd be worth it. / - Will we have to wait?
I'm going to eat it even if I have to wait for it.
What I really liked was that
I was hungry as soon as I got off,
but the famous restaurant was only 5 minutes away.
- Only 5 minutes? / - Yes.
Fukuoka is great because
you can reach everywhere on foot.
- That's awesome. / - You're right.
That's the type of city I like best.
It's only 3 or 4 minutes away from here.
- Really? / - On foot.
We won't have to walk a lot.
It's quite tranquil here, isn't it?
- It's not crowded. / - Yeah.
Unlike Tokyo
or Ginza Street.
It's autumn here.
We get to walk around the park.
It's relaxing, isn't it?
The weather here is...
Where is the restaurant?
I think this is the place.
Jungah, I think this must be the restaurant.
- Is this the one? / - Yes.
This is the restaurant.
Come here. Hurry.
Hi.
Welcome.
My gosh, that's a long queue.
- It's like... / - There are so many autographs.
- It was a famous restaurant. / - Looks tasty.
But you didn't have to wait?
In Japan, I always had to wait in line so...
You normally would
but we arrived a little late.
So we were lucky.
It already looks tasty.
The table says it all.
Look at all the autographs.
Jungah, you should leave yours here too.
Why would I do that? I doubt they know who I am.
- I'm hungry. Let's order now. / - Right. We should.
Excuse me.
Give us the menu, please.
Nice.
"Give us the menu, please."
- She spoke like a local. / - Nice and short.
Well done.
What's good here?
- I want... / - Everything is in Korean.
- That's right. / - This is nice.
- Was it all in Korean? / - Yes.
Really?
You're right.
- I like it. / - A combo?
The rice with pollack roe
is the most famous one.
I want this one.
- We'll get one of that. / - I want this one.
Since we are here...
- We should eat noodles. / - You're right.
- Tsukemen. / - This looks good.
- We'll get those two? / - Excuse me.
Please give us this and this.
She's good at Japanese.
Thank you.
- They understand. / - Korean...
It's all in Korean...
- Right. / - Don't you speak Japanese?
What are you talking about?
I know things like,
I just know interjections.
Amazing!
Pretty!
Really?
We're unbelievable.
Jungah, our food is coming.
Here they are.
It's finally here.
How good would it be?
Here, here.
Be careful. It's very hot.
Ah, yeah.
I'm salivating.
- Right? / - Yeah.
Just the visuals makes me drool.
It's kind of like...
When we eat soba,
it'd be nice to dip a little every bite.
I want to try that.
- We'd better go. / - Yes, we ought to visit.
- Pollack roe. / - This is the famous dish.
That looks really good.
It was amazing.
- I bet it was delicious. / - Mix it with sesame.
Mix it?
Jungah, it wasn't sesame.
It was pollack roe.
It was pollack roe?
Yes. You told me to mix the sesame but...
It was pollack roe.
It's not like I know. Geez.
We are funny, aren't we?
This looks so good.
Try it, Jungah.
I'm so excited.
My mouth is salivating.
I even ate my hair.
I can taste the flavor more now...
- Than when I was eating it. / - You're right.
Is it good?
Is it delicious?
Why? Why? Why?
- It was a little. / - Haeyeong...
- Has a unique sense of humor. / - Why?
Is it delicious?
I must have been starving.
Is it good?
(Mouthful)
Was it salty?
It was slightly salty.
- We thought... / - It could be too salty for Koreans.
- Pollack roe is salty for us. / - We just go there so...
Is it good?
It's salty.
It's salty
but it's good.
- We should've poured the water. / - It's salty!
We didn't pour the broth there.
- You were supposed add the broth? / - Yes.
I don't believe this.
- You have to add the broth. / - That's usually salty.
This must be hot water.
- I don't think this is broth. / - We don't know anything.
Japanese food is either salty or sweet.
- But it's still tasty. / - It is, right?
The aftertaste is quite flavorful.
We had it too strong.
By the way, the noodles are exceptional.
They are firm.
- You were supposed to dip them? / - That's right.
That must be so good.
With the water,
it's the flavor I like.
It has an addictive depth to the flavor.
- It had depth. / - Depth of flavor.
It's good.
Let's try this one now.
- That's right. / - When you make onigiri...
- You make it with roe. / - How do you eat that?
- Is there rice on the bottom? / - Yes.
I see the rice.
- Japanese rice is tasty. / - It's similar to gyudon.
Goodness, my mouth is watering.
- It's good. / - Kimchi, please.
This is so good.
- I want to eat kimchi now. / - What?
By the way,
I should try this too.
I can put the rice in the bowl...
And make an easy meal at home.
- You're right. / - It's that type of menu.
We'd need rice and dried laver
with pollack roe on top.
We can add
the spicy sauce.
We can mix it with the sauce.
You can make this at home.
- But it wouldn't taste the same. / - You're right.
- Not at home. / - It's not the same.
The sauce is unique.
There is seasoning like furikake on top.
You're right. They don't taste like pollack roe.
I can taste something else too.
Wasn't it salty?
It wasn't soy sauce.
- It's a kelp... / - Tsuyu sauce.
We ordered the original one but
there are other special sauces, like spicy sauce.
- You can pick and choose. / - You can choose?
- Is it good? / - Yes.
- Isn't it good, Haeyeong? / - Yes.
My gosh, I'm full.
I ate so well.
I'm hungry.
- Let's eat more while shopping. / - Sure, sure.
Thank you for the food.
How much is it?
Fukuoka is famous for this ingredient.
One of the things we must buy from Fukuoka is...
Pollack roe.
And the desserts.
I heard that anyone who visits, must buy pollack roe.
Every snack tastes delicious
with pollack roe mayonnaise.
The pollack roe will be enough to
make the whole dish taste delicious.
We need to buy something like that.
This store is located in downtown, Fukuoka.
- That must be a famous shop. / - Yes.
It's extremely famous.
This must be the shop.
- I think so. / - It's the famous pollack roe shop.
I heard this shop is really famous.
Hello.
My gosh, what is this? It's a tube.
Hey, I guess that's pollack roe ice cream.
That's ice cream?
- Pollack roe ice cream? / - That's unique.
I see canned pollack roe too.
- Canned pollack roe is great. / - Looks so good.
Is that alcohol?
They eat pollack roe
out of the tube?
I guess so.
Aren't they like mayonnaise?
The one in the tube?
They are probably flavorful.
I bet it's really good.
Ah, taste...
It works?
All you need is rice.
Taste the samples.
- So you can have a meal while you taste. / - Yes.
- Let's try it. / - These are all samples for tasting.
- We can taste them. / - Let's try them.
Original...
Original.
How is it? Is it good?
It's good.
- It's good. / - Is it that good?
It's really good.
Now, I understand why people say
Japanese pollack roe has depth.
Precisely. It tastes like fermented pollack roe.
It's good. It's not bad, right?
It wasn't salty. It was delicious.
It's not that salty either.
This is good.
This one is spicy.
I'm thinking of buying these two.
I'm sure you'll like it too, Jungsoo.
- So pretty. / - I want to taste it. I really do.
They come in tubes too.
- It's convenient. / - That's so good.
Is it delicious?
I can taste the roe.
I can taste the pollack roe.
And it's savory too.
It's easier to eat it when it's in a tube.
Besides, it's not salty at all.
We can just eat it by itself.
- We can just mix it with rice. / - Exactly.
Just squeeze it over the rice.
- Kids will love that. / - You're right.
That's so...
It's tasty.
- It is, isn't it? / - Yes.
- It's similar to the original one. / - You're right.
I liked the one with olive and basil.
Rice?
You can mix it with rice.
You can put it in rolled omelets.
Pasta?
Pasta would taste great with this.
Isn't it salty if you eat that much?
- No, it wasn't. / - It wasn't that salty.
We kept on tasting it.
These would go really well with drinks.
How is it possible?
This is squid.
I should buy this.
- It's cheap too. / - I am going to buy this...
This one and this one.
Thank you.
I made reservations for a hot spring with a great view.
- Really? / - Yes.
- Let's hurry then. / - Let's go.
This is the main event at last.
Right, now that we had our meals.
Ryokan in Karatsu.
The countryside is charming.
- That's so true. / - Rural areas are more charming.
Then how long did it take to get to Karatsu?
It took 1 hour.
- An hour by bus. / - 1 hour by bus.
(This is Karatsu)
Jungah.
- We're walking on a quiet street... / - Seriously.
In the countryside.
There's a ryokan in a place like this?
Yes, but the thing is that...
They are going to pick us up.
- Really? / - I arranged the pick-up service.
- Someone's coming? / - Yes, we have to wait.
But this is such a...
It must be an old Japanese village.
I thought so too.
It's really quiet.
- The weather is great. / - The village...
The village is very peaceful.
I think that must be it.
It's here. It's here.
The ryokan provides...
- Do they provide pick-up service? / - Yes, they do.
I heard that even small ryokans provide...
- A pick-up service. / - Yes, they do indeed.
So it was really convenient.
Come here.
It's an automatic sliding door.
Automatic.
After you book the place,
just request the pick-up service,
and they come and get you.
The van comes to the bus stop you get off at.
It comes to the bus stop.
We are here. This must be the place.
- Is that it? / - Yes.
How pretty.
Thank you so much.
Jungah, this is it.
Let's get off.
It's so pretty.
I can feel the wind from the sea.
It's really breezy.
It looks great.
I know, right? Jungah, look at that. My goodness.
- Should we go inside first? / - Yes, let's do that.
How beautiful.
Hyunjoo, we ought to go there.
How much was the ryokan?
I'm sure it was expensive.
- They're always expensive. / - Ryokans are.
But the price includes dinner
and breakfast.
- That's right. / - Really?
Let's take off our shoes first.
- I should look elegant walking in. / - Haeyeong!
Yes?
- Look at the view. / - My gosh!
I love this!
Actually, that's really cheap.
- Right? / - Yes, yes.
That's so nice.
- It was really clean too. / - Does this make sense?
The view from the room was...
The ocean...
I love this!
This is the best ryokan ever.
This is incredible.
Isn't the view breathtaking?
This is nice!
- This reminds me of... / - This is awesome!
Haeundae in Busan.
- Don't you agree? / - You're right.
This is just so beautiful.
Even the waves are calm.
I can't believe this, Jungah.
It feels like I'm on top of the world.
This is so great.
I've never stayed in a place like this.
Hey, where is it?
Where's the hot spring?
- Let's hurry. / - The hot spring?
I read that there's an
open air hot spring upstairs.
- Open air hot spring? / - Yes.
Seriously. That's a great ryokan.
- We had the sea for our view. / - Seawater pool.
Hyunjoo, you are awfully quiet all of a sudden.
- I want to go there now. / - Excuse me?
- You worked hard, Hyunjoo. / - She wants to go.
- I really want to visit. / - You really want to go there?
It was named as 1 of 100 beautiful views in Japan.
It was 1 of the 100?
That's right.
Hey.
Why is the hot spring so tiny?
Should I go in first?
You go in first.
Me first?
It's warm.
Oh, my. The music...
Do they always play this music?
Is it automatic?
Hey.
I feel like I need to dance.
This is almost...
The water isn't as warm as I thought it'd be.
It's hot though.
Because the hot spring here...
I love this. Oh, my.
When I dipped my feet first,
it wasn't that warm.
But as I stayed in the water a bit longer...
- I could feel the heat rising. / - It was warm.
It's so hot!
It's hot?
It's not that hot.
This is nice.
So nice.
Cold above.
And warm below.
Amazing.
(Refreshing air and warm mineral water)
- This is amazing. / - Unbelievable.
Can we use this at night?
Of course we can.
I think we can stay here until 10 p.m.
We should have brought a can of beer.
I'll get you some later.
- Drinking cold sake would be great there. / - Exactly.
You know.
With pollack roe snacks.
Let's get some beer later.
What is that?
With this...
Let me pour it on you.
Like this.
I heard water is excellent here.
This is so sleek.
My skin feels smooth.
- It does, doesn't it? / - Yes.
This is the thing about hot spring.
When you're done, you check your skin once it dries.
When I was in Korea,
I hurt my shoulders while filming a drama.
My shoulders ached a lot.
I'm not lying when I say this.
We did the hot spring on our first day.
- The next day, I didn't feel pain. / - It got better, right?
It got so much better.
Because it helps with circulation
so it can't help but lessen the pain.
- It's a hot spring but... / - It was a mineral hot spring.
- The view is spectacular. / - It improves circulation.
The view...
- It's been so long... / - Since you relaxed?
Yes.
I haven't had time to relax.
Though there are a lot of hot springs in Japan,
we drove here an hour and got to soak in one...
- And see the sea. / - And the ocean.
The view is so nice.
Karatsu is actually very famous
for saltwater hot springs.
It's Karatsu, not Oratsu.
- Stop saying nonsense Japanese. / - Karatsu.
Just because I don't know, you're making...
No, no. It's so you can memorize it easily.
I'm considering you...
Think before you talk.
She's so tough.
What a great expression.
"Think before you talk."
Think before you talk.
This place is really great.
We get to relax.
It's super close to Korea.
Exactly.
I heard they
serve us delicious dinner here.
Yes. It's a course meal.
I'm so happy.
Let's go and eat the delicious dinner.
Bye!
When you go to your room after a hot bath,
the dinner is already prepared for you.
It's really delicious.
- There's no need to explain. / - It makes you so happy.
Fukuoka is very famous for squid sashimi.
It's coming up.
Squid?
(The first dinner on their trip is kaiseki)
After enjoying a hot bath,
you have a feast.
It's coming up.
Squid?
The squid was so sweet.
- Squid is so tasty. / - It's so delicious.
(Kaiseki is usually a course meal)
(The menu changes seasonally)
Hyunjoo is won over.
Can we eat all of this?
We must.
- It's so pretty. / - It's so pretty.
- Shouldn't we take a picture? / - It's too pretty to eat.
Was it included in the accommodation costs?
- Yes, yes, yes. / - They're included.
Both breakfast and dinner.
I saw people having dinner
with 20 different dishes
after soaking in a hot spring at a ryokan on TV.
- Yeah, yeah. / - I always wanted to try that.
- 20 dishes? / - Yeah.
You're in your 40s.
Can you stop with the dad jokes?
I'll keep doing it if you laugh.
- I know. / - It looks delicious.
Shall we open them one at a time
and see what's inside?
Let's open this.
That one first?
- It's raw fish. / - It's sashimi.
It's warm.
(Ta-da!)
(It looks beautiful)
I think we get to grill this.
- I think so. / - Because we have this.
It looks delicious.
Thanks for a great meal.
It's so good.
- The salad is good too. / - It was really good.
It's so pretty.
This is increasing my appetite.
You already have a great appetite.
She has a good appetite to begin with.
It can't get any better.
How can a salad taste so good?
It's fresh.
- It's nice when actresses eat so well. / - Our skin...
It looks so good after the hot spring, right?
- Yes. / - You're right.
That's without any skin makeup
and it looks so good.
- Haeyeong. / - Yes?
Try the sashimi.
- Is it good? / - Yes.
It's delicious.
You two should talk a little.
- They aren't talking at all. / - Because it's delicious.
True.
You stop talking when it's so delicious.
Aren't I opening too wide like some anglerfish?
- No. / - I'm talking about me.
Not at all.
Isn't the abalone cooked already?
It'll get tough if it's cooked too much.
Gosh, it's abalone.
You should put some salt.
Dip it in the salt!
- Just eat it as is. / - You don't need salt.
- It tastes sweet without it. / - Eat it as is.
I think it's all cooked, isn't it?
All I see is abalone and nothing else.
I just want to have it now.
It's so plump.
It smells roasted.
Shouldn't I dip it in sauce?
Try it as it is first.
Goodness.
I couldn't chew it because it was so firm.
I want some.
The abalone aroma.
The texture is so chewy.
It's so firm.
I'm happy.
We need to grill this.
We need to eat it on that plate.
(The top 3 kaiseki menu, wagyu)
Oh, butter.
It must melt in your mouth.
Right, Jungah?
Put some vegetables.
The smell...
Oh, dear.
It's all done.
- It looks good. / - It looks amazing.
I love that.
- Having a personal grill... / - Exactly.
- And grilling what you want to eat. / - Yes.
Just for you.
- It's so neat. / - It's cute.
That's the Japanese style.
That's right.
Let's eat the meat.
I think we should dip it in this sauce.
Right here.
We can dip it in whatever we want.
I guess you can put some
bread crumbs over it.
It's salty!
Jungah, it's not bread crumbs.
Goodness.
Why would there be bread crumbs?
This is all real.
My goodness.
Haeyeong thought that was bread crumbs.
She dipped so much in it.
I thought the grains were too big to be salt.
I don't believe you.
I can still taste...
The salt chunks.
You drive me nuts.
I thought it was something unique.
It's super salty. Try it.
Does it melt in your mouth?
Hey,
is this meat?
It's amazing.
It's so good.
I'll try dipping it in something else.
You don't even need to chew it.
- It's so tender, isn't it? / - Yes.
- Hey. / - Yes?
Is that squid
for display?
- That squid sashimi was so good. / - It's really...
- Chewy, isn't it? / - Yes.
- Chewy. / - Yes, chewy.
- It looks good. / - Look at it. It's alive.
Look at its heart beating. Right?
I feel bad for eating it.
Why?
Because its eyes are open.
It's delicious.
- It looks delicious. / - It was.
Add a little wasabi.
Wasabi?
(Don't you think there's too much green on there?)
Oh, the burn.
I put too much wasabi.
Haeyeong, you're driving me crazy.
It's like you're shooting "2 Days and 1 Night."
It's like I'm playing game of chance.
Game of chance.
It's chewier than the abalone.
The squid here is so delicious.
It's sweet.
The squid was so sweet.
I'm going there next week.
- Really? / - So jealous.
- Try the squid. / - It's close.
- He can go any time. / - I'll have that squid.
Goodness.
It's so sweet.
My goodness.
The abalone was good
but the squid is much better.
It's sweet.
- Isn't it? / - Yeah.
It melts in your mouth.
It's so good!
I'm happy that you're happy.
That one, that one!
They fry the leftover squid.
- You dip that in salt, right? / - Yes.
That must be salt too.
Salt?
It's curry salt.
Oh, curry salt.
Dip it in that.
I think I should be careful.
I don't want to dip it in something weird.
I'll try it.
- I'll... / - Salt.
I'll taste it first for you.
It's salt.
It's curry salt.
It's salt again.
- After that, Haeyeong... / - What's with Haeyeong?
She became paranoid about salt.
- Did you put too much again? / - Yeah.
I told you to be careful.
I thought it was curry.
It was delicious though.
You dip a tempura in salt when it's hot.
- Like that. / - That's right.
It's so good.
It's seasoned inside.
Right? This is seasoned, right?
The coat is seasoned.
- It's delicious fried. / - If it's good raw...
It's going to be good fried.
- Gosh. / - There it is.
That...
No way.
You have to drink beer with fried squid.
Like drinking water...
That should've been served before the fried squid.
- It was so good. / - That must've been so good.
That makes you refreshed, even to your stomach.
Does it quench your thirst?
- We were in a hot spring earlier. / - Exactly.
- We've been thirsty. / - I really wanted a cold beer.
Drinking beer after taking a hot bath and sweating...
It was so great.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
I keep eating when I'm full.
I can't stop eating.
It was good, right?
We know that it's nice but we're still jealous to see it.
That's right.
I've never been to Fukuoka.
It was also my first time.
But people recommended it to me a lot.
It's nice to know where
I should go and what I should eat.
Hyunjoo, are you crying?
Your eyes are teary.
I was so confident.
But after watching their video...
No, no. Not so for me.
To go with family...
Nha Trang is better.
Let's see the second-half of Fukuoka.
Everyone, let's go to Fukuoka.
(A secret hot spring trip)
It's a different feel here.
It's so pretty.
There are more than 28 hot springs here.
This is awesome.
Hot springs are so nice.
We'll have beautiful skin.
I think we were in the hot spring for too long.
Aren't you hungry?
- Looks so good. / - Yakiniku.
I've never tasted this before.
We really did a full tour of Fukuoka.
Yeah.
Fuku, Fuku.
(Fukuoka hot spring trip)
(A secret nutritional route)
(Kurokawa Hot Spring Village, yakiniku, food cart)
(The morning comes as usual)
Everything looks so peaceful.
Are we going to a hot spring first?
We have to head to Kurokawa by bus.
Okay. Let's go.
(2.5 hours by bus to Kurokawa Hot Spring Village)
You can use that pass to go to Kurokawa, right?
Yes, the SUNQ pass.
You can go everywhere.
- For 3 days. / - That's nice.
(The roadside trees are starting to change color)
(This place looks like a landscape painting)
(Kurokawa Hot Spring Village)
- Kurokawa means, "Black River." / - That's right.
(This small village has a very relaxing atmosphere)
That was a long journey, wasn't it?
Yes, it was hard to come here. Where are we?
- Kurokawa? / - Since they're actresses...
It feels like a drama.
You're right.
We came here from Karatsu...
You go to Karatsu now.
(Turning his back)
- This won't do. / - She only makes dad jokes.
It's really not funny when I see it here.
You go to Karatsu now.
(She's at it again)
Kurokawa.
Haeyeong, this place...
- Has a different feel to the other place. / - Totally.
- This place is like... / - It feels like...
Seoraksan in Korea.
Right? This is a secret course.
It will be hard for Korean tourists to find this place.
The location was too secretive.
They'll start going now.
I'd better hurry.
Following Yufuin and Beppu,
Kurokawa is the next famous place.
A lot of Koreans who found this place
are starting to come here a lot.
This place is still fairly unknown, isn't it?
It's starting to get famous.
We have to buy a secret
that will allow us to be here.
- Is it this thing? / - The medal.
- Here too? / - Medal.
This place is a hot springs village.
There are more than 28 hot springs here.
We can go to about three of them
with this medal.
Normally, to go to one hot spring,
it costs 500 to 700 yen.
So three would cost at least 1,500 yen.
That's why you were up last night. You were studying.
Come here. Let's ask the information desk.
Let's go.
I'm saying it's cheaper this way.
Hello.
- The medal? / - The medal.
One medal please.
- It looks like a medal. / - It does.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
That seems fun. You will take it with you everywhere.
Yes. They give you a stamp
when you use the hot springs.
There are ryokans here.
It's possible to lodge here.
It's pretty.
That's so nice.
The entire neighborhood is a hot spring village.
- What is that? / - Isn't it so pretty?
- It'd be so nice when it snows in winter. / - Yes.
It's nice for all four season.
What is that place?
The sound of the flowing water is so nice.
- I know. / - All diseases would be healed here.
Jungah, it smells lovely.
The smell of the forest is so nice.
My goodness. This fragrance.
It's a fragrance.
I liked Karatsu yesterday
but I like this place much better.
This hot spring village is so nice and beautiful.
The village itself is really pretty.
It was really pretty. Hot spring villages are great.
Check out the foliage.
It's pretty.
I didn't know that there was a place like this.
- I can't help but compare it with yesterday. / - I know.
It's so charming and cute. It feels like a dwarf village.
That's a good way to put it.
It's a dwarf village. There's quite a bit of tourists.
I know.
I can't believe how cute and
pretty the stores are here.
Aren't they so pretty?
Japan has a lot of cute things like these.
Look. What is this?
What kind of place is this?
Haeyeong.
Haeyeong, this must be...
A foot bath.
This is nice.
Can you use that for free?
- If you pay $1. / - That's cheap.
Check out the sound of the river.
It's so nice.
All my stress is being relieved.
I hope the swelling in your legs goes down.
Relieving our legs as soon as we arrive,
then hitting the hot springs.
We have to go to several places.
Let's go out now.
That was a good foot bath.
I feel hot after that.
- I'm hot. / - We're recharged now.
If you book the accommodation there...
- You can sleep and eat there. / - Yes.
If you book here
and don't go to Karatsu...
- You'll save 2 hours. / - That's good too.
- This must be the place. / - Is this the place?
- This must be... / - This must be a temple.
Look here. They tied up something here.
People hung their wishes here.
That's right.
Oh, my.
- There are a lot hung here. / - That's right.
Okay.
You can put in as much money as you want?
Yes.
Try it.
I hope it has something good written on it.
I picked one.
- You did? / - Yeah.
- Should I read it? / - Yes.
Goodness.
- Goodness. / - Don't worry.
I tore it too before.
It'll only have good words.
There's something written here.
Great...
Great luck!
What does it say here?
It's the best one there is.
Why?
Is it really the best one?
Great luck was the best one.
They have small luck, good luck and great luck.
Great luck was the best.
Sure this is great luck?
You have hope with relationships.
And you'll get as much work as the effort you put in.
You'd better work hard.
Really?
Thank you.
There's no luck. You just have to work hard.
Don't ask for luck...
In life.
I'm saying my life is like that.
Right.
You pick too since I picked one.
I'll pay $1.
Pick a good one.
I don't think it will be good.
What are you talking about?
If one person is lucky, the other person usually isn't.
It's fun that way.
I'll hold this so open it.
What if hers is very great luck?
The ones with great luck are all the same.
Is this really great luck?
(It is great luck)
They say it's hard to pick great luck.
- It's easy to get great luck. / - Yeah, this one!
What's this?
(Narae and Gukju's Hokkaido trip)
Great luck!
- It's all great luck. / - They all got it.
Great luck has been common.
I got great luck.
I got great, great, great luck.
My goodness. There's such a thing?
What is this?
Let's go.
Why did they hang these?
Those must be unlucky results.
They hang them back up?
Aren't they all good?
Right?
- No, he said it's rare. / - How did we get so lucky?
Honestly, I feel like we're very lucky
to be on this trip.
Let's be thankful for the small things.
Oh, my!
She tore it while trying to tie it on.
Oh, my God.
Why?
I tore it because of that bug.
What do I do?
- Darn it. / - It's okay, tie it up again.
Nice, Haeyeong. Using spit as glue.
This is just for fun.
I don't believe this.
All done.
Good job.
You did a really good job.
Ours. This is yours, this is mine.
This is my one.
These are the little things that make it fun.
It's really quiet.
All of the alleys are really cute.
Wow.
Check out the bakery.
This must be the bread that the others were eating.
Hello, this must be famous.
- Were they Korean? / - Yes.
This must be what we've been hearing about.
Let's try it.
- Looks delicious. / - The smell...
It's custard bread.
It's a famous custard bread.
- Looks so good. / - They sell those in Korea now...
Don't they?
Give me one.
Thank you.
Let's go.
- We bought it. / - Let's eat it over there.
Sit over there?
Where we can hear the water.
What is this?
What is that thing?
Isn't that a hot spring?
I think you steam your face here.
What? Is there steam?
- It's steaming. / - Let me see.
Wait. Put this down first. You'll spill it.
- It smells like sulfur. / - It smells like sulfur...
I think it's a place where you steam your face.
I guess so.
It smells a little.
This is called a kaoyu.
It's also very good for your eyes.
Since it's a sulfur hot spring...
- This is nice. / - Wait a minute.
It's so cute and small.
There's a table for us too.
Here, Haeyeong.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
I was hungry.
Is it good?
There's custard inside.
Look at this.
Wow.
- It's good. / - It looks good.
(With plenty of custard)
- Isn't it good? / - Yes.
The custard is moist and cool.
And it's really savory.
The custard isn't really sweet.
It was savory.
In Korea, custard bread is soft
on the inside and outside.
- That's right. / - But this was crispy on the outside.
This is really crispy and savory.
It's really good.
Please show us a proper reaction.
These people become silent when they eat.
All they do is eat.
You have to eat it right away after buying it.
- It will get soggy if you don't. / - You're right.
- You have to eat bread right after it's made. / - Yeah.
We're starting to enter the hot spring village.
This is the first hot spring.
Jungah.
We're finally at a hot spring.
It's so pretty.
It's here.
We'll start from here.
I'm so pretty.
The entrance is so pretty.
- It's like entering a fairy's house. / - You're right.
We came at the perfect season.
I know.
Won't it be hard to visit all 3 hot springs in a day?
We thought it would be hard too,
but people stay in a spring for only 10 to 15 minutes.
Because there are so many to experience.
Hello.
Ryokan.
(They finally receive their first stamp)
We're going to receive the stamps like this.
Look, we're going to start from here.
Let's go in.
Can you pay more to get into
more than three hot springs?
That's right. You can buy another medal.
It's cheaper if you buy three
instead of one.
- It's not right at the entrance. / - It's a little secluded.
That's right. I heard that Japanese celebrities
have secret love affairs here.
Really?
Famous celebrities come here...
- To use the hot springs. / - Is it their secret location?
It's their secret location. This place is a little bit...
- More secluded from the entire village. / - Right.
- They come here in secret. / - It's very private.
Very private.
It's a really famous hot spring.
You can enjoy it while standing.
I was shocked.
I almost got on it thinking that it was a swing.
(There is something special here in this hot spring)
(A hot spring where you enjoy while standing)
(There are only two of them in Kurokawa)
(This one is the deepest one)
It's deep.
You need to hold this.
Oh, it's hot!
It's not hot if you come in completely.
We're shooting right now,
but do you have to wear a bathing suit?
- Or go in naked? / - You're supposed to be naked.
- Is it a mixed bath? / - No, it isn't.
It's so deep.
This must be a handle.
I thought it was a swing.
I was going to try it.
What if this breaks?
- This is so fun. / - It seems nice.
I feel less tired standing
than sitting in a tub.
I'm less dizzy.
It feels good hanging from here.
You feel less tired when you're standing there.
I like saunas, so I am loving this.
My skin feels so nice right now.
This place is bigger than other hot springs.
Isn't that right?
This is a standing hot spring.
Sitting ones are over there.
- Should we go? / - Why you little...
Yun Haeyeong, please don't do that.
Yeah, I'm like that. But it's really not funny.
(There's another hot spring next to the standing one)
We're like fairies.
- You're right. Let's sit here. / - Fairies.
(Blurp)
What was that sound?
This sound isn't coming from my mouth.
It's the sound of the wind being split.
There is even a cave.
It's over there.
Haeyeong, go take a look.
Wait a minute.
What is that place?
- Oh, my. / - How is it?
(She discovers the cave)
- Is it a cave? / - Yes, it is a cave.
People must have secret affairs here.
Haeyeong, come back alive.
Okay, don't worry.
Look at this cave.
(Ahhh)
(Huh?)
(Green mountain)
(What's she doing now?)
(She ends her cave exploration after a song)
Hot springs are the best while sitting.
It's more stable than standing.
The first hot spring is
good for sore muscles and problematic body parts.
This place is good for the skin.
The water is really good for your skin aesthetically.
This is nice.
The color of the water is kind of black.
It's also murky.
True.
It's unique that it's murky.
You can see the out through the bamboo trees.
It's an open-air bath.
- This will be best in the winter. / - That's right.
This is our first hot spring, and it's so nice.
- I know. / - What will the others be like?
I'm really looking forward to it.
- It would be nice in the winter. / - It's so nice.
I know.
You know this?
We have to use up our medal.
Should we go?
Let's move to the next location.
- We sweat out a lot already. / - Yeah.
Let's go.
That's the good thing about Japanese hot springs.
- It's in harmony with nature. / - Right.
It tires you out less and makes you feel good.
The second one is famous for aesthetic purposes.
- I feel so good. / - Me too.
I'm so excited to see what the second one is like.
This is so nice.
I feel refreshed.
What if our skins peel from all these hot springs.
You'll have beautiful skin.
- The last one. / - This is the third one.
- With a history of 150 years. / - This is nice.
This is a bamboo forest hot spring.
That place is really nice.
- Jungah. / - I feel refreshed.
- I feel refreshed again. / - It's tiring, right?
We have to show our medals.
Yes, we accomplished three hot springs.
- Ta-da. / - Ta-da.
See the stamps?
- Do they hang them there? / - Yes.
People all hung them there.
We have to clearly show that we
accomplished our mission.
There you go.
- Let's hang them next to each other. / - Okay.
Let's hang them together.
- When we visit Japan next time... / - Yeah.
We'll come back to this hot spring.
Good-bye.
Farewell.
Hot spring village.
I think I'd book my hotel in that hot spring village
and just keep visiting hot springs.
(Kurokawa Hot Spring Village to Hakata Station)
(Fukuoka downtown, 4:40 p.m.)
- I'm hungry. / - You're hungry again?
I spent too much time in the hot spring.
- From Kurokawa... / - I'm totally exhausted.
- To here took too long. / - It was too long, right?
Since it's dinner...
- Let's eat something expensive. / - Grand meal?
Shall we?
- Please do everything I ask for. / - Okay.
I want to drink beer while bathing in the hot spring.
- And udon. / - Udon.
This is udon.
- Yakiniku. / - Yakiniku.
- It looks so delicious. / - Yakiniku.
- Yakiniku. / - Yes.
- Japanese yakiniku. / - Yakiniku is really good.
- Yakiniku. / - Yakiniku.
- I want to eat yakiniku. / - It's good, right?
- Let's go, let's go. / - Yes.
- It'll be so delicious. / - It'll be delicious.
- This must be it. / - Is this it?
- It looks clean. / - Yeah.
I love it.
It'll be so good.
- Jungah. / - We're finally here.
I know.
- Let's order. / - Looks good.
Order.
Welcome... Wait, that's not right.
- It's really crowded here. / - It is.
- It's starting to get crowded. / - It's about time.
Since it's dinner time...
- They're crowding. / - We overdid it at the hot springs.
- Yeah, we did. / - Aren't you hungry?
Visiting three places is not easy.
Aren't you hungry?
I think I'll really enjoy it once the food comes out.
Ginger?
We seem to get to drink highball a lot.
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
(Gulp)
Mine tastes like juice.
Excuse me. Could you mix some soju in this?
- This need soju. / - Try some.
- It's just juice. / - Will this do?
- It's just a soda. / - You're right.
- Is it different to mine? / - It's the same.
There's not much whiskey in it.
You're right. It's a bit...
- It's tasty though. / - It's tasty but...
It's weak for us.
- This is beef tongue. / - It's beef tongue.
(Grill and meat are the best combination)
It was really good.
Hyunjoo's been won over.
(A table of yakiniku will fill their empty stomachs)
(The special cut is beef tongue)
It was really delicious.
The color is amazing.
- Let's grill it. / - Right away.
Jungah, you should try a piece.
- Shall I? / - Yes.
Take a piece of meat.
I didn't know you eat this.
I don't think I've ever had tongue before.
- Same for me. / - Even in Korea.
- Have you had it before? / - I don't think so.
- This is a cow's tongue. / -  I know.
Then...
Is this how big a cow's tongue is?
Goodness, Jungah. Don't say it.
Just eat it.
- The tongue... / - What's wrong with you?
Doesn't this mean its tongue is this big?
It's burning.
It sucks in all the smoke.
It looks delicious.
- Looks so delicious! / - Gosh.
- Shall we begin? / - Try it. See if it's good.
- Haeyeong, with this... / - Squeeze the lemon?
Squeeze it here.
You dip the tongue in the lemon.
This is sauce for the meat and this is for the tongue.
- That looks so good. / - Looks so good.
(How does their first tongue meat taste?)
That's a genuine expression.
It's tongue meat.
Does it melt in your mouth?
It looks tasty.
Just watching you eating it makes me...
I've never experienced it before.
- Really? / - I've never tasted such flavor before.
- Try it. / - Is it a new world?
It kind of...
Tastes of liver.
- It tastes similar to beef heart. / - Beef heart.
Right? It's good.
- My saliva's just... / - It's good.
- It's not gamey at all. / - Not at all.
It tastes much better in the lemon juice.
It's really tasty.
- Let's grill the next one. / - Grill one of these?
This is beef loin.
And this meat is lightly marinated, right?
Like with soy sauce.
- It's nice and sweet. / - I know.
I like that we can cook our own meat.
Right?
If someone takes a piece of meat that I cooked,
it upsets you.
I know.
What if someone takes my meat?
- Exactly. It'll cause fighting. / - It's annoying.
I'm going to eat mine.
It smells delicious.
Jungah, you look like you're truly enjoying it.
- It's not salty at all. / - Is it good?
Let me try it.
- It's good, isn't it? / - Yes.
- It just melts, right? / - It melts.
The meat is really tender.
- It's good, right? / - Yeah.
- This is... / - The ribs?
- Yes. / - I see.
Boneless rib meat.
They cut the meat thick here.
So the meat is really juicy.
It holds in the beef juices. That's why it's good.
- This time, Haeyeong. / - Yes?
I'll try it with wasabi.
That's so...
How is it? Good?
(This is the third time she's been moved by the meat)
It just melts.
Wow, the burn from the wasabi...
(Burning sensation)
I was thinking you put too much wasabi on it.
- You're so... / - I'm crying because it's so good.
What's with you, Haeyeong?
It was still good.
I knew you put too much.
Oh, this...
This is Japanese cold noodles.
- I've never had this before. / - Me neither.
Why does Japanese noodles have kimchi?
You're right. The noodles are unique.
Japanese cold noodles are eaten with kimchi on top.
How do the noodle taste?
- Is it good? / - It's like radish water kimchi.
Really? They look like chewy noodles.
- You need to eat it with the eat. / - Looks so good.
- Is it good? / - Yes.
Japanese cold noodles taste good too.
- It tastes so good together. / - Really?
- Meat and cold noodles go well together. / - Exactly.
You be the meat, I'll be the noodles.
Since we go well together.
Yeah, do whatever you want.
Shall we eat another piece of meat?
Yes. I'll eat cold noodles.
- After we eat this... / - Yes?
We should go for a last drink.
As our second stop?
It's too much of a waste to not enjoy the night.
(15 minutes to Nagahama food cart)
(The darkness falls and it starts to drizzle)
The food cart.
You're right. It's called "yatai" in Japanese.
(The night makes them crave fish cake broth)
But food cart is expensive.
Since it's tourist-oriented.
- But our one wasn't. / - If you find the right place...
- We found a cheaper one. / - Good, good.
- It's not one of those places. / - Very good.
This must be where we have our finale.
I know.
This place is... Food carts are called...
- "Yatai" in Japanese. / - Yatai?
Yatai.
A lot of Koreans and tourists
go to Nakasu for food carts.
- But we're going to Nagahama. / - Nagahama.
It's like, let's grab a drink.
- Drink up? / - Yeah.
How old are they that they keep making dad jokes?
- They are at the age of old men. / - Yes.
Nagahama is a food cart village.
This is the original.
This is the original place.
Hey, this place is empty. Let's go here.
Yes, it's empty because we booked it for the show.
- Come on in. / - Let's go in.
- Welcome. / - Hello.
Hello.
Sikyung, you go there often, don't you?
I'd love to.
- It was really nice. / - There are lots of foreigners.
- Haeyeong. / - I know.
It's supposed to be famous only among the locals.
Thank you.
That draft beer looks so good.
The locals bring them here.
You're right. It's even unknown among locals.
Exactly. This is our secret course.
By the way, we haven't eaten any ramen in Japan.
- We had no time to have ramen. / - You should eat it.
- They sell ramen there? / - Yes.
It's called hakata ramen.
- It's made with pork broth, right? / - Yes.
It's tonkotsu ramen.
I heard this place is where
the tonkotsu ramen was invented.
Not only this food cart
but also all those shops there
all sell tonkotsu ramen.
Let's order ramen
since it's famous.
We're in Japan. We should try ramen.
- It's made with pork broth, right? / - Yes.
It's tonkotsu ramen.
(When the noodles are cooked)
(They drain and put into the broth)
(Lastly, meat and spring onions are added on top)
(Goodness)
It's ready.
This must be minced garlic.
I heard it tastes much better with it.
I'm sure it helps with the gamey taste.
Should I add the spice?
Add some.
That's enough.
It's not enough. This is nothing.
If Jungah and Jungsoo travel together,
it'll be exhausting.
- Why? / - There will be a lot of conflicts.
I think you two should go on a trip together.
- I like it spicy. / - We'll have a fight.
Let me try.
It tastes much richer now.
- It's delicious. / - Yeah.
It's delicious.
It tastes like thick beef bone broth.
It's savory, isn't it?
It does.
We just had dinner but this
late night food is so tasty.
This is the most food I've eaten recently.
- You're eating this after having yakiniku? / - Yes.
We're spending our last night in Fukuoka...
- At a food cart. / - I never imagined this.
Jungah, how did you like our trip?
Did you have fun?
For me... Honestly...
When I imagined our trip to Japan...
I just thought we'd go to hot springs...
And eat delicious foods. I thought it'd be a normal trip.
I really loved the Kurokawa.
I think it's a perfect place to go
with your friends or mother.
- Kurokawa was beautiful. / - Right.
The scenery was so nice.
And going to each of the hot springs...
- Experiencing hot springs. / - A real hot spring.
And also eating custard bread on the street.
That was so fun.
Even after I go back to Korea, I won't forget this trip.
Me too.
Whenever I go to a sauna, I'll think of Kurokawa.
It was so nice.
What was the most impressive thing during this trip?
For me...
I just liked how I escaped my daily life...
With a great friend,
and staying at nice places.
I wondered if I had been to Fukuoka before.
It's like I felt the true charm of Fukuoka
through this trip.
We did a proper tour of Fukuoka on this trip.
(The last night of the trip makes her tear up)
Are you crying?
Sometimes you just tear up.
- I can understand her. / - Why did you cry?
It was just so nice.
- Sometimes you cry tears of joy. / - I got teary too.
- Did you? / - Yes.
It's so...
Are you crying?
I told you not to cry.
- It's just so nice. / - It is, right?
- I'm crying because of the smoke. / - Let's toast.
I can understand that. Being in a nice place...
- With a nice person... / - That's right.
- You can cry. / - You can cry over beer.
- Haeyeong, thank you. / - I thank you.
Love shot.
(It was a great trip no matter what)
So good.
It's delicious.
- That mood. / - It was so nice.
(Their hot Fukuoka trip is over)
Very nice.
To be honest,
both of your trips to hot springs
we so great.
- They were so good. / - So good.
There's nothing bad to say.
- That's exactly I wanted to say. / - They're similar.
They're both good and both a little different.
- Nha Trang is great for energetic kids. / - The vibe.
Like in grade school. It's great for family.
It's great to go with elementary school kids.
And their one was good with friends, lovers.
Good to go with them.
- It was more for adults. / - That's right.
- Also... / - For trendy adults.
Above all, it just felt like a short trip
to Haeundae or Jeju-do.
- But it felt like so much more. / - It's not tiring.
- We spent so much time at hot springs. / - Thank you.
Our teams have traded places.
Jungah was won over by Nha Trang last week.
That's right.
And Hyunjoo was won over by Fukuoka.
I was so jealous.
They're so jealous of each other's trips.
You've fallen for Fukuoka, right?
Yes, I really have.
Next time, Guide Yun and Guide Kong go together.
- Swap teams. / - No, no.
Jungsoo and Jungah will clash.
- Clash? / - You clash.
- They're the same. / - When fire meets fire...
You get trouble.
- That's what I want to see. / - No, no.
You won't get any footage for TV.
- We might end up fighting. / - We'll burn up.
- We'll burn up. / - They're actually soft-hearted.
We have to find out how much the Fukuoka trip cost.
This is the most important.
Our Kong Tour was, per person...
- $225.90. / - $225.90.
- How much for Fukuoka? / - How much?
Jungah, how much was it?
$302.00
For 2 days?
- More than you think... / - It was just overnight.
- It was only overnight for us. / - Ours was 3 days.
Actually, we were worried
that their trip was too cheap.
But our trip... It's not that different.
- Plus cost of living is high in Japan. / - It is.
You must prepare the SUNQ pass.
- Yes. / - That's right.
The SUNQ pass is a must.
With it, you don't have to worry about
the transportation cost.
For our hot spring tour special, we went to
Nha Trang, Vietnam and Fukuoka, Japan.
- This week... / - Let's switch it up.
Should we do a national vote?
On the official Battle Trip social media page...
The trips to Nha Trang and Fukuoka will be posted.
The team that gets the most likes
will win.
- We'll only find out later then? / - That's right.
- Later. / - I'm curious.
Even after hearing this Jungsoo
knows she'll win.
- Of course we'll win. / - Just as it is.
Just from what you saw.
Just from what you felt.
Just vote that way.
Our trip was great to go on with a friend.
You can go there without any burden.
Fukuoka was a great place for that.
Thank you.
The two week long hot spring tour is now over.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
We'll be back next week
with better travel tips.
Thank you.
(Next week)
- First time in Australia, right? / - We're here.
(We've worked hard at Battle Trip to prepare this)
It feels refreshing.
Vietnamese local flavors.
(Travel is all about food trends)
(Battle Trip)
("I Want Love" by Kassy)