Xin chao, Hanoi!
The Yeom Tour is no ordinary tour.
With Yeom Tour, there's just us.
A place you must visit before you die
but it's still not very well known.
It's Ha Long Bay on land.
Unbelievable!
It was really good.
It's Vietnamese style sausage stew.
It's so good.
It's just too good.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Choi Eunkyeong, Ahn Sunyeong)
(Lee Jihye, Boom)
Travel is war!
Battle Trip!
Following on from last week...
We're joined by our travelers who went on a tour
planned by locals.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
(100 judges in the audience)
We had Eric Nam
as our special host last week.
He was almost lost for words.
He kept saying he wanted to go.
- Right. / - That's what he kept saying.
I wanted to try all the dishes you were eating
and visit there.
I think I'll be visiting Hanoi very soon.
- Yeom Tour. / - Yeom Tour.
Eric, if you join us as a trip designer,
where would you go? Except Hanoi.
If I were a trip designer?
I'd go to a place I've never been.
Where?
I think somewhere in Africa would be fun.
I think it'd be tough but fun.
He's been to Africa.
He has.
- Where? / - I visited Ghana.
Ghana?
- With Sam. / - Sam Okyere.
Yes, I visited Ghana.
But the people there are all so energetic.
- They're just exploding with energy. / - Right.
Eric would feel dizzy there.
They dance non-stop.
- It's worse than here? / - They dance non-stop.
They do greetings like this.
Like this.
I'm telling you.
- I mean it. / - Too much exaggeration.
- Are you serious? / - No way.
Sam boasted about it.
They don't need to go clubbing.
Wherever you go, they're laughing and dancing.
It's just an African thing.
How do they greet you?
Like this.
They're the best. The most energetic.
We're looking at tours that were planned by locals.
There are hidden local restaurants
and hidden tourist attractions.
When I go on a trip,
I eat 7 meals a day.
7?
As soon as I get off at the Incheon Airport,
I go to a good sashimi restaurant nearby.
- Knife-cut noodles. / - I have that first.
I cross the river to Paju
for some good bean paste stew.
- That sounds good. / - I eat a meal there.
Then I go to a cockle restaurant in Ilsan.
Then go for some tea in Hongdae.
Then Mapo for soy sauce marinated crab
and fritters.
Then once you cross over Samgakji...
- They have that good codfish soup. / - Stop, stop.
There's a lot to introduce to foreigners in Korea
because they love our rice wine.
And strangely, they really enjoy the fish market.
It's fascinating.
- That's true. / - They love small octopus.
And they really like the fact you can eat fresh sashimi.
- They find that interesting. / - They do.
Just as we announced,
today, it's a Filipino top star.
A trip planned by Ryan Bang.
We'll be heading off to Boracay in the Philippines.
I can't wait.
Boracay is such a famous tourist destination.
It's a popular honeymoon spot.
It's a popular destination worldwide.
It's almost too popular in that it's been abused.
I'm sure you've read the articles.
They're planning to shut the island down
temporarily for environmental cleanup.
So if you're planning to go there,
you need to check before you go.
When it comes to environmental issues,
it's not just Boracay.
- It's a global issue. / - It is.
We'll have to be careful to keep
the environment clean and come back.
We'll start the Boracay trip.
How satisfied were you with Ryan Bang?
In Yeom Tour, Yeom Gyeonghwan was
like the CEO of a travel agency.
Ryan Bang is like the deputy section chief.
He's like the head of the department.
- Yes, he's full of energy. / - That's great.
It will feel really different.
- He'll try his best to show you more. / - Guide...
He doesn't rest.
I have also been to Boracay.
- A lot of people have been there. / - Really?
- Boracay is... / - People might be disappointed...
- If you go on a basic tour. / - That's right.
Is there anything special?
It really isn't obvious.
We've been to hidden attractions.
It's amazing.
- Even the name is charming. / - What is it?
This is Blue Lagoon.
It's called This is Blue Lagoon?
No.
It's Boracay's Blue Lagoon.
- It's Blue Lagoon. / - You got it wrong.
Boracay's Blue Lagoon.
- This is Malumpati. / - That's right.
You'll like that place too.
- It sounds like "party." / - Right.
It's a party in itself.
It's the wrong spelling though.
- The spelling's different. / - Yours is "pati."
The spelling doesn't matter when we travel.
You said that language was important.
This is Malumpati.
Pati, pati.
Not "party," it's pati.
- I'm looking forward to it. / - I was surprised...
After looking at the water.
The water was so blue...
It was like, this is emerald.
This is emerald.
- Emerald. / - They really were.
- She got it from Boom. / - This is emerald.
It was so beautiful.
This is the harmful effect of Korea's English education.
- What's wrong? / - Wait a minute.
We experienced both the sky and sea of Boracay.
Valuable attractions that you didn't know about
will continue to come out.
Why would people keep talking about Boracay?
It's 1 of the 3 best beaches in the world.
- One of the best 3 in the world? / - Top 3.
There are three 3 beaches in the world.
Gold Coast, Australia.
- Yes, Gold Coast. / - And...
- In Miami, U.S.A. / - Palm Beach.
That's right.
Then there's Boracay.
- White Beach. / - White Beach in Boracay.
That's right.
The sunset is also amazing.
It's so pretty.
Is it one of the best 3 sunsets in the world?
It is.
Actually, it isn't.
- It isn't? / - It's not one of the top 3 sunsets.
We never discussed this beforehand.
They're a bit strange.
Where are the top 3 sunsets?
Where?
Kota Kinabalu in Malaysia,
- And... / - It's really pretty there.
- Santorini. / - Santorini in Greece,
That's right, Santorini.
And then...
- Bali. / - Bali!
- Boracay isn't one of them? / - It's Bali.
Boracay isn't one of them?
- Why are they talking about it then? / - No.
- It's not even top 3. / - It might not be top 3...
But the sunset is as beautiful as rare jewels.
That's how we actually got the Korean term
for "jewels."
- From Boracay's sunset to jewels... / - Jewels...
So the locals say,
Hey, let's go watch the jewel.
The locals there refer to the sunset in Korean?
They know the word?
- Korean has been globalized... / - Excuse me.
- So did you see the jewel? / - Anyway...
- We did. / - To be honest...
Yes, we saw it.
The sunset we saw...
- Was the best in the world. / - You'll be shocked.
It was that beautiful.
Please pay attention to that.
Let's start the Boracay trip.
The food and trip itself was good in Hanoi...
- But the costs... / - Great affordability.
How about Boracay?
Boracay is a city that makes money from tourism.
So you can't compare with Hanoi.
- It must be expensive. / - The cost is quite expensive.
- It's a tourist spot. / - You need to spend at times.
That's right. You're going there to spend money,
why try to save?
It's expensive compared to other Filipino islands?
- We worked so hard to earn money. / - Of course.
We're going to have an amazing tour.
You need to spend to have fun.
It's an expensive place.
It's going to be hard for us today.
It's expensive.
- How's the exchange rate? / - It's a little too much.
The exchange rate changes every day.
- What? / - Yes, it changes every day.
- That's right. / - Is it?
It changes by the hour.
Is there no standard?
To set a standard...
Take the Filipino peso and calculate to Korean won...
This is the easiest way.
Just multiply the given price by 20.
Then you will get the Korean price.
Hanoi took a zero out.
- They removed a zero. / - Multiply by 20.
- It's the complete opposite. / - Yes.
For example, if it's 1,500 peso,
multiply by 20.
- It's $30. / - It's $30.
You get $30.
That's how you calculate it.
- I see. / - Anyway, when it comes to Boracay...
It is so beautiful.
I have a quiz for you now.
- Try to get it right. / - Quiz?
In Boracay, there are 5 "S."
5 "S."
"S." Guess what they are.
- Picturesque 5 "S." / - Sky.
Sea.
Sky?
Correct. Sea, correct.
- Sky is correct. / - Steak, sausage...
- Smoothie. / - Wrong.
What?
- It's not food. / - Food is important.
- It's important. / - Excuse me.
Don't you know how important steak is?
- What could it be? / - Sand.
- Sand? / - Sand?
Sun.
Sun?
- Sun... / - Sun...
Stamina?
Sunset, sunset.
- Sikyung? / - Sunset.
- Sunset. / - Sunset.
Correct.
Do we have all the answers?
I'll give you a hint.
Beer.
- Oh, San Miguel! / - Correct!
- San Miguel. / - Beer?
There's one left.
You didn't mention star.
- Stars? / - Yes.
It'd be great to do all of that at once.
- 5... / - Sitting under the stars in the sky...
Drinking beer.
- We did that! / - With the sunset...
We did it.
- I just got goose bumps. / - We did it.
- Do you want to enjoy 5 "S?" / - Yes!
Just wait a little bit more.
Okay.
We really hope that we get to see those 5 "S."
We head off on the RaBang Tour to Boracay!
Let's go.
It's Boom.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Did you get your husband's permission?
I didn't get his permission yet.
I'll tell him once I come back.
You can't do that.
- I'll tell him later. / - I'll be in an awkward position.
It's okay. Business is just business.
Really?
How is your traveling style?
I'd describe my traveling style as...
Day fire, night fire, dawn fire.
What is that?
I'm on fire during the day, night and dawn.
When do you rest then?
- You could get tired... / - When do you rest?
I don't get enjoyment by abusing my body.
Then what about something dynamic?
- Do you like leisure sports? / - No, no, no.
I like to eat, rest,
then eat some more.
Then have a little drink.
She's like my mom.
- Excuse me. / - That's travel for the elderly.
That's how my mom travels.
You should take rests while doing anything.
That's like a senior's travel package.
No, no. But I like that.
But I have a lot of energy
so I can keep up.
I always take a Bluetooth operated mic with me.
I always sing when I'm excited.
I attach a mic here like a musical actor.
Right here.
- Really? / - Yes.
- It's Bluetooth operated. / - You mean it.
- Make sure you do it for me. / - Okay, okay.
A local who lives in that country...
A local?
Will plan your trip.
That's the special you will take part in.
The Philippines in Southeast Asia.
- The Philippines? / - Yes.
Who lives in the Philippines?
If it's the Philippines, isn't it Sandara Park?
You don't pronounce her name like that.
It's Sandara.
That doesn't sound right.
No, I mean it.
- Are you sure? / - Sandara.
- It's Sandara. / - I think how I said it was correct.
He's the Yu Jaeseok of the Philippines.
Yu Jaeseok of the Philippines.
He hosts shows.
- Really? / - He's so good at Tagalog.
- He's like the local Yu Jaeseok. / - He's Korean?
Yes, he's Korean.
He's funny.
He's my junior.
No, you're a singer.
No, I'm a TV personality.
- Ida Daussy is my senior. / - Right.
We are TV personalities.
- Robert Holley is also my senior. / - Robert Holley.
- That's funny. / - So...
- He's my junior. / - You're so funny.
Hello.
I've been working in the Philippines since 2010
to the present.
My name is Ryan Bang.
I came to the Philippines when I was in 7th grade
due to my parents.
I came here as an overseas student.
Then in 2010,
I starred in "Pinoy Big Brother," the audition program,
and came 2nd.
I started working in television since then.
That's right. He came 2nd in an audition program.
- Here we go. / - He's extremely popular.
- He's unbelievably popular. / - Which one is he?
- On the far left. / - Really?
He's loved by the middle aged women
in the Philippines like a son.
- The national son of the Philippines is here. / - Hey!
That's right. He was on the Dara Tour.
- He's a celebrity. / - Hello.
- He really is a national celebrity. / - Hello.
Yeah, Ryan Bang.
Are you at a restaurant?
- I'm on a drama set. / - Our first meeting.
- A drama? / - Drama?
Do you also act?
I'm on a daily drama.
He's so busy.
I've been to Boracay many times
so I know it well.
Boracay has the most beautiful sunset in the Philippines.
The sunset.
- It was amazing. / - I ask with caution.
Is there a party we can enjoy during the sunset?
Boracay is the most popular in the Philippines
among Boracay, Cebu and Palawan.
That's because there are clubs three steps away
from the beach in Boracay.
Here we go.
When you walk on the beach, it's all clubs.
- Really? / - Like outdoor clubs.
By the way...
Do you have a car?
- Car? / - Car?
Will you drive us around?
Motorcycles in Boracay are
convenient like taxis.
Motorcycles are dangerous.
Have you ever thought about buying a car?
Boom wanted to travel conveniently.
- Something like that. / - Like in a van.
I still have a year left on the car I bought in Manila.
I took out a loan for that.
I can't buy another car in Boracay.
Please visit.
I'll relieve all of your stress in Boracay.
He's so kind
when he must be so busy, isn't he?
I think it's going to be so fun.
Let's meet soon.
Yes, come here quickly.
I'll wait for you in Boracay.
- Bye. / - He's so trustworthy.
He's trustworthy.
He's very meticulous.
It would be great if you had a friend like him there.
- Of course. / - Boracay is good.
Someone as enthusiastic as him.
Look at the sea.
It's so pretty.
Look at the color. Look at the sky.
(One of the top 3 beaches in the world)
I'll use the knowledge and skills
I have gathered from my trips to Boracay.
Boracay is fairly well-known to Korean tourists.
I've prepared a lot of unique activities
that not many tourists know of.
I can trust Ryan.
Gyeonghwan's only lived in Vietnam for 2 years.
- Ryan's been there for 13. / - No need for words.
- The thing is... / - That's true.
We know that it's at least 5 times better in person.
- That's right. / - I've prepared...
Places Koreans don't know of.
I love that.
I'll give you a tip.
Tip?
- How much? / - How much?
Hey...
Why do you keep saying my lines.
We kept saying the same thing.
Koreans come here and only spend time on the island.
But we'll take a boat out.
Outside of the island.
We head out.
Check it out!
Isn't this amazing?
This place is the best.
It's the cleanest area.
I'm certain I will never forget this trip.
I'll remember the nature when
I'm about to die.
And the traditions we experienced.
- What is that? / - Tradition.
- Traditional meal. / - You eat with your hands.
We could experience everything there was.
That's what I loved about the trip.
The trip begins the day before you depart.
(Their destination is Kalibo International Airport)
It's such a big city, you know.
What do you want to do the most
when you get to Boracay?
I want to go clubbing.
Clubbing?
I quit going to clubs a long time ago.
Is this Jihye's husband?
Well, your wife just said that she wants to go...
Geez.
Don't do that.
- You need his permission. / - No, no. He needs rest.
My husband needs his rest.
I'm sure he'll go clubbing too.
- How could you say that? / - He must rest too.
What's with that?
Here are your meals. Please enjoy.
I love the in-flight meals.
- It was delicious. / - Aren't the meals delicious?
I'm sure that next to the pilot
is a row of crocks for the kimchi.
Like a kimchi fridge.
This kimchi is so good.
(Korea)
(Kalibo International Airport)
(Boracay island dock)
The ocean there was breathtaking.
If you spend 3 days just watching the ocean...
What is that?
- Just sand. / - I see.
I love things like this.
My gosh, look at that.
This is great.
Which song does it remind you of?
What's the first song you thought of?
♪ How can it be so good? ♪
It's Jihye's song.
Jihye really loves herself.
I have a bit of narcissism so
I sing my songs often.
♪ Under the burning sun ♪
POSITION.
That's right!
Right.
♪ Summer time ♪
This is incredible. It's like a music video.
Come to think of it, the old school songs
all shot music videos in a place like that.
- Starting with COOL... / - Right.
- Doing this on the yacht. / - On the ocean...
Bang, Bang.
- RaBang? / - Yeah.
Our Ryan Bang.
We're supposed to meet him at the beach.
- How can we find him? It's big. / - We can't find him.
- Ryan! / - Where are you, Ryan?
Isn't that Ryan Bang?
Where is he?
We can... Hey, he's right there!
Where? Where?
Ryan.
Is that you, Ryan?
- Ryan Bang? / - Don't act like you didn't see me.
- Ryan. / - Hello.
Welcome to the Philippines.
When did you get here?
When I don't have work, I come to Boracay very often.
From Manila, Boracay is the closest island
that has beautiful beaches.
It only takes me about 30 or 40 minutes.
We are at Angol Beach now.
- Angol Beach? / - Angol Beach.
Angol Beach.
I wanted to meet you here
because Korean tourists don't know about it.
Only the locals know about it.
Yes, locals and Westerners come here.
Because in the past, Boracay
didn't have Stations 1 and 2.
20 to 30 years ago,
there was only Station 3 at Angol Beach.
30 years ago.
It was a long strip of beach.
3, 2, 1.
We like the sound of that.
3, 2.
(Surprised)
He's cute.
He doesn't know this song.
- Let's check out 3 and 2 first. / - He doesn't know.
Only his hair is old-fashioned. He doesn't know.
He has the SOLID hairstyle.
- SOLID hairstyle. / - Lee Jun.
- Lee Jun's hair. / - He uses a tub of gel.
Boracay is the best from December to May.
- Why? The weather? / - The peak season.
- I see. / - The weather's great and so is the air.
Prices go up a little but...
Prices go up?
- Just a bit. / - But that's normal during peak season.
Aren't you hungry?
We'll walk toward Station 2 as we feel the ocean.
Boracay is very famous for
it's steaks.
We should cut up some steak since we're here.
- So this is connected to Station 1? / - Yes.
You'll lose weight if you walk to there. Too far.
It's like 6, 7km.
Amazing.
We're here.
You can walk along the beach.
I was grateful to Gyeonghwan...
- But I'm grateful to Ryan too. / - Yes.
For people who live there...
- Taking care of guests is work. / - That's true.
- Is that it? / - Yes.
Jihye, look at that.
The ambience here is great.
Koreans don't know Station 3.
Check it out.
I love places like this.
Here's the menu.
- The menu? / - It's here?
If you look, the burgers are good here
and so is the salad.
Steak with beer...
- At the beach? / - Yes.
The menu is as thick as an encyclopedia.
It's so big.
(There are more English descriptions than photos)
(If this is the case)
Let's stand up.
This is how they hand over documents at the summit.
We'll hand the menu over to you.
Thank you.
Me too.
What's happening?
- You want me to order for you? / - That's right.
- That's right. / - He's so nice.
He always plays along.
Filipino language.
It's Tagalog.
He's extremely fluent.
Big size, big size.
White wine.
One glass of white wine.
He brought a new sheet of paper
and he's filled it to the bottom.
Is this a group order?
We ordered so much
that they've come out of the kitchen.
They're wondering who put in such an order.
I'm guessing this the most
that three people have ever ordered at this place.
Buffalo wings. Spicy chicken.
- Look so good. / - Looks delicious.
- It's for beer. / - Buffalo wings.
It's beer.
It tastes exactly like you expect it to taste.
- It's that exact flavor? / - Yes.
Let me debone a wing for you.
There's a way to do that.
Grab the bone,
and turn it twice
like you're turning a screwdriver.
Then you can separate the bone like this. Look.
Right?
Turn this one twice too.
You just need to turn it twice.
And you can give the love of your life...
- It's all meat. / - A boneless chicken wing.
You can do that for her.
There's no bone, right?
It's completely boneless.
What is it?
There's a bone.
Did you bite on something?
- Did you? / - Don't do this to me.
I'll spit it out here.
Boneless chicken.
Isn't it great?
What do the locals usually eat?
The locals eat bread. It's called pandesal.
That's why when you go to a club
that opened for the first time 30 years ago,
they drink beer from jam jars because
they have so many jars left over.
Really?
That's the history.
That's interesting.
Isn't this the great thing about having a guide?
Of course. You need to hear these stories.
Here's the steak which is the main dish.
Is that the steak?
It's so thick.
Look how thick it is.
Jihye, you have a taste first.
Hold on. Let me do this.
- Check out the thickness. / - Like so...
- Hurry, hurry. / - The juices are dripping.
Hurry up and eat it!
Drip, drip.
I'm drooling.
You first, Jihye.
Thanks.
Is it hot?
What the?
- It was too hot. / - Why?
- It was too hot. / - What are you doing?
- You should've held it in. / - It was hot.
- So what? / -She's very honest.
You should've kept it in for the show.
You should've burned the roof of your mouth.
That's a given.
I thought a frog jumped out of her mouth.
(So far, they're enjoying their fancy meal)
The texture is different to the steak we normally have.
Thin steak melts in your mouth.
It's really good.
I don't like steak that just melts.
You want something you can chew on.
- Nice and chewy. / - Kind of rough.
But you can find buffalo wings and steaks...
We eat them in Korea too.
- Eat it at Itaewon. / - Yes, but it's just the start.
- I'm sorry. / - But you can get that local flavor.
- You're sorry? / - You're sorry?
I wanted to eat it so bad.
It's known as the 5 "S."
- So 5 things that start with "S?" / - "S?"
5 "S."
Sexy?
- Sexy? / - Sexy.
- You can find sexy in Gangnam. / - ♪ You're so sexy ♪
You are sexy.
Clubs in Gangnam played this song often.
- Sea. / - Sea. The ocean.
- Okay. One right. / - Correct.
- Sky. / - Sky, correct.
This is the best part of trips.
Secret.
- Wrong. / - Secret.
5 p.m.
Sunset!
- Sunset. / - Sunset.
- Right. / - Sunset.
Do you know Noel?
I know it.
- ♪ I miss you, I miss you ♪ / - ♪ I miss you ♪
♪ Because I miss you so much ♪
Not that Noel.
- The sunset. / - Oh, the sunset.
It's really beautiful.
That's what I meant.
It's so cool. You can go down further if you want.
Goodness, it's a turtle.
What is that?
A turtle.
We're flying. We're flying now.
We're flying.
Unbelievable.
Sunset.
- It really is breathtaking. / - So pretty.
This isn't a postcard.
That's amazing.
It disappears in a moment.
The stars are so pretty.
The atmosphere seems great there.
They're the best parts of Boracay.
Amazing.
Now that we've eaten, next up...
Of the 5 "S," we'll do the sky.
- A helicopter tour is expensive. / - A helicopter tour?
- Yes. / - That would've been really expensive.
Jihye and Boom.
- I've never been on one. / - It's hot to walk around.
And it's far.
Then use the e-trike.
E-trike?
Use this to get around.
- You can get on right away? / - Yes.
Grab one that's waiting
and for a dollar or two...
- You can bargain the rate? / - Yes.
I love the color. It's so pink.
It's the perfect color.
It's pretty.
So cute.
You must post a photo of that trike.
I want to buy one.
30 minutes.
- 30 minutes. / - The island is quite small.
It's windy.
The weather here is amazing.
Of the 5 "S" that I mentioned...
Which one is it?
This is sky.
- Sky? / - Sky.
The sky in Boracay is beautiful.
Yes, it is beautiful indeed.
We are hiking, right?
We'll be close to the sky.
Please come this way.
I prepared this for you two.
Seriously, it's so...
I have to live off instant noodles for a week now.
- What is it? / - I prepared this for you.
I prepared this.
You mean it?
Come this way.
The helicopter was just right there.
(We'll go up to the sky on that?)
I'm slightly afraid of heights.
I can go up to 5 to 7m...
5m is only this high!
I prefer being safe.
You're easily scared.
- Why don't you get on it? / - Don't be like that.
This must be an aviation museum.
No, it's not a museum.
What is that?
Why is that drone so big?
- Let me control it. / - That's not a drone.
- It's not? / - It's not.
Get on it.
Is this for real?
Come this way.
Look here.
Hop on for now.
Step inside...
- No... / - First...
It's hired on a timed rate.
If it goes over 30 minutes, it gets very expensive.
- Are we really flying in this? / - Just get on first.
- Is this for real? / -  Just go in.
You don't have to take off your slippers.
We're really using this?
(Sealed in)
- Goodness. / - What's this?
He didn't mention this beforehand.
You're slim so...
- Be careful. / - Really?
Driver on call.
He just turned on the engine.
Wait, isn't Ryan getting on?
He didn't.
Saying he's scared of heights.
Ryan just dumped us in here.
I'm scared of heights so...
When you ride it for the first time,
you do get nervous.
You get a little nervous when it goes up.
He's saying he's the worst.
He's not getting along with the guide.
That's when it's the scariest.
- It's scary. / - That is scary.
Really?
It's really scary.
We're going up.
Amazing.
Wow, amazing.
The wind is strong so it'll shake a lot.
It'll be really pretty though.
Wow. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Using all the English he knows.
This is crazy.
He's scared.
Jihye, look.
(He's really happy now)
Forget being scared.
It's so beautiful.
He took a turn.
Look at the island. Jihye, look.
Jihye, we are about to see Stage 1, 2, 3.
It's Station not Stage.
We perform on a stage.
This is Station.
- Stage 1, 2, 3? / - Stage.
It's like three stages.
We can see the harbor where we took the ferry.
There's the harbor.
You can see everything.
I can't believe I get to see Boracay from the sky.
This is spectacular.
What a fantastic view.
♪ I believe I can fly ♪
♪ I believe I can touch the sky ♪
♪ I think about it every night and day ♪
I don't know the lyrics.
Wow, beautiful.
Look at the shape of the island.
It looks different from there.
From this point of view,
it's not a big island but it's definitely beautiful.
Now, I understand why Ryan prepared this for us.
The water there is so clean.
Even from up here.
Say that if you're a couple...
- It's worth taking a ride. / - I agree.
- You can confess your love up there. / - Right.
You should take 10,000 photos in the air.
Jihye, I see where we're going to land.
(I can see you too)
Why is it going down so fast?
Slow down...
(The helicopter is about to land)
(Argh)
(A perfect landing)
His face just changed.
He's relieved to be alive.
- Captain! Captain! / - Captain! Captain!
- Captain! / - Captain!
Hey, that's overdoing it.
Why would you bow to the helicopter?
I'm just so thankful.
Wasn't it fun?
Isn't that too excessive?
My knees are very glossy
because I kneel down so often.
Wasn't it beautiful?
It was beautiful.
I was nervous but I saw such a beautiful scenery.
A weird sensation surged through me.
Everyone should try this.
Of the 5 "S..."
- Sky. The sky is beautiful, right? / - Yes.
- I agree. / - This time...
We'll check out another "S."
Where will we go?
To the sea.
Then let's ride the helicopter and dive into the water.
Okay. Let's take it slow.
- Yes, we'll take it slow. / - Do you have red ginseng?
You went snorkeling.
- You learned how to free-dive? / - Yes.
Free-diving.
You just dive down.
It's really fun once you're hooked.
Of the 5 "S..."
We saw Boracay's sky.
We need to focus.
And?
This time...
Of the 5 "S..."
We'll go to sea.
- Sea. / - The sea.
- We need to go in the water. / - You're coming too?
It's beautiful to observe the sea in Boracay
but it's even more beautiful underwater.
That's why I prepared free-diving as an activity.
- Free-diving. / - Be free.
Normally, for free-diving...
You go in without the oxygen tank.
you go in without the oxygen tank.
It's probably with no oxygen.
The oxygen mask...
Jihye, have fun.
I'll see you later.
Why would we remove our masks?
- You have to come. / - Why remove our masks?
How could you think about ditching me?
(What is free-diving?)
We go in without the oxygen tank.
- You dive in without any gear? / - Yes, yes.
Without any gear.
First, you grab the rope to go down.
I've tried that before.
It gets tough because your ears ring.
We're heading to the Boracay sea.
Let's go.
(Let's go and free-dive)
(They head to the free-diving spot)
Look at the color of the water.
The color of the sea is so pretty.
Welcome to Boracay!
(You can't not sing here!)
It's a tough experience.
Look at Ryan.
Ryan Bang...
It was the same for Gyeonghwan.
They get exhausted on the first day.
- You're right. / - He's aged rapidly.
Go, go. Go, go.
- ♪ Always waiting ♪ / - ♪ Always waiting ♪
♪ Boracay is always waiting ♪
Boracay! Boracay!
Bora, Bora, Boracay!
We're here already?
(Everyone, come here)
It was scary at first.
Was Ryan Bang good?
Yes, he was good.
(Jihye joins them too)
(They are clustered together)
That looks great.
The color of the water is so pretty.
(The instructor demonstrates)
Who is that?
- It's the instructor. / - Oh, the instructor.
(You're so cool)
(Let's dive in without the breathing gear)
It wasn't easy because of the waves.
Plus we were beginners.
Ryan goes down.
(The beginner's course is good for practicing)
(Ryan goes all the way to the bottom in one breath)
(I'm fine)
(They are relieved)
(It's the best)
Since you're going down without oxygen,
I was on my own.
- Right. / - That was the frightening part.
I'm going down now.
- You're taking forever. / - Is that you, Boom?
- That is me. / - Are you really going down?
Don't I look like a fish who doesn't move?
(Going slow)
(I'm out of breath now)
I'm coming back up. I need air.
- He has to return. / - I had to go back up.
On the way up...
I'm really fast on the way up.
- You can't do that. It's dangerous. / - No, no.
When you wear the scuba gear
and breathe in the air,
there's nitrogen too.
That's why coming up fast is dangerous.
But you hold your breath for this,
so it doesn't matter how fast you go up.
Oh.
(This is a beginner's course, mostly for practicing)
(But if you're skilled, you can free-dive in various spots)
(This time, Ryan goes down without holding the rope)
(I want to go down without holding the rope too)
What is she doing?
She's floundering.
- It's not as easy as you think. / - What is this?
You should do that under water.
You should pull yourself down.
It isn't as easy as you think.
(This is how you do it)
(Happy)
(Safety is important)
I heard it's fun.
It is fun.
I heard it's incredibly fun once you become skilled.
Once you overcome the fear in the beginning,
you will enjoy it a lot.
- It looks fun. / - It's exhilarating.
(They enjoy their time underwater in Boracay)
(Let's go back)
(They're finished with free-diving)
When you go to a place with clean water,
you must do things like that.
- You're right. / - You must see inside the water.
Applause.
Free-diving!
- Free-diving! / - You were great.
Ryan was great.
He was leading us underwater,
which helped us go down deeper...
- Ryan is... / - Ryan looks very exhausted though.
- He needs some food. / - He looks down.
- Ryan looks so exhausted. / - I'm hungry.
- Hungry, right? / - Yes, I'm hungry.
We're going to a restaurant in Boracay.
These days, well-being food is popular in Korea.
We're going to go eat well-being food.
- Let's go! / - Let's go!
Let's go.
We're going to head out to eat now.
(5 minutes to the Well-being restaurant)
This restaurant is known
for their well-being food.
We're here.
- I'm hungry! Let's go. / - Let's go in.
- What's this? / - This place was really delicious.
- It looks delicious. / - It's a hip restaurant.
It's a hip place in Boracay nowadays.
Well-being food.
(The well-being meal in Boracay will soon be revealed)
What is that?
Tour guides usually prepare gifts.
Ryan prepared those himself?
- Yes, he did. / - Souvenir shirts.
Boracay.
- It's a T-shirt of this place. / - It's Boracay.
The local guides sometimes give presents like this
when they like the tourists they guide.
Jihye, we saw all this.
- Right? / - We did.
We took off here and...
- We flew around the island. / - It was this shape.
The shape of a janggu.
I can't just sit like this when I got a present.
I think we should give him something as well.
I heard you guys were coming
so I prepared something.
Please open it. It's a T-shirt.
Jihye.
What's this? Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Go ahead.
It's fine.
What is this? It's Boom T-shirt.
It's a Boom shirt.
Feel free to wear it anytime.
Look on the back side.
Who is this?
It's me.
Gold comes out of my mouth.
And this...
This is my signed CD.
You took your CDs all the way there?
What's with these signed CDs?
Thank you so much.
You don't have to thank me.
I have about 400 of them at home.
I have too many CDs at home.
Leftovers.
It's a barbecue burger with kimchi.
Well-being.
- That looks delicious. / - That looks delicious.
- It was incredibly good. / - I'd love that.
The kimchi is homemade from the restaurant.
That must taste very unique.
After diving, we were so hungry.
In this restaurant, they make the kimchi themselves.
It's a new kind of dish.
I should just eat it with hands
rather than use forks and knives.
Let me try.
The viewers would not know
that we're in Boracay.
It's tasty, isn't it?
The person who made this kimchi must be a master.
It's so good.
They make good kimchi.
The kimchi was very delicious. I was surprised.
The bun looks really good.
The bun as good.
I didn't think the bun and kimchi would go together
but it tastes like rice with toppings.
You're right.
It tastes a bit like boiled pork too.
- It does. / - This meat is the brisket.
It's used in jangjorim.
With kimchi, it tastes like boiled pork.
It must be like eating jangjorim,
kimchi and rice.
It's similar to that but it's a little different.
It's so delicious.
This kimchi is very delicious.
The combination of bun, kimchi and meat
is something new
but they go so well.
They have a lot of great skewer dishes there.
- The sauce is great. / - Grilled over charcoal.
Anything grilled on charcoal is delicious.
You're right. It's barley.
Wow, it's barley.
It's charcoaled meat with barley rice.
This is perfect for Korean palate.
The barley rice is good too.
It's so delicious.
- It's good, isn't it? / - Yes.
It's like
cream risotto made with barley...
And barbecued meat.
With barbecued meat on it.
(What is this?)
This is a Filipino dish called kangkong.
It looks like spinach.
Isn't it too strong?
It's good. It's something Koreans would love.
This is a common ingredient in China as well.
- Kangkong. / - Kangkong.
It's just like herbs, right?
Hey, this is good.
Is it soft boiled?
Yes.
My gosh.
Soft boiled eggs are the best.
- Eggs are good anywhere. / - I liked the chef there.
Add some kangkong on top.
Let's add our love on his spoon.
Let's do that.
- Add this on the egg? / - Of course.
- It's soft and delicious, right? / - It is.
- This is the friendship of Korea. / - Friendship.
It's so delicious.
- It's dessert. / - It looks so pretty.
This dessert was amazing.
- Mango? / - It's like yogurt...
- It's the best. / - It's 100% mango puree.
- That'd be good. / - It was really good.
- You have to eat fruit there. / - You must eat mango.
- There's millet in it. / - There's millet and oats.
There are strawberries, banana, mango.
And is this mango porridge?
- Mango. / - I think it's crushed mango.
It was very thick.
- I don't think it was thick. / - Oh, yes...
Are you sure you ate the same thing?
- It's not thick. It's very soft. / - Excuse me.
When are you going to have teamwork?
They use these terms
on the home shopping network,
so I tried using it.
Let's have a bite.
Let's mix them.
Look. It looks thick.
- That doesn't look thick at all. / - It doesn't look thick.
- It looks soft. / - That would melt in your mouth.
- It melts in your mouth. / - It melts.
That would melt in your mouth.
- Wow. / - It's so good.
- It kind of feels like baby food. / - Baby food.
It's similar to pumpkin soup
but it's cold and refreshing.
- It's like mango yogurt. / - Yes, it's like yogurt.
Mango yogurt.
Things like that bloat in your stomach
so you feel full for longer.
It's a good diet food.
Whatever food Sunyeong explains, I want to eat that.
Please keep explaining.
Shall I? Should I add some comments?
This is the best restaurant in Southeast Asia
that I've ever been to.
- Seriously? / - Yes.
When you travel, you start to miss Korean food
on the second day.
- Here, I don't miss Korean food. / - Right?
- Yeah. / - It's amazing.
What are we doing next?
Now we will take a break back at the hotel.
Then experience the nightlife in Boracay.
- Club. / - Her eyes are sparkling.
We actually don't enjoy ourselves much in clubs.
I'm a married woman
so I will just briefly drop by the place and leave.
I'm a little conservative.
So I just wanted to go there for a short time and leave.
You're saying this now but you won't change like this
when you're in there, right?
What is this?
She's very conservative.
Her outfit looks very conservative.
- Her outfit looks so conservative. / -  Her outfit...
She looks like a tropical fish in Boracay.
We're running out of time. We've got to hurry.
Let's go.
It's going to be fun this evening.
Oh, Ryan...
- Goodness. / - I'm a reflector.
- I look like a reflector. / - I thought you were a fish.
You and I are dressed up...
- But Ryan... / - He took a jacket.
He looks funnier.
- Are shorts allowed? / - Why did you wear that?
What's great about clubs in Boracay
is that you can wear whatever you like.
Everyone is wearing shorts and flip-flops here.
- It's very free. / - Yes.
Inside, they'll think you own the club.
- He's over-dressed. / - The club owner.
You need to wear a jacket.
- Boracay. / - This is so good.
It's been a while since we introduced a club.
(Club "G" is a new hot place for nightlife in Boracay)
It's a bit similar to old-fashioned night clubs in Korea.
- There are tables as well. / - Tables lined up.
- There are booths as well. / - You're right.
That's so us.
And you can dress in shorts and flip-flops.
That's fascinating.
- This place is newly opened. / - Really?
Not many know there's such a big club in Boracay.
It's so big.
- There's an entrance fee. / - That's the entrance fee.
- Let's order. / - Yes, let's order.
For me...
San Miguel.
This is a new club that's popular in Boracay.
It opened not too long ago.
Hey, it's "Run To You."
Let's step out.
Wait. Jihye, you said you'd leave after saying hi.
Oh, dear.
- You said you wouldn't stay. / - Here she comes.
- Here's the conservative girl. / - Conservative.
The Boracay tropical fish is here.
Oh, dear.
It's a function.
You're too conservative.
(Filipino style)
(He repeats the same dance moves)
(Boom takes over the stage)
(Shake it, Boom)
He's going off.
What will we do about him?
Oh, dear.
They'll think that every Korean is like him.
We've never seen anything like this on Battle Trip.
I became friends with the locals right away.
He still got it.
This is Boracay.
I can't believe we're sober.
- This is Boracay. / - We went when it was empty.
That's so funny.
I feel like all my stress is melting.
So funny.
- But Boom doesn't drink. / - I can't drink either.
Boom can't drink.
(I can't stay down here like this)
(The night in Boracay begins now)
I made him go up
to liven up the mood.
RaBoom.
Boom and Bang.
- RaBoom is good. / - Boom and Bang.
(People respond to Boom and Bang's music)
(The stage starts to fill up)
(Jihye also goes up on the stage)
(I'll take care of the night in Boracay)
Hello!
- She's so conservative. / - So polite.
- She's way too conservative. / - So polite.
What's with the greeting?
She did say that she'd say hello and leave.
Why did you say hello like this?
He looks so cool.
(Let's dance like crazy)
(They would've regretted it if they didn't come here)
Are they a new group?
We seem like KOYOTE.
KOYOTE.
- They won't be able to get up tomorrow. / - I know.
You did so well.
(The sky is clear the next morning)
The course I've prepared
has many things that Koreans don't know about.
- I love that. / - We love things like this.
Koreans come here and only stay on the island.
But we'll take a boat and go outside of it.
I love the idea of going outside of the island.
That was awesome.
It's like rafting.
You flow down the river.
The water is clean enough to drink.
- I drank some. / - For real?
For real.
Nature.
Don't you feel phytoncide just by looking at it?
It's too short.
That's really good.
- I love this place. / - Diving.
(Around $98 for the Malumpati tour)
We're the first to broadcast the Blue Lagoon
of Boracay on TV.
Boracay's Blue Lagoon?
It's probably the first time anyone's seen it.
This one's bigger than the one in Laos.
It's something we didn't know about.
This is the hottest place right now.
If you look from here, it's just water.
But it's blue in the deep areas.
It's really deep.
This place has never been on TV.
I recommend this place because...
I thought you were conservative.
I didn't know.
I was just told it was a swimming pool.
I recommend it because...
It's nature.
In Boracay, the way to the airport...
Most of the flights returning to Korea are at night.
You're right. It's at 1 a.m.
There's nothing to do on the way.
This is on the way to Kalibo Airport.
- You should stop by. / - Yes, you should.
When you go to a water park...
- You go around in a tube. / - Right.
Here, you're floating down the river
with a guide's escort.
Just a little bit of man-power.
By hand. With human power.
There is a cave up there.
It's about 40m deep.
This is amazing. This is nature.
Goodness.
Gosh, look at the sky.
How much longer do we need to walk?
- 20 more minutes. / - Really?
All of a sudden, I was hiking in a swimsuit.
- That became your hiking clothes. / - I know.
You have to climb the mountain?
- Look here. / - Don't film me.
It's the jungle.
What is that?
- Please apologize to the viewers. / - I'm sorry.
How can you make us laugh with this?
I'm sorry.
(1990s Miss Korea's swimsuit style)
I would've brought my pants if I knew about the hike.
Everyone, start recording with your own cameras.
Let's do that.
Make sure you pack your pants.
The most important thing to remember is no bikini.
Wearing a bikini might look too over the top.
We'll talk about bracken today.
Alright. Bracken fern.
You can see it here.
Bracken.
(Ryan Bang's Pinoy News)
They're coming.
I'll tell you about the rafting later.
- Bye. / - They're coming.
- Viewers, right now... / - Hello.
- They're coming right now. / - The rafting has begun.
- 1st place. / - Many are coming in together...
That looks like fun.
We'll go down the river like them.
- Is that it? / - That looks like fun.
(You wear a life vest and receive safety training)
Unbelievable.
Right here. It's 40m deep here.
Really?
This is where the water starts.
This is cool. Awesome.
You'll be surprised.
This is where the water starts.
This is so...
- It's so unbelievably clean. / - Amazing.
You can just drink it.
Look at the fish.
You can drink this water.
It's the second cleanest water in the world.
(Boom tastes the water)
How is it?
It doesn't smell at all.
It's pure water.
It's clean like spring water.
Freshwater can smell.
But that has no smell.
This is completely natural.
- Look at the color. / - It's so beautiful.
- It's like paint. / - People can't go in there.
They drink water from there
and move downward.
People just drink from it
and move down.
- Is it cold? / - Wait a minute.
Oh, it's too cold.
- It's too cold. / - It's too cold?
- You go second. / - Slowly please.
I'll be startled if it's too cold.
- I have a weak heart. / - Water tastes like water.
- You're in. / - Wait.
Oh, it's cold.
I think it's the same as the hotel water.
(He's overreacting)
Wait.
- That looks like fun. / - It is fun.
The tube has a cross on it, so you don't fall through.
Each person has a guide.
That looks like so much fun.
It was really great.
In that clean water.
It was like going back to our childhoods.
Experiencing nature has its own charm.
You just have to float.
- You just relax. / - So nice.
I love it.
- Your guide escorts you... / - So it's safe.
To keep you safe.
I really want to try that.
(Screaming)
- That looks so fun. / - I love that.
It's nice because it's not too rough.
(The water flows more rapidly as they go down)
It's getting rough now.
You go in and out.
Since you can drink that water.
- Gosh, this is nice. / - It's really nice.
- Ryan. / - Yes?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Isn't this great? / - Totally.
- This place is the best. / - I love outdoor activities.
It looks so good.
You have to check this place out.
- It's not very well known yet. / - I should go there.
- Yes. / - Look at the water.
That's nature in its original form.
- This is like a pool. / - That's paradise.
A lot of people came with kids.
There were many local families.
- You could sleep there. / - Right.
- They have hotels, right? / - It's near the airport.
Ryan Bang!
It's so high.
Didn't Ryan say he's scared of heights?
He was so scared
but there are so many people cheering for him.
- It's so high. / - It's about 7m high.
You can do it.
(An official cheering squad for Ryan)
(Hang on a second)
(He gives up)
Ryan is scared of heights.
So instead of him, I...
So Ryan didn't jump?
- You're a man. / - He tries again later.
- Gosh, Jihye. It's so high up here. / - Boom first.
I worry about my safety a lot.
I'm very sensitive when it comes to safety.
I try to be as safe as possible.
That's how I travel.
I can go up 5 to 7m.
Hey, that's like only this high.
5m is meaningless.
(That's why this is 4m)
- Is it 4m? / - It's only 4m.
(Gosh, I don't think I can do this)
No, no, no. You'll get hurt.
What?
We can't do that.
I was so shocked.
I heard it's incredibly deep
under the water.
I heard it's deeper than 50m.
That's scary.
(Please cheer for me)
(He jumped)
(He plucked up courage to fight the fear in himself)
(Great job)
Good job, Lee Minho.
Good job. You looked really cool.
(I was so cool)
(Ryan gives it another try)
Ryan retries.
- Jump! / - Everyone there cheered for him.
It doesn't look so scary from here
but it was so scary there.
It's a frightening height.
- Once you do it, you feel good. / - It's like this.
The water was so deep, it was scary to go in.
You can't see the bottom.
- Seriously... / - It's way deeper than the ocean.
It was so scary. You're really cool.
It was scary, right?
I could only do it because you went first.
After doing this, I feel like,
I can do everything.
- I feel confident. / - Go again?
- No, no. / - No?
- You guys must be hungry by now. / - I'm hungry.
Since we're hungry... Do you guys like buffet?
Buffet.
- I love it. / - Let's go.
- Buffet time. / - Let's go.
(2nd day of RaBang Tour)
(Local buffet)
We were hungry so we went to eat again.
Not many Korean people know about
boodle fight.
Here you can experience the traditional way
of eating with your hands here.
- They eat with their hands? / - Traditionally.
Eating with your hands.
It's very delicious.
It's my favorite dish here.
You must be hungry.
I could eat anything right now.
- I'm starving. / - Swimming makes you hungry.
I prepared food for you.
It's a fancy buffet.
- Really? / - Yes.
- Like a welcome ceremony. / - Since it's a valley...
- I feel like boiled chicken. / - Here?
Can you see the buffet?
What is that?
- That's the buffet I prepared. / - Really?
- What is this? / - We can eat this?
- This is called boodle fight. / - This is amazing.
Boodle fight.
This is the way soldiers used to eat.
- The weather was great. / - They'd remove their ranks.
- What is this? / - And enjoy food together as equals.
That's where boodle fight originated from.
This is how Filipinos eat with their families and relatives
on family holidays like
Chuseok or Seollal in Korea.
They set the food like this
and eat together with their hands.
There's chicken as well?
- It's a variety of flavors. / - Yes.
- It looks good. / - There's pork too.
Everyone stands around the table and
eats the food with their hands.
It's a Filipino buffet.
You wash with the calamansi like this.
- I've never used calamansi as soap before. / - Yes.
This is a natural soap...
- Since it's acidic. / - Exactly. It's a disinfectant.
I'm nervous.
Grab some rice like this...
And put some meat on the rice.
Jihye, this is the culture of this region.
I think it's a good idea to experience
how locals eat here.
It was strange for me because it was my first time.
Goodness.
It was hard to try in the beginning.
But once you try, it's delicious to eat with your hands.
It's very tender.
It's good, right?
I've been to the Philippines many times
but I've never seen something like this.
- This is similar to... / - It looks delicious.
- Pork ribs in Korea. / - I love pork ribs.
It tastes like ribs.
I think I will miss this food back in Seoul.
- Really? / - I'm sure I'll miss this.
If you like the food after a bite, go like this...
And then do this.
Send your mom a heart to tell her it's good.
This is the traditional Filipino noodle, pancit canton.
- You eat that with hands too? / - This is delicious.
- The noodle was delicious. / - I like the noodles.
You're good with chopsticks.
I can eat it like this.
Seriously...
We all have this.
- This is comfortable. / - This is good for noodles.
I think you adapt very well.
There's a spicy sauce next to the food.
It's soy sauce mixed with spicy chili peppers.
If you eat it with the chili pepper and sauce,
it's spicy and tasty.
I prepared a surprise here.
- It's good for your health. / - Really?
- I prepared something. / - I love things like that.
Things to do with good health.
It felt like eating chicken next to a valley.
It was fun to eat with our hands.
- It was nice. / - Here comes the chicken.
- Really? / - This was amazing. It's boiled chicken.
- What is that? / - They add the meat whole.
Yes, whole.
It's so good.
Is that a pot?
- It's a pot. / - They add it whole.
How big is the dish?
It was big enough to feed all the staff.
They're cooking something similar boiled chicken.
They added the vegetables.
- Is this like shabu shabu? / - Exactly.
They even put flowers in it. Can you eat the flowers?
You should go in.
Oh, no.
Whatever you imagine, this is beyond.
What's going on?
It's good for you.
Isn't this for cooking?
We're going to cook you.
It feels weird.
This is like a public bath in Korea.
- Not many people know about this. / - It's a bath.
It's so nice in here.
- It prevents flu. / - It smells good.
Yes, it does.
- There's lemon in it. / - Excuse me, sir.
Sir?
You can leave the fire alone.
Wait a minute.
He's heating the pot.
What the?
- For real? / - He's heating it up.
- Wait a minute. Is this okay? / - Amazing.
He's heating it up.
Just like a barbecue.
If you heat the bottom...
- Amazing. / - The heat fills the pot.
Once they're done cooking, you eat them?
The traditional Filipino pot spa...
Is very popular these days.
Some people come to Boracay just for this spa.
This is comforting.
- It's nice. / - This is really nice.
It's so good.
When else would you experience such a hot spring
here, in the mountains of Boracay.
The three of us...
But isn't Ryan's fire too strong? Sir?
It's so hot here.
- It's so hot here. / - Oh, dear.
He shouldn't have taken off his shirt.
- It's like he's being cooked. / - He took it off.
That isn't CG.
It's good for your skin too.
- It's really good. / - I love it.
It feels really nice to sit in here...
- Bathing in nature like this... / - This is so nice.
I feel like I'm one with nature.
It's like Gangwon-do. It's so nice.
It's a very unique experience.
(I'm one with nature)
He's hilarious.
It was so warm.
After this, we'll go back to Boracay.
It's the pork hock place with the best view in the world.
- A pork hock place with a view? / - With a view.
(See you again in Boracay)
This is so nice.
- That looks really unique. / - That was great.
- Eating with your hands, then that. / - So nice.
- It's the best. / - It looks fun.
In Boracay, you eat and play, eat and play.
Yes, yes.
When we first arrived here, we ate near Station 3.
- We're now at Station 2. / - No. 2?
This is the most crowded area.
Not many Koreans know about this place.
The reason why the pork hocks are so good...
- Because the view here is... / - Amazing.
It's the view of Boracay.
While looking at the emerald ocean and the sunset...
You eat pork hocks.
- Sunset of 5 "S." / - Let's go.
- Let's go and have pork hocks. / - Let's go.
That's about when the sun starts going down.
- It looks so nice. / - That's the dream life.
They have local Filipino dishes.
- We should have local dishes. / - Pork hocks...
I didn't know they ate pork hocks here.
I've never been to such a fancy pork hock place.
- This is like... / - I know.
- The setting... / - Check out the view.
- It's beautiful, isn't it? / - It is.
It looks different in the evening when
the boats come together.
It looks beautiful.
Many couples ride boats here
at this time of the day.
It's a view that you really want to share.
The sound of the waves is nice.
You can come here straight from the beach too.
Food tastes so good when you do that.
- It does. / - Here's another booklet.
- A thick booklet. / - Menu.
We need to order the crispy pata first,
the pork hocks.
- Crispy pata. / - It tastes good already.
I felt like beer again.
Bulalo soup.
Adobong pusit.
It's squid.
The Koreans living in Boracay come here for this.
- Let's order one of these. / -  Okay.
Looks so good. Crispy on the outside.
Of all the places I've been in Southeast Asia,
this place matches the Korean palate the best.
The squid.
- Here it is. / - It's here.
- Bulalo soup? / - Bulalo.
- It's a bone broth. / - Like ox bone soup?
(Bulalo)
(Made by boiling the hind leg of a cow for a long time)
The bulalo was amazing.
The soup was so rich because they boiled bones.
The meat was so tender.
- It suits our taste. / - It does?
Yes, it suits Koreans. It feels a bit like ox tail soup.
It's so good.
You know that clean ox tail soup?
- It's just like Korean food. / - You're right.
The beef is so tender and it suits our taste.
This place is amazing.
I'd say this has a 50-year history.
(Bulalo with a taste of 50-years of tradition?)
This dish is from...
The cold regions of the Philippines.
The people living in the colder regions...
- Eat this to warm up? / - Exactly.
So it suits Korean tastes really well.
I want to take this with me in a tumbler.
That was like short rib soup.
- Rib soup? / - You can slap 2 bottles of soju easy...
Slap what?
So conservative.
There she goes again.
What is this?
This is what Koreans like best.
- It's squid ink. / - That looks so good.
This is the pork hocks?
- The famous pork hocks. / - They were so good.
- It's fried, right? / - Yes, on the outside.
Inside, it has really tender pork.
- It's like Beijing duck. / - Yes, Beijing duck.
The outside is cooked crispy.
Do you eat it dipped in a sauce?
This is the sauce for crispy pata.
Let me tell you how to make the sauce.
- Put peppers in. / - You have to put spicy ones in it.
That looks so good.
- With lots of onions. / - Use your fork.
That's calamansi.
Using the fork to keep the seeds out.
Filipino pork hocks.
It's so good!
Isn't it amazing?
This means that Jihye really likes it.
It was so good.
- It looks so good. / - I can't lie.
It's like meat...
The skin is crispy so
the texture in your mouth...
Should we buy some pork hocks and fry it?
It's pork hocks but tastes like boiled pork.
Boiled pork.
It's really good. I'm speechless.
Even old Korean people who can't eat
foreign foods will love this.
(She courageously takes a bite)
(Her eyes get bigger)
- Isn't it really good? / - Amazing.
When you go to Korean restaurants,
they have stir-fried squid.
It's like that.
You can taste the sauce more than the ink.
It doesn't smell fishy at all.
How could it taste so clean?
Since we like to do variety shows...
- When they see this. / - He's an old comedian.
Old comedian.
- You have to make this funny. / - Of course.
We have to get footage of us eating.
What should we do?
Let's just eat it naturally.
Just take a bite and give a big smile.
Take a big bite and give us a big smile.
(Expectant)
It's so good.
(Ta-da)
He has to do it.
You're so ugly. What are you going to do?
You should also try it.
She did well.
This is how they really do it in the Philippines.
My emotions really welled up earlier...
(The reason why everyone exclaimed)
(You can see Boracay's sunset as time goes by)
- It looks like a calendar. / - That's another "S."
This is amazing.
It really is one of the 5 "S," sunset.
Isn't it really pretty?
You have to acknowledge that's a beautiful sunset.
We have no choice.
- It was like art. / - It's really pretty.
- It was an unforgettable scene. / - The clouds...
I feel like we're saying good-bye
to the sunset at this moment.
I feel emotional.
- Isn't the Philippines beautiful? / - It's so beautiful.
The Filipinos also acknowledge that Boracay has
one of the most beautiful sunsets.
Some people come here to visit and don't go back.
- Because it's so nice. / - Because they like it.
- The view, experience, it's perfect. / - I know.
We'd better do this when he comes to Korea.
Yes, the next time RyBang comes to Korea...
- He's not RyBang. / - Ryan Bang.
- Not RyBang. / - That's not right.
- Sorry, I meant Ryan Bang. / - Geez, Jihye...
(Beach bar)
(8 minutes to the beach bar from the restaurant)
You hear music the entire walk.
You can just sit on the beach.
- You can drink on the beach? / - This is Boracay.
It feels so good here. Singing songs...
They have live performances too.
There are a lot of clubs on the sand beach.
Let's enjoy this while drinking cocktails.
- Isn't it so nice? / - It is.
This is the sea breeze.
Boracay has two different charms by day and night.
- Three steps forward and it's the ocean. / - Ocean.
- Three steps back and there are clubs. / - So good.
Which "S" is this then?
- Of the 5 "S," this is star. / - Star.
- Star. / - Star.
For real?
The sky was so clear.
(Drinking cocktails on the beach under the stars)
- You have to go there with your lover. / - Yes.
Pizza! Thank you.
This place is famous
for having pizza with cocktails.
- Do you eat it with the cocktails? / - Yes, together.
I love it.
- Let's eat it. / - Let's eat it.
It's delicious to eat pizza with the cocktails.
(They try pizza with cocktails as Ryan recommended)
Isn't it so delicious?
- Don't they go well together? / - Yes.
- It goes so well with the cocktails. / - Right?
- It's pizza. / - The owner is a European.
He's an Italian and he makes pizza here.
- It's so good. / - Italy...
(Boom kept eating and drinking since it was so good)
He's drunk.
He's a terrible drinker.
Seriously...
He looks like he'd be a very strong drinker
but he's actually quite like a model student.
He's really like a model student.
- Just lie down. / - I can't drink.
- And the cocktail was so strong. / - He's cute.
- Really? / - He woke up right away.
Time out.
- You're red too. / - I'm drunk too.
- The two guys here can't drink. / - Ryan can't drink.
Only Jihye can drink well.
They don't go well with liquor.
- Only Jihye. / - Yes.
- They drank a lot. / - Please blur me out.
- He's drunk. / - How is that possible?
He had like a sip.
This is our last night.
I'm sad for it to end.
Let's say one good thing and one bad thing.
Let's say a bad thing first. How was it?
You didn't give us a lot of snacks during the tour.
I was so hungry while we were in the water.
We played a lot in the water.
I was so hungry.
The reason why we didn't have snacks was
to make you enjoy the meals.
Are you drunk?
The reason why we didn't have snacks was
to enhance Boom's reactions when eating meals.
- I made you hungry on purpose. / - That's right.
Say one good thing.
I felt that there was more to Boracay than the beach.
There's nature...
The activities we could experience...
The sea.
We could experience so many things.
- I liked that so much. / - Thank you.
I met a new Boracay.
A new Boracay.
I feel like I've healed on this trip too.
- Ryan Bang is so adorable. / - So good.
I really love this, Jihye.
This is unforgettable for me.
It doesn't matter if we lose.
So long as we're happy.
- Let's do this. / - Let's go.
♪ Cay, Cay, Boracay ♪
Battle Trip!
(RaBang Tour in Boracay, the end)
The mood is amazing there.
Continuing from last week,
a lot of people go to Boracay for their honeymoon.
They only think about the beach.
- There was a Blue Lagoon there. / - That's right.
It was amazing.
It looked so nice.
Malumpati has never been shown on TV.
Not even on Pinoy TV.
- Really? / - It's never been aired.
But it's such an amazing place.
If you ask the travel agencies,
there are package tours
where they provide pick up services.
- It's a must-visit. / - Yes.
- I have to mention two things. / - Yes.
Being boiled in the pot.
I love it.
And I want to taste the pork hocks so bad.
I was surprised at first,
because I thought they were boiling something
since we ate right next to there.
I thought they were boiling pork hocks
or something.
- Then all of a sudden... / - They tell you to go in.
Yes, they told me to go in.
I was surprised.
But the temperature was perfect and
the scent of lemon...
There was a stream right next to it.
It felt like paradise
looking down from there.
Japanese hot springs are famous.
But I never knew that they had such an amazing spa.
- It's so unique. / - I want to try it once.
- It looked so nice. / - It was unique.
- Let's check the expenses. / - Okay.
The Yeom Tour in Hanoi
cost $217.70 cents for 2 days.
- It was cheap. / - What about the RaBang Tour.
Excluding air fares, how much did you spend?
Our trip was 4 days and 3 nights.
- 4 days? / - That's an extra day.
- It's an extra day. / - Yes.
- The amount we spent in Boracay... / - The amount?
$530!
- It's okay. / - $530.
- It's double our budget. / - It's okay.
- It's okay. / - It's double our budget.
They went on that expensive helicopter ride.
If you take that out...
And it cost an extra day for accommodation.
- That's right. It was 4 days. / - More on accommodation.
And you spent more on food.
Final remarks, Boom.
People say a lot of things about Boracay, right?
But there's only one thing I felt about Boracay.
Boracay is a treasure to the world.
Tourists around the world should protect the island.
It's beautiful.
And I want to go there again sometime
when I get a break.
That's what I felt about Boracay.
This could be our last so let's sing it one last time.
1, 2, 3.
♪ Cay, Cay, Boracay ♪
- The harmony is wrong. / - It's wrong.
(Nervous)
- That was great. / - Just vote fairly.
Would you go to Boracay...
according to the RaBang Tour's plan?
Please vote.
(RaBang Tour planned a trip to Boracay)
(What will the judges choose?)
Yeom Tour introduced good local restaurants,
hidden tourist spots and hot photo locations.
They revealed everything
you need to know about Hanoi.
Will the Yeom Tour in Hanoi win?
They showed a beautiful beach,
the hidden lagoon...
And there was the unique iron pot spa.
- That was so good. / - Will you go to Boracay?
What will the judges choose?
- This is so hard. / - I have no idea.
No, no.
- The first digit first. / - What is the first digit?
- Is it the same? / - RaBang.
- RaBang. / - No!
No, no!
- What is it? / - 8, 7, 6?
(Hanoi wins with 91 votes)
This is amazing.
It's been a long time since we got over 90 votes.
- Really? / - That's how good it was.
- And 86 is extremely high. / - Of course.
Tell us how you feel.
Our trip wasn't just for the shoot.
It was just great.
Because it was my first trip with friends,
without the kids, after becoming a parent.
Every moment was a precious memory.
It will mean a lot in my life.
- It was so good. / - Thank you.
- Okay, Eric. / - Yes.
Now that it's over, let's say you have a girlfriend.
Would you go to Hanoi or Boracay with her?
Where would you go?
1, 2, 3.
I heard you sing with Boracay.
- He's happy imagining that. / - 1, 2, 3.
Hanoi. I should definitely go to Hanoi.
I'd go to Hanoi.
That's all from the special host.
Sikyung, it's another special next week?
It's no ordinary special.
It's Battle Trip's 2nd-year anniversary.
- For our 2nd-year special... / - It's on a larger scale.
The hosts traveled overseas.
It's Korea's most beloved tourist attraction.
The no. 1 location for family trips.
- It's Guam. / - Guam.
It's Guam.
Next week, it's a special 2-year anniversary episode
where the hosts go overseas.
Please don't miss it.
The world is your school, life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
(Next episode)
(Battle Trip's 2-year anniversary)
I've never felt like this before.
(78 cities in 29 countries and 92 trip designers)
We've arrived in Guam!
They're so cute.
(Hot places picked by the hosts)
Let's be happy for a long time.
- Battle. / - Battle.
Trip.
("LADY" by EXID)