(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Hwijae, special host, Lee Suji)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
(Travel is war)
Travel is war! Battle Trip!
Nice to meet you.
She's finally here.
Today's special host is Lee Suji.
- Nice to meet you. / - Nice to meet you.
I'm a beautiful comedienne, Lee Suji.
- Good to be here. / - Do you like to travel?
I love to travel so much.
I think there are two types of trips.
The wandering around type and the inner healing type.
I'm here to relax and enjoy the trips like I'm at home.
Yes.
I'll get vicarious enjoyment out of it today.
You're the most popular these days.
What are you talking about?
You're a radio DJ.
Wait, doesn't she have a connection with you?
- She's like a family. / - That's right.
Why?
They have a special relationship.
- We were lovers. / - We acted together once.
- Did you act as lovers? / - Yes.
Sikyung's concerts are full of variety.
He turned a video clip on in the middle of his concert.
- We parodied the drama, "Guardian." / - Yes.
He was Gong Yoo, and I was Kim Goeun.
- You played Goeun? / - Yes.
You were not the goblin?
What are you talking about?
Can't you act out a scene for us?
- Just one scene. / - Should we do it on the side?
- Let's change seats. / - I don't remember the lines.
Here we go.
Okay, the camera is shooting.
And action!
Because it's a good day. Because it isn't a good day.
Every day was happy for me.
Who is Nari?
Who is she?
I love you, mister.
- We acted like this. / - It was like this.
- They're really good. / - You have to be shameless.
Okay, what is today's topic for Battle Trip?
For the last 2 weeks, 20-year-olds went on
a domestic spring flower festival trips.
It was so fresh.
It was so nice and full of delicious food.
We'll go to international festivals this time.
It's festival season these days.
Domestically and internationally.
Let's see who went to international festivals today.
Let's meet the trip planners.
Let's have them here.
They planned the international festival trips.
Please come out.
(Hongbin, N of VIXX)
(Sojin of Girl's Day, Shin Ayoung)
I'm curious about something.
Since you're on the same team,
it must have been so fun on your trip.
But Sojin and Ayoung's friendship is unexpected.
- It's unexpected. / - Right?
As far as I know, they aren't close.
How was it?
- We didn't know each other. / - Right?
Really?
People said that we would really get along.
How was it? Did you get along?
- Yes. / - You'll know when you see.
We really enjoyed our trip.
- I think... / - You'll know when you see.
You're just saying that you're close.
It doesn't seem like they
became really close.
Let's see what countries they went
to enjoy festivals.
- Sojin and Ayoung will start. / - Should we start first?
We went to Thingyan, which the New Year celebration.
We went to the city of gold and
the unknown country, Myanmar.
I really like Myanmar.
Really?
- I've always wanted to go to Myanmar. / - Me too.
Yes, Myanmar.
- It's really popular these days. / - It is.
We'll ask our opponents.
We went to Songkran, one of the world's top 10 festivals.
We went to Thailand that boasts various charms.
That festival is really famous.
- People know a lot about Thailand. / - Really famous.
- Already attacking us. / - But Thailand...
Aren't you so curious about Myanmar?
- Thailand's just... / - Songkran is famous.
Songkran festival is really unique and
only happens once a year.
Is there a festival that happens 10 times a year?
Well, no, but...
- Songkran is famous, right? / - Yes.
Songkran is influenced by Thingyan.
That's how it was created.
- Thingyan is the original. / - Yes, it's the original.
- Are you sure? / - It's the original?
Yes, I'm sure.
- Who said that? / - It was from a book.
- It was from a book? / - It was in a book.
I also read something from a book.
It originated from Thingyan
but Songkran is the most famous and the hottest.
You can't say you've had blood sausage soup
until you try it at the original restaurant.
You don't have to eat
Pyeongyang cold noodles in Pyeongyang.
- Good job. / - Good job.
- Good job. / - Good, good, good.
We came here thinking that we already won.
Thank you.
I love this attitude.
Wait a minute.
It isn't the first time we're going to Myanmar...
- On Battle Trip. / - That's right.
That's right.
We already went there once.
- Kim Suyong and Park Hwisun went there. / - Yes.
- We lost by a landslide, right? / - Yes.
I only remember them sitting on the floor.
They couldn't do much though they wanted to.
But that time, they only went to Yangon.
- Right. / - Yangon, Myanmar.
- We went to Bagan. / - Where?
Bagan.
- Bagan. / - Bagan?
Will you show a completely different Myanmar
from the last visit?
It's going to be a different picture.
People who travel a lot
often say that you've never been to Myanmar
if you haven't been to Bagan.
We didn't go to Bagan last time.
I think that's why you lost.
Let's go to Bagan, Myanmar first today.
- Okay. / - That's forcing the issue.
I think both trips will be amazing.
Okay.
We have our 100 impartial judges with us today.
Welcome.
Today's match is a little different.
Originally, we would watch the Myanmar trip and
then watch the Thailand trip and end it in one round.
But there's an extra round today.
What is that?
It's 2 plus 1 today.
So much content.
- It's simple. / - Quite amazing.
Let's see who will win after 3 weeks.
Please look forward to it.
Let's see Myanmar on the map first.
Where is Myanmar?
Myanmar is close to Cambodia and Thailand.
It's quite far.
It takes 5 hours 40 minutes
from Korea to Yangon.
It takes 1 hour 20 minutes
by plane from Yangon to Bagan.
- That's quite far from Yangon. / - Yes.
Then is the Thingyan festival in Yangon?
Yes, Thingyan festival happens
throughout the whole of Myanmar.
It's like Korea's Seollal.
So we thought that it would be better to go to Yangon,
since it's easy for tourists to go there.
- So it happens all around Myanmar. / - Yes.
- And you decided to go to Yangon. / - Yes.
- Do you have a tour name? / - They have one.
- We have a tour name. / - Show us.
1, 2, 3.
Firefighting Tour, bboom bboom!
- Let's watch the Myanmar trip... / - So out of synch.
They don't match at all.
(The day they leave for Myanmar)
(Ayoung arrived at the airport first)
Is this it?
I'm here.
- Hi. / - Hi.
Are you a little less awkward with each other now?
Don't ask whether we're awkward or not.
That makes us awkward.
We were okay.
It's awkward if people ask that.
- Hello. / - That's right.
(Do I look good on camera?)
I'm not going by myself.
A lot of people around us said we would get along
with each other really well.
People around you are usually right.
Ayoung looks like a teacher there.
I had to go there after work...
You're the same age as me, right?
Are you the same age?
- Yes. We're friends. / - That was so awkward.
- I was born in 1986. / - You're the same age?
This is a bit awkward. I was born in early 1987.
It's messy.
Let's just make it easy and be friends.
Let's be friends.
I'll slowly try to stop speaking formally to you.
(Awkward)
Is there a wall between them?
They're adorable.
My father was born in early 1939 and
he doesn't befriend people born in 1938.
It's true. He doesn't want to mess up the age rank.
We're here to see your traveling preferences.
If people get along well,
they get really close after going on a trip together.
Korean food or local food?
Choose what you like on a trip. 1, 2, 3.
- Local food. / - Local food.
Activities or rest? 1, 2, 3.
- Activities. / - Activities.
- They match. / - Rest or sight-seeing?
1,2,3.
- Sight-seeing. / - Sight-seeing.
They're the exact opposite of us.
I like to have a lot to do when I go there.
I go to a lot of places.
I think I'm the most diligent out of the year
when I'm traveling.
I usually don't like to rest
and not do anything.
There's a reason why they're slim.
Suji, rest or sight-seeing? 1, 2, 3.
Rest!
There's a reason why people are slim.
I like to go to historic sites.
I also like to go to museums.
I was so surprised.
I hate going to historic sites the most...
They're divided.
- She hates it the most. / - That travel package feel...
- She's trying to make up for it, right? / - Yes.
I simply think that there's a place like that.
I search for it and just pass by.
That's it. Some people go on tours
to only see that historic building.
That's me.
That can be meaningful, sure.
It's not for me.
They're awkward again.
It's really interesting when people like her explain...
- The historic sites for you. / - That's nice.
People like Ayoung study about them before they go.
- I buy a book. / - She buys a book before going.
The theme is... International festival special.
- Festival? / - I see.
It must be the season for Southeast Asian countries
to have festivals.
I've heard about Songkran before.
Songkran?
It's the one we went.
That's how they splash water.
They look excited.
That was nothing compared to what we did.
(Researching)
These water festivals originated
from Myanmar.
- Myanmar? / - Have you been there?
No, I haven't.
Let me think about what I've read about it.
- She loves reading. / - It's a country of gold.
She read many books before coming.
She learns everything from books.
- Was studying the easiest for you? / - No...
I think it's an undiscovered country.
I feel like Myanmar is an undiscovered country.
That's the one.
That was on Battle Trip before, right?
- They washed with water there, right? / - Yes.
That's pretty.
It does look pretty on video.
People say it's a pagoda we must see before we die.
(Myanmar, the last gem of Asia)
We have to name our tour.
- Right. The name of our tour. / - What should we do?
Water...
Fire...
Fire, water?
Fire, water? Are we firefighters?
I think Firefighting Tour is okay.
Then let's go with Firefighting Tour.
And one day, we'll do a fire day.
And the other day, we'll do a water day.
How about that?
- I think Firefighting Tour is fitting. / - Let's go with that.
You chose that because of water and fire?
Bboom bboom.
So pretty.
I looked into this. I read in a book.
They tried to disseminate it...
She keeps saying she read about it.
Is that a catchphrase?
Ayoung begins her sentence with
"I read in a book."
The fire day begins at last.
(Fire goddess prepares fire day in Bagan)
That's a hot air balloon.
- I'm really envious of that. / - That's on N's bucket list.
That's beautiful.
(A hot sunrise and a hot dish)
This is the highlight.
It looks so hot.
It's burning up.
I summon the water goddess.
I see the seaweed on her head.
Nose, mouth.
I'm Hasandra.
- Eat some ants. / - Out of the blue?
Oh, no. I seriously don't remember saying that.
I don't remember.
Whether it was a dream or not.
You could be shocked.
(Water goddess, Sojin)
Today is my day.
Sojin's day, it's water day.
So refreshing.
(The highlight of water day)
That looks fun.
- That's how they spray it. / - It's no water gun.
Round 1.
What is this?
I bet you read that in a book.
- They're so good. / - Sojin.
Sojin!
That's amazing.
That's amazing. I never expected so much action.
(Korea to Myanmar)
After you arrive in Yangon,
you have to take a domestic flight to get to Bagan.
(Capital of Pagan Kingdom of Bamar people)
Look at the hot air balloons.
That's something you see in paintings.
It still looks beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
Bagan.
Bagan!
We have to do it ourselves?
We have to take it out from the plane ourselves?
No...
Oh, there are people...
Wow, that's fascinating.
There's no conveyor belt.
The employees take out your bags for you.
Then when your luggage comes out, you just take it.
- I think that's faster. / - Once you see yours...
-  Once you see yours, you have to take it. / - Yes.
(Ayoung successfully snatches away her luggage)
(That's mine)
Thank you.
Where do we need to go first?
We actually have to buy something first.
We must buy a ticket.
- A ticket? / - Yes.
This ticket allows us to get into
every historical site in this city.
25,000 kyats?
This ticket is valid for 5 days!
We need to go to Mani Sithu Market?
- Yes, 5,000 kyats. / - 5,000 kyats?
So you just tell them the destination and get on?
- That's $5. $4 something. / - It's fixed prices there.
Taxis here only have fixed rates, so there's no meter.
You have to agree on a price first.
- They have no meter. / - Right.
(10 minutes to Mani Sithu Market from the airport)
This is Mani Sithu Market.
There's a lot to see even from the entrance.
My gosh, there must be a lot of stuff you can buy.
Sook, you shouldn't go there.
I'm a big spender, I have to buy everything there.
I spend a day at a market like that.
She spends all her paychecks there.
- That looks like our traditional market. / - Yes.
Myanmar old coins?
They don't use coins now.
- They have hexagon coins? / - They only use bills now.
- The coins are so unique. / - Those are old coins.
They sell coins there.
- People buy those for souvenirs. / - Exactly.
- I thought only Korea sold coins. / - So you remember.
We must buy longyi here. Longyi.
- Longyi? / - Yes.
What was that again?
Longyi is like the traditional clothing here.
We have to wear that to enter the temples.
- We can't show bare legs or shoulders. / - Right.
To enter the temple...
- Then what about... / - Longyi is like pants...
What about those people who dress like monks
and show their shoulders?
That's a monk?
So it's okay for monks? I'm curious now.
That's so cute. How cute.
It's her stream of consciousness.
Look how big the pants are.
That is longyi.
I love longyi.
You'd stay cool in those.
- You must wear them to buffets. / - Absolutely.
Pretty, pretty.
A longyi...
Who's that?
That's Suyong.
Oh, the previous episode.
- That's Suyong... / - You wrap it and tie it, right?
It never falls down.
- That one has a string. / - That's got a string.
There are ones like modernized hanbok
with rubber bands and shaped like pants.
Red one.
Which one's prettier?
I like this one.
- Is this prettier? / - The color...
I think Sojin wants the red one.
Her mind's already made up.
I want to wear an embroidered one
since I'm in Southeast Asia.
Why did she ask then?
Why did you ask in the first place?
I'm sorry.
I'll take this one. Oops, I spoke informally.
I'm sorry. No.
So funny.
She looks good in it.
Just putting that on makes you
really feel like you're on a trip.
- Each one costs $3. / - Yes. So cheap.
- We're going to ride an e-bike next. / - Really?
- Will that be okay with you? / - I love it.
- Will this continue? / - I guess so.
Sojin, Sojin!
- Sojin tries so hard. / - Sojin used up all her energy.
(E-bike)
A lot of people are riding bikes, right?
Everyone travels on bikes.
Luckily, the one we'll ride
doesn't require a license.
- Really? Is that it? / - We'll get around with this.
Ta-da. Aren't they pretty?
- That's a scooter. / - It doesn't look like an e-bike.
Right?
If you look, it's vast like a meadow.
There's this thing called an e-bike.
I guess it's an electric bicycle.
An electric bike?
Do you want to each get one?
I love riding scooters.
(Sojin enjoys riding scooters)
I've never ridden a scooter.
But I'm sure this one is easier
than a regular scooter.
It's too big for us to get around on foot.
We can go to places by bike.
We can stop at anywhere we like...
- Take photos, and look around. / - That's scary.
Look at her face.
Read books about bikes now.
(Pull handle to accelerate)
When you pull the handle like this, it'll go forward.
Just like this? Like this? Okay, okay.
- I think I'll be okay. / - Okay.
Ayoung failed the driving test 6 times.
The practical driving test.
Did you not read books on driver tests?
- I got 100% for the written test. / - She's all theory.
She got a perfect score on the written test.
I've never seen anyone do that.
(She's filled with worry)
(Why did I suggest riding this?)
(Sojin leaves as if nothing worries her)
- Hey, wait up! / - Can you catch up?
You can't?
- I'm worried. / - Indeed. I'm worried too.
Ayoung, you have two left feet?
A little. I'm just a little lacking.
This is so much fun.
Ayoung, are you okay back there?
You're following me, right?
(She's in a war with herself)
That doesn't look too fast...
Mommy! Why?
That was about 15km per hour.
I'm so worried.
You could get badly injured.
No, no.
The ground is sandy...
It could be hard.
Ayoung is gone! Ayoung is gone!
Oh, no. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Seriously...
I might die before we get there.
I actually can't control the bike.
No, I think I can do it.
(They head out again to the restaurant)
(They come to the fork in the road)
(This is how very nervous fire goddess turns left)
I have to turn left. I can't use the turn signals.
Oh, no.
I'll turn left.
Argh.
Sorry! Sorry.
(It's okay)
I'm going to turn right.
I'm turning right. Right.
- Turning right. / - Excuse me but who are you talking to?
I couldn't use the turn signals.
She sounds like a GPS.
(Charcoal)
(The fire day will be heated with)
(A fantastic combination of vegetables and meat)
That's so pretty.
It looks delicious.
First time I've heard someone say that meat is pretty.
The arrangement of the colors is so beautiful.
It is beautiful.
Even the sound is pretty.
So this is charcoal.
Can we eat it just like this?
Pineapples.
- Asparagus. / - Carrots.
- Chicken. / - Broccoli.
(Let's see, where's the sauce?)
This is peanut sauce.
- This is fish sauce. / - That sauce looks delicious.
It was so delicious.
- Right? / - Yes!
It looks deliciously mixed.
(My style)
It's quite spicy.
Are they steamed?
- They're grilled. Like on a brazier. / - Grilled?
They steam it first then grill it on there.
It tastes different.
(Sniffing)
Try it.
Soy sauce, soy sauce...
It smells like soy sauce braised chicken.
It was so difficult to explain how it tasted.
Altogether.
The meat looks delicious.
Chicken?
Although it's grilled, it's moist.
It's so delicious.
It tastes similar to chicken skewers, doesn't it?
(What about grilled vegetables and fruits?)
Grilled fruits and vegetables won't make you fat.
Because it's grilled.
- Grilled pineapples are really delicious. / - They were.
That looks good.
I want to carry peanut sauce around.
Everything is delicious when it's dipped in it.
The vegetables and fruits are delicious with the sauce.
I'll dip this in
garlic chili fish sauce which is my favorite.
That sauce was really delicious.
(It's delicious)
(She eats 3 ingredients in a row)
- Chicken? / - Yeah.
Is it okay to eat it all at once?
It's sour, salty and sweet.
It's somehow addictive, isn't it?
This sauce is so delicious.
I think you eat it for this taste.
What is this?
- It's cilantro. / - Isn't it cilantro?
Isn't it cilantro?
(She's curious, therefore she tries it)
You said you like it?
I normally really like cilantro...
This reminds of something I ate in the playground.
- You ate it at a playground? / - You ate grass?
Yes.
- Oh, it's parsley. / - It's parsley.
I munched the whole piece and it shocked me.
Today is the first day I met you.
Parsley.
I normally like spices but that was too strong.
After this, we're going somewhere.
There are thousands of temples in Bagan.
And we'll visit the most beautiful one.
No dessert?
That's bad.
You must be shocked.
- Suji's shocked right now. / - Let's just keep watching.
It must be satisfying to ride there.
Driving and looking around like that makes you feel...
It was really nice.
It's so pretty, isn't it?
There are so many things near us and far away.
Oh, my God. It's like an unknown world.
I can't look around right now.
She looks more comfortable than earlier though.
I want to turn my head and look around too.
I bet it'd be beautiful.
Ayoung, where is our destination?
We have a little more to go.
It looks very fancy.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
- It's Ananda Temple. / - What is this?
- It looks somewhat European. / - It does.
- You're right. / - Right?
It looks European.
(It's 1 of the 1,001 buildings you must see)
(Cave structure makes it look solemn and mysterious)
(Sunshine through the lattice windows creates beauty)
When you enter the temple,
you need to take off your shoes and socks.
You need to dress respectfully too.
In the early days,
there were different zones for prayer.
Because of the caste system.
The third room was for common people.
The second room for nobles and monks.
The first room was for the king.
(Even monks take pictures of this sacred place)
There's a Buddha statue on every side.
North, south, east, west. There are 4 of them.
One of the statues looks very solemn
from where the king prays.
It almost looks angry.
It's telling the king to do a good job.
If you look from the commoners view...
- It looks kind with a look of deep meaning. / - I see.
It's fun to go to historic site with people like her.
Of course.
If you don't know the story, you don't fully appreciate.
- It's no fun. / - Right.
(He looks strict, serious and solemn)
Does he look solemn and angry?
No.
- He's like this. / - Let's go back and check again.
I'm confused.
No way!
- Doesn't he look like he's smiling? / - I spat.
- Right? / - Yeah.
That's unbelievable.
(He looks merciful and is smiling)
His eyes look different.
You're right.
- Isn't it fascinating? / - You're right.
- Isn't it different? / - You're right.
It looks like a different statue.
It's like folding bills as a kid.
And you look from above and below.
You're right.
- That's fascinating. / - That's so fascinating.
It's like he's saying he'll protect us.
- I'm watching you. / - Do a good job.
- That's what it is. / - Do it right.
That's the expression he's making.
- You're right. / - Fascinating.
- This place... / - So pretty!
- It looks like a monastery, right? / - Yes.
Can you take pictures inside the temple?
- Yes, you can. / - Oh, you can?
(The hot sunshine of Bagan is the lighting of nature)
Ayoung, pretend you're a noble. I'll take a picture.
This is the good thing...
- About traveling with girls. / - I'll try.
(Wait a minute)
Excuse me.
- This is the king's zone. / - Yes.
The noble should take a photo of the king first.
Does it have to be that way?
I'm just kidding.
Men never do that.
Think about it. When a man says,
"Hey, you should take a picture of me first."
"Sorry."
We never do that.
(She tries to take her best shots)
It's backlit.
What is this?
- It's backlit. / - That's a shame.
(Ayoung, the noble, goes to meet Sojin, the royal)
(Well?)
Where are we?
- Oh, no. / - She's lost in there?
She's not only a bad driver,
she's directionally challenged too.
- Are you? / - Yes, I am.
- All she does is read books. / - Directional dyslexia.
I'm really lost.
Hang on a second.
Hey, there you are.
How do I get over there?
You can never reach me.
You're already... Not anybody can be a king.
Wait there. I will... I will...
What's the word? Anyway, I'll go to you.
I saw the statue over there.
But the statue is here.
- This is the way. / - What? How did you get here?
We looked at this statue...
And then walked over there and met there, right?
Is this the statue we saw?
Hey, can you stand here for a second?
- I need to check this. / - Okay.
Clearly, Ayoung is the one that's confused.
- I'm still confused. / - You're going again?
You were supposed to be there.
Hold on. Stop lying.
Ayoung, look at the face of Buddha.
- It does look exactly the same. / - Right?
(Surprise!)
She almost hit me.
That was a very natural hand movement.
You...
You need to self-reflect.
- Just watch it on the broadcast. / - No...
I'm serious.
(What is this mystery of Ananda Temple?)
Hey, can you stand here for a second?
- I need to check this. / - Okay.
(When Ayoung went to check the directions)
(Glancing)
(She runs at full speed)
I'll stand exactly as I did before.
- Sojin tricked her. / - I see.
- See? / - You were supposed to be there.
Hold on. Stop lying.
Ayoung, look at the face of Buddha.
(Forget the face, I need to check this)
Sojin fooled her good.
- You were here the whole time, right? / - I was here.
- You were here, right? / - Yeah.
Look at the Buddha's face.
We were standing here before.
I'm so confused right now.
So which way do we have to exit?
Are you asking me that?
Hello,
this is Sojin GPS.
Please drive safely as always.
Yes, this is what I saw.
Hey, this is so amazing.
Hey, I read this in the book.
This is the most symmetric building.
Even the color is beautiful.
I want to climb up there.
You have to go barefoot outside too.
- You have to be barefoot outdoors? / - Yes.
We have to show our respect.
If you climb up here...
- That's so pretty. / - That's such a great photo.
How about we look for a spot with this view?
That's what I thought.
- We could look on our bikes. / - Yeah, let's go.
- Is this it? / - Here.
- It's so easy to get around there. / - We're here.
Yes, it was so convenient.
So hot.
(This is the real lime juice)
Lime juice?
Electric.
A glass of that when you're hot and you're good to go.
Can we get one original
and one mint?
(She casts a magic spell to quicken their order)
- Hi. / - This is the lime juice, miss.
- With mint? / - Yes, with mint.
How much was that?
1,900 kyats. So around $1.50?
Great price.
Lime is the best to quench your thirst.
Fresh fruit juices in Myanmar are really good.
We had the lime juice because the country
was best known for it and we couldn't stop.
Hot countries have tasty fruits.
Try this.
This is so cool.
(This is delicious)
The original one tastes just like lime.
The scent of the lime is great.
I just thought limes are sour
but it has a scent.
I don't normally like sour drinks.
But it's not overpoweringly sour.
I feel like I'm taking in a month's worth of vitamins.
My gosh, this is so cool.
(How does the lime juice with mint taste?)
(It seems she drinks to live)
Is someone chasing you?
I love this.
Doesn't the one with mint taste like a mojito?
It does, but after some time passes,
the scent of the mint makes its way back in my body.
If I had to recommend just one drink...
Mint.
Me too. Mint.
- Right? That one is better. / - Lime with mint.
The fragrance of the herb is stronger than usual.
It sort of puts you in a good mood.
I bet it feels like you brushed your teeth after that.
- You'd feel refreshed. / - Should we ask them?
Ask what?
If there's a temple we can climb.
(He's the target)
Excuse me, we want to take these kinds of pictures
on top of the pagoda.
After the earthquake... The temples you can climb up...
After the earthquake, you can't.
Because it's very dangerous.
You know the last 2 years?
Last 2016, again, earthquake.
One of the temples,
you can climb up.
But it is very hard to find.
In the middle.
Around here.
Like about around here?
Yes, around here.
Could you take us? We'll follow you.
Yes.
- Okay? / - Okay, yes. Perfect.
He said yes so easily.
He's saying yes to everything.
Thank you, thank you.
Let's go after we finish the drinks.
Most of the people in Myanmar are really nice.
I heard they're really kind.
They're so nice.
I met one on this show with foreigners.
- The person on the show was nice. / - Really?
It's a Buddhist country, and they're really nice.
They're nice to foreigners.
Let's get going.
There are a lot of temples here.
(Firefighting Tour cuts through the forest in Bagan)
(She's happy with the thought of taking photos)
Go faster!
Don't you think you're going too fast?
Please!
My gosh.
Hey, this looks like the countryside.
It must be hard to find this one.
(At the end of the trail, a temple comes into view)
There's a woman. A woman.
Where is she?
- She's on the left. It's a woman. / - Yes, I see her.
- That's the place. / - Photo zone!
Amazing.
I think you can't come here unless you know.
You can't find this place on your own.
- There are too many temples. / - Right.
This temple doesn't have a name.
It means people don't know about it.
- Then there aren't any signs? / - There's none.
- Do you have to go barefoot there too? / - Yes.
Goodness.
(Surprised)
Seeing it from the ground and seeing it from the top...
- Is completely different. / - It's not the same at all.
I don't believe it.
It's so picturesque.
There are over 3,000 temples.
There are no supermarkets in between.
It's just all temples.
- So pretty. / - Unbelievable.
But why are there so many temples in Bagan?
The king of the Bagan Kingdom
was a devout Buddhist.
In order to popularize Buddhism,
he built these temples.
To popularize his faith?
He wanted to spread Buddhism.
That's how it became the most practiced religion.
There are no residential areas
between the temples at all.
Not at all.
- There's the photo of a lifetime. / - So pretty.
Did you get one?
- So pretty. / - Yes, we got our photos.
You did.
See that? The cylindrical building?
- The high one? / - Yes.
There's a famous infinity pool there.
We'll enjoy the pool as we watch the sunset.
Amazing.
What a pretty picture.
- Is that your hotel? / - Yes.
It looks so great from above.
Whenever this song plays, something weird happens.
She looks like a game character.
(The water goddess that defeats the hot weather)
That's confidence.
This is amazing.
- Isn't it pretty? / - I'm so jealous.
- It's so nice here. / - So pretty.
Hotels with those kind of view costs a lot.
That hotel was only $100 something.
Hey, wait. This is way deeper than I thought.
It's very deep.
- You can't even swim? / - No. How did you know?
Just all books...
You need to grab the ledge.
(Holding the ledge and enjoying the view of the temple)
(They come face to face with Bagan's hot sunset)
- The sunset is beautiful. / - Isn't it beautiful?
It's so pretty.
You can watch the sunset from there.
That's so beautiful.
- It's so beautiful. / - It was the perfect time.
It feels like a garden.
I really do feel like I'm in an unknown world.
So pretty.
Seeing the temple in the water...
I like going to places
but spending time like this is also great.
You can see the sunset to end the day.
It was so hot today.
But this nice swimming pool is the perfect finish.
This place is so nice.
I really want to go there.
- The night view was also amazing. / - $100 is...
So affordable.
I just want to stay there for 3 days.
What was the most fun for you?
- For today? / - Yes.
I really liked riding bikes.
If it wasn't for that,
I wouldn't have enjoyed the temple tour.
You said you didn't like looking at temples.
I think it would have been boring for me.
But it wasn't because we rode the bikes.
It felt really exciting.
I really liked going to the top.
It was like a secret garden.
We saw the sunset today.
We're going to see the sunrise tomorrow.
Really?
We're going to see all of Bagan
from in the sky.
Okay.
- From the sky? / - Yes, from the sky.
Firefighting tour, bboom bboom.
- It's so nice. / - It's really nice.
It's amazing.
There aren't a lot of Korean tourists, right?
I don't think I saw any.
There were a lot of Europeans.
Europeans like things like this.
People don't go to Myanmar a lot.
Who would have gone to Bagan?
4 a.m.?
Why did you wake up so early?
We had to start early
because this was the highlight.
How do you feel?
- Starlings are chirping. / - Are you still not awake?
Isn't this too much?
But we really have to see this.
This is the highlight of the fire day.
Hot air balloon?
This is it.
- Hot air balloon? / - So you have to go early?
I thought they were going to see the sunrise.
We went there early to see the sunrise.
- Sunrise on a hot air balloon? / - Wow, amazing.
They picked us up from the hotel.
A bus comes to pick you up.
- It's so pretty. / - It's interesting.
We're leaving.
I don't usually exaggerate but this is really worth it.
I searched for photos. It's really pretty.
Temples look really beautiful at night.
It feels different looking at them in dark.
I've never been on a hot air balloon before.
- You haven't? / - No.
I have really severe acrophobia.
Why does it feel like I've been on one before?
I'm not sure if I've been on one or not.
I don't remember whether it was a dream or not.
I feel like I've been on one.
It's not easy to experience a hot air balloon.
- The weather has to be nice. / - That's right.
- It can't be too windy. / - That's right.
This isn't the balloon, is it?
I think it is.
- That must be it. / - Oh, my.
They rise all at once.
A few dozen hot air balloons...
That's why it's so pretty in the photos.
Because there are many balloons.
You have to lie down?
Does it really land like that?
Wow! Amazing.
When I first saw the photos...
- That's really big. / - They were huge.
I didn't know it would be that big.
- You're right. / - Look at this.
(It's slowly preparing to fly to the sky)
How many are there? There are so many.
This is so exciting. They're so pretty.
They're all standing up.
This is unbelievable.
(Dancing from excitement)
- She's full of excitement. / - She's still half asleep.
That's the most excited she's been on this trip.
I was too excited.
We, we, we...
(Running furiously)
They aren't tired anymore.
Of course. This is on...
- Many people's bucket lists. / - Right.
(Boarding complete)
Do they have a weight limit?
They did check our weights.
Because there's a limit to the number of people.
Is that a problem?
I'll have to check.
(They got on bravely but they're actually scared)
Sorry, folks. You'll have to get used to that.
I was so...
(Continuous blast)
- Are you there with tourists? / - Yes.
I see.
People who were on the same bus go on the same balloon.
Thank you.
(The hot air balloon leaves)
It's rising.
Isn't it so pretty?
I'm really going to try this in Myanmar.
Even the bus is adorable.
It rises quickly.
I thought that was a sunset but it was the morning.
It's the morning.
It's going up so high.
It goes up really high.
Wasn't it scary?
- Slightly. / - You could greet airplanes.
I'm so happy.
- The wind is refreshing. / - This is so moving.
You'd actually cry if you're up there.
When else could you see such a view?
- There are so many temples. / - It's so pretty.
The air balloons are pretty.
I'm so happy.
This is so great.
- N, you should go there. / - I really want to.
Look. Isn't that so pretty?
There isn't a set course.
The wind conditions of the day
determine where you go.
- Look down there... / - So it's new every day.
I thought she was still because she was moved.
But she was scared.
Actually, I have severe acrophobia)
Really?
But since I can't tell how high I'm up on a balloon...
(It's such a realistic height)
I'm scared.
You just need to look straight ahead.
- I can't look. / - You don't look well.
Wait a minute.
Everything looks so adorable while looking down.
Sojin is really fearless.
I couldn't feel the distance, so I wasn't scared.
- You regret coming up here, don't you? / - No.
- Look down. It's like a picture. / - No. It's okay.
We do this when we really can't stand something.
In that low tone.
Look behind.
She looks so unhappy.
That's so funny.
She looked with her philtrum.
It's really pretty.
- It really is. / - It's really amazing.
- I want to go there this year. / - It's quite big.
- Me too. / - I could do it even if I'm scared.
(Even if your burning heart bursts)
The sun is rising on the other side.
You can see temples on this side.
You can do it even if you're acrophobic.
(Let's get soaked in the sunlight)
It's so beautiful.
I was scared because I was acrophobic
but I would've regretted it if I didn't try this.
I really would've regretted it if I didn't do this.
(The greeting of the innocent people warms your heart)
I'm so happy.
It's like a dream.
- She's crying. / - I was so happy.
You cry when you see a really beautiful sight.
I had such a strange feeling.
I know.
You cry when you see beauty.
Where would we be able to see historic sites
on a hot air balloon?
I think you can only do this in Bagan, Myanmar.
In my opinion...
Myanmar is the best among Southeast Asian trips.
- You're right. / - It's very charming.
Thank you.
- What is that? / - I'm about to cry.
Is this included in the $30?
Yes. It's unlimited.
- What? / - You can drink an unlimited amount.
- It can't be unlimited. / - It's unlimited.
I mean it.
- Suji. / - Yes?
I'm about to cry just seeing that.
- What? / - Because of the unlimited food.
She didn't feel anything while they were in the sky.
(Wasn't it worth coming here in the morning?)
Thank you for enjoying it.
Thank you for bringing me here. Thank you.
Cheers.
Thank you.
(The fire day has come to an end)
- You came back to Yangon from Bagan, right? / - Yes.
- We came back to Yangon. / - On the plane back.
It's burning up.
I'm watching you.
Look forward to it.
(Water goddess is summoned)
It's my day. It's Sojin's day from today.
It's water day.
I invite you to the world of water.
You're all dead!
(The Thingyan Festival)
Expect a lot.
It's the day of water.
I really want to try those noodles.
Oh, my.
It's so cool.
We'll start the water day of the Firefighting Tour.
Bboom bboom!
Now I'm attacking.
We haven't seen this before.
(Flailing)
There's just something weird.
She looks somewhat awkward, yet she's having fun.
- She's offbeat. / - She's having fun.
It's like walking like this.
That's right.
You should've done this.
(Kandawgyi Lake)
Today is my day. Sojin's day.
It's day of water.
We're going to start off at this lake.
This lake is called Kandawgyi Lake.
"Kan" means lake in the local language.
- Where is that? / - Kandawgyi.
Did such a place exist?
- It does look like a city here. / - Yes.
It's like a city, right?
(Kandawgyi Lake is a popular dating spot)
I think they went to that lake.
- Really? / - Kim Suyong and Park Hwisun.
I don't have any recollection of it.
By the way, it's too hot.
- It's so hot. / - Isn't your day over yet?
It's fire here. There's a golden tower.
Oh, that. It's called Shwedagon Pagoda.
It's the landmark of the city.
- Really? / - Yes.
Everybody who visits Myanmar visits it.
- I think I saw a photo. / - It was on Battle Trip.
Right.
Why is it so different to when Suyong went there?
Is it really the same place Hwisun went?
Anyway, I was thinking of taking a train.
- We need to take a train? / - Yes.
Just like Line 2 on the Seoul metro,
there's a train that goes around Yangon.
- It's 16 cents. / - It's a circulating train.
It's so cheap.
The train ticket is 16 cents?
Yes.
- It's like Line 2. / - Among the foods related to water...
There's food that I really wanted to eat
when I came to Myanmar.
You have to eat noodles in Southeast Asia.
- Look forward to it. / - Alright.
- Let's go. / - My first time on a train in Myanmar.
Me too. Let's go.
(Kandawgyi Lake)
(Puzundaung Station)
(17-minute walk)
- Right. / - It's such an old train.
You learned how to read the letters, right?
No, I don't know the letters.
I just memorized the name of the place we're going.
Is it written in English as well or
is it only written in Burmese?
It's only written in Burmese.
Can they speak English though?
Yes, they can.
It doesn't matter where you're going.
1 ticket costs 200 kyats.
And you can go anywhere you want with the ticket.
So both you and I can travel for 40 cents.
It's so cheap.
Excuse me.
Two tickets please.
Pardon?
Not everyone speaks English.
Don't they speak English well?
Not as well as you think. Some are really good.
Most speak Burmese.
- Two tickets please. / - That's why you spoke in Korean?
Yes, so long as he understood.
60 cents.
- Bye. / - I think the train is coming.
No.
We can't miss this, right?
No, no.
Wait a minute.
- Oh, no! / - You were wasting time...
Without realizing.
Can we get on this?
Is this right?
Just carry this on?
After she made up her mind...
He told them to just get on.
It's like they're in Korea.
Don't they have to check our tickets?
Did they all give their tickets?
Maybe they don't check.
- Just in case... / - I'll hold on to it.
This train is so interesting.
There are no windows.
Goodness.
- It feels dangerous. / - You can get off.
There's no door either.
There's no door.
It'd be cool to stand out there.
You know where to get off, right?
- I know where, but... / - Don't make us worry.
Will they announce it? I can't read...
Let's see where we get off.
There was no announcement.
- So restless. / - You'd be so nervous.
Excuse me.
We're going to Central?
Central?
Central? Central?
Central Station.
She won't even look at you.
She's so cute.
- Central Station? / - Yes.
(She looks at her desperately)
I watched a fun TV show she was on.
Through that show, I realized she was very smart.
I heard she could speak different languages.
I can rely on her for communication issues.
Recently, I visited Boston, where I used to live.
- You used to live in Boston? / - Yes.
That's interesting.
(How good is her English?)
(Slurping?)
(Do you know the noodles restaurant?)
(Ayoung)
Look at her.
What are you doing?
I wanted to say we were going to eat noodles.
(She patiently explains)
Shan noodles? Do you know Shan noodle?
(They have great teamwork)
Shan noodles? You don't know?
(She's indeed a master of communication)
What happens if we miss our stop?
If we miss it? Then we take another train going back.
We can ride the train as much as we want.
- It's great, isn't it? / - No.
I think it's here.
It's here. I think it's here.
It think this is the station.
I was right.
- You found the station? / - Yes.
She just guessed.
Is this restaurant famous?
It's very famous.
It's popular among the locals.
If it's popular among the locals then it's really good.
Right.
Why is it called Shan noodles?
Shan people are the second biggest population here.
- Shan people? / - Yes.
This is the noodles Shan people eat often.
Is this it?
Doesn't the menu look like that of a good restaurant?
This place must be a good restaurant.
It's so crowded although it's so hot today.
This place is more popular among the locals.
There's one with soup and one without.
It looks delicious already.
- Let's order one each. / - It was so good.
- It's good. / - It is?
It's already good.
That was $1.60.
$1.60?
- Suji. / - Yes?
What do you think?
If it's $1.60, I could eat 1,600 bowls.
That's the good thing about traveling with your friend.
You can order two different dishes and share.
Chicken.
- Chicken. / - Chicken.
Chicken and pork for this one.
(Special sauce is added together with the meat sauce)
(Sticky Shan noodles salad complete)
(With well-cooked broth poured in it)
(Sticky Shan noodles complete)
It's ready.
I think our dishes are ready.
Okay.
- Ah, salad. / - Thank you.
There are many different ethnicities in Myanmar.
The biggest population is Burmese.
The second biggest is Shan.
- It looks so delicious. / - It's their staple food.
It looks so delicious.
$1.60 is so cheap.
It's a bit different from the rice noodles I imagined.
That's the mixed.
- It's like mixed noodles. / - Is it good, Sikyung?
- It's tasty right now. / - It's tasty no matter what?
It's tasty right now.
Ayoung, is it spicy?
- It's not spicy. / - It's a little spicy.
It has all kinds of flavor in it.
It's so sticky.
- It's like sticky rice. / - The noodles look very sticky.
- It was really sticky. / - Right?
I can feel the stickiness from the video.
Want to try watermelon juice?
Do you like it?
It's fried noodles that's like five spiced sauce
and black bean noodles.
- Mapo tofu. / - Yes, yes!
It's delicious.
Yes.
- No artificial spices. / - I get it.
It's a taste we've had.
I'd love to try that.
The noodles are
as chewy as hand-pulled noodles.
It's extremely chewy.
- It's a small serving. / - It's called sticky noodles.
It must be chewy and sticky.
It's made of sticky rice, so it's very filling.
If you take rice cake and really flatten it out,
I think it'd have this texture.
- Let's try the broth. / - Try it.
You need two bowls of this.
(Expectant)
Why do I taste bean paste from all the dishes here?
I think it tastes similar to bean paste noodles.
- Do you taste the bean paste? / - Yes.
- I'm not strange, right? / - I get the feeling now.
It tastes like bean paste noodles.
Like bean paste noodles.
Bean paste rice soup.
It's like rice soup.
This must be pork broth.
(Ayoung wonders what the sauces on the table are)
You know, we add sauces in rice soup in Korea.
- Can I add a little bit of it? / - Yes please.
- Can I? / - I love this sauce.
Let's mix it well. It might be spicier than we think.
It tastes similar to pork soup rice.
I love this.
This one looks more delicious.
There are different sauces you can add...
- To your liking. / - How is it?
(So happy)
It's sweet and spicy.
It's not what I expected.
It's better with the sauce.
If you like spicy food, you'll find this delicious.
It has a fiery taste.
- It's like chili oil. / - Oh, that's what it is.
- The aftertaste. / - It taste fiery.
Can I crush this and add it?
What's that?
It's like deep fried pork skin.
- With noodles... / - That's in the Philippines.
- Please save me. / - Why not?
Let's add it.
Try it. It's tasty.
Excuse me.
(Making a fuss)
Please give me a small bowl.
- Let's eat. / - Thank you.
It's good.
- You added it, didn't you? / - No, I didn't.
- You did. / - I didn't.
The soup tastes different.
No way.
It must've gone in when the bag exploded.
Why can't you tell me precisely?
The pressure inside the bag was high.
Some went in when it exploded.
I think it'd taste better with it.
Please give me a small bowl.
Personal dish.
(So much)
- You look calm. / - You're so quick.
You're so quick when you're doing that.
How does it taste?
(This isn't the taste I know)
The original taste is gone.
Is this revenge for the temple?
The meat stock taste is gone.
(Screaming)
- No! / - It looks better.
- Are you sure? / - I'll try it.
(Ayoung tastes it first to put Sojin at ease)
Hey, wait a minute.
Is it like crispy batter?
It has a crunchy texture.
This one's good.
(Ayoung is nervous)
(She agrees this time)
Was that okay?
Yes, that was tasty.
You can think of it as frying powder
like the one you put in udon.
Sprinkling the crispy pork powder was a great choice.
It was like eating spicy pork rice soup on a hot day.
It was savory. I really liked it.
That looks delicious.
Their noodles are great.
- I should try both noodles. / - Of course.
- The mixed and soup. / - Definitely.
Myanmar has traditional tea called lahpet.
It's water day.
Why do you keep suggesting hot things?
On this hot day.
- But the locals... / - Like hot soup.
Spicy food. Hot tea.
Why are you doing this?
It's the water festival tomorrow anyway.
So we're getting ready for that.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
2,000 kyats. 2,000 kyats.
2,000, 2,000, 2,000, 2,500.
What?
No.
This one is 300.
This wasn't free.
So this one costs 300 kyats each.
I thought it was free because it was on the table.
You can mistake it for free.
- Still it's less than $10. / - Right.
Left hand, left hand.
- That's really weird. / - Left hand.
Right hand, right foot.
I was wondering what was weird.
She used the same side.
(Lahpet)
Where should we go?
- It's near 28th street. / - 28th street?
- It's frustrating since you can't read. / - 28th street.
You have to look for the numbers.
- This is it. This is 28th street. / - We're here.
We're here. We're here.
- Where is it? / - This is it. This yellow sign.
- Is this it? / - Yes, it is.
- This is it. This is it. / - You're right.
We're here!
This is fun.
- Going to a tea house to drink tea... / - Yes.
- In a foreign place. / - Yes.
(Lahpet)
(Famous tea house located in the 28th street)
(Traditional tea of Myanmar, similar to milk tea)
- It's traditional tea. / - Is it like milk tea?
It looks like milk tea.
- Let's try lahpet. / - Lahpet.
Can we get the menu please?
- You're virtually... / - Is this Myeong-dong?
There is no lahpet.
It's all food.
Look. Tea.
Special tea.
Coffee mix.
(Are we in a wrong place?)
There is no lahpet.
(Puzzled)
Lahpet is...
Everyone is drinking it.
It looks like that.
It looks like it's with milk.
(Even the table next to them is drinking it)
Excuse me.
We're looking for lahpet.
- Is this lahpet? / - Yeah, yeah.
Where is lahpet?
(A nice Myanmar man points to the menu)
Thank you.
Lahpet has four kinds of tea.
- Four tastes? / - Yes.
- He's so kind. / - He is.
- Normal. / - Very sweet. Not sweet.
- Bitter. / - Bitter?
How much is it?
1 for 400.
So 4 cups is 1,600.
30 cents?
Just order all four.
That's what we did.
Good job.
Yeah, you need all four.
- The colors are different. / - They taste different.
(Normal, very sweet, not sweet, bitter)
- The bitter one is the darkest. / - They're different.
They said it tastes like black tea.
It's milk tea.
It's just like milk tea.
(Lahpet tastes similar to milk tea)
- Is it tea mixed with milk? / - Yes.
- It's milk and condensed milk. / - Condensed milk.
Is it cold or hot?
- It's hot. / - I see.
Wait, so this is the very sweet one.
This must be really sweet.
Because normal is just right.
(Wide eyes)
Drink it.
- This is my taste. / - The cup is so cute.
(She compares the normal tea and the sweet tea)
It's not sugar. I can taste condensed milk.
- Condensed milk. / - That's right.
It's good. It's good.
You need sweet food in a hot country.
- You're right. That gives you energy. / - Yes.
- Your eyes light up. / - Right.
This is not sweet.
If it's not sweet, will it be bitter?
Oh...
- It's good. / - Is it?
- It's like soy milk. / - It's savory.
It was delicious.
It's just with milk. It has a clean taste.
This is the bitter one.
I don't think it's that bitter.
It's not bitter.
These ones had a smooth aftertaste.
But this one is different.
(Sojin takes a sip)
Right?
Isn't it good?
(I feel happy)
This is what I like.
It has a strong black tea flavor.
It's slightly sweet with not much milk.
The other ones taste like they used regular tea.
But this one taste like they roasted the tea once more.
Which one do you like?
I like the taste of condensed milk.
- The very sweet one? / - I should take normal.
- That's the safest. / - Yes, to be safe.
I want sweet. The very sweet one.
Me too.
Because the weather is hot, when you feel tired...
Eating something sweet...
- Energizes you. / - You're recharged.
Especially if it's something hot...
it'll warm you up from inside.
In the very sweet one,
they put condensed milk instead of sugar.
It's black tea with milk.
It's yummy.
This suits my taste perfectly.
- Tomorrow is the Thingyan Festival. / - Yes.
I think it'll be fun to get water guns.
I don't have a water gun.
There is a market near here.
We can buy it there.
The New Year in Myanmar starts now.
It's holiday season.
- Restaurants will be closed. / - Really?
Yes. Everything will be closed.
Should we ask how people spend the day?
- You mean, during the festival? / - Yes.
Should we?
(The nice guy who helped them earlier)
- This... Thank you. / - Okay.
- How? / - What?
Bucket?
We use the guns. Water guns.
Water gun.
We're going to buy water guns.
Water guns aren't sold at Bogyoke Aung San Market.
(Bogyoke Aung San Market mostly sells jewelry)
They sell jewelry?
Where can we get water guns?
You can buy water guns at the 18th street or 19th street.
- 18 and 19? / - 18 and 19. Yes.
Okay. Okay.
You can buy a water gun you like there.
- And I'll buy one if there's anything I like. / - Okay.
Bring a big one.
(I'm going to get you)
Don't regret it if I should bring a sprinkler truck.
Go buy some water guns.
I'll go buy some pockets to keep our phones...
- Waterproof pack?  / - So they won't get wet.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Have a nice time.
Welcome to the real world of water.
(The original water festival of Myanmar)
(A water festival that everyone enjoys!)
You're all dead.
(Water to wash away the heat)
(A refreshing party time)
I'm going in now.
Look forward to it.
It was so fun.
- It was really fun. / - It really was.
- They have such different characters. / - Yeah.
When you go to Bagan, can you only go by plane?
You can take a bus or a train,
but it takes more than 8 hours.
Just go by plane.
You'd be driving on unpaved roads.
Yes. It'll be very hard.
An airplane is better.
Are there many flights to Bagan?
There's a flight every hour.
The flight leaves from Yangon,
so it departs on time.
But as I said...
- It stops by at many places... / - On the way back?
So it might be delayed on your way back.
It was actually amazing.
It's not over when the plane landed.
It just keeps taking off and landing.
- Is that right? / - Yes, like a bus stop.
Like an express bus.
- So the plane is rather small? / - A light aircraft?
Yes, it's a light aircraft.
I'm glad that it's not a parachute.
You may get off now.
So you wanted to go up the temple,
but you couldn't.
There's a big temple where you can see the sunrise.
- Right. / - We can't go up there either?
You can't anymore.
It used to be open before.
There was a temple called Shwesandaw Pagoda.
It's one of the highest temples in Bagan.
A lot of people went up there
to enjoy sunset and sunrise and take pictures.
But it's under restoration work now.
There was an earthquake. There are safety issues.
You can't get up there now. But once it's restored...
- I believe you'll be able to... / - I guess so.
- That's our hope. / - Alright.
It's time to cast a vote then.
Even the production staff said
this place is worth visiting.
Right, right.
Because it's a new tourist attraction,
I think it makes your trip more special.
Please say some final words before the vote.
It hasn't been so long since Myanmar opened up.
So the old is well preserved in the country.
When you travel to Southeast Asian countries,
you usually think about swimming pools.
So I'd like to recommend the
new attractions of Myanmar.
That's nice.
Will you go to Myanmar according to
Firefighting Tour's itinerary? Please vote.
(Sojin and Ayoung designed a trip to Myanmar)
(What will the judges choose?)
The two women went on a trip to Myanmar.
Then how would the two men's trip to Thailand be?
Please look forward to our next episode.
Thank you.
(Next week)
Just relax and enjoy.
- It's magnificent, right? / - Wow.
That looks so scary.
This is amazing.
So pretty.
It's like a house from my childhood dreams.
- It's like a fairy tale. / - It's like my own hideout.
We can't find an open space like this in Seoul.
Make the trip enjoyable.
This is so nice.
(Returning to the innocence of childhood)
(Excited vs. Relaxed)
It'll be fun. You can look forward to it.
I'm already satisfied.
5, 6, 7, 8.
Hakyeon, Hongbin, do it, do it, yeah!
(Battle Trip)
("Love,ing" by Ben)