- Let's go. / - Let's go, let's go.
(Play Day, Rest Day)
Amazing.
It's good.
Jin...
It's not over yet.
(Wan Jun Tour never stops)
Saved in my heart.
I can't believe I'm seeing such a sight in Jeju-do.
Check out the waves.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Jun Jin and Kim Dongwan of SHINHWA)
(JR and Baekho of NU'EST W)
(Special host, Dayoung of WJSN)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip.
Continuing from last week...
The 2018 newest edition of Jeju-do.
We have two teams of trip planners here.
- Welcome back. / - Nice to see you again.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
(100 judges in the audience)
A lot of them voted for our team last week.
I'd like to thank them again.
Dayoung is...
- From Chujado. / - That's right.
- She knows a lot about Jeju-do. / - Yes, I do.
What if you're the one to go to Jeju-do?
- Yes. / - How would you plan your trip?
To be honest,
a lot of people know about Jeju-do,
but most of them don't know about Chujado.
- I've heard of the name though. / - Yes.
It's a good place for fishing.
Is there a good place to go in Chujado?
- In Chujado... / - Yes.
- There's Navarone Cliff. / - Navarone Cliff?
Yes, it's called Navarone Cliff.
It's so cool.
After 40 minutes to an hour of trekking...
- You can enjoy the great views. / - It sounds cool.
It's really beautiful.
Jeju-do is good,
but the nearby islands are also beautiful.
Udo is amazing.
- Right. / - And Gapado is also great.
Gapado is good
in April and May.
You should call us again for the next special.
- For the islands? / - Island tour.
- I'd love that. / - It sounds so fun.
We watched Wan Jun Tour's trip last week.
- And it actually rained a lot. / - Right.
Despite the weather condition...
- They had a great trip. / - It was really good.
They're not my team, but the trip was amazing.
- I was envious. / - Do you accept the defeat?
Do you accept the defeat?
- No. / - It will be determined by a vote.
I think Baekho Tour is a little dejected now.
- That's not true. / - Baekho.
How was the weather during your trip?
Actually,
we bring rain clouds with us.
- Some people do that. / - That's not good.
And we went to Jeju-do on the same day.
- That's right. / - So...
We were in a different place in the same weather.
So it was cloudy one day and sunny the next day?
The weather wasn't so good for the two days.
It wasn't quite sunny.
We will show them we can still win though.
- Right, it was good though. / - Alright.
You are the Aewol Prince.
You shouldn't be like this.
- That sounds strange. / - Aewol Prince.
He's the Aewol Prince. He's an expert in Jeju-do.
Can you tell us some general knowledge?
- We're curious about it. / - Yes.
- Aewol Prince. / - Alright.
There are two kinds of dol hareubang.
- What? / - Huh?
- Really? / - If you look at it carefully...
One hand is placed higher than the other.
Some have their left hands higher.
- And others, their right hand. / - I didn't know that.
Are they left-handed and right-handed?
Which one is genuine?
- They both are genuine. / - Oh, really?
The one with its right hand on top is...
The right hand is for holding the brush when you write.
So they are a civil servant and military officer.
The one with the right hand on top
is a civil servant.
And the one with the left hand on top
is a military officer?
People say you will have a son
if you touch the nose of dol hareubang.
If you want to have a smart son,
you should touch the nose of one...
- A civil servant. / - With the right hand on top.
What about your mother?
Which one did she touch?
My mom...
I guess she touched...
- The left-handed one. / - I think he's right.
Is there one with both hands on top?
That's a fake.
Really?
That's a fake one?
There's no such thing.
This is a fake, everyone.
It should have only one hand on top.
He's so good.
He knows something that we didn't know.
- I feel ashamed. / - I'm relieved now.
- By the way... / - Is that true?
It was JR's first time in Jeju-do?
- Was it your first trip? / - Well...
I've gone abroad
for TV shows and concerts before.
But it was my first time going somewhere for a trip.
I think he's a homebody.
- Right, I like to stay at home... / - Am I right?
Playing video games.
- He likes to play games. / - I rarely go out.
And I didn't like to travel.
That's new. Dongwan didn't like boiled chicken.
And you don't even like traveling.
But...
Baekho planned such a fun trip.
I really enjoyed my first trip.
Are you going to start traveling now?
If I have a chance to go on a trip,
I'll take a trip planner with me.
- You need someone to guide you. / - You two can go.
And I'll go with Baekho.
Didn't you design one day each?
No, for us...
- I planned it all. / - It's Baekho Tour.
Since it's Baekho Tour.
- That's interesting. / - Let's begin then.
Is there anything we should focus on?
On the first day...
We went to the western part, where Baekho grew up.
We went to Aewol.
We had a lot of fun playing in the water there.
Dongwan had fun playing in the water last week.
Didn't you take off your shirt to play in the water?
(Dongwan took off his shirt last week)
(He dove into the water for perpetual youth)
Did you not take it off?
No, we didn't.
I regret it now.
That's what we want to see.
On the second day,
we traveled around the eastern part of Jeju City,
which is really popular these days.
For that area, I had to look up information.
- So I didn't know much about it... / - Yes.
But we had a lot of fun.
Did anything like this happen?
Didn't you run into one of your friends during the trip?
- You could come across one. / - It's your hometown.
Baekho!
What's the dialect?
(Teasing him)
When did you come?
- Gosh. / - I'm good, right?
I don't think so.
He's objective.
Baekho is objective.
Can you talk with Dayoung in Jeju-do dialect?
- Can you do that? / - Oh, right.
Have a talk with her.
- Did you eat? / - Yes.
- What did you eat? / - I...
I had a box lunch.
Really? Was it good?
- Yes. / - Let's eat together next time.
- They're so good. / - Good.
Dayoung is really good.
But Baekho seemed flustered.
He's sweating a lot.
That's because I lived in Jeju-do for a long time
and I'm younger than him.
Alright then.
So thoughtful.
- Why are you sweating? / - So thoughtful.
He sweats whenever he talks.
Alright. Let's begin then.
- We can win. / - Right.
- Can we win? / - Yes, we can.
Let's start by shouting the team name.
- You know it, right? / - Yes.
- You will sweat again. / - Are you ready?
- Open. / - And straightforward.
- Baekho Tour. / - Baekho Tour.
Let's watch.
(They're one of the hottest idol groups)
It's NU'EST W.
(JR and Baekho of NU'EST W)
(They feel excited from the beginning)
(First trip)
(First activity)
(First food)
I want to eat it again.
(He shows his whimsical charm)
This is my first trip.
(A complete trip novice, JR)
- Wait. / - So young.
- So sweet. / - Please calm down a little.
(He's from Aewol, Jeju-do)
I was born here and grew up here.
I know this place well.
What's that?
- Prince. / - He does look like a prince.
There are no thieves here.
Stonewall making is an actual job.
That number there... That's the regional number.
(He's not shy)
It's stuck.
They did lipstick challenge.
The nickname suits him well.
Aewol Prince.
Planned by Baekho.
It's Baekho Tour.
(Jeju City, Seogwipo City)
(The best drive along the coastal road of Aewol)
It's here.
It looks delicious.
What's that?
(The new trendy taste of Jeju-do)
SHINHWA ate instant noodles and kimchi stew.
It's on another level.
We're not going to lose.
(The taste of Jeju-do makes him take a bow)
It'll be more fun.
(New activities)
What's that?
What?
What's this?
Baekho.
Tour.
(Baekho Tour's trip to Jeju-do begins now)
- Wait a minute. / - The judges are too biased.
Why don't we take the vote first?
The audience seems excited now.
(Jeju International Airport)
- It's Jeju-do. / - Jeju-do.
- Since we're on a trip... / - Yes.
- We're dressed differently today. / - Yes, we are.
What's the first thing that is different today?
- T-shirt. / - T-shirt.
T-shirt. Check out the back of my T-shirt.
(They prepared a matching T-shirt for the tour)
- It's a white tiger. / - That's the T-shirt.
- Did you draw it yourself? / - Yes, I drew it myself.
- Is that your dorm? / - Yes, it's our dorm.
(He designs the T-shirt, kneeling down)
(A tiger with a human nose)
- He draws well. / - It's finished.
- Something like this. / - And...
He draws really well. Did you study art in college?
Now, let's begin the tour Baekho planned.
Let's begin Baekho Tour.
- Open and... / - Straightforward.
- Baekho. / - Tour.
- Let's take off. / - Let's go.
(Open and straightforward Baekho Tour starts)
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
- It's the first day of Baekho Tour. / - Yes.
What's the itinerary like on our first day?
On the first day,
we're going to my neighborhood.
- Jeju City. / - It's where...
I was born and grew up.
The neighborhood I know very well.
We're going to go to this place.
Jeju City is in the north and Seogwipo is in the south.
- Jeju City is very big too. / - Right.
We're going to check out the western part today.
- We're going west today. / - Yes.
We're going to the eastern part of the city tomorrow.
- Are we? / - Yes.
Where is our first destination?
This is what you really wished to eat.
- What I wished to eat? / - Yes.
It must be that food I wanted to eat.
- Yes. / - What is it?
You had a dish in mind?
Yes, there's a dish I wanted to try in Jeju-do.
- Cold raw fish soup. / - Yes.
I searched Jeju-do cold raw fish soup on the internet.
- It's good. / - One of the related search words...
- Yes. / - Is Seogwipo.
- In Seogwipo. / - There are good restaurants there.
But Jeju City has good ones too.
There's a good restaurant near the airport.
Then let's eat cold raw fish soup there.
What seafood do you like?
Me? I like...
- Abalone. / - Good. It's an abalone restaurant.
- Really? / - It's abalone cold raw fish soup.
(Baekho Tour Day 1)
There's a night market in Jeju-do?
- It's new. / - I've never heard of one.
(Baekho Tour Day 1)
(10 minutes to the restaurant by car)
Let's order first.
- Let's order. / - I'm really starving.
- Excuse me. / - This is...
The cold raw fish soup restaurant.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- You went to eat right away? / - It's a famous place.
We'd like to order abalone cold raw fish soup...
- Abalone cold raw fish soup. / - And raw fish noodles.
- That's it? / - Yes.
(I can't wait)
Isn't cold raw fish soup the same everywhere?
Cold raw fish soup in Jeju-do has different soup.
It has a little bit of bean paste in it.
- Bean paste in cold raw fish soup? / - Yes.
- Crunchy. / - I've never heard of it.
- It looks amazing. / - The bowl is so full.
(Sliced fresh abalones are added to the bowl)
(Abalone cold raw fish soup in Jeju-do)
I'm so excited.
(Cold raw fish soup is served)
Here it is.
The abalone cold raw fish soup is the signature dish.
This is abalone cold raw fish soup.
This is the raw fish noodles.
(Raw fish noodles, $9)
- Now... / - This looks amazing.
- They serve big portions. / - He mixes with his hand.
- He mixes it with his hand. / - It makes it tastier.
I can't mix it well.
(The appetizing red sauce is mixed with the noodles)
- Go ahead. Try this. / - Let's eat.
(Slurping)
(What does JR think of the noodles?)
(His face tells how it tastes)
It's good, isn't it?
(He stands up)
He approves.
Enjoy your food.
Doesn't it taste like spicy chewy noodles?
It looks so delicious.
It seems like they used medium-thick noodles.
You're right.
It's not like the noodles you eat with seasoned whelk.
Cold raw fish soup.
(It's time to try abalone cold raw fish soup of Jeju-do)
- My goodness. / - Abalone cold raw fish soup.
I'm glad I stuffed myself before we started shooting.
- Just to avoid a hard time here. / - Yes.
I will eat cold raw fish soup as soon as I get off.
(Abalone cold raw fish soup looks so appetizing)
(His frowning face shows how tasty it is)
- Is it a pass? / - It's a pass.
(Will JR give it a pass as well?)
How is it?
(He shakes Baekho's hand in awe)
This is a pass.
- He really wanted to eat it. / - He's thankful.
I'm thankful that he brought me to such a place.
Right, right.
JR has never been on a trip...
And cold raw fish soup greatly impressed him.
(I'm glad he likes it)
Good.
I like the texture of the food.
(Abalone is crunchy in the mouth)
- The texture of the abalone? / - Yes, it's crunchy.
- It doesn't taste so strong. / - It looks so tasty.
I loved the texture of the abalone.
- It's sour. / - It's a hangover dish for me.
It's not the main dish for me.
I would eat it the next day after I drank.
- This and soju make me feel better. / - Right.
- It makes your stomach numb. / - It's good.
How about we mix the dishes with rice?
Shall we? Now?
(It's time to mix rice in the cold raw fish soup)
My gosh, it looks too delicious.
- That's your breakfast, right? / - Yes, it's breakfast.
- We had that when we arrived. / - They put rice in it.
Those who like cold raw fish soup always mix rice in it.
(It looks so good even at a glance)
- Goodness, it looks so good. / - I can't imagine it.
(He takes a bite first)
(Tell me how it is)
Why are you not saying anything?
Because it's too delicious.
It's rude to talk in front of...
- Yes. / - Good food.
You're right.
(It was so good that no words were needed)
It was a great idea to mix rice in it.
It's delicious with rice.
Their signature dish is abalone cold raw fish soup.
What's interesting is that you have to cook
fried eggs yourself if you want to eat it.
- That sounds fun. / - It's unlimited.
Not many restaurants offer...
- Unlimited eggs these days. / - I know.
It's delicious with rice.
(It's the perfect breakfast)
(They start to dig in)
(Baekho from Aewol and JR from Gangneung love it)
(The harmony of refreshing soup and fresh abalone)
(This is the perfect menu for breakfast)
(They drink the soup out of the bowl)
- They drink it out of the bowl. / - This is amazing.
You two are young yet you're quiet when you eat.
We don't talk much.
I'm so full.
Keep your eyes forward.
(It's time for JR to rate the food)
Eyes to the front.
(JR will rate the food behind Baekho)
Baekho.
The restaurant you brought me to...
What in the world are you doing?
He kept doing that.
(Cringe)
I can't stand this!
Hey! What are you doing?
What about it? I like it.
- What's the problem? / - I lost my appetite.
The restaurant you brought me to...
(He secretly whispers to the stuffed animal)
It was our first course.
This was my first cold raw fish soup this year...
And it was very successful.
I feel like I will want to eat more in the future.
The first course was a big success.
Thank you.
It was my first time traveling.
He told me to be honest with the evaluation.
Why couldn't you just tell him in person?
(40 minutes by car from the restaurant to Aewol Port)
How does it feel to travel to your hometown?
- I'm curious. / - It's nice.
Well, coming here has always been
visiting my home, not traveling.
But traveling to a familiar place...
Actually feels quite nice.
When it comes to cars at least, we won.
Your car is a regular sedan.
- And our car was a convertible. / - It was rainy.
You must drive a convertible on a coastal road.
He's right.
Now, we're on Aewol Coastal Road.
- It's nice here. / - Yeah.
(Although their car isn't a convertible, this road is open)
It usually has a beautiful color.
When it's sunny, it's emerald green.
- The sea? / - Yes.
It's so beautiful.
The sea is emerald green?
(On sunny days, you can see the emerald ocean)
(Aewol Coastal Road is beautiful on sunny days)
It's really beautiful here.
The color of the ocean is so pretty.
I could see this view from the junior high,
from my classroom window.
- From your junior high? / - Yes.
My school is right here. It's near here.
You could see the sea from school?
I could see it from the classroom
when I turned my head to the right.
This is the junior high school I graduated from.
It's here.
This is the junior high you actually went to?
Yes, this is the junior high I actually went to.
??Along the ranges of Hallasan ??
How do you still remember the song?
(This cheerful boy who went to this junior high school)
(Became a reliable trip planner after 8 years)
He does look reliable.
He really was.
(Trip Planner)
Since he doesn't drink, he was the best as a driver.
(What is the next stop on their itinerary?)
What do you think about doing some activities?
- Activities? We'll do activities. / - Activities.
There's a new activity facility around my house.
- Where is that? / - It's awesome that he lives nearby.
It's in Eoeum.
- Is this it? / - Hey, you got it.
- They'll roll the ball? / - Yes, there's a person inside.
I like rolling.
You do? Then it's awesome.
(Baekho Tour Day 1)
We went towards the mountain.
(20 minutes by car from Aewol Port to the facility)
It's raining hard. It keeps pouring.
(It keeps on raining)
- I'm worried about this though. / - What?
What if the facility is closed?
It'll be even more fun.
- I'm looking forward to riding it. / - Right?
- Yes. / - Me too.
(Me too)
- We're here. / - My gosh.
This would be more fun on rainy days.
- We've arrived. / - We're here.
(Luckily, the balls are rolling down without problems)
- There's a track for that. / - Yes, there's a track.
- That looks fun. / - I prepared everything I could.
I can see that. My gosh, it's really huge.
- The balls are massive. / - Yes.
(A newly rising activity in Jeju City)
Inside the ball was much more fun...
- That's right. / - Than we expected.
(Zorb Course, $27 per person)
(2 people roll down a 300m hill with seatbelts on)
(Big Ball Course, $33 per person)
(Maximum of 4 people inside the ball with water)
(And roll down the hill like riding a water slide)
(Baekho Tour decides to experience both courses)
You can try both courses.
If you want to try both...
- You only have to pay $55 per person. / - My gosh.
- That would be nice for couples. / - Yes.
I think it'd be great for the two who want to be a couple.
- That's right. / - It must be more than two people.
I prepared one more thing.
For this big ball activity.
I stayed up all night to prepare this.
- You stayed up all night? / - Yes, you bet.
- It's in my pocket. / - Okay.
(It's a lipstick)
I thought he was doing a heart. That scared me.
Our program is known for the lipstick challenge.
(Changseob from BTOB did it)
(Eunkwang also did it)
We put on the lipstick too.
- Sikyung put it on nicely. / - Right.
(The lipstick challenge, the custom of Battle Trip)
(It brings back memories)
- That was really scary. / - No, it was fun.
Let's play for something.
- You do this too often. / - Let's do it.
- That will motivate me to do it. / - Okay.
What should we bet?
The loser buys dinner.
- Anything? / - Anything.
- Let's go. Are you confident? / - Let's do it.
- We'll use our own money. / - Are you sure?
- We'll pay out of our own pockets. / - Yes, of course.
- Let's do this. / - Are you confident about it?
- I can do this. / - You know...
- You can't take back what you said. / - Of course not.
- I will never do that. / - Don't give me excuses.
Gosh, I won't do that.
That's the longest track in Asia.
It's 300m long.
- It's quite long. / - 300m?
You will roll for a good amount of time.
You have to put on the head gear before going in.
(They're fully ready)
- Because you might get hurt? / - It must be rough.
You'll keep rolling inside the ball.
- So you won't hurt each other? / - Yes.
(The players enter the ball)
This is bigger than I expected.
(They put on the safety belts)
Ready.
- Put it on as soon as we start. / - Okay.
Put it on as soon as we start rolling.
Hold on! Wait!
(Laughing)
That's just a big squirrel cage.
Yes, it feels like we're in the hamster wheel.
It looks dizzy.
Because you keep rolling.
- If two guys try that out together... / - That course...
- They would get really close. / - Is only 8 seconds.
- It's a long track. / - Yes, it's very long.
What is this? Hey!
(Laughing)
You are laughing there, right?
It was scarier than I thought.
- You laughed because it was scary? / - Yes.
I ate the lipstick.
(It's hectic inside)
What's wrong with this?
(Laughing)
(Let's find out how well they put on the lipstick)
It hurts.
(The traces of the lipstick)
He did it.
This is bad. I'm in big trouble.
(Yes, indeed! His face is in big trouble)
- He's completely ruined. / - He's ruined.
It looks like he's in a zombie movie.
- It's a zombie movie. / - I tried very hard.
Look at the camera. I'm completely ruined.
I want to try that.
(They check each other's funny faces)
Who won then?
Come here. Come here.
Doesn't it look like I won?
- The lipstick is on his teeth. / - He ate it.
But you couldn't finish applying it all the way.
- No. / - You have a bit of your lips left.
- Gosh, this is tricky. / - Baekho did a good job.
But JR applied it all over his lips.
Hey! What is this?
(Baekho couldn't apply it as he was too busy laughing)
(He didn't apply it during the whole ride)
(When they arrived, he applied it then)
My gosh, you did that?
(The feeling of betrayal surges through him)
- Really? / - Who do you think won?
Given everything...
- This is a tie. / - Don't I look prettier?
The cameraman should film only the winner.
Film the winner.
It's a tie.
You owe me dinner.
- You cheated. / - No, I didn't.
I didn't cheat.
Let's go. We have to ride one more.
- There was one more course. / - Right.
- At the same facility? / - You should ride one more.
There's one more. They filled it with water this time.
That must be hard.
Then, up to how many people can fit in that ball?
- 4 people can fit in. / - About 3 to 4 people...
- Can ride that. / - 3 to 4?
If four people get on that, it would be hectic.
I think this will be scary. We're in big trouble.
I'll see you in one piece.
(Nervous)
What happened?
- You don't have safety belts? / - That looks fun.
- No safety belts. / - We don't put them on for that.
- That looks fun. / - This one is really fun.
(Their bodies don't rotate, they just slide)
- My gosh! / - It's long too.
Wait, that won't feel dizzy.
- It'd feel like a water park ride. / - That's right.
JR...
They bumped their heads.
JR is being crushed.
(Splash)
That was a header.
Are you sure that this is supposed to be fun?
- Yes, it was so much fun. / - It was fun.
- Is that supposed to be fun? / - So much fun.
(They're washing off their lipstick as they roll down)
(1 minute which felt like 1 hour passes by)
(Floundering)
- It's a fun ride, right? / - Yes, it is.
To us, it looks like a penalty.
No, it's not.
You look exhausted.
They can't walk after getting out.
(The beastly sexy guy)
- I think you look a bit annoyed. / - No. I'm not.
It would be funny if they fought looking like that.
I have a runny nose.
(They find this situation ridiculous)
- This is certainly... / - Yes?
It is exciting.
Liar!
- Which one will you choose? / - That's expensive.
- I'll ride the one with water. / - The one with water.
But here's my tip. You must bring swimming goggles.
- I agree. / - Because you can't open your eyes?
- Right. You need them. / - You can't enjoy the ride.
- Where are we going next? / - They're exhausted.
Now... Did you have fun?
Since we had fun,
we should enjoy the atmosphere of the night.
- As we enjoy that, will we... / - We'll eat again.
We'll eat again? Let's go then.
Let's go.
- It's perfect now. / - Alright.
I'm hungry again.
Let's go.
- You should get that. / - Let's go.
- It was fun. / - Yes, it was fun.
Great.
(It's time for JR to evaluate again)
He's doing it again.
You should have at least removed the lipstick.
At first, I was scared.
Now that I've tried it once, I want to do it again.
It's addictive.
As for the rating, I will give it 4.2.
(The activity gets 4.2 out of 5)
I deducted 0.8 because I lost.
(From the activity facility to the night market)
I can't wait to check out the night market.
- The night market was great. / - I didn't know about it.
Was it always there?
- It's new. / - When you go on trips...
When you travel abroad, there are night markets.
At first, it was the place where
you went for a walk in the forest.
But now, there are food trucks too.
It's like a night market now.
It's only until the end of December.
- Because it gets cold at night. / - This is...
- The night market. / - Until December.
Usually, in Jeju-do...
It becomes quiet at night.
But this place gets bright at night.
- I want to go. / - This is the hot place.
I didn't know Jeju-do had a place like this.
(It's the newly emerging hot place in Jeju-do)
(A night market in an arboretum)
It's a night market in an arboretum.
- There's fresh air. / - Yes.
There are foods from all over the place.
Usually, night markets are in the city
where the air isn't clean.
Right.
But here, it's so clean.
- Let's go. / - Let's go in.
We brought a mat too.
- We'll buy food. / - Yes.
- Then we'll eat on the mat. / - Right.
- As if we're on a picnic. / - That's right.
By the way, thanks for the food, JR.
Am I buying?
I'll just give you my wallet.
Great. Can I buy everything with this?
- Sure. Go ahead. / - Nice.
- I got enough cash. / - Let's go.
- Enjoy. / - Let's go.
Enjoy the food.
Let's look around. Here.
This is it.
Here. Sook is here.
- She's here. / - Yes.
Her picture is there.
- I ate there on Battle Trip. / - Yes.
It's starting again today.
I'm lucky.
I remember that food truck. The cube steak place.
(For Battle Trip's 1-year anniversary)
(Sook ate their cube steak in Jeju-do)
- She's here. / - Yes, she is.
- Hello. / - Hello.
We're from Battle Trip too.
- We're... / - Please say...
- Thank you to Sook. / - Of course, we will.
- He said that. / - Why?
Thanks to her,
we got a lease.
(No more rentals)
(Everyone is cheering for him)
That's really great.
- Let's try the steak. / - Of course.
If you order this,
we'll make it really delicious.
- Okay, we'll order that. / - Okay.
That's my wallet.
- How much is it? $16. / - It's $16.
- $16. / - Thank you.
He's buying.
(Bitter)
(Cube steak set, $16)
- I was feeling okay until then. / - Thank you.
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
- It's amazing. / - That's a lot of food.
It looks delicious.
What do you think? Is this okay?
$16 from the start?
($16 from the start?)
Don't you guys drink? Did you just have food?
I don't like to drink.
He doesn't.
- You had a beer. / - I had a beer.
- Let's go get turkey. / - Turkey.
- Turkey. / - Turkey.
(Turkey at a night market?)
That's awesome.
- Turkey drumstick. / - I saw someone eating it.
(Popular dish at the night market)
We have to eat it.
What should we do?
- Should we get in line? / - This must be it.
- What's this? / - Goodness.
- I thought it was pork hock. / - That's a turkey leg.
It was a turkey drumstick.
- Do they sell turkey? / - Yes. It's a turkey leg.
(Extremely popular)
- Do you eat it as a whole? / - That's right.
Thank you.
That looks good.
- You have to try that. / - Look at the size of it.
Wait.
Fusion fried noodles.
- Fried noodles. / - We have to eat that.
- We do. / - Fried noodles.
- How many are you guys having? / - Give us one.
- It's $6. / - How much?
- $6. / - $6?
Give her $6.
Okay.
- Thank you. / - It looks good.
- I need to eat more. / - Let's go get a seat.
- I have to eat more. / - Sure.
Go ahead and eat more.
You make the most money.
(Of all the members, he's on the most TV shows)
(He can't deny that)
(The noodles JR paid for are being fried)
Vietnamese food!
- Vietnam. / - Yes.
- One banh xeo, please. / - Yes.
A Vietnamese person cooked it.
- That looks great. / - A Vietnamese chef.
I felt like I was in Vietnam.
- She's cutting it. / - Alright.
- It came out so fast. / - Amazing.
Film this.
(JR spent $48.10 so far)
- What is it? / - What's that?
He got beer.
They have everything there.
How much is it?
(Baekho can't drink, so he gets soft drinks)
$9? Thank you.
(JR spent $57.10)
Are you drinking already?
When did I spent that much?
Your face is looking more and more upset.
Are you okay, JR? You don't look good.
I'm fine.
(A table full of food)
($57.10 in total)
You bought so much.
I'll have tangerine juice.
I'll have beer.
Cheers!
This is good.
Let's eat. It'll get cold.
That looks great.
(First, they'll try the cube steak)
- Chop steak. / - Yes.
It's good.
- It's delicious. / - He deserves to get a lease.
- That soup looks good. / - You have to dip the bread.
(Soup comes with the steak)
You should dip this roll in the soup.
You're right.
(The roll tastes good with the soup)
- The one that had the longest line. / - Yes.
Turkey.
Let's eat this.
- Yes, try that. / - Mustard sauce costs 10 cents.
You can grab it like this.
It looks like a sausage.
(Adding a lot of sauce)
Can you put it in your mouth? Try the other side.
(You should take a big bite of it)
I want it too.
That looks so delicious.
It's good for taking photos.
You look good with it.
- It's fried. / - It doesn't taste greasy.
It tastes like smoked meat.
- Isn't the meat tough? / - No, it's tender.
Good thing we got three sauces.
You should buy three sauce packets.
One isn't enough.
(They fell in love with the turkey leg)
Goodness.
That looks good.
You should've taken a picture. Didn't you take any?
We don't take pictures when we eat.
We should've done that.
JR, you look very manly
when your eyebrows are showing.
Thank you.
(JR devours the turkey leg)
(Then he takes a sip of beer)
- Banh xeo. / - Have you tried it before?
Is it your first time?
- It is. / - It was so good.
I'm hungry.
- I see. Banh xeo isn't shrimp. / - Right.
I thought it was shrimp.
- I had it for the first time. / - It's good, isn't it?
It was so good with the lettuce.
That's banh xeo.
(JR eats banh xeo for the first time)
Goodness.
How is it?
- Is that good? / - Fried food...
Tastes awesome with lettuce as a wrap.
You're right.
(Baekho takes a bite of banh xeo too)
He eats it so deliciously.
It's super tasty.
This is really good.
I've tried it a few times before.
This is very good.
I've never seen JR
eat this much before.
- Me neither. / - Right?
That means it's really delicious.
- Usually, I don't eat a lot. / - Right.
But that was so good.
You're really eating a lot.
I forgot that I was full and I kept eating.
This would...
Make a perfect family trip.
Mom and dad can have a drink,
and the kids can have food.
It'd be perfect.
(A perfect ending to the first day of their trip)
(Baekho Tour enjoys the final meal of the first day)
(Refreshing beer with the cool breeze of Jeju-do)
That looks like a beer commercial.
(Baekho drinks refreshing cola)
We're done eating, so are we going to the lodging?
Yes.
But...
It's a bit far.
What?
- Our lodging was a bit far. / - Really?
- Do we have to go somewhere else? / - Shall we go?
Yes.
Tomorrow, we have to...
Tour the east side.
- Because we looked at the west. / - Yes.
Now we'll go to the east side and sleep there.
- Let's go. / - Okay.
Our lodging is on the other side.
(Hoping tomorrow will be as fun as today)
I know all about the west...
- You were researching hard. / - Yes.
- So you studied the east side. / - This place is great.
Wow, it's beautiful inside.
It's my first time on this side.
- Me too. / - It's a trip.
It excites me.
It's so beautiful.
- You said you liked dol hareubang. / - Yes.
So we're going to visit a stone maze.
- Baekho, do you hear me? / - It's so pretty.
Baekho isn't familiar with that neighborhood.
This is amazing.
It's my first time having this.
- That was so good. / - This is good.
What's that?
- That was awesome. / - That was great.
- That was the highlight. / - True.
(One bite after another)
(Empty bowls are getting piled up)
JR, what have you done?
(Continuously being deeply touched)
(Day 2 of Baekho Tour begins now)
- Baekho Tour. / - Baekho Tour.
(Baekho Tour Day 2)
- Green tangerine soba sounds delicious. / - It does.
Green tangerine soba was good.
- It must be refreshing. / - The houses are so nice.
- Did you sleep there? / - It was a separate house.
(Entire house, $160 per night)
(The trip planner gets up)
Did they fight the night before?
Wait, he doesn't look that cute.
- He's cute... / - He looks like a Mexican.
But his beard has grown a lot.
(Half asleep)
(I should wake up JR)
(JR)
(JR doesn't seem to want to wake up)
When you go on a trip for TV show
while having a busy schedule...
- You get a really good rest. / - That's true.
You get to eat delicious food.
- We slept a few more minutes. / - Did you fall asleep?
You're sleeping like that?
(30 minutes later)
Let's get it.
It's definitely...
- He shaved. / - I didn't see this yesterday.
- This looks totally different now. / - Right?
This house has all the features of a Jeju-do house.
There's the stone wall.
And there's no gate.
Yeah, it's interesting that there's no gate.
We don't have gates here.
How pretty.
- It's so pretty. / - They kept traits of Jeju-do houses.
And built new houses there.
Even the roof is low.
- See? / - Don't houses have low roofs...
- Because of the wind? / - That's right.
That's right.
I felt it when we arrived yesterday.
The wind of Jeju-do.
(What's their first itinerary on Day 2?)
What's the first itinerary today?
We must have breakfast.
(It's breakfast)
Aren't you hungry?
We ate a lot yesterday.
- But I got hungry after I woke up. / - Right.
We must keep eating.
Did someone beat you up in the face?
No, I ate a lot the day before.
- He ate a lot. / - That's why, right?
I thought someone hit you last night.
(He just got puffy from eating a lot)
(12 minutes to the soba restaurant from the lodging)
You'll definitely like it.
(Day 2 of Baekho Tour begins)
Overall, it is quiet and peaceful around here.
It's so nice here.
"Doreumeong."
(He spots a sign while driving)
- Is that a dol hareubang? / - No, "doreumeong."
"Doreuda" means "to run."
- To run. / - Then what does "doreumeong" mean?
"While running."
"Meong" comes at the end of a verb
to use the progressive tense.
- That's why our tour name was like that. / - Right.
- While playing, while resting. / - We did that.
With Jeju-do dialect, the sentences end abruptly.
It's similar to the American accent.
It ends with "man."
A lot of sentences end with "man."
- Like "What's up, man?" / - Yes, something like that.
That's right.
I didn't know "What's up, man?" was from Jeju-do.
It's a welcoming greeting.
- "What's up, man?" / - That's right.
(They travel while talking about the Jeju-do dialect)
We're going to eat some delicious food again.
We're here.
We'll see it once we turn.
- Isn't that it? / - Right here...
- Is... Is that it? / - Isn't that it?
- Right here... Is... Is that it? / - Isn't that it?
All the houses look European.
- Yes, it's the soba restaurant. / - Like Europe.
Is that the place?
(Green tangerine soba)
You're right.
(Baekho researched a lot about the east of Jeju-do)
I wonder what JR will like.
(Researching diligently)
Green tangerine soba?
This is it.
- That looks delicious. / - Green tangerine soba.
- That's... / - That looks good.
Green tangerines are refreshing.
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
Yes, this is the green tangerine soba restaurant.
Is this the place?
- Yes, it is. / - Is that a new restaurant too?
Yes, this place is fairly new too.
The interior design was cute and pretty.
(Welcome)
(How will the green tangerine soba taste?)
Green tangerines are...
Tangerines that are green.
You know it well.
(This is a piece of cake)
Green tangerines are in season right now.
- Really? They're in season now? / - Yes, they are.
They are delicious even when you eat them raw.
- They look like calamansi. / - How pretty.
They weren't that sour.
I'm curious about how it will taste.
- Here's your appetizer. / - Thank you.
- This must be the soba roll. / - Is this the dish?
This is the soba roll.
(Soba roll?)
- They rolled soba like rice roll. / - Looks delicious.
A long time ago, that dish was popular.
This fried tofu looks like a pot.
They added hijiki in there.
(Fried tofu stuffed with rice and hijiki, $8)
(Soba noodles rolled up like rice rolls)
It doesn't have many calories.
- That looks delicious. / - It's less fattening than rice.
It's less fattening,
it doesn't mean you won't gain weight.
If you eat a lot, you'll gain weight.
The sauce was really good.
- The owner made that tsuyu himself. / - It looks good.
We should generously dip the sauce for this.
(He has a piece of the soba roll first)
It's good.
That looks so good.
(Feeling happy)
It's good.
The soba roll was really delicious.
The texture was interesting too.
- Normally, you order... / - It does look good.
Soba noodles to dip in the sauce.
- It tastes just like that. / - Yes, it's a bit similar.
(How will the fried tofu stuffed with rice and hijiki taste?)
(Hijiki is on top of the rice)
- You must eat it in one bite. / - Hijiki is really good.
- Some people add it in the rice too, right? / - Yes.
- In fritters and soup too. / - It's good for you.
(A big bite)
(Baekho has a big bite too)
I can smell the tangerine.
You can smell the tangerine?
- Don't you smell the tangerine? / - No, I don't.
Try it again.
It's because you didn't eat this.
(The smell of tangerine comes from the yuzu sauce)
The green sauce was on top of the rice.
That was like yuzu sauce.
- The yuzu sauce. / - I see.
- He dropped it. / - I didn't know I dropped it.
- This is the tangerine sauce. / - Is this it?
- You two look so close. / - You're right.
(Eureka!)
(He eats everything in one go with the sauce too)
You have to eat it all in one bite.
That's how you can taste the real flavor of the dish.
(Hijiki goes well with the refreshing yuzu sauce)
(Fried tofu stuffed with rice is a hearty breakfast)
- It's not spicy? / - No, it's not spicy at all.
I really want to try that.
This is really good.
Give us our second round of food.
- Where should I put this? / - You can put it there.
Right, we came here to have this.
(The green tangerine soba, $9)
- That's the green tangerine soba. / - In soba?
- That has to be good. / - That must be delicious.
I don't know how they'll taste together.
With soba, sauce is the most important.
That's right.
The owner cooked it really well.
- On top of the noodles... / - On top of the noodles...
- I'll put this slice. / - Put the slice on top.
(Have a spoonful with a slice of green tangerine)
- That looks delicious. / - Yes.
Cheers, to the green tangerine.
The same yuzu scent from
the fried tofu stuffed with rice.
(On another level from the yuzu sauce)
The tangerines are way more aromatic here.
They made the dish so appetizing.
I think it would go really well with some fried food.
They do serve fried food. They have fried shrimp.
- Right? You need fried shrimp. / - They do.
- Eating it like that... / - You need something fried.
It'd be too sweet and sour.
Once I put it in my mouth,
the citrus flavor fills my mouth.
I love tangerines.
(Trying to describe the taste)
You're right.
I couldn't think of what to say.
I was expecting something so much better.
- You have to eat... / - Yes.
The noodles and green tangerine together
to truly feel its charming flavor.
Eating this makes me feel like I'm in Jeju-do.
Jeju-do produces a lot of buckwheat.
Buckwheat?
Jeju-do is the largest buckwheat producer.
- Really? / - Yes.
It must taste really good then.
(They fill themselves up from breakfast)
Are we going somewhere fun now?
Since we're in Jeju-do,
we're finally going to go swim.
But the weather is...
Let's go and see.
Let's at least see the ocean.
Yesterday was the first day I swam this year.
It's hard to say we were playing in water yesterday.
There was enough water for me.
Since I can't swim...
That was deep enough for me.
Let's go and see.
There must be fun things to do there as well.
Of course.
We should ride a banana boat.
Have I ever ridden a banana boat?
I think the last time we rode it was in Thailand.
You're right. I rode a banana boat in Thailand.
- And... / - Could you please stop it?
What? Banana boat?
I was looking forward to riding a banana boat.
What if I can't ride it?
I didn't know you wanted to ride it so badly.
You're really going to ride a banana boat?
Yes, we went to a beach.
- Hamdeok Beach is famous. / - It's Hamdeok Beach.
I used to play there when I was young.
I think the weather has become better than earlier.
The weather is better than I imagined.
- Over here. / - Yeah, it's not bad.
I feel like it'll go smoothly from now on.
I trust you.
- We'll make it. / - As a trip planner...
I believe you checked the weather beforehand.
We'll make it. Don't worry.
(He's worried they might not be able to swim)
I see "Hamdeok" on the sign.
(They arrive at Hamdeok Beach)
(Hamdeok Beach)
Hamdeok Beach is very popular these days.
There are so many people.
- The water is so clear. / - That's right.
(The beach is famous for its emerald color)
(The water is shallow, perfect to play in)
(You can try various water sports here as well)
There are many leisure activities here.
Many people enjoy leisure activities there.
(But)
My goodness.
This team had bad weather too.
(A strong wind welcomes them)
(Due to the hazardous sea warning)
(The beach is closed)
(The beach is closed due to strong wind)
It was sunny...
- But there was a windstorm. / - That's right.
You can't go into the water, right?
- What a shame. / - It's too dangerous.
Explain this.
(Tell me what this is)
What about my unicorn boat?
(I can't believe this)
This can't be true. Let's go ask.
Hey, it's obvious.
We can't go in, can we?
There will be a typhoon today.
Oh, no.
It's his first trip to Jeju-do.
What should we do now?
Let me go have a look.
It's okay. Everyone makes mistakes.
- You can make a mistake sometimes. / - Yes.
I'll check other places to go.
(Baekho checks out other places to go)
He's not going to the RC car place too, is he?
(Instead of playing with water, he plays with sand)
This looks nice.
JR, I found something.
What did he find?
Did you find something?
(What's Baekho's back-up plan?)
- I made something. / - This place looks awesome.
What is that?
This is a maze.
- A maze? / - What do you think?
- Shall we go? / - Okay, let's go.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
We're going to a maze park.
- It's really nice there. / - It's what we saw in the video.
Yes.
- Natural. / - Disaster.
- Baekho. / - Tour.
I'm sad.
(Baekho Tour Day 2)
(Maze Land)
- Jeju-do is known for three things. / - Yes.
Stones, women and winds.
This park has mazes in the shape of the three things.
Let's have fun there to make up for this.
To make up for this, how about doing this?
We were supposed to see who holds onto
the banana boat longer.
Since we can't play that game,
let's play another game there.
Whoever's faster...
It doesn't matter if we run together.
- Whoever reaches the exit first... / - Yes.
- Becomes the winner. / - Okay.
- Okay? / - Are you sure you can beat me?
Of course, I am.
(Baekho Tour Day 2)
It's near Gujwa.
There are many interesting things to see
other than the maze park.
There are parks and sculpture galleries too.
It's here.
- So, this is the place. / - Yes, it is.
(Looking forward to it)
(The biggest maze in the world)
The biggest maze in the world.
(Maze Land consists of three different mazes)
It looks like it's in the United Kingdom.
This place was really cool.
(This new type of theme park exists nowhere else)
There are three different kinds of mazes in here.
Once you pay $11 for the entrance,
you can stay in the maze as long as you want.
What if you entered the maze and can't find the exit?
Then, just like you did with the convertible,
you have to jump over it.
Stone maze, woman maze, wind maze.
- That's the three symbols... / - Exactly.
We'll go to... You said you like dol hareubang.
- Yes, I did. / - So we're going to the stone maze.
Okay, I'm very excited now.
Good.
You'll be around 5 minutes later than me.
Baekho is an easy match.
You and I will start from a different point.
I hope they meet in the middle.
- Baekho starts from there. / - That's right.
I'll put the flag here.
Let's put the flag at the starting point.
I will quickly go and take your flag.
I'll be quick.
That's the opposite of the truth.
The loser...
- Has to do elephant spins. / - 12 times.
He will run 30m in...
- Let's say 9 seconds. / - 9 seconds.
And he has to repeat until he makes it.
Alright.
It sounds quite cruel.
(The penalty is quite cruel)
(Baekho's starting point, Baekho's finishing point)
(JR's starting point, JR's finishing point)
- It looks really hard. / - It looks so difficult.
I heard it usually takes about 1 hour to 1.5 hours.
- To escape the maze? / - Yes.
You'd lose weight.
Jun Jin would just jump out of it.
3, 2, 1, go!
(Start)
Let's go.
(The two walk into the maze)
I'm very good at these things.
I heard this should take one hour.
But I'll finish it in 30 minutes.
It can be a good workout.
It'd be exhausting.
(JR keeps walking without hesitation)
I can do it easily.
(Relaxed)
How do I know which way it is?
All I can see is the front.
(Baekho is already lost)
It should be this way.
Once you're in it, you'd lose all sense of direction.
- You do. / - You lose it.
(He keeps jumping)
It must be exhausting.
- This isn't easy. / - It must be so confusing...
- The paths must look all the same. / - That's true.
There is only one right path,
so if both Baekho and I are on the right track,
we will run into each other. Baekho.
Baekho, can you hear me?
(He can't hear him)
(He tries to find the way with the camera but fails)
I can't see the screen.
What did I just do?
What is this?
There's a stone grave.
That's where I have to go, right?
(Baekho's destination seems nearby)
- It's the eye of the dol hareubang. / - It's the eye.
- Should I go this way? / - Everyone climbs up on...
The stone grave...
- And checks the way. / - You can check the way.
- You can check where you are. / - Yes.
But it doesn't help much.
I can imagine that.
There's another stone grave. I've been here before.
(He sees a stone grave again)
You were lost the whole time.
I don't know the way out. I gave up already.
(He keeps walking back to the eye of dol hareubang)
You have to drop candies on the way.
- That's clever. / - Dropping candies on the way.
Yes.
(Surprised)
(He found JR)
(Baekho runs to him)
This is the right way. Now I found the way.
It's so difficult to find a way here.
(Baekho runs to him)
I think Baekho will get lost around here.
(Baekho is here)
- He caught up. / - Trying to scare him.
He approached me while I was talking.
Why would I get lost, you punk?
What the?
What happened?
- Why would I get lost? / - What?
- When did you come? / - Why would I?
(He runs away)
That's not the right way.
That's not it. There's a stone grave.
It was the right way.
- Really? / - Yes, I got out that way.
I'm lost again.
What was that?
Why is Baekho so good?
Did he take a picture of the map?
I took a picture of it.
He's the foul king.
Each team has a foul king.
I want Jun Jin and Baekho to play a game together.
It's a map.
Wait.
(Baekho took a picture of the map before he began)
I'm now...
(Let me see)
Please take a look at this.
Do you know where I am now?
He has the map but he can't read it.
- Because you can't tell where you are now. / - Right.
Can I look down on the top of it?
(He goes up the stonewall)
(He keeps climbing up)
(He finds someone familiar from a distance)
What?
(There stands someone familiar)
(JR already reached the line)
What are you doing?
- It took less than 30 minutes. / - Yes.
(10 minutes ago)
I should look at this.
I'll use the picture.
(JR also had the map)
I knew it.
I knew JR would do something.
- You also had the map. / - He's amazing.
(He finds the way out using the map)
Okay. It's this way.
JR, you could read the map?
Yes. I memorized it.
Here I am.
(He gets Baekho's flag in 15 minutes)
JR wins today.
How are you so good?
I memorized my way.
Some people are good at that but some aren't.
I should go. Gosh.
(Baekho lost after wandering around)
This doesn't suit me.
He'd be good at the punishment though.
This is hard.
Here I go.
It's 9 seconds. Start.
How many times does he have to spin? 12 times?
- 12 times. / - 1, 2, 3...
I feel dizzy already.
(He's trying hard for the penalty )
It's 12 seconds.
(He keeps spinning over and over again)
This isn't going to work.
Here I go.
(Baekho runs with his teeth set)
You have to do the same pose as the statue.
It's 8.01 seconds.
(He finally succeeded)
- Let's go now. / - 8 seconds.
(He's tired from running)
- Where are we going now? / - Let's...
- Go eat. / - We're going to eat?
- Okay. Let's go. / - Let's go.
- That was amazing. / - I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
He must be hungry.
(Baekho Tour Day 2, rockfish meal)
- This place was really good. / - Rockfish set?
- Rockfish meal? / - You have to try this restaurant.
You studied a lot for this trip.
- And searched for everything. / - Yes, I did.
(He discovered a new dish of Jeju-do)
JR would think we have to eat...
Jeju Black pork or cold raw fish soup in Jeju-do.
This must be really good.
We have to eat this.
It looks like a Chinese dish.
That's not predictable.
Gosh.
(Predictable dishes of Jeju-do)
(Special new taste of Jeju-do)
(Deep-fried rockfish)
(With a sweet sauce)
We can also eat the bone.
(It's chewy and crispy at the same time)
Look at the flesh.
I want to tear off the tail and eat it.
The tail is so good.
They serve deep-fried eel bones...
- At an eel restaurant. / - Deep-fried eel bones?
It tastes just like that.
This isn't the Black pork restaurant I imagined.
It's not Black pork.
It's a rockfish set meal.
Rockfish set?
Alright, I'll just trust you.
- Okay. / - I should trust you.
- I'm sure it will be good. / - Okay.
We usually eat rockfish raw.
- Right. / - Exactly.
- Or we eat braised rockfish. / - Right.
The main dish...
(Surprised)
It looks amazing.
(They are thrilled to see it)
- It's here. / - What's this?
(Deep-fried rockfish served with side dishes)
You have to order at least two servings.
(You can eat the head and fins of the rockfish)
I've never seen deep-fried rockfish before.
You should order 2 servings for 1 person.
- 2 servings for 1 person? / - It's $24 for 2 servings?
- Yes. / - It's not so expensive.
We cooked two rockfishes as they are small.
Really?
They usually serve one rockfish
but they cooked two as they were small.
He's doing it with his hands.
He pulls them apart for us to eat.
- Please try this. / - Can we eat now?
- You can eat it now. / - You eat the fins?
We can eat now.
The fins are really good.
(He gives JR a fin too)
My mouth is watering.
(They taste the fin first)
(Can you hear it?)
(It sounds crispy)
It's ASMR.
(It sounds delicious)
(It sounds crispy)
It's good, isn't it?
- Do you like it? / - Thank you.
Thank you.
This is so good.
(Bowing out of gratitude)
It must be so good.
Thank you.
This is amazing.
I like the texture.
It's very crispy.
At an eel restaurant,
they serve fried bones.
It tastes like that.
- Please enjoy. / - Thank you.
He pulled them apart into bite-sized pieces.
It will taste good with rice.
Let's eat.
(It's time to enjoy the dish)
Didn't you order alcohol?
- We didn't. / - Gosh, that's too bad.
I wish I was there.
There's something I really wanted to try.
(JR wanted to try something when he saw the dish)
Spoon the rice up...
You should eat it with rice.
The sauce must be delicious.
The sauce is really good.
(He puts a piece of rockfish on a spoonful of rice)
(And he puts it in his mouth)
(Baekho takes a big bite too)
(It tastes like)
This is so good.
(Bravo!)
I love it.
Thank you, Baekho.
(He is grateful)
This is really good.
It's very crispy.
And the flesh is so firm.
(It's a perfect harmony of crispiness and firm flesh)
The sauce is sweet.
- It's sweet and salty. / - It must be great.
It is even better because...
Each part tastes different.
Exactly. I like that.
Each part has a different level of crispiness.
And they taste different.
It's so good.
(It's time to munch on the dish)
It sounds so crispy.
(He takes a big bite)
(He can't stop eating)
And the bean paste stew served with it...
- Was really good. / - That's right.
(It is the happiest moment)
I'm happy.
(He's looking for something)
How many fins did you eat?
What?
(He's eating a fin)
(He chews it carefully)
- What did you say? / - How many fins did you eat?
We fought over fins.
- Really? / - We rarely eat fins.
He argued.
- "How many fins did you have?" / - I only had one.
(But there's none left)
(Did I eat three fins?)
- There's one. / - It's here.
- You can eat it. / - No, you should eat it.
I don't want it.
- You can eat it. / - My gosh.
No, you should.
- You eat the fin. / - It's okay.
I'll eat the big bone.
Is he going to feed him that personally?
I'll eat it then.
My gosh.
(JR finally eats the fin)
That's rare.
- You should try this. / - See?
See?
(Dongwan's prediction was right)
I knew it.
(He feels shy all of a sudden)
How did you know that, Dongwan?
We did the same thing 20 years ago.
20 years ago?
This is really good.
This is the best meal.
Gosh, I really want to try it.
(He ate it up already)
Do you want more rice?
Okay.
Can we get 2 more bowls of rice?
(Baekho emptied his rice too)
- Thank you. / - We have to...
- Order more rice for this. / - You need 2 bowls.
- You two really liked the dish. / - Right.
I don't usually eat two bowls of rice.
You should eat a lot when you're on a trip.
He eats a lot because it's that good.
(They start eating the rockfish again)
(Gobbling up)
(They keep eating without a break)
It's good.
(Rice bowls piled up)
- They ate their fill. / - Four bowls.
We should reflect on ourselves looking in a mirror.
(They emptied the second bowls too)
It's been so long since I had two bowls of rice.
Me too.
I tried not to eat too much.
Baekho is a gourmand, right?
- Yes, I like to eat a lot. / - I thought so.
My gosh, we're in trouble.
(Traces of refraining)
I forgot about the Black pork as soon as I ate this.
I really wanted to eat it.
But I forgot about the Black pork after eating this.
That's good.
They also sell braised rockfish there too.
So you can choose whatever you want to eat.
Are we going home now?
We have one thing left.
We have to end the trip now.
Are we going to have dessert?
(The end? Dessert?)
- Isn't it dessert? / - Yes, it is.
- Is there dessert? / - Did I act that way that day?
It doesn't feel like dessert.
But we're going to end the trip there.
- We'll organize our thoughts... / - The end?
And go back to our daily lives.
(They shake hands for the last time before they go)
- They're shaking hands again. / - Very satisfied.
Thank you.
Baekho worked so hard for this trip.
I worked hard on the research.
I saw this place earlier and it was really nice.
The atmosphere is amazing.
I think it will be a really nice place
to prepare ourselves to go back to our daily lives.
This place is so nice.
(Baekho Tour Day 2)
This is where we ended it. It's a cafe.
It's a really unique cafe.
(22 minutes by car to the mountain cabin cafe)
What is that?
This is a cafe made by renovating a stable.
It really feels vintage.
(A mountain cabin-like cafe that renovated a stable)
(It boasts a unique atmosphere)
- It's amazing. / - Oh, my.
- That's so cute. / - They even do...
Live performances there sometimes.
Isn't it nice?
I really tried hard to find this place.
You can start a campfire outside.
How is it?
It feels old...
(You can feel a sense of old sensitivity here)
But I think it's the best place...
- To be the last course. / - Right?
I picked this place from only looking at photos.
The atmosphere is even better than the photos.
- You chose the perfect spot. / - Yes.
- And... / - Did you see this?
Do you know what this is?
It signifies the business hours.
This is the business hours.
How is this the business hours?
They light it when the sun is about to set.
When the candles go out, business is over.
- That's interesting. / - When the candle goes out...
They close the cafe.
(Open from 11 a.m. until the candle is out)
(Their drinks are here)
Thank you.
The tray is also really unique.
- This is Irish coffee. / - It's coffee with whiskey.
It's their signature menu.
(Irish coffee, $10 for 1 glass)
(Non-alcohol Irish coffee for Baekho)
- It's really good. / - Yes.
(They drink it while appreciating it slowly)
It's really good.
- It's a taste I never had before. / - Yes.
It's better than you expect.
- It's good. / - It's really good.
It's sweet but the bitterness of the coffee is well mixed.
I think this isn't bad.
It's really good.
They sell wine, right?
I think they also sell alcohol.
You must have become really close.
- Though you were already close. / - We were...
We did a lot of things.
We really did a lot of things.
- It's the first trip for me. / - Right.
- It's your first time. / - I'm 24 years old.
In fact, I worried about it a lot.
I didn't know if I would think it was fun.
I didn't know if I would be interested.
From yesterday up to today...
I realized that...
I still haven't seen so many things.
I think I was so happy.
I liked that I was getting to learn about new things.
I made a lot of new memories on this trip.
I'm relieved.
I think I would want to
travel a lot from now on.
It's the first time I went on a trip after planning it.
It made me feel really proud...
That you liked...
What I searched and learned about.
(Baekho was proud because his friend was satisfied)
It feels weird to watch this.
Don't cry.
I'm not going to cry.
Don't do things like crying.
Thank you.
I know. The trip was fun.
It was fun.
My left arm is really heavy right now.
(Baekho's left arm is really heavy)
I'm going to...
(The armband he was wearing during the trip)
Take this off now.
Will you give me your left arm?
Take this...
And plan a trip when you go to Gangneung.
You should take one of our members on a trip.
Ren would be nice.
(His arm suddenly feels heavy)
His facial expression changed.
Planner JR, are you confident?
Let's go with all of our members.
Let's go together.
You'll have a driving license by then, right?
- Should I get it for this? / - You don't have a license?
- I got it now. / - He didn't have one then.
He's got it now.
- Should we chant our slogan? / - We'll come back?
- Of course, we'll come back. / - Then...
I will be back.
- I'll be back? Okay. / - Okay?
- Okay, let's go. / - Okay.
- I will... / - Be back.
Baekho Tour.
(Baekho Tour will be back)
(The end of Baekho Tour)
That was good.
I didn't know that Jeju-do produced buckwheat
that much.
- That's right. / - I didn't know that either.
When you travel to Jeju-do, you will see gardens...
- With white flowers. / - That's right.
They're the buckwheat fields.
Bongpyeong's famous for buckwheat noodles.
Jeju-do is also famous for buckwheat noodles.
- If you go to Ora-dong in Jeju-do... / - Yes.
- There is a big buckwheat field. / - Yes.
You can take great photos there.
People from Jeju-do like buckwheat flour...
- So they put it in a lot of soup. / - Yes.
- Is that right? / - Yes, that's right.
He's good.
The fake dialect sounds real
and the real dialect sounds fake.
My dialect is real.
I have a lot of friends from Jeju-do, so I used it a lot.
- That's right. / - "Musamasin."
- Musamasin. / - What does that mean?
"Why."
- "Musamasin?" / - Yes.
Let's see the final expense.
How much did they spend?
We also ate a lot.
Wan Jun Tour spent quite a lot, $320.
We used $323 per person for 2 days and 1 night.
- We spent a lot. / - You rented a convertible.
What is the final expense of Baekho Tour...
- Excluding airfare? / - Yes.
- Per person. / - Per person.
$287.
- It's similar. / - We won.
As we already mentioned,
It'd be the same if we didn't rent the convertible.
The tumbling activity cost more than $50.
- Yes. / - That was expensive.
Their lodging was expensive.
- That's right. / - Their lodging was expensive.
Let's hear their last words before the vote.
Baekho Tour, please tell us your last words
before the vote.
This was my first time going on a trip
and I didn't know how to enjoy it.
I didn't go on trips because of that.
Thanks to this chance, I learned how fun traveling is.
If you've never gone on a trip,
I recommend going to Jeju-do for your first trip.
- It was so nice. / - Yes.
For 1 night and 2 days,
there isn't a better course than Jeju-do.
- You mean Jeju City. / - Jeju City!
Jeju City is good.
- Jeju City is the best among them. / - That's right.
- You're emphasizing it. / - It's really nice.
Please visit
Are you ready to vote?
Would you go on a trip to Jeju City
according to Baekho Tour?
Please vote.
(Baekho Tour was designed by Baekho from Jeju-do)
(What will the judges choose?)
They say it's really close.
Will it be SHINHWA who showed their 20 years of
experience through Wan Jun Tour to Seogwipo?
Or will it be NU'EST W's Baekho Tour
to Jeju City?
What will the judges choose?
Here we go. They said it was a close match.
- What will happen? / - Wan Jun Tour.
- Wan Jun Tour. / - Wan Jun Tour.
Okay.
The first digit is the same!
- It's the same. / - No.
- It's over. / - Gosh.
(Who won this match?)
Congratulations.
(Baekho Tour wins)
- Congratulations. / - Thank you.
75 votes is a lot.
- Yes. / - I'm sorry, but to be honest...
I was attracted to this trip more.
- That's right. / - That's right.
Maybe it's because we're all getting old together.
- The course was so meaningful. / - It just...
Made me feel theirs was better.
I haven't felt that way in a while.
- But our team won. / - Yes.
Well, I think we were satisfied
with our trip regardless of the result.
We think we did a good job.
It was nice to see that they had fun and relaxed...
- When they're so busy. / - They relaxed well.
It made me feel like I was watching my little brothers.
- Nice, Dongwan. / - I also would have voted for them.
- It was a relaxing trip. / - Let's hear your thoughts.
- Your thoughts after winning. / - Baekho, tell us.
- I thought their trip was also... / - Yes.
- Really nice. / - Yes.
That's why I want to go to Seogwipo
when I go traveling to Jeju-do again.
- I want to go there. / - We'll go to Jeju City next time.
- I really want to go there. / - Me too.
- Yes. / - It was so fun.
How about you, JR?
If I go on a trip to Jeju-do again,
I will go for 4 nights and 5 days.
I want to go to the places I went to in Jeju City again,
and the places where they went to looked so nice.
I really want to try the RC car.
I really want to enjoy it
while wandering the street.
It was so fun.
It's been a while since we've seen SHINHWA.
- Yes. / - We went to nice places...
But NU'EST W also went to a lot of nice places.
- I really want to go later again. / - That's good.
- Dayoung, I almost forgot. / - Yes.
Thank you so much for speaking in the Jeju-do dialect.
- It was fun. / - Thank you.
I would like to let you know SHINHWA just released
their 20th-anniversary album.
- I hope the best for you. / - Good luck.
Thank you.
Dayoung, you were with us for 2 weeks.
- Yes. / - How was it?
I was on the show for the Jeju-do special.
They say that the people who recently came back
from Jeju-do knows the most about it.
I think that's true.
- I heard some news. / - Yes.
There's a rumor that you will go on a trip
if you were a special host.
- It was the same for JR. / - Yes, it was.
I really want to go on a trip for Battle Trip.
(We will look forward to Dayoung's trip)
We always have a new special.
- Is it a special next week? / - It's embarrassing...
But it's a trip for sisters.
The representative sisters of celebrities will be here.
It's a special for real sisters.
Yes, please look forward to the sisters special.
We will come back next Saturday.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip.
(Next episode)
(Xiamen, China, Yang Heeeun and Yang Heekyung)
It's been a long time, just the two of us.
I'm filled with expectation.
How would it taste?
Hold hands like this all day.
Today was like an unexpected gift.
(Kenting, Taiwan, Mijoo and Jisoo of Lovelyz)
Isn't that ocean too blue?
- It's the same color as the sky. / - I know.
Each of these become memory.
And they're all fascinating experiences.
It was great.
(Battle Trip)
("Save Me, Save You" by WJSN)