This is Peak Father and Son Tour.
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
Let's go to the most beautiful place.
Wow, it's so cool.
It's amazing.
This is the hidden card. It's great, isn't it?
Oh, that's delicious.
This was really good.
They cook so well.
It's so pretty here.
Father, let's come again next time.
- I love you. / - I love you.
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Kangnam, Tae Jinah)
(Mun Cheonsik, Shim Hyunbo)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip.
Just like last week,
we have the trip planners...
- Who took a domestic fall trip. / - Right.
- Nice to meet you. / - Nice to meet you.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
Welcome.
(100 judges in the audience)
Last week, Peak Father and Son Tour
went to Danyang and it was amazing.
We won, right?
Choi Taeseong told us a lot of
fun stories about history.
- Doribaengbaeng. / - Doribaengbaeng.
I liked spicy mandarin fish stew.
Spicy mandarin fish stew.
- I see. / - It's famous.
Wondering what your hidden card is while watching
made it more fun and absorbing.
- Right? / - You should probably start worrying.
We're fine. We have our hidden card too.
There are good foods everywhere in Korea.
- Yes. / - But...
We'll show you why Jeolla-do is known for good food.
- Yes. / - And our hidden card is...
- Very powerful. / - Is it?
Our hidden card has just arrived.
- It has just arrived? / - Is it here?
Yes, our hidden card is a real trip planner.
- Really? / - Yes.
Please tell us about this person.
He's a host of a travel related radio show.
He even wrote a book about good restaurants.
He's a good photographer too.
He takes great pictures too.
He's a well-rounded man.
- Really? / - I'm so curious. Let's meet him.
- Please come in. / - Hidden card, please come in.
(Who is their hidden card?)
Hey.
- Hello. / - He's our hidden card.
Meet our hidden card.
All of them have been the guest of my radio show.
- Yes. / - Each of them.
- All of us. / - On different days?
Yes, it's nice to see them here.
Actually, I'm very thankful to Sikyung.
- Why? / - He's like a teacher to me.
He taught me how to attract the radio listeners.
My radio show totally flipped.
- It really did. / - "Good night?"
- I know it did. / - "Good night."
"Good night" totally flipped.
Mr. Noh, I heard you have an interesting way
to find good restaurants.
I can tell you one thing.
Find grass-roots restaurants.
- What does that mean? / - Grass-roots means...
Restaurants that have been open for a long time.
Small, shabby and old ones.
Those restaurants are not famous
on mass media or SNS.
If there are a lot of middle-aged
or old ladies in a restaurant,
it's definitely a good restaurant.
Because they usually cook at home,
they don't eat out often.
Rather than young people?
- Exactly. / - These days...
There are so many recommendations on the internet.
It's hard to figure out if those are
actually good restaurants.
It's hard to find good ones.
Then Mr. Noh, have you ever failed
in finding a good restaurant?
Sikyung and I almost never fail.
I can give you some tips.
First, find signs that look old.
Second, find restaurants that only have one dish.
- Only one? / - Third, no menu is even better.
No menu?
The owner will treat you as he or she pleases.
- He loves humble places. / - I do.
We have the same taste.
We introduced him as our hidden card but actually,
every single restaurant he picked
and every single dish he picked are our hidden cards.
- They're all hidden cards. / - You won't be disappointed.
Right.
Were you traveling together for the two entire days?
- Yes. / - Yes.
We were traveling together the whole time.
- Really? / - I planned everything.
Then Junghun should've been the planner.
- He's the main planner. / - He's not a hidden card.
- He's the main. / - The two of you are hidden cards.
He's not a hidden card.
- I'd like to ask a question. / - The focus.
What should we know in advance
before watching your trip?
Mokpo is the essence of Jeollanam-do cuisines.
Mokpo is the best place to travel if you want to learn
about the modern cultural heritage and history.
Is that so?
Have you heard of "dark tourism?"
- No. / - What is dark tourism?
It means to travel to the cities or towns where
there were crises like wars or natural disasters.
By visiting the places,
you can learn about the past.
You can experience the wound in person.
That's dark tourism.
During the Japanese colonial era,
Gunsan and Mokpo are the cities...
- That were plundered the most. / - Yes.
There are a lot of buildings built in that era.
It's the best place to check out
modern cultural heritage by foot.
It's Mokpo.
Mr. Noh, doesn't this side of your face hurt a bit?
- Why? / - Jinah has been glaring at you.
- I see. / - He's not glaring.
He's just fascinated.
I thought he was pretty old.
What are you talking about?
I thought he was older than me.
- He thought he was older than him. / - Come on.
- Jinah, he's not married. / - That was a low blow.
I really thought so.
Anyway, we'll be looking forward to your contribution.
Let's watch Nilriri Manbo Tour in Mokpo.
(Nilriri Manbo Tour in Mokpo starts)
- Hello. / - Hello.
(The planners begin the trip with a bright greeting)
I'm Mun Cheonsik.
Hello, I'm Shim Hyunbo.
(They went to Tokyo with Sikyung 2 years ago)
- This trip was a lot of fun. / - Oh, you rode that.
It was the best.
(An all-round entertainer)
(Now successful in the home shopping business)
(Comedian Mun Cheonsik)
(This man next to Cheonsik)
He composed a lot of songs.
- Really? / - Was that your song?
Those songs are all composed by him.
Really?
(He's a hit song maker)
"My Love from the Star"
- He composed a lot. / - He's an amazing man.
You didn't know that?
Kangnam didn't know it until now.
He's a rich man.
- Awesome. / - He's looking at him differently.
He was condescending to him earlier.
Could we shake our hands later?
(Singer-songwriter Shim Hyunbo)
Why are we here today?
This is Battle Trip.
It's the best show in KBS.
When you feel bored and
want to escape from the everyday lives,
watch Battle Trip and it will motivate you to travel.
It's a great show.
He's a great seller.
So, where are we going?
Can we go somewhere far away?
This week's theme is a domestic fall trip.
- Domestic fall trip. / - Domestic fall trip.
We have a problem here. I've been on this show.
- You were once on the show. / - I went to Japan...
With Sikyung.
If you don't have anything special,
you will lose the competition.
So we need a strategy.
You need a strategy.
If you don't do anything like Hwijae,
if you just eat and sightsee...
If you do it like Hwijae, you'll lose.
You're right.
Who are our opponents?
I heard they had someone else with them.
Yes, they're with an expert.
It will be hard with us two alone.
(Sighing)
Do you know anyone?
Let me type, "travel."
Someone who knows a lot about traveling and food.
- I have one person in mind. / - You do?
We meet him from time to time.
(The two meet him from time to time?)
- Mr. Noh? / - Yes.
It's Mr. Noh.
(They call him right away)
Hello. Where are you?
Cheonsik and I are on Battle Trip and
we need an expert in our team.
I think it'd be nice if you could come over now
and talk more.
Okay. We'll be waiting for you.
He has been to almost every country.
He's been to many foreign countries too.
The best thing about him is...
That he knows a lot of small local restaurants
he found himself.
Right, I follow him on SNS as well.
He goes to all kinds of interesting places.
- Here he is. / - Come in.
It didn't take you long.
It's a little embarrassing to say this myself.
It's okay.
You might not know well about me
but I'm a living legend in the world of travel writers.
He looks like a comedian.
This is what annoys me.
I'm a living legend in the world of travel writers.
- Right? / - Yes.
A travel writer with 20 years of experience,
I'm Noh Junghun.
Travel writer Noh Junghun.
We feel very confident with you here.
(Noh Junghun, professional travel writer)
Whenever I have a foreign guest,
I ask him where I can take this guest to.
Then he sends me a long list of restaurants.
Goodness.
He's an important person.
Many of the restaurants are places I've never been.
(How did you three first meet?)
We were all guests of Sikyung's radio show.
- We were all guests. / - That's right.
- On different days. / - Tuesday's guest,
I was Saturday's guest, and he was Sunday's guest.
But we weren't on the show on the same day.
Then you can't meet each other.
We had a gathering together every day.
(Alcohol brought the four of them together)
We waited each other until the show finished.
It was a get-together.
Cheonsik and I are going on a trip and
you're our hidden card.
Who's on your opposing team?
We don't know.
Could you at least tell me if they have a travel writer?
They don't?
- Good. Because... / - Why do you ask that?
- I'm a travel writer. / - If they did...
You feel like we'll lose?
That's not it. What are you talking about?
If they did, you feel like we'll lose.
If I lose the competition with the tour I planned,
although I don't know who my opponent is...
I'll give up my post.
- You'll give up your post? / - It's not a real post but...
You don't have a post.
You can't give up your post when you don't have it.
It's about my pride.
- I'm a travel writer. / - Why are you getting so upset?
Many of the viewers don't seem to know me.
I'm a bit worried.
I searched fall trip on the internet
and it shows Fall Trip Week.
- Yes, there's that. / - Fall Trip Week.
It shows where you can go
and what you can do there.
It shows recommendations for different time periods.
It's easy to find information on the internet these days.
It's great.
It's easier to plan a trip these days.
By the way...
Listen. You called me...
- And it means you want to eat. / - Exactly.
- Right? / - That's it.
- Which province has the best food? / - Jeolla-do.
Right. There are a lot of cities in Jeolla-do.
There are a few cities I love the most among them.
- In Jeolla-do? / - The essence of...
Jeollanam-do is this city.
Mokpo in Jeollanam-do.
- Mokpo. / - Mokpo.
It's hard to get there.
- It's far away. / - Surprisingly, yes.
There are so many delicious food in Mokpo.
There's a Buddhist saying, "3 steps and 1 bow."
It means you take a bow after three steps.
Here, it's "3 steps and 1 food."
You can find food every three steps.
Mokpo is a famous city but it's quite small.
Right in front of Mokpo Station is the old town.
That's what I like about Mokpo.
Everything is near the station.
The old town is right in front.
What do the three of us like?
What brings us and Sikyung together?
You know what it is.
After we drink, we don't even need to call a chauffeur.
- We can just walk to our hotel. / - That sounds great.
- It's the best. / - Sounds good.
Every time I watch Battle Trip,
I realize the team name is important.
- What about 45? / - 45.
- 45? / - Our average age is 45.
What about 136?
- 136? / - 136 doesn't sound bad either.
136?
How about something that is related to walking?
- Something with walking. / - I have an idea.
Something related to walking.
Nilriri Manbo.
Isn't that nice? Let's walk with our pedometers on.
Let's walk 10,000 steps in Mokpo.
- Eat a lot of good food. / - Yes, let's eat a lot of food.
That's right.
We won't be following a strict or busy schedule.
- We can stroll around there. / - Right.
- We can relax during the trip. / - That's right. I like it.
- Nilriri Manbo. / - Nilriri Manbo.
- I like the name. Nilriri Manbo. / - Nilriri Manbo.
- Okay. Okay. / - I think that's a good name.
If we lose, what will you do for a living?
- We won't lose. / - We won't lose.
- We're going to win. / - He's confident.
Everyone, please vote carefully.
A man's life is at stake.
There isn't much he can do to make a living.
- He doesn't have a proper post. / - I'm too old.
He doesn't have any post either.
When it comes to food in Jeollanam-do...
You can't miss out Mokpo.
Here, it's 3 steps and 1 food.
- My goodness. / - My gosh.
What's all this?
How many are there?
- That looks delicious. / - It's just getting started.
(The true city for the best eating show)
This is a cuisine.
(Endless parade of food)
We ate a lot.
Did you share all of your tips?
- What's up with your clothes? / - "Friend."
Were you guys wearing uniform?
The Mokpo small octopus is the best.
(A day isn't enough to try all of these dishes)
- Totally. / - Totally.
Is this why you brought me here?
I'll put my post on the line.
Around 220m.
If you take a right...
To break the prejudice that port cities only have
good seafood.
You're talking too much.
(Noh Junghun, a chatty travel writer)
(Cheonsik, the cute youngest who was born in 1977)
There you go acting up again.
He's lucky to have become a travel writer.
- He gives the best reactions. / - He's the best.
He's the youngest too.
The song changed all of a sudden.
(His looks even change the flow of the air)
It's pure.
(He's a man of deadly sentiments)
I love the fact that there's an ocean behind me.
(An naive good-looking guy, Shim Hyunbo)
- He gives the best explanations. / - Really?
Nilriri Manbo!
(Nilriri Manbo Tour in Mokpo)
What am I going to do? This is so awkward.
(Nilriri Manbo Tour, Day 1)
(Breakfast, trending alley)
(Rough lunch, aromatic dinner)
(Nilriri Manbo Tour, Day 2)
(Breakfast, ride along the coast, night of Mokpo)
(They gather at the train station in darkness)
Ta-da.
By the way, aren't we leaving too early, Junghun?
- What? / - Isn't this too early?
We gathered too early.
- The sun isn't even up yet. / - Exactly.
It's not even 4:30 a.m. yet.
- It's 4:25 a.m. / - It's 4:25 a.m.
4:25 a.m.
It's still dark.
You left at 4:25 a.m.?
- When is the first train? / - You left really early.
- Why did you leave so early? / - To eat a lot.
- To get there early? / - To eat a lot.
- To eat breakfast there. / - First train.
They want to have breakfast in Mokpo.
Today, I am going to... Didn't I tell you in advance?
We have to eat something every three steps we take.
- 3 steps and 1 food? / - That's right.
What are you talking about?
- Let's shout the name of our team. / - I like that.
- Alright. / - Nilriri...
Manbo!
- Let's go. / - Let's go.
Seriously.
(They set out to Mokpo)
I can't believe we're leaving at 4:25 a.m.
(Their trip on the first train has a fresh start)
It's nice that it's not crowded.
(2.5 hours to Mokpo Station from Yongsan)
- Mokpo isn't that far away. / - Yongsan Station.
It only takes 2 hours and 30 minutes.
- They left from Yongsan Station. / - Yes.
- I was surprised that it was close. / - It's quite close.
The sun must rise now.
- It's so pretty. / - That's right.
(In no time, the morning breaks)
(They arrive at Mokpo after climbing over Yudalsan)
- We've arrived in Mokpo. / - We've arrived in Mokpo.
We're here.
(After traveling for 2.5 hours, they're welcomed by)
The fall sky.
- The fall sky. / - The fall sky.
It's low and cloudy.
- What's up with the weather? / - It's low and cloudy.
- Where is your pedometer? / - We should turn it on.
- We'll start at 0 from Mokpo. / - We'll start at 0.
- We'll start here. / - I set it at zero now.
It's only 280m away from here.
Your hidden card prepared hidden breakfast!
Great, hidden breakfast.
What's our breakfast? I'll tell you after walking 280m.
(They start walking to find breakfast at 280m away)
- From here. / - Walk 280m from the station.
(4 minutes on foot from the station to the restaurant)
We keep finding stuff after short walks.
Turn right at the corner there.
You'll see it.
What are we having for breakfast?
7:30 a.m. No, 8 a.m. is a great time to have noodles.
- Noodles at 8 a.m.? / - Yes.
- What? 8 a.m.? / - Yes.
- That's the perfect breakfast. / - I understand.
- Seriously? / - You can just slurp them in.
- Are they spicy or refreshing? / - You can slurp it.
No, just like your lyrics, Hyunbo.
It's plain, subtle and bland.
It's noodles in cold soybean soup.
What?
- Who has that in the morning? / - It's famous there.
- It's delicious. / - I'd have that for breakfast.
- They make them really good. / - Isn't it for summer?
- But it's fall. / - What?
- It's fall now. / - It's the perfect season for it.
- It'd be great if it's delicious. / - It is?
The best noodles in cold soybean soup
I had was in Jeonju.
- Jeonju. / - My gosh, Jeonju.
- Jeolla-do's is the best. / - You'd go crazy for that.
They always serve you sugar too.
- You sprinkle sugar on top. / - Look at that.
(Fill it with nicely boiled soybeans)
(Soybeans are ground in a millstone)
(Only the soybean soup and noodles make up the dish)
That looks delicious.
- They don't serve you cucumbers. / - No, they don't.
- They don't? / - You don't need cucumbers.
- They don't put toppings in. / - That's nice.
They don't need help from the toppings.
- Do they sell this dish... / - That's right.
- All year along? / - That's interesting.
You have many combinations.
- Soybeans and black soybeans. / - Black soybeans.
You can choose either one. And then...
- Soybean soup? / - Soybean soup?
- Soybean soup. That's right. / - Soybean soup?
- Good restaurants sell that. / - They sell it in bottles.
I think the one with black soybeans must be better.
It's $2 more expensive.
I'll go with the black soybeans.
(The more expensive it is, the tastier it is)
- Do you want the hot soup? / - Hot black soybean soup.
I'll go with black soybeans.
Noodles in soybean soup should be...
- Cold? / - Yes, cold.
In that case,
I want you to taste a variety of dishes here.
I'll order noodles in cold soybean soup.
- I think... / - We can eat it all year round.
Seasonal dishes like noodles in cold soybean soup
sort of feel like...
A cold girlfriend.
All of a sudden?
- Because... / - At 8 a.m.?
That came out of nowhere.
But you don't have a girlfriend in real life.
- We just sat down. / - I heard you never had one.
Me? My last breakup was on April 7th, 2000.
- In 2000? / - What? In 2000?
- I'm joking. / - Before the World Cup in 2002?
Isn't that really pathetic that you memorized the date?
Everyone, that could be true.
He hasn't dated since 2000?
Don't do that.
I feel really bad because it might be true.
Anyway, we can only eat this in particular season.
Usually, during summer.
But here, you can eat this all the time.
It's convenient.
Here's our food.
(Noodles in soybean soup is served)
(The flavor of the soybeans will be the deciding factor)
- They make it from scratch. / - My goodness!
Can you tell it's good already?
How could that not be delicious?
- Right, it looks delicious. / - Look how creamy it is.
(Black soybean, $10, soybean, $8)
I don't see any toppings. There are no toppings.
No toppings.
It's the purity law for noodles in soybean soup.
How should we eat this?
- Here's my recommendation. / - How?
(How to enjoy noodles in soybean soup)
Carefully and with your whole heart,
hold the bowl with your two hands.
Don't apply too much or too little strength.
Isn't he too much?
I get the feeling that you're going too far with this.
He's a travel writer because it worked out for him.
- Taste the soup first. / - Okay. The soup?
(It's time to taste the soup)
(How does noodles in black soybean soup taste?)
(He's expressing his approval with his eyebrows)
- What is it? / - Look at his eyebrows.
It's a genuine reaction.
He's putting on that scary facial expression.
(He smiles right away as it's delicious)
- Isn't this great? / - This is great.
It must have been rich. Was it rich?
- Yes, it was. / - It looks so rich.
I ordered the hot black soybean soup.
- You ordered the hot one. / - How did that taste?
It wasn't too heavy at all. It was savory.
- The thickness... / - Right.
- It's not watery at all. / - Right.
- But it's not too thick either. / - I know, right?
(Savory, rich and thick soybean soup)
- Can I have a sip of your soup? / - Yes, yes.
- The soybean soup. / - The soybean soup.
It's thin.
It tastes different.
I can taste the soybeans from the soybean soup.
I can taste the black soybeans
from the black soybean soup.
- This is so interesting. / - Yeah?
Compared to the black soybean soup...
- The soybean soup is lighter. / - Yes.
- It's closer to the one we usually have. / - Right.
- Exactly. / - The black soybean soup is heavier.
- I can only see the soup. / - Yeah.
Right, the soup isn't too light or heavy.
It has the perfect thickness.
It falls right in the middle.
- He's right. / - That's a hard thing to pull off.
- That's right. / - We have sugar...
- And salt. / - Right.
- In Seoul, we add a bit of salt. / - Yes.
Why is there sugar here?
A lot of people in Jeolla-do add sugar into this.
- Really? / - They add sugar more than salt.
I don't think I need to season it more.
I think this is already seasoned.
- It's slightly seasoned with salt. / - Right?
Depending on your preference...
- You can add whatever you want. / - Okay.
But since we're in Mokpo...
Why don't we try the way locals do here?
Add sugar?
Yes, sugar.
You can add two spoons of sugar.
- What? / - You can add a lot of sugar.
- It's better than adding a bit. / - You should add a lot.
- Let me just add one spoon for now. / - Sure.
Add the sugar as you taste the change in flavors.
- Look at him. He's scared. / - Is this too little?
- You should add more. / - The locals here...
- Add big spoonfuls. / - Really?
- Scoop up a lot. / - That's why I added more.
- It was good. / - Right, that looks good.
(Sprinkle a bit of sugar on top)
(Sprinkle a lot of sugar on top)
(Mix the sugar in)
- It looks delicious. / - That's really delicious.
- This clip is like a work of art. / - That's really good.
- I'm hungry. / - The sweetness wakes you up.
- My gosh, look at that. / - It was my first time...
To have noodles in soybean soup for breakfast.
- Yes. / - But it was good.
It's really thick.
- It was good. / - Gosh.
(Now they try the noodles)
(It tastes so good, they hum)
It's interesting. It became more delicious.
It tastes more delicious. It's interesting.
(Yum)
(Bursts out laughing)
- I don't know if I should say this. / - It's delicious.
Noodles in soybean soup with sugar
tastes like noodles in red bean soup.
It does.
It really does.
- You're right. / - Because red bean is sweet.
- That's right. / - Yes.
It was similar but more savory.
- That's why people put sugar in it. / - Of course.
(Noodles in soybean soup is more flavorful with sugar)
This noodles are really interesting too.
- Aren't they? / - They are.
They aren't thin noodles or chewy noodles.
- They're somewhere between. / - Yeah.
- It's chewy. / - Exactly.
They're thin but they don't plop down.
The noodles are thinner than udon noodles.
- They're thin but firm. / - They're chewy.
People will think it's cream pasta.
- Carbonara. / - You're right.
Usually they pour soybean soup over the noodles.
- That's the usual feeling. / - Yes.
But with this one,
it's as if noodles were added to the soup.
More than anything.
I found out that noodles in soybean soup...
- Is good for breakfast. / - Yeah.
I was worried about eating this as breakfast.
But it's so good.
(They start the day with hearty breakfast)
(It looks like they might eat the bowls too)
- It's good without seasoning it? / - Yes, it is.
- It's already seasoned slightly. / - I see.
That looks good.
Would you order warm noodle soup again?
- Yes, I would. / - Really?
- I'm really curious. / - Is it in Seoul?
- I've never seen it. / - I've never tried it before.
(Where are they off to next in Mokpo?)
Now that we had a meal, we'll go for a dessert.
We'll have rice cake.
Rice cake?
- Rice cake for dessert? / - That's wrong.
It's a snack stand to be exact.
- A snack stand? / - Yes.
I think Junghun eats a lot.
There are a lot of rice cake cafes these days.
You had just had flour. Now you're having rice cake.
That place is only 500m away.
We had a hard time leaving Mokpo Station.
The second place is only 500m away
from Mokpo Station.
- So it's only 200m away from here. / - About 220m.
From the noodles in soybean soup place.
(They're only 200m apart)
We're still near Mokpo Station.
I can see Mokpo Station.
Mokpo Station right there.
(They're circling around Mokpo Station)
We're within 200m.
We got  here 2 hours ago but
we're still near Mokpo Station.
Our goal today is...
To get out of Mokpo Station.
- All three of them love talking. / - Yes.
That's very close.
We're here.
- What? / - We're here.
- Is this it? / - This is the place.
- This is it. / - Where?
- Mugwort rice cake. / - Mugwort rice cake.
This is what we'll have today.
Mugwort rice cake.
- Mugwort rice cake? / - Yes.
What is mugwort rice cake?
You'll be surprised.
- I've never seen such color. / - What's that?
You put red bean paste on mugwort rice cake.
- Yes. / - Then you pour rice syrup on top.
- Pour over it? / - Yes.
It like what's inside is applied on the outside.
Exactly. It has a filling and has stuff outside.
- What is that? / - That was good.
(Mugwort rice cake, $5)
Here it is.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Thank you. / - It's pretty.
(Excited)
It's pretty.
So this is mugwort rice cake.
- Doesn't it look pretty? / - Yes.
It's unique. I've never seen something like this.
Those who graduated from Mokpo Girls High School
still come back for this.
- Looks delicious. / - Sook, isn't that what you like?
I love that.
- I can eat 100 of them. / - But doesn't it...
- Look like fish cake? / - Fish cake?
They have regular rice cake too.
Anyway, Mokpo citizens love this
and this has been their favorite snack for a long time.
For example, Tongyeong is famous for honey bread.
- Mokpo is famous for this. / - Exactly.
- Let's eat. / - Go ahead.
This looks...
(Looks very sweet)
- Extremely sweet. / - Yes.
- It does. / - No.
- It's not that sweet. / - Is this rice syrup?
Yes, it is.
(He nervously takes a bite)
It's rice syrup.
(Yum)
(He takes a bite too)
It looks good.
(His face tells us that he's satisfied)
I have a female high schooler's palette.
- This is so good. / - I knew you'd like it.
Hyunbo has a female high schooler's taste.
Every female high school student in Mokpo
knows this place.
It's a really old snack stand.
You have a female high schooler's sensitivity.
Yes, I have.
It can't be clearly defined.
There's no line between mugwort rice cake
and red bean paste.
They kind of seem mixed.
So when you put it in your mouth,
the ingredients mix.
It's soft and moist.
It's perfect for dessert.
So we ate a lot of it.
(Simple appearance, amazing taste)
You can't use your hands.
You need a spoon because of the syrup.
- Yes. / - That's right.
You need to use a spoon because of the syrup,
so they called it rice cake for noblemen.
When you said we were going to
have rice cake for dessert...
I thought, "But I'm full."
- But it's satisfying. / - Yes.
It's good.
If it was regular rice cake without the syrup,
it would've been too much.
Exactly, because it'd stick to your mouth.
How?
(Like this)
- Did you like it? / - How much was it?
- $5. / - Is that it?
Sir, please order one more.
- One more? / - More?
- What? / - It was so good.
You have other things to eat though.
I said, "Who eats rice cake for dessert?" at first.
But I ordered one more.
You can eat a lot of it because
it's not that sweet even with all that syrup.
- Really? / - It's not that sweet.
- I actually don't like sweet stuff. / - Right.
Still it was so good.
- I couldn't stop eating. / - Their syrup must be good.
- Yes. / - That's right.
(Yummy and sweet)
(Junghun's dessert is a success)
It's hard to make mugwort rice cake.
So $5 isn't very expensive.
You can have rice cake very elegantly.
What's next?
It's a hidden point.
- What? / - A hidden point?
Third place. A hidden card.
I'll take you to a cafe
for a late morning coffee.
- Are we going to a franchised cafe? / - Gosh.
Stop that nonsense.
Alright. I wouldn't take you to a franchise.
Right.
Can I look forward to it?
It's a beautiful place.
How far?
About 890m.
Can we get away from Mokpo Station?
- Yes, we can get away. / - That's important.
We can't see Mokpo Station from there.
- You can't see it. / - Is that right?
The weather is amazing all of a sudden.
Look at that.
- The sky is blue. / - It's nice.
It got cleared up.
- We'll start the real Mokpo trip. / - Right.
(13 minutes from the snack stand to the cafe)
But this neighborhood...
- Has a different atmosphere. / - Yes.
Actually, this place is the main area
for the old Mokpo walking tour.
What you see on my right is...
Mokpo Modern History Museum 2.
- It's an old building. / - Yes.
(Mokpo Modern History Museum)
It was Oriental Development Company.
There are buildings left from Japanese colonial-era.
- It's like a film set. / - There are inns too.
Mokpo has the most Japanese colonial-era buildings.
They kept the hurtful memory.
They turned it into Mokpo Modern History Museum.
That's right.
I mentioned it earlier. What is this called again?
- Dark tourism. / - Dark tourism.
It's also called black tourism or grief tourism.
To remind us so that we don't repeat the sad history.
Mokpo needs questions and answers
that are related to history.
- It has a historical background. / - It's meaningful.
- We need to ask questions. / - Yes.
The cafe we're going to was an old Japanese house
that was built during the colonial era.
- Is that where we're going? / - Let's go.
- Is it here? / - Yes.
(Nilriri Manbo Tour's hidden card)
(Jeoksan Gaok cafe)
- Jeoksan. / - Jeoksan Gaok cafe.
Houses that were built and resided by Japanese
during the colonial era are called Jeoksan Gaok.
Any houses or property is called Jeoksan.
Which literally means enemy property.
Enemy property.
Jeoksan means enemy property.
(Houses owned by Japanese are called Jeoksan)
- That must feel weird. / - Yes.
I felt strange.
If we didn't know about history,
we would've just said, "That's pretty. That's different."
But knowing the history and background...
- Made me feel sad. / - Right.
- Because it's a painful history. / - Yes.
(Jeoksan Gaok cafe)
(An old Japanese house turned into a cafe)
They decorated the interior very well.
(This house belonged to a Japanese merchant)
They have old furniture and handmade linen items.
So it gives off foreign atmosphere.
(Jeoksan Gaok cafe is open from 11 a.m. to 10 p.m.)
(If you order a drink, you can use the dessert buffet)
Look at this. They haven't changed anything.
- Yeah. / - It even creaks.
That goes upstairs.
It's a sad history but it's good to remember it.
- Of course. We need to study it. / - It's good.
It's a very...
Different combination.
Outside is very traditional Japanese style.
(Unlike the traditional Japanese style exterior)
It's not just Japanese style.
Actually, the interior is very Western.
- It's European. / - Yes, it's a mix.
It's a mix of Western and Eastern styles.
It's very nicely decorated.
- But we can't just say it's pretty. / - Right.
- It's an odd feeling. / - It is.
In any case...
Unfortunately, for most of the cases,
people were busy trying to demolish...
- This style of building. / - Yes.
Well, it's probably because
the areas didn't get developed.
Whatever the reason may be...
These houses in Gunsan and Mokpo
are well-preserved.
As I mentioned earlier,
these cities present such high values
for modern cultural heritage.
My explanations are as good as Choi Taeseong.
- You're complimenting about yourself? / - Yes.
- Yours wasn't as good. / - Come on. Why don't you...
- Compliment me on my work? / - Alright.
(Nilriri Manbo Tour decided to take a short break)
- Thank you. / - Thank you.
Thank you.
- All three of them calmed down. / - Thank you.
- There's a balcony? / - My gosh.
- Isn't this a beautiful house? / - It's very beautiful.
If you want to live here, don't go. Live here.
(If you think the house is pretty, live here)
- The cafe was awesome. / - It was great.
- Drinking coffee outdoors is great. / - So amazing.
- It's popular among cafe-goers. / - That's true.
The breeze is so nice.
- The sunshine is great too. / - Right?
- All of us got quiet. / - I see.
- That was my favorite part. / - I agree.
(What is their next destination?)
Is our next stop a hidden card or not?
Our next destination.
That place...
Is a hidden card.
If you keep that up, we can't win this battle.
You say all of our destinations are hidden cards.
What is this?
If you continue this, they won't be our hidden cards.
Yeah.
What is this?
You say every place is a hidden card.
- If you continue to be like this, I might hide. / - What?
- I will hide. / - That'd be a real hidden card.
I can go into hiding, you know.
That would be our hidden card?
If you hide, we'll use internet.
(Where is their next destination?)
(14 minutes on foot from the cafe to the alley)
- Are you going to eat more? / - No, no.
(They set out to feel the ocean with the fall breeze)
We went for a walk.
(Before going to the alley)
Our trip was about walking and eating.
- Isn't this your first time here? / - Yes.
Right here.
- The coastal walk. / - The coastal walk.
It's my first time seeing the ocean
after getting off the station.
How many hours has it been?
I finally feel like I'm in Mokpo now that I'm here.
- This is a nice path to walk on. / - Right.
- That was great. / - Tides must come in all the way.
They made a nice trail to walk.
- Can you walk along the coast? / - Yes.
(This is Nilriri Manbo Tour's destination)
(Nilriri Manbo Tour's hidden card)
(The alley)
(This place got popular due to the movie, "1987")
- Really? / - I saw that movie.
- Was that Yoo Haijin's house? / - That's right.
- That was Kim Taeri's house. / - In the movie.
- Yes, I saw that. / - That neighborhood is so pretty.
- The house Gang Dongwon visited. / - Yes!
This place is near Seosan-dong and Ongeum-dong.
This neighborhood is so pretty.
This reminds me Yeonhui-dong.
- That's right. / - The houses are similar.
This is the real spot, actually.
- It's near Yonsei University. / - That's right.
- The atmosphere is similar. / - Right.
- I didn't know. / - The moment he saw this area...
- He said two areas looked similar. / - Yes.
The scriptwriter for the movie
stumbled upon this neighborhood.
That's how this place ended up in the movie.
- What a beautiful neighborhood. / - Sihwa alley.
It's named "Sihwa" because it has poems and art.
Is that so?
- Can you see the end of the road? / - Yes.
- Can you see a small store? / - Yes.
- I see. Yeonhui's Store. / - You can see it, right?
That was in the movie, "1987."
That's the place.
It says so right there.
- Right on the storefront sign. / - That's right.
"Cigarettes, popsicles, liquor."
The very look of it looks so old-fashioned.
I love those three things.
(Cigarettes, popsicles, liquor)
- Do you want to go inside? / - Should we?
This is really fun.
(It's a space set up with things from the past)
- It's set up like the old days. / - My gosh.
- You're right. / - Juice jars from back in the days.
- It's hard to find those. / - Isn't this awesome?
- I can't find those juice jars anymore. / - Yeah.
- Everyone had one in their fridge. / - In the summer.
- By the way... / - Stickers from the old days.
Do you remember this coin bank?
- I see. / - I used to have one of those.
The coin bank.
(A walk down memory lane while looking around)
When we were young,
we had this lunchbox with a spoon inside...
- And put it in our backpacks. / - Right.
When we ran...
- It used to make a rattling sound. / - Yeah.
Usually, moms used to pack...
- Rice and side dishes in this box. / - Exactly.
- I had a fried egg on the bottom. / - Right.
I put my fried egg on top of rice. I put it on top.
- I couldn't do that. / - He's so odd.
Gosh, so nostalgic.
It's near Seosan-dong and Ongeum-dong.
Actually, it's a fishing village.
It's a fishing village on the hill.
How should I put it?
This is the authentic scenery you can see in Mokpo.
If you want to see this scenery,
you have to come to this old town.
But after the movie, "1987,"
this village started to stand out more.
(You can rent old school uniforms and other props)
By the way, the uniforms...
I just looked at them.
- They look really small. / - They are small.
They are tiny. Do you have bigger uniforms?
- In bigger sizes? / - No uniforms here will fit you.
(School uniforms that remind us of "Friend")
"Friend." That movie was really fun.
("Mokpo Friends")
I knew that I was pushing it.
I think you went too far.
I knew it. The actor is the best at this.
He was good. He was the best.
Only actors can pull it off.
- He looks awkward. / - He looks slightly awkward.
(3 friends show up in Mokpo)
(The journey is like traveling back in time)
(Showing in theaters)
(The end)
I want to see the three of you on "Gag Concert."
(The trio is wanted on "Gag Concert")
- They make the perfect team. / - Three Stooges.
(Nilriri Manbo Tour climbs up Sihwa alley)
Just like the name, there are poems.
And drawings.
They are all over the alley.
That's where the name comes from?
Yes, that's why it's named Sihwa alley.
(Sihwa alley in Seosan-dong)
Some of the residents
wrote the poems and drew the paintings.
Some of them are written by poets.
People actually still live there.
The residents drew these.
- They did? / - Yes.
- It's similar to the one in Busan. / - Stop talking.
- Like Gamcheon Culture Village. / - That's it.
Although it's smaller than that one
but it's cozy and cute.
It's a perfect alley to go for a slow stroll.
Since people still live there,
you should be careful on your walk.
(The three of them climb up as they admire the alley)
The drawing style is very innocent.
(This time, they walk 1.4km)
We have to walk for 1.4km. About 1.5km.
- We can easily walk there. / - I see.
(We'll walk again?)
At times like this, what do we need?
A fast mode of transportation.
- Taxi. / - We'll go by taxi.
I'll feed you some delicious food.
What could it be? What will we eat? I'm curious.
- It will be amazing. / - Right?
- Hello. / - Hello.
- We can go now. / - Okay.
(They set out to their next destination)
I'm hungry. I want to eat something delicious.
We're heading to Yeonghae-dong 1-ga.
Isn't it really close from here, sir?
You'll be there in no time.
- How come you know everything? / - Yeah.
In which area are you not well-informed? Sports?
(Something I don't know much about)
- What women want. / - I knew it.
- That's right. / - He has a point.
I knew he'd say that.
His last relationship ended in 2000.
(It gets quiet in the car)
(I couldn't get married)
(6 minutes by taxi from the alley to the restaurant)
(If I keep going, where will I be?)
Alright, we're here.
We're here.
- We have arrived. / - Please drive safely.
- This is it. Yes. / - That restaurant?
Remember what I said?
- Is that short rib patty? / - Yes, and...
- This is the restaurant. / - This is the one.
- Here it is. / - This is it.
- You ate short rib patties too? / - This is the place.
- Will it beat the one from Danyang? / - Seriously.
Did Jinah go home?
You've gotten awfully quiet.
He must be tired.
- You're not sleeping, are you? / - He's exhausted.
He's been sleeping for 20 minutes.
Let's try this.
Hello.
There is a short rib patty restaurant...
- That's been running for 57 years. / - Is that so?
Where's the birthplace of short rib patties in Korea?
- Short rib patties... / - People name Danyang for it.
I think this restaurant's short rib patties
are the best in the country.
- It's that good? / - Let me explain.
Their patties are a bit similar to Sikyung.
- Sung Sikyung? / - Pardon?
(Sung Sikyung?)
I guess it tastes arrogant.
- Hey, you. / - "It tastes arrogant?"
"It tastes arrogant."
(What a neat comparison)
- He's very masculine with us. / - That's right.
This short rib patty is just like that.
- I'm curious. / - Should we take Sikyung there?
- Should we ask him to join us? / - He'd go crazy.
(Nilriri Manbo Tour's hidden card)
If he can confidently say that it's the best...
- Then it must be. / - It was.
- That restaurant is a real gem. / - If he says so.
- That place is no joke. / - What is that?
- They grill the bone too? / - It's not what we're used to.
- The bones... / - On top of briquettes?
- They don't grill it too much. / - On briquettes.
They grill it just long enough.
That's why it's still juicy.
Goodness, look at that.
(Battle Trip Part 2 will be aired soon)
(Nilriri Manbo Tour's hidden card)
(Short rib patty)
(Marinated beef rib patty is casually put on the grill)
(It's grilled on blazing briquette fire)
(Short rib patty)
- Here we are. / - We're finally here.
What do you think? Do you think it'll be delicious?
How do I know if it'll be delicious?
I don't see anything here.
It's great timing though.
After running around in the uniform,
I've become hungry.
- I'm a bit... / - It's great timing.
We're on a trip now. Let's have a beer.
- This is a walking tour. / - Exactly.
- Awesome. / - Nilriri.
- Manbo. / - Manbo.
(Some beer before the short rib patty is served)
This is what's good about traveling on foot.
That's right.
(This is the beauty of traveling on foot)
It's here.
- Already? / - Gosh.
- It's here. / - Already?
- Short rib patty and beer together. / - Is it that big?
- It's perfectly cooked. / - It looks amazing.
It's perfectly cooked.
It's so big.
It looks like a huge portion.
- That's one portion. / - Really?
- What? / - Is that for one person?
Yes, it's for one person.
I told you.
- Usually, it's shared by two though. / - It's for two.
Most customers can't finish it alone.
- I love it. / - $25 for one person.
- It's a little expensive. / - It's not cheap though.
(Short rib patty set meal, $25 per person)
This must be your hidden card.
It's almost my hidden card.
Almost.
- What does that even mean? / - It's very close.
- It can be your hidden card. / - Exactly.
(How to enjoy short rib patty like a wild man)
First, smell it with your nose.
(They take a smell of the dish)
- You can't stop. / - They have one each.
That smell is indescribable.
- Look at his face. / - It was a graceful smell.
You must try this.
(How does it taste?)
Look at this.
(The frown means it's delicious)
It's hard to find a short rib patty
that has such a texture.
Right?
(He can't help smiling)
(It's delicious, isn't it?)
(He's touched again)
It's amazing.
If usual short rib patties are submissive...
- That's right. / - This rib patty is...
Fighting against me in my mouth.
I know.
(The short rib patty resists in the mouth)
No other short rib patty has such a texture.
- It's hard to cook it perfectly. / - Exactly.
It has a very rough and unique texture.
You look so happy.
(The patty is juicy and the sauce is sweet)
Look at the chunks of the patty.
- I know. / - The patty consists of the chunks.
Usually, it's hard to pick up the patty with chopsticks.
- This must be chewed thoroughly. / - Exactly.
You can't just swallow it.
- The moment I'm about to swallow it... / - That's true.
The patty talks to me.
"You can't swallow me yet."
- "You'd better chew me more." / - The patty talks.
That short rib patties do not melt in your mouth.
It's not like that at all.
- So this has a nice firm texture. / - It's really chewy.
(Feeling absorbed)
Usually, short rib patty is not stuck to the rib.
They remove the meat from the bone.
Usually, short rib patty doesn't
come with the rib stuck to it.
The sauce isn't too sweet.
- No. / - It could be too sweet sometimes.
- I don't like sweet meat. / - I know.
It's perfectly seasoned.
Junghun, I really love it.
This kind of short rib patty
doesn't sell on home shopping.
(Laughing)
- What? / - I think I should...
- You're working here. / - Get the owner's number.
Cheonsik wants to sell this on home shopping.
- Cheonsik is eyeing this item. / - I wanted to launch it.
This restaurant is over 50 years old.
It's an old restaurant. Over half a century.
(Cheonsik's Battle Trip, it's not like the usual rib patties)
(Fantastic short rib patty for wild men!)
($25 per portion)
The real hidden card is coming next.
There's one more.
(They stayed in this restaurant for a while)
Now I'm getting full.
We're now traveling the longest distance in this tour.
What do we need then?
- Taxi. / - We're going there by taxi.
(They ride a taxi for about 16 minutes)
- Now... / - What now?
To wrap up our day in Mokpo beautifully,
we're going to drink a little bit of alcohol.
- Something light. / - Let's go simple.
I don't need to give you any hint about this.
You'll know it by its smell.
- The smell of the food? / - You'll smell it.
- We can smell it? / - Yes.
- Don't go to Heuksando. / - Fermented skate?
It's a food to eat with alcohol.
Fermented skate is delicious.
Let's wrap up the day here.
It goes amazing with rice wine.
(Nilriri Manbo Tour's hidden card)
(Fermented skate dish)
(Forget all the other fermented skate)
- This is a skate's nose. / - What's that?
- This was amazing too. / - What's that in the middle?
- It's a skate's nose. / - Nose?
It's soy sauce marinated crabs.
- Marinated crabs. / - It's a set meal.
That's on the house.
- The king of side dishes. / - It comes with the main.
- Marinated crab is served freely. / - Look at that.
It comes with the main dish.
(Fermented skate set, $85)
That's a meal for four.
It's very cheap.
They serve skate from Korea, it's not expensive.
Marinated crabs are included.
- $85 for 4. / - It's a good price.
In Seoul, skate from Korea would be...
- Over $100. / - It's more than $100.
Skate isn't cheap.
This is fresh skate from Heuksando...
- That is barely fermented. / - I see.
- Let me make a tower. / - Let's do it.
- It's fermented skate combo. / - Jeollanam-do kimchi.
The color of the kimchi looks beautiful.
That aged kimchi looks really delicious.
That's fermented skate.
(Aged kimchi,  boiled pork, fermented skate)
Let's have a bite and drink.
This is my favorite.
Clinking the glasses while holding food.
Having the food ready.
- Say our team name. / - Nilriri Manbo.
It's a bit more transparent than
the fermented skate I know.
Right? This skate is...
Not fermented much.
It's more like raw fish.
This isn't that pungent.
- No, it's not. / - This is fresh.
Some people might not realize
that this is fermented skate.
- I can see that. / - For real.
- This can be any deboned raw fish. / - That's true.
(It's like a regular deboned raw fish)
It's very fresh like regular raw fish.
It doesn't have a strong smell at all.
It doesn't burn your throat or nose.
Those who haven't tried fermented skate
would like this.
You're right.
When you eat fermented skate,
you usually focus on the smell
and don't think much about
its texture.
- But today, I recognized... / - You're right.
It's very chewy and bouncy.
My molars bounce it back when I chew it.
There are bones but they don't feel like bones.
It's like a very hard chewing gum.
(That's an amazing way to put it)
- You know what I mean. / - Yes.
(Fermented skate is like a chewing gum)
It goes well with sesame oil as well.
- I love sesame oil. / - It's served as well.
- It's good with just salt too. / - Like croaker.
- It's delicious that way too. / - That's how experts eat.
I usually don't eat fermented skate
but I'd like to try this one.
Enjoy.
(After eating fermented skate, they drink rice wine)
(It smells nice)
It goes down very nicely, doesn't it?
(This is amazing)
This is so good.
When I saw its color, I thought it'd be like...
- Pumpkin rice wine. / - Look at that.
It's not pumpkin rice wine?
- It's made of honeysuckle. / - Honeysuckle.
- It's a little bitter. / - I see.
(Bitter honeysuckle rice wine)
- Right. / - I like that it's not so sweet.
Yet it has a rich flavor.
This restaurant has great soy sauce marinated crabs.
Does that come with fermented skate?
Yes, it's in the set.
It looks delicious.
(He takes a big bite)
(It's delicious)
Personally,
I don't like the saltiness of marinated crabs.
It's marinated with soy sauce. If it's salty...
- I see what you mean. / - I don't like it too salty.
- This one is flavorful. / - It is.
- It's pretty good. / - You're right. It's flavorful.
We're here for fermented skate
but you can eat soy sauce marinated crabs too.
Seriously, it's too good for it to be just a side dish.
I thought I was full but I can eat more.
(They cleanse their palate with rice wine)
- It must be delicious. / - It was really delicious.
It must be very hard to resist the food.
It's not like you'll be on a diet when you travel.
- That's the sesame oil. / - Here's the sesame oil.
- Have you tried it? / - Of course.
I think the owner prepared
something stronger for us.
Later, could you please bring us the strong one?
Something that'd make us cry.
(You should taste the real fermented skate here)
- It's a strong one. / - It's like cheese.
The color is different.
You can smell it already when she brings it in.
Of course it's different.
It's fermented for a month.
It tastes good when it's fermented.
You're right.
Only masters can enjoy it. I can't even eat it.
This is the scent I've wanted.
This is the smell.
This is it.
(Nervous)
- Is this the smell you've wanted? / - Yes.
I like the smell.
(He can feel the pungent smell of fermented skate)
- That's the smell. / - It smells like the bathroom.
It will cure a sinus cold.
(Blissful?)
The color looks totally different.
This is transparent, and this is not.
- It's totally different. / - The color is different.
- Look at the color. / - Why is it so different?
(The difference is clearly visible to the naked eye)
(What does the skate fermented for 30 days taste like?)
Seriously...
This is the most exciting moment...
- Of the day. / - Really?
Without the sauce.
Mr. Noh seems to love that.
He just eats it?
- Without sauce? / - I don't need the sauce.
He really loves fermented skate.
(Calm and peaceful)
He doesn't budge an inch.
It's peaceful like a nap on Sunday.
It's so peaceful.
(They are curious about the taste of fermented skate)
It's skate fermented for 30 days.
I'll try.
Try it.
(He just dips it in salt to appreciate the taste of skate)
He's a novice.
Junghun eats it so well.
He can't eat it.
(They understand how he feels)
- It was so strong. / - I know how he feels.
- It was so strong. / - He breathed in.
You can feel it as you breathe in.
He's a novice.
Junghun eats it so well.
Why did you spit it back out?
It touched my uvula.
It's still a bit pink in the middle.
(He tries it for real)
(Hyunbo is doing better than expected)
- I thought... / - He could eat 10 pieces.
(There it is)
You can feel it a bit later.
That's when you should drink rice wine.
Do you like it?
This feels different from a cough.
It's not like a cough.
It comes from the diaphragm.
Like this.
(Is it that bad?)
I'm excited.
Cheonsik, you've tried fermented skate before, right?
I like fermented skate but...
The smell has great implications.
(Cheonsik tastes it with just a bit of salt as well)
I want to blow the smell off.
- Not because it's hot. / - Wait.
It's against the rule.
(A foul)
(He finally takes a bite)
I'm actually...
You have to chew it before you swallow it.
- I really like fermented skate. / - You should...
Chew it at least 20 times.
You have to wait a while.
(Peaceful)
For about 40 seconds.
(Breathing hard)
He's breathing harder.
(They burst into laughter)
His nose seems to have changed.
(The day passes as they fight with fermented skate)
You should eat fermented skate with some kimchi...
- Instead of sesame oil and salt. / - That's right.
And with some boiled pork.
- Boiled pork. / - You should eat it with them.
Then kimchi neutralizes the smell.
- That's right. / - It tastes better that way.
(It's not over yet)
It's not over yet.
Only a day has passed.
We only watched them eat.
- They went there to eat. / - We went there to eat.
- We prepared a lot, right? / - You did.
We prepared a lot.
This feels great.
(They don't stop laughing on the second day)
What is going on?
Gosh, what is that?
I love that place.
It looks amazing.
I like things like this.
I love the colors.
Mokpo is the best.
(The night view is a lot flashier than the day)
(Alcohol can't be missed)
(And)
I love it.
- This is unbelievable. / - It's great, isn't it?
It's great?
- Where are they? / - You could come here...
On the train just to eat this.
- You could. / - Yeah.
This is just perfect.
(Nilriri Manbo Tour, Day 2)
(Breakfast, ride along the coast, night of Mokpo)
(The clear sky welcomes them on the 2nd day)
(They greet the morning sun of Mokpo)
The sun is up and high. You got up so late.
That's because we let loose and had a drink last night.
You drank with us.
- He drank more than us. / - He pretends he didn't.
He drank a lot.
They are all swollen.
- They are. / - We were swollen a lot.
We ate a lot.
I got up after a sound sleep.
- And I saw it all cleared up. / - I know.
- It's amazing. / - Look at the sky.
It's beautiful.
Mokpo is a small city, so we didn't need to hurry
and we slept enough.
And we got up late.
When would I sleep in like that?
Because of the baby, you can't sleep in.
A father of two children can't sleep in, right?
I have to get up at least by 8 a.m.
We can have an intensive trip here.
Even if we get up late,
we don't need to hurry.
We talked about this before the trip.
- I want to walk slowly. / - That's right.
Anyway, since we got up late,
we should have breakfast before lunchtime.
Are you sure you can handle it?
What is it?
- What is it? / - Can you handle it?
Is this your hidden card?
That's right. It's unknown to the public.
It's been hidden.
They look slimmer here before the trip.
He's not swollen at all before the trip.
I got puffy in a day.
I actually...
Went to Mokpo again a few days ago
because it was so great.
I will show you some pictures of the food I had there.
- Here. / - I'm excited.
This is...
- What I had on the last day. / - It looks delicious.
- I went there a while ago. / - What is that?
I think the highlight of the food of Jeollanam-do
is a meal set.
- You're right. / - It's amazing.
- I love it. / - Me too.
- I think it's about $12. / - Right.
About $12 to $15.
- It was only $8. / - $8?
- What? / - Can you believe it? It's only $8.
- How many side dishes? / - 18 side dishes.
- Did you say 18? / - Total.
- For breakfast? / - Yes.
You still get 16 side dishes for $8 even if you go alone.
It has to be at least $10?
Why is it only $8?
(Nilriri Manbo Tour's hidden card)
(A meal set)
(Around 20 side dishes)
(The greatest happiness you can get for $8)
There's no single dish you wouldn't like.
There are restaurants who serve many dishes...
- That aren't so good. / - Yeah.
Egg roll.
They make the egg roll to order.
That's a lot.
Don't egg rolls cost over $8 in tent bars in Seoul?
- Exactly. / - It's about $10.
It even costs $12 to $15 at some restaurants.
That's right.
(The hidden card of hidden cards)
I go to a Korean restaurant to have a meal set
at least once.
A meal set is great.
- It is. / - It's great.
A Korean table d'hote is expensive
but a meal set is cheap.
I can't order a Korean table d'hote alone.
While a Korean table d'hote is like a feast table...
- A meal set is like mom's cooking. / - Right.
I should go there before this episode airs.
Sook just said she should go there before
this episode airs.
Before this is aired.
Once this is aired, people would line up there.
Mokpo is a 4-hour drive.
It looks amazing.
(The side dishes keep coming)
This deserves to be the hidden card.
This is another level.
I wonder how they even profit.
There won't be much profit.
- It's her heart. / - She's just generous.
She's generous.
I will show you how they served us the rice.
- It's so full. / - Right.
It looks like the rising sun.
And we had more rice.
When I was a kid, I drew a bowl of rice just like that.
People used to give rice like that in the past.
Braised cutlassfish as a side dish?
Usually, this is served as a main dish.
(Braised cutlassfish)
It's braised cutlassfish.
- They serve braised cutlassfish? / - It's in season.
It has the taste of mom's cooking.
I like braised cutlassfish served in a restaurant
but this doesn't taste like that.
It's more like mom's cooking.
It's really good.
(Braised cutlassfish is rarely served in a meal set)
(They cook it off hand with fresh ingredients)
Cutlassfish from Jeju-do is better than
one from Mokpo.
Jeju-do's cutlassfish is different to Mokpo's.
- It's huge and delicious. / - Jeju-do is best.
It's huge and delicious.
We haven't even touched these side dishes yet.
They serve about 20 side dishes.
(They don't even know what to eat first)
A good thing about a meal set is
that they serve different dishes every day.
(They serve different dishes each season)
I think this is the best thing
I can get with $8.
It has all kinds of dishes.
They also serve grilled yellow corvina.
Even yellow corvina?
(Grilled yellow corvina)
It's amazing. What's that? Is it seasoned skate?
- Seasoned young skate. / - Seasoned young skate?
- This is seasoned eggplant. / - Seasoned eggplant.
It's so delicious.
Every dish looks so good.
It's spicy marinated crab.
(There's nothing lacking)
And there was something with clams.
- Right. / - Where is it?
- What's the finishing stroke? / - This is the best.
- That's Manila clams, right? / - Oh, this. Yes.
Did you order this separately?
- No, it's included in the set. / - Isn't that $20?
It's included in the meal set.
- It's $8 per person. / - Manila clams are expensive.
(It's the hidden menu with a clean taste)
It's so cheap.
Because you guys drank the day before,
it must've been so good.
- We drank for that. / - We don't like to drink normally.
(They drank against their will to have that)
The Manila clams look big.
- They are chewy. / - They're big.
- You're right. / - They are big.
The soup must be so good.
(They each have a taste)
This is amazing.
Isn't it good?
- This is perfect after drinking. / - I know...
Cheonsik very well. He's not faking.
- Like a baby. / - After having a sip...
- He seems like he wants to drink more. / - Exactly.
(He takes another sip because he was so surprised)
It's refreshing, right?
(It's blissful)
- It's pure. / - It's pure?
It tastes like water and Manila clams.
But how can it taste so smooth?
(First time eating such a pure tasting clam soup)
This is a meal on its own.
- It's a meal. / - As you eat the side dishes...
And then take a sip of the Manila clam soup...
- It clears up everything. / - Yes, it clears it up.
The surprising thing is that,
you can choose the Manila clam soup, kimchi stew,
bean paste stew or cutlassfish soup for the main dish.
- I want to have everything. / - That's right.
Kimchi stew will be good with that too.
You can tell by the kimchi that it will be good.
Actually, even a simple soup
tastes different.
It just tastes simple, honest, unsophisticated
and original.
If I could, I would take this out on the go.
- The soup is so amazing. / - Really?
(They want it by their side when they're hung-over)
If you eat that when you're about to catch a cold,
it will go away.
- That's right. / - It's 100%.
- Clam soup. / - $8 including the Manila clam soup?
- That's right. / - $8 per person.
It's unbelievably cheap.
There's a reason why this is the main highlight.
- Right? / - I agree.
- It's completely right. / - It's completely right.
- It feels so good. / - Yes.
It really is.
That place is amazing.
They even gave me Manila clam soup
when I went there by myself.
Look at how much clams they give you!
Even for a table for one.
It's worth taking a train to here just to eat this.
It couldn't get better than this for breakfast.
- Is it that good? / - Is it that good?
- Yes, I could go there. / - Is it that good?
It's possible.
I haven't cleared a bowl of rice like this before.
I think it's the most I've ever had for breakfast.
It was the biggest portion of rice that
I've ever had for breakfast as an adult.
I'm serious.
Who eats breakfast with rice piled this high?
They don't.
It should be hard to eat a lot after
you ate so much last night.
I'll have to go there tomorrow.
It's my first time seeing Hyunbo sweat while eating.
There are so many dishes.
Look at those Manila clams.
- That really looks good. / - It must be good.
- I want to go again. / - It's $8.
It's amazing for $8.
- It's $24 for 3 people. / - That's right.
- I already set things up. / - Really?
- Do we move? / - Should we go?
- Thank you for the food. / - Thank you for the food.
This was amazing.
This is the first time that they're using their bodies.
Come here.
Look at how skinny he is before he left.
Before he was on this trip.
- She's so cute. / - Oh, my.
- She's so big now. / - She's so pretty.
Say, "Please show a lot of love for Battle Trip."
- She's so pretty. / - She must look after her mom.
Please show a lot of love for Battle Trip.
- Smile. / - She's so cute.
She's so cute.
Zoom this in.
- What is that? / - I had to look for some activities.
A nightclub?
- A nightclub? / - He's wary of his wife.
Do they really have things like this?
Both of them will like this.
They don't like to move.
We should drive around the sea in a convertible.
- They will like it. / - A convertible.
- Let's do this. / - In Mokpo?
Cheonsik, you like cars, right?
- I will really do. / - It's perfect for a coastal road.
Junghun hates to move.
(Driving a convertible on a coastal road)
A convertible on a coastal road.
That will be like art.
- I just want the clam soup. / - Me too.
- I feel like it. / - Where can you get it in Seoul?
I suddenly became so hungry.
- The reason I brought you here... / - Yes?
ls because of the hidden card for activity.
Are we finally doing something?
I'm imitating you.
At this sea that is spread in front of our eyes...
We will drive around openly.
- With what? / - A convertible?
(Driving a convertible on a coastal road)
- Yes. / - I have a bad feeling.
- That can't be it. / - He won't make fun of us like this.
That can't be it.
Hyunbo, you should get in this.
Junghun, get in the red one.
What is this?
How romantic is this?
Is it really that?
It was really that.
(You can comfortably enjoy the coastal road)
It's perfect for a date course.
Those toy convertibles are for babies.
- This is your activity? / - It was a really timid activity.
I was joking earlier.
The activities are this way.
As you can see, there are bicycles and everything.
Both of you should ride a tandem bicycle
because Junghun only rides planes around the world.
He's not that good at driving.
- I can't drive. / - No, you can't.
You need a driver's license for this.
Do you need a driver's license?
- Safety is important. / - Of course.
You should always wear safety helmets.
- Grab it like this. Be careful. / - Yes.
(Electric bicycle, $15 for 30 minutes)
- I prepared a lot, right? / - You prepared properly.
I told you I prepared a lot.
It feels good.
(Let's go)
(They finally show off their coolness)
- What is that? / - What is that?
(The studio is filled with laughter)
I didn't feel good while I was riding that.
It's not that nice. What is that?
(What are they laughing at?)
Only Cheonsik got to ride a cool bicycle.
That's an electric bicycle too?
Their back and belly are stuck together.
They were.
(Hahaha)
What will you do with your hands?
(Even they think that they look funny)
How could you do this to me?
They're cute.
How is that cute?
It looks like a tricycle.
It looks really dirty.
Are both of your hands really around his waist?
I really didn't feel good at that moment.
Did you bring me here to do this?
I can't believe this.
He's evil.
(The cute tandem bicycle moves slowly)
Mokpo is the best.
Where would you drive along the coastal road like this?
Only he rode the cool bicycle.
Cheonsik, this is the maximum speed.
(Hahaha)
Is this the maximum speed?
It feels like Junghun is pulling me from behind.
Are you guys together?
(It's so funny that he can't speak)
I'm scared.
- That is the worst. / - What is he doing?
- Gosh. / - It's so tragic.
The person behind is bigger.
I think I saw this in a cartoon.
I'm scared.
- I'm scared. / - Is this what you wanted?
We came all the way to Mokpo to do this?
- You can't sing ballads anymore. / - What is this?
You think we're funny, right?
Look at him running away because he's embarrassed.
- I should get a girlfriend soon. / - They're too close.
It's surprising that both of them could even fit.
They didn't fit. They were crammed in there.
It's quite fast.
(They're still positive)
- It feels cool. / - It feels cool.
It feels cool.
(The three of them are enjoying fall properly)
It feels nice.
It feels cool.
(It feels cool)
What is this?
It's so funny.
There's a really nice place here as well.
- Are we going to walk? / - It's called Gatbawi.
Can we air this?
They enjoyed everything.
It was so nice. I really liked it.
- Here? / - It's here.
- Gatbawi? / - Yes, it's Gatbawi.
The rock looks like Buddhist monks wearing a gat.
It's one of Mokpo's representative scenic spots.
There's a footpath.
If you go around it, you can see Gatbawi.
If it rains a lot, the path gets submerged under water.
It got cracked because of the sea water.
(Mokpo's natural sculptures)
- It's interesting. / - How is that possible?
The waves come this way.
Maybe that's how it was made.
This is a natural masterpiece...
- That represents Mokpo. / - A natural sculpture.
You have to see this before you go.
It looks like someone
put a gat on the rocks on purpose.
- But nature made this. / - That's right.
- It's so interesting. / - Isn't it so interesting?
- It was made from sea water and wind. / - Wind.
And a long, long time.
- It's a sculpture made by nature. / - That's right.
Since we're here...
Let's take a photo as this represents Mokpo.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3.
(Let our friendship continue for a long time)
(The sun sets as their Mokpo trip ends)
(Rain is starting to fall gently)
It's the last itinerary already.
- It rained. / - It rained for us to drink.
- The atmosphere is so amazing. / - That timing.
- That's right. / - They want you to drink alcohol.
I like parasols that are that color.
The one with red, blue and yellow.
It's already the last itinerary of our trip.
- The weather can't make up its mind. / - Yeah.
This trip was full of variety.
It was rainy and sunny.
I feel a little tired but we should keep this feeling...
- To finish this trip beautifully... / - That's right.
- With the last hidden card. / - Hidden view.
- The weather is helping them. / - Yeah.
They're not going to anywhere random.
It was good for 3 men. How good will it be for lovers?
This is so pretty.
It's a cart bar where you can see...
- Mokpo Bridge. / - Cart bars.
- You don't have to go to Fukuoka. / - That's right.
- The atmosphere is amazing. / - It's dreamy.
It's a pity that three men are here together.
It's so pretty.
Rain was gently falling,
so a dreamy atmosphere was created.
It made it even prettier.
Let's have a last drink while watching...
- The pretty panorama. / - Let's do that.
Let's end our trip.
I'm 100% confident that if we make Kangnam choose
between Danyang and Mokpo, he will choose Mokpo.
Kangnam, just come this way.
- Is he betraying his father? / - Yes.
Danyang is the place that made you gain weight.
That's right.
(It's popular during chilly fall)
(Spicy fish roe soup, $22)
- It's small octopus. / - Raw octopus.
Small octopus is good during fall.
- Fall small octopus is good. / - They sell that there?
Small octopus is a health food.
(Food that go well with cart bar)
Mokpo small octopus tastes amazing.
How could you eat so much?
- You should eat bit by bit. / - It was stuck together.
- It was so strong. / - I want to drink alcohol.
There's a reason why he doesn't have a girlfriend.
- Nilriri Manbo. / - Nilriri Manbo.
(You can't leave alcohol out from an occasion like this)
(They empty it right away)
Old men always drink bottoms up.
It's like soda.
Before the trip, we promised each other
that we would eat 1 meal every 3 steps.
We promised 10,000 steps.
- Let's see how many steps we took. / - Finally.
3, 2, 0.
(How many steps did they make?)
10,649 steps.
(They successfully walked more than 10,000 steps)
- We did it. / - We made 10,648 steps.
Even if we ate that much...
We barely made it.
We are just punks, right?
We exceeded that number
even though we ate so much.
You could drink alcohol endlessly there.
- It's so pretty. / - The air is clean.
The view is nice...
- And it's raining. / - Perfect for the finale.
- It's like a movie. / - This is so nice.
I think to go to a cart bar for the last is nice.
- I think it's nice. / - Yes.
The mix of the sea and the lighting from the bridge.
You won't get drunk if you drink by the sea.
If Sikyung was there with them...
- It would've been perfect. / - It would've.
- It appeals to your senses. / - That's right.
It's tasteful and it feels so nice since it's raining.
Look. Night, rain, bridge, alcohol.
What more do we need?
(Impressed)
He looks so cool.
Your face looks so small.
- That's so cool. / - That's a photo of a lifetime.
My background is the sea.
My background is the night view of Mokpo.
(They become very sensitive)
(They are completely immersed in the amazing view)
Didn't they shoot Junghun?
I took them there but how could they not shoot me?
How could they do that?
He was even waiting for it.
- What happened? / - He really waited for it.
- They shot it... / - Yes.
But the producer said, "Let's edit it out."
He was looking forward to the end so much.
(They are completely immersed in the amazing view)
1 night and 2 days can be
very short depending on the way you look at it.
- We didn't drive. / - That's right.
We moved by train
and we could take our time looking around.
We had a beer during lunch yesterday too. It was nice.
We had Junghun as a hidden card.
- That's right. / - He researched for everything.
A trip for three men is really cool.
Junghun's been to 70 countries around the world.
So I thought he wouldn't know much about Korea.
- I was mistaken. / - This was not good.
This was a mistake.
I can hear the votes dropping.
- He did a really good job... / - That's right.
As a hidden card.
- Let's chant for the last time. / - Okay.
- Say cheers... / - Okay.
- And go back to Seoul. / - Alright.
Our trip reintroduced Mokpo for Battle Trip.
Nilriri Manbo!
- Cheers. / - Good job.
It was really enjoyable.
(Nilriri Manbo, the end of their Mokpo trip)
- The end was amazing. / - Thank you.
- Okay. / - Oh, my.
- It was nice. / - Yes.
We ate a lot.
- That's right. / - If you had to choose one.
What would you eat?
- The meal? / - I want the short rib patty.
- The short rib patty? / - The short rib patty?
It was the first time I ever had a texture like that.
- The short rib patty. / - Yes, the short rib patty.
It was a real hidden card.
- The meal. / - The $8 meal?
- Yes, the $8 meal. / - That was the best.
- It was the best. / - It had the clam soup.
I want to eat noodles in soybean soup so much.
I want to eat the rice cake dessert.
- That was good. / - The mugwort rice cake.
I want noodles in soybean soup.
- Every single meal was good. / - What would you do?
Noodles in soybean soup delivered all over the country.
I really want to tell you this.
This isn't the end.
If you go to Mokpo,
there's a place that does good beef bone soup.
- Beef bone soup? / - There's a place that's sold...
Only dumplings and instant noodles for 20 years.
The most famous croaker restaurant in Korea
is in Mokpo.
I usually don't say this
but I think you should empty your mind today.
So, how much did they spend?
- They must've spent heaps. / - Too much.
For the 2 days and 1 night in Mokpo...
- The Nilriri Manbo Tour spent... / - The total.
- Per person. / - Per person!
- A total of... / - Total.
$179.20.
- They were three though. / - After all that eating?
That's right.
We accept that.
Okay, any last words?
Mothers, you were all busy, right?
What is he doing?
You must have been busy.
Escape your busy daily lives.
Put your steering wheels down...
And you should also get a drink during the day.
You can walk slowly to the place your feet leads you.
- Enjoy the beauty of nature. / - Oh, he's good.
I think it will be nice. Order automatically.
(Order automatically)
- Automatic order. / - Automatic order.
You're ready to vote, right?
Would you like to go on a trip
according to Nilriri Manbo Tour's plan to Mokpo?
(Would you go to Mokpo according to their plan?)
(They designed a domestic fall trip to Mokpo)
(What will the judges choose?)
Will it be Peak Father and Son Tour to Danyang?
Or Nilriri Manbo Tour to Mokpo?
What will the judges choose?
- Mr. Noh. / - This is nerve wrecking.
- He was too strong. / - I hate you, Mr. Noh.
Mr. Noh was too good.
We had spicy mandarin fish stew.
Our trip was also nice.
- What is it? The last digit's a zero. / - Please...
(The last digit is revealed first)
Three.
We won the last digit.
(Which team will win?)
Did we win or lose?
(Mokpo won)
- Congratulations. / - That was amazing.
- That was amazing. / - Thank you.
- Did we win? / - They won.
- That's a lot of votes. / - They tied in 11th place.
(Mokpo tied in 11th place for the most votes ever)
First, in 6 months, to be in 90s range.
- It's a really rare thing. / - Yes.
- Wow. / - That's so fortunate.
Please tell us your thoughts.
I think it will be nice
if you go on a trip to Mokpo.
A lot of people have only heard about Mokpo.
- They think it's further than it is. / - That's right.
It's closer than we think
and there's a lot more good food than you think.
It's really perfect for fall.
I hope many of you go to Mokpo.
- Okay. / - I see.
Kim Hwan, you were with us for 2 weeks.
How was it?
- My daughter is only 7 months old. / - That's right.
I want to take her out but
I didn't know where to take her.
- We saw two trips in Korea. / - That's right.
Danyang and Mokpo are on my list now.
- I really want to go there. / - You should really go.
I also want to go to Mokpo.
Stop it now.
Right?
- It's 91 votes now. / - That's right.
Is next week also a special?
Of course, it's a special.
Next week. "You're really going there?"
"Where is that place?"
It's a surprising location that will make you say that.
- "There? Really?" / - Is it a new location?
We will come back next week.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
(Next episode)
I've chosen all the must-visit landmarks
of Bandung.
Men and women of all ages will enjoy this place.
Have a Bandung day!
Bye.
Sakhalin! Yeonwoo, this is Sakhalin.
I'm overwhelmed by the beauty of this place.
Yeah.
- I'm scared. / - No, no!
Screaming together and not caring about anyone else.
I think that was so nice.
(Battle Trip)
("Cookies" by Lee Honggi)