(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Lee Hwijae, special host, Han Donggeun)
(Kim Sook, Sung Sikyung)
Travel is war!
Battle Trip!
Today's special host for Battle Trip
is extremely nervous.
It's singer Han Donggeun!
Hello, I'm today's special host,
singer Han Donggeun.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, Han Donggeun.
He's such a good singer.
- He can start singing at any minute. / - Thank you.
- Really? / - Yes.
Do you like to travel?
I do like to travel
but I haven't traveled a lot.
So I really enjoy the show.
What was your favorite?
Where did you want to go the most
when you watched Battle Trip?
The place Shin Dong went to.
- Shin Dong? / - China?
The place you could take home wine in your bottle.
You like to drink.
I see.
This is good.
We like this sort of thing.
I like his smile.
There's a reason why Donggeun's the guest today.
In fact, he has something to do with today's trip.
- Is that right? / - Yes.
Why?
The thing is
I was an overseas student there
for 4 years.
Can you introduce
today's destination in their language?
- That's right. / - Good things about the place.
He's starting with "umm."
- Umm. / - Umm.
It's like...
(Oh)
Yes!
Yes?
That kind of place.
It's an English-speaking country.
- Yes. / - English-speaking country.
And?
It's a very warm place.
And nearby the beach.
Thank you very much.
Today's destination is
connected to Han Donggeun.
It's California in the West America.
- California. / - California.
Where did you stay for 4 years?
- Urban... / - I lived in 3 places.
Did you cause trouble?
- I didn't study very well. / - I see.
- So where did you stay? / - Where?
First, I was in Murrieta.
It's in the countryside.
I stayed there for a while.
- You did. / - Then I went to Fullerton.
After Fullerton...
I also lived in La Habra.
It's a small city near
Diamond Bar.
I've never been to those cities.
If you stayed in 3 cities for 4 years,
I guess you're a California expert.
I don't think we should ask him to speak English.
I heard today's trip designers...
- Had a good time there. / - Right.
Let's meet them now.
The four trip planners
who traveled to California. Come on out!
(Choi Jungwon, Kim Jihun)
Hello.
Minah and Yura are in the same team.
Jihun and Jungwon,
how did you know each other?
We're in the same basketball team.
- Oh, you play basketball together. / - Yes.
Jihun, was it your first time in the U.S?
- I've been there a few times. / - Really?
Yes.
What? You thought I've never been to the U.S.?
Is that how I look?
So what did you do in California?
L.A. is the most famous city...
- In California. / - Right.
But we traveled the northern part
of California.
- So we... / - They saw the real California.
We went to hidden tourist attractions...
Which you haven't seen a lot before.
- You did? / - Yes.
When you said you went to the northern part,
Han Donggeun said
you saw the real California.
- Only those who know, know this. / - Yes.
- Really? / - Yes.
First-timers in the U.S. usually go to L.A.
- Or places with a lot of Koreans. / - Right.
But if you're an intermediate traveler,
you head north, where you can experience nature.
When Yura was our special host, she said...
- She wanted to go on a trip. / - That's right.
- And she finally went on a trip. / - Finally.
I'm sure they will win because
they love to eat.
Definitely.
We ate a lot there.
That's the thing we remember the most.
- We ate so much. / - This is good.
That's a successful trip.
We ate too much.
Did you guys hit it off during the trip?
- Yes. We are... / - Since you're so close.
We've been together for 9 years now.
And we have the same taste in food.
- We have similar tastes. / - We like the same food.
- So... / - That's all you need.
- We like crunchy food. / - And flour-based food.
With egg yolk...
Sweet and salty.
We eat like kids.
There was the perfect sweet-salty combination.
- Okay. / - Normally...
You diet but none of that today, right?
None of that today, right?
You can work out after you eat.
- That's right. / - That's right.
- You should enjoy your food there. / - Right.
- Otherwise, you'd be stressed. / - What's the point?
You can't travel then.
We will show you the map of California.
We need your explanation.
Please tell us about California with the map.
- It must be very far. / - This is Seoul.
- There we go. / - So far.
It's so big.
Here's Los Angeles.
- Palm Springs. / - Palm Springs.
- There's Orange County. / - Orange County.
- San Francisco. / - San Francisco.
- It's in the northern part. / - It's much more north.
Napa Valley.
There's Yosemite National Park.
I've heard of that place before.
- Yosemite. / - The U.S.
The U.S. has huge natural areas, right?
Right.
They have the 3 top national parks.
One was shown here...
- Grand Canyon. / - Okay.
- Yellowstone. / - Okay.
And Yosemite.
They're the top 3?
We went to one of them.
The great thing about San Francisco is
that it's always autumn weather.
- Always, right? / - Always autumn.
The rainy season is from December to March there.
So we were very worried about it.
But it didn't rain even a single day.
But when you go to Yosemite National Park,
you can see the snow which is unbelievable.
So usually, when you go to Yosemite,
you can see the snow...
- And you can go skiing there. / - Right.
But as you know, the Earth is hurting these days.
So due to the change in weather,
it didn't snow.
- That's weird. / - But we saw snow.
You saw snow?
- Actually, we... / - In the south?
It was actually cold for us.
The Earth really is sick.
- We... / - It snowed in L.A.?
- This is so strange. / - It snowed in Palm Springs.
That's unbelievable.
It snowed in Palm Springs.
We enjoyed both the city and the nature.
- You can enjoy both. / - We experienced both.
You can do that in Busan.
- No, no. / - Excuse me. Go to Gangwon-do.
Is there a desert in Busan?
L.A. is similar to Korea.
You can get food delivered in L.A.
You're spot on.
I got soft tofu stew delivered.
The owners ask you to order in Korean.
They have better food there than in Korea.
L.A. is on top of the list for cities
Koreans love to travel to.
They go to L.A. and San Francisco.
No, no.
- We can confirm this on screen. / - You don't know.
- Thing is... / - This is good. It's competitive.
Okay.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
- Welcome. / - Nice to meet you.
The trips will be divided into two halves.
You'll vote once after each half.
That's four votes in total.
The votes aren't totaled.
Only the vote in the second half is the final vote.
Why don't we start?
Do you want to go first?
Who wants to go first?
Where should we go first?
I think we should check out the gloomy guys first.
Okay.
That'd be better.
Why do you say we're gloomy?
- Since you're guys. / - Men first.
What's interesting is that the two teams should have
met for the first time here, in the studio.
But I heard they'd already met.
- Did you meet in the U.S.? / - We met already.
You met already?
We didn't meet in the U.S.
We met on the day when we planned our trips.
Oh, then...
Oh, my face. What do I do?
- I just woke up and went. / - Seriously...
Your face is in trouble?
What do I do?
- You have to watch this. / - Her face is in trouble.
- Oh, no. / - We knew it was a shoot.
So we had full makeup on.
But these two came as if they were
visiting the supermarket in front of their house.
Please don't do a before-after comparison.
This doesn't look like a battle.
It's like a family trip.
Are they on a date?
I thought we were all going together.
I thought Battle Trip
was changing concepts.
I thought it'd be a Love Trip.
Love Trip?
You thought it was similar to "We Got Married."
We got together and had the meeting so...
For us...
Give us one spoiler.
Who likes to drink?
- Me. / - Me.
- Me. / - You all do, right?
- We... / - Sikyung...
Sikyung, you don't actually have to walk over there.
Sikyung!
He doesn't like to drink. He is alcohol.
He's made of alcohol.
- For today... / - Yura's here too.
I think we've won in this respect.
Because the highest of quality wines
in the U.S. are made in...
- Napa Valley. / - We went to Napa Valley.
- There's a wine train there. / - Sikyung's still there.
- He won't come back. / - We took the wine train.
We had a course meal on it.
Visiting the various wineries...
- Wineries? / - We tasted the wine...
We saw how the wine is made.
Napa Valley wine can be
bought in Korea for cheap.
Who are you?
- Let's just watch. / - You'll see it.
Okay then.
Let's check out the gloomy tour.
Let's check out Northern California.
You have to play this song.
Are you there already?
- Oh, here... / - This is it!
You can see Girl's Day with no makeup.
It wasn't completely without makeup.
Who is that?
Hello.
No one is here yet.
But with Minah...
- Yura... / - You look better without makeup.
Yeah.
(He's a Girl's Day fan)
She's so cute.
Donggeun just gasped.
Okay.
Today...
Will she...
Will she actually be on time?
I'll keep watch today.
Current time.
1:50.
We agreed to meet at 2 and I'm 10 minutes early.
Do you know your opponents?
(Never met before)
I hope it's Yura.
First meetings are awkward.
(Surprised)
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
He's all dressed up.
Dressed up.
How awkward.
(It's the first time they're meeting)
(Awkward)
(Why does it feel like a date?)
(What do I talk about?)
(Think! Think! Think!)
I'm your senior, right?
- Senior, right? / - It's like a blind date.
That's the first thing you said?
Thought it was "We Got Married."
That was a strange question, right?
"I'm your senior, right?"
That is a very strange first question.
I've watched him ever since
I was a little kid...
Choi Jungwon has changed so much.
Yes, of course.
Can we drink this?
Is Jihun not here yet?
Why isn't he here yet?
He's a better talker.
Why are you doing this to us?
Then how old are you now?
Is this an arranged marriage?
- Is that what you were doing? / - Geez.
Come on, Jungwon!
- Jungwon's always serious. / - "I'm your senior."
I'm turning 26 this year.
26.
- Year of the Rooster. / - Yes.
What zodiac are you?
Rooster.
- Really? / - Yes.
That's why you calculated so fast.
- Jihun's the same age. / - Same age.
- Same age. / - Year of the Rooster.
What is this? It doesn't feel like I'm on Battle Trip.
Is Battle Trip some kind of a front...
- It's sort of like... / - To pull a prank on us?
When is Jihun going to be here?
Why do you keep asking for me?
That's funny.
(The third trip designer arrives exactly on time at 2)
Hi.
- Hello. / - Hello.
Hello.
Oh, I see...
- Oh, I see... / - She's cute.
Yura actually has swollen eyes.
Sorry, I'm late.
- Hello. / - I'm sorry.
I just came too.
She's really cool.
What?
She just got up and came here.
(Jihun, what on earth is wrong with you?)
- I couldn't dare ask. / - I got up an hour ago.
I was shocked when you came in.
Why?
I thought you were a lion.
I feel weird because we're so dressed up.
We shouldn't have dressed up either.
You've got full makeup on?
He's put a lot of thought into it.
I see.
You have to choose where you'll go.
I've been on Battle Trip as the special host.
I was a special host once.
In the end,
the destination the judges want to go end up winning.
Nice places.
Then when we pick our destination...
So the team that chooses the better place will win.
So in a nutshell,
Southern California is from L.A. to San Diego.
Northern California is...
San Jose to San Francisco.
San Jose?
There are two major cities.
L.A. and San Francisco.
I like San Francisco...
- Because... / - Me too.
Me too.
What's going on?
What about you, Minah?
Then I choose L.A.
Then let's divide 3 to 1.
- San Francisco. / - You go alone.
- The three of you go. / - Let's go, us three.
- She can travel alone. / - 3 to 1.
- Traveling alone isn't too bad. / - Right.
You can make many good memories.
Let's do a 3 on 1.
It was actually decided
when you entered.
If you look under your seats...
- What's going on? / - You'll see a panel.
One seat has the king panel.
On the floor?
- Oh? / - Is this it?
- So that's how they decided. / - That's how.
Great idea.
Is this it?
Oh, everyone has one?
What? I thought only I had it.
What is this?
1, 2, 3.
- Who's the king? / - 1, 2, 3.
What's going on?
- You're the king. / - This is...
So the oldest person is king.
It's in order of age?
Order of age.
He and I are the same age.
- Oh, really? / - Don't be like that.
We're the same age.
Then...
Isn't L.A. better?
- It's the "La La Land" shoot location. / - It's hard.
It's the "La La Land" shoot location.
I don't really like "La La Land."
I haven't seen it.
Hasn't seen it...
Thing is...
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you want to go to L.A.?
- I want to go to L.A. / - Really?
Why?
I like warm weather.
Is San Francisco cold?
- San Francisco is more autumn weather. / - I see.
Last year,
and it was the worst cold I've ever had...
- So it's a bit... / - You had a cold?
So it's a bit...
Then for Yura...
(Thanks, Jihun)
Let's let her enjoy L.A. for real this time.
- We'll send you to L.A. / - Okay.
Why does everyone hate L.A.?
L.A. is awesome.
Because for us,
we've been to L.A. a few times.
But the northern area...
There wasn't much of an opportunity to go there.
- That's true. / - That being the case...
We'd like to take this opportunity
to really explore California.
- Sorry about this. / - I want to go to San Francisco.
Yura.
- Have fun on your own. / - Yura.
If we go to a warm city,
we can go to the beach and surf.
I'm not interested in that.
Yura.
- Then what do you like to do? / - Mark my words.
After the shot of her saying this,
they'll play her having a blast on a surfboard.
I guarantee it.
(Sneak preview of next week's episode)
I wanted to go to San Francisco...
Take this.
We can go to San Francisco.
1, 2, 3. California!
Let's go!
(On the day of departure for Northern California)
Aren't you cold?
It's too cold in Korea.
- Did you get some sleep? / - It's so cold...
But you dressed for looks not warmth.
No, I didn't.
That's the natural look of myself.
Jihun is always late.
So...
I have to always nag him to come early
so that he actually arrives on time.
Stop talking nonsense.
Did you come up with our itinerary?
I sort of have an itinerary.
But we'll go with the feel.
Use our gut feelings to make good decisions.
- Cluck. / - Cluck.
Let's go.
(They set out to San Francisco)
- The flight isn't that long. / - Right.
It only takes 10 hours and 20 minutes?
Flights usually take 10 to 11 hours.
Golden Gate Bridge...
It's the bridge we always see in the movies.
That reminds me of our trip.
You must visit there.
I love that place.
That's the symbol of San Francisco.
The beach stretches along the road.
There's a city on a hill
that stretches far behind it.
San Francisco is the no. 1 city
that Americans want to live in.
Seals.
You saw that many seals?
I'm going to San Francisco this year.
The most famous winery in California.
The largest producer of wine.
We take a train...
Wine train!
- That's... / - Winery!
- See that? / - That place, everyone...
- I said I wanted San Francisco! / - Waterfall.
Yosemite!
Is that Yosemite?
- We saw rainbows there too. / - Amazing.
- Right now... / - Wine...
- How can L.A. win? / - We've won.
- How can L.A. win? / - Isn't it game over already?
I've never seen any of this on Battle Trip before.
That's North California.
- Where's that? / - The night sky of Yosemite.
Do we have to win with Korean food or what?
(Day 1 in San Francisco, Northern California)
Now that we're in California,
we must wear our sunglasses.
- The weather is amazing here. / - The weather...
Hey, this is Alamo Square
which is located in the heart of the city.
- Alamo Square? / - Yes.
What do we have here?
First off, this area is...
What's this architecture style?
You mean this?
- Is this called Victorian style? / - Victoria from f(x).
Victoria from f(x).
It's on TV a lot.
You mean those buildings, right?
Seven houses.
But people actually live in them.
- They're all individual houses. / - It's residential.
We came here...
With the intention of taking a great trip.
- We go up here... / - Can you film it from that side?
It's blocking my entire face.
Jihun is really picky.
Be more considerate.
- You should hold it like this. / - I didn't know that.
- Can't you see he's filming me? / - Okay, okay.
The view from here is excellent.
That's the city of San Francisco, right?
Downtown.
All the high-rise buildings are there.
The ocean must be beyond that.
The view is indeed spectacular from here.
This park feels like
a park in your neighborhood.
A park in your neighborhood.
- Be quiet. / - That's right.
He's right.
- That's how a regular park looks. / - Regular park.
So what are we doing today?
First...
We will rent a convertible today.
A convertible.
Since it's warm weather.
You need to drive a convertible in the U.S.
If you drive a convertible there, you'll freeze to death.
It's really warm in the afternoon.
A convertible...
- Really? / - I booked one.
- A convertible? / - The weather is great here.
- We need to drive a convertible. / - You're right.
But it must be expensive.
I booked us a luxurious one.
- Let's get going. / - Really?
I can drive.
I got the international driver's license from Korea.
Let's take a look around this area on our convertible.
We are like those
rich international students,
living in this posh area.
(They take the cable car downtown)
The cable car is like
the town shuttle bus in Korea.
Bus...
This is...
The famous cable car of San Francisco.
This is so cool though.
When you travel down the hill on the cable car,
you can see the beach.
That's beautiful.
I was finally on the cable car.
(Cluck Cluck Tour in North California)
(Drive around Lombard Street in a convertible)
Let's look around Lombard Street.
This is the street that was in "Inside Out."
It was in that animation film.
No wonder!
- You've seen it a lot, right? / - Yes.
So this is that place.
Hey.
You said you booked a convertible.
- Oh, an old car. / - What's that?
How much did that cost to rent?
It's pretty expensive.
3, 2, 1.
Ta-da.
(The Cluck Cluck Tour convertible!)
That's cute.
What is this?
Does it use the smell of flowers for gas?
That's so cute.
I didn't know Jungwon was into that.
- It can travel 120km/hr. / - For real?
- You must try it. / - 120?
This is the trend these days.
So cute.
That's so cute!
I want to buy one.
- But it is cute indeed. / - That's really cute.
You wave to people in that
and they all wave back.
You just become friends.
(You get safety training and gear)
It's so hard to get into this thing.
I think we were supposed to ride this with women.
My goodness.
Hey, this is...
Why's it so tight?
Is this the convertible?
Can you move your shoulders? It's too tight.
(He feels guilty)
Let's go.
What is this?
Shouldn't we have rented a convertible like that one?
Isn't that a convertible?
Shouldn't we be in one of those right now?
Why do we look pathetic?
We do look pathetic.
- We look poor. / - It's still a convertible.
It's like we're riding a cart in the amusement park.
Look at the fire truck.
It's like the one in a museum.
It's so cool.
The fire truck looks so nice.
Keep driving straight,
and we're going to take a left.
Here. Take a left.
(Okay then)
It's the perfect weather to be on a convertible.
You can drift.
Really?
It was fun.
(He drives furiously)
(Let's go to Lombard Street)
(Jihun, could you slow down?)
The fastest speed!
200km/hr!
(Hey, it's dangerous)
Hey, hey. Hey!
- Why are you so scared? / - Hey, slow down.
Right now...
- Hey! Hey! / - I'm driving safely.
(Something feels wrong)
I dropped my phone.
- What? / - Are you serious?
(No way!)
200km/hr!
Good-bye.
- What happened after that? / - We won.
Can you pull over?
Hold on. A car is coming.
You idiot.
I guess he found it. I think he picked it up.
Such a peaceful place.
You look very laid-back.
You should've rented a real convertible, dummy.
(Is your phone okay?)
My gosh. Seriously.
I think I would've cried.
- That's my worst nightmare. / - But those roads...
The cars don't travel fast.
It's because you drove too fast!
You should've got one with doors.
Let's go.
Hey, hey.
A car's coming.
Oh, there's a car.
Get out and push!
Geez!
The one bad thing about those...
- They can't reverse / - They can't reverse?
What?
Next time, get one that can reverse.
Sorry.
Is this it?
You have to drive well from here.
This is a great spot to take pictures.
This is it.
This is from "Inside Out."
It's so pretty.
They made it so it's less steep.
Amazing.
This is like a roller coaster.
You need to get ready
to go down this street.
There are stairs for people
on the side.
Hey, slow down.
Slow down!
That's so pretty.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Don't worry, we're safe.
We're finished.
- Hello. / - That was fast.
The cars are driving very slowly.
That's how we came down.
You drove three times faster than that.
- Really? / - Yes.
- Did I? / - Yes.
This car performs really well.
Great cornering.
You're hungry, aren't you?
- I'm super hungry. / - Me too.
Let's go take pictures with sea lions
then eat some good food.
- Fisherman's Wharf. / - Okay.
Let's transport like this.
How?
Please don't.
- No, no. / - No way.
Jihun, don't do it
Goodness.
Like in the old days.
Let's transport to Fisherman's Wharf.
Like this.
Must we do this?
Many have failed trying to do this.
Let's transport to Fisherman's Wharf!
Why did they do such a poor job in editing?
- Why didn't they use CG? / - "We're sorry."
"We're sorry."
That's clever.
They apologized in advance.
- Did you have fun? / - Yes.
It was cold.
I was cold because it was an open car.
I think my nose is running too much.
Seriously.
It's over there.
Fisherman's Wharf.
We're here.
That sign with a crab is huge.
It's here.
It's like a market street.
That looks good.
Do you want to try it?
What's this?
Gosh, that looks good.
- That looks amazing. / - How many claws is that?
- I want the one with crab meat. / - Crab meat?
- What's this one? / - I think it's a lobster roll.
I think this one is a lobster roll
and this one's crab...
With lobster.
Just one please. Here, here.
It's packed with lobster?
Yes, all lobster.
Lobster claw.
Koreans won't be able to finish an entire one.
There's too much.
It's not imitation crab meat?
- It's real lobster? / - Real lobster.
The entire thing.
There's so much.
(While Jungwon is paying)
(A bite)
Are you cutting it? What are you doing?
Why are you eating it alone?
You should wait for me.
You two don't get along well.
I only ate a little.
There's a lot of crab meat.
American food is usually quite salty.
But it's not salty.
There's so much meat.
Lobster and
crab meat together
taste really delicious.
The buns are just regular buns, right?
It's like a baguette.
- American bun. / - Was it good?
The buns tasted like ordinary buns.
Let's try the crab cake.
This?
Just one please.
That's a crab cake.
- What's that? / - It's fried crab meat.
- Like a croquette? / - Croquette.
Yes, it's fried like a croquette.
It's easily found in America
but they don't really sell it here.
This?
It's a croquette.
It could be hot.
How is it?
It's cold.
It looks hot.
It's good.
It's like a cold cake.
- Exactly. / - It's a croquette.
It's a crab meat croquette.
That's right.
Was it delicious?
- It was really delicious. / - It was really good.
Donggeun, have you tried it?
I've never even seen it.
I like...
The crab roll better.
Really? I think this is better.
You think so?
Should we go over there?
Okay. There are more people now.
(Pier 39)
(A large shopping center with restaurants and gift shops)
(Built on a pier in San Francisco, California)
(There's a sea lion habitat nearby)
(With street and band performances)
- There are so many of them. / - This is it.
This is the crab sculpture
I told you about.
- It's symbolic. / - We should take a picture.
I can make you look much taller.
Look. This is amazing.
Look at this.
This is so...
- What is this? / - Look.
Check out the next one.
Hey.
- Goodness. / - It's a good shot.
I took a great picture.
These old guys...
Pictures are really important when you go traveling.
Look at the composition. Get the right feel.
I took it like this so you'd look taller.
Let's see how good you are at taking pictures.
Kim Jihun.
When it comes to photos...
- It's all about... / - Geez.
How much care you put into it.
Just take it.
Pictures turn out better if you put more affection.
He's right. You need affection.
He should lie down on the floor.
If the subject looks good,
then the photo turns out good.
Can't you put that bag away?
It's a souvenir. Just take it.
- That looks good. / - Nice use of negative space.
That looks better.
- He cut out the bag. / - Which one is better?
Jihun looks like
he's wearing a crab backpack.
It looks like a heart.
Which one is better?
Yours is better.
- See? / - Let's go.
Photos are all about
how much love you put into it.
- That makes good photos. / - So you love me more.
You hear that, don't you?
You hear what you heard earlier, right?
- Is it the same sound? / - Yes.
They're not seagulls?
No.
I can hear them.
It's their sound.
- I hear it. / - I see them!
There were so many.
Seriously, there were about 2,000 of them.
There are so many.
They're really loud.
- They keep grunting. / - Thing is...
- That... / - They grunt.
Back in the day, people who lived here
didn't like the noise.
They started liking it because
it attracted tourists.
- They're so cute. / - So cute.
I don't know why they're there.
- But they are resting there. / - They're fighting.
It's trying to block the other one from coming up.
- That one? / - Yes.
Look at that. It's not letting it come up.
- Those two... / - Yeah.
It's a lovers' quarrel.
It's blocking him. They're fighting.
(Roar)
It won't die, will it?
(I'm leaving)
Let's go.
Do you see the crab?
(Pier 39's seafood set)
That looks good.
Check out the crab.
What should we get?
The recommendation is...
Steamed whole crab.
And...
- It's not clam chowder. / - That looks good.
It's crab chowder.
- Crab chowder? / - It's made with crab...
- Instead of clam. / - Mussels and shrimps.
You can have as much seafood as you like.
There are crabs everywhere.
Look.
Crabs are everywhere.
Seriously, crabs are everywhere.
(Hey)
(Wow)
They serve it as soon as we ordered.
It'd be wonderful around sunset.
- Yes. / - That's right.
It has a great atmosphere.
He's pouring white wine.
(Jihun, look at that)
This is like a work of art.
Right?
The crab even looks handsome.
This is a must-have dish.
This is for you.
Is this crab chowder?
Yes.
That's cute.
- Is it your concept to be cute? / - Is that provided?
- Yes, they gave it to us. / - Is it from the restaurant?
That's so cute though.
Eat it with crab meat.
- There's so much crab meat. / - Cheers.
(What does the special crab chowder taste like?)
Why the face?
- What's wrong? / - Did it taste unfamiliar?
Why are you shocked?
(Cluck Cluck Tour gives it another go)
It tastes familiar.
Don't you think there is hot pepper in it?
It's a little spicy.
Isn't it?
It's tasty.
It's something kids would love.
(This is so good)
I think we're going to win because of their reactions.
That's right. Their reaction isn't that good.
- That tasted good, right? / - Since they're men...
Their reactions aren't very good.
- We were... / - Wasn't it good?
Food is only a small part for us.
Food doesn't mean a lot to us.
We'll show you just how important that small part is.
That's right.
Look at this bread.
It's the lid.
This is amazing.
We have to eat this together.
You have to eat the soup with the bread.
Of course.
(His eyebrows are dancing)
It's better with the bread.
(Should I taste this?)
More crab?
That crab was amazing.
- I remember it. / - It's so big.
I thought it was a replica.
It's cooked in butter.
- It's so full of meat. / - You're right.
That looks so good.
(Chomp)
This is the good part.
(The corner of his mouth is going up again)
First...
It's completely full of meat.
I think they grilled it with butter.
It's greasier
and different to how it tastes in Korea.
There's no need for words.
I'm sorry.
Yura, I'm sorry.
Minah, I'm sorry.
He's teasing us.
Girl's Day, are you watching this?
Girl's Day?
(They are having so much fun teasing Girl's Day)
What if we faint from eating this
because it's so good?
Let's eat it all up.
Don't you think I'll look too greedy?
- Right now. / - Will you keep going?
Your face looks greasy.
Why you...
(KBS complies with the broadcasting regulations)
It was so good.
- The wine. / - You have to drink white wine.
- It goes well with seafood. / - Yeah.
- I can't say how good it was. / - Look so good.
Now we head to the Golden Gate Bridge...
I can see the Golden Gate Bridge from here.
Over there.
You can see it between the fog.
We're going to see it from up close.
You planned this trip really well.
Cluck Cluck Tour. Cheers.
Cheers.
(Cluck Cluck Tour in Northern California)
(Golden Gate Bridge)
Golden Gate Bridge.
We have to see the Golden Gate Bridge.
It's really long.
That's right.
I went there by car and
the Golden Gate Bridge was the most memorable.
Even if people don't know the name correctly...
They've all seen it once.
- That's right. / - It's in a lot of movies.
There's a movie where aliens blow it up.
The NBA home team is the Golden State Warriors.
Who's on that team?
Stephen Curry.
Curry, Stephen Curry.
On his chest
is the Golden Gate Bridge.
You have to buy things like a
Golden Gate Bridge snow globe.
When you boast that you
went on a San Francisco trip,
you have to show off things like that.
Have you ever been there?
I've been there.
Do you have to talk so tauntingly?
Why are you so taunting?
Okay.
(When darkness falls in San Francisco)
It's the place we've only seen
in movies and pictures and we walked on it.
- Isn't it too long to walk? / - Isn't it too long?
No, no. It's not that long.
- You can walk it in less than an hour. / - We're here!
Do you know why it's called this?
- This bridge? / - Yeah.
It's Golden Gate Bridge
Why is it Golden Gate?
- I know it. / - Why?
California was the place
where America had the gold rush.
You studied.
- This place has a lot of gold. / - You studied.
(San Francisco was called the Golden Gate)
(During gold rush period)
(The Golden Gate Bridge is)
(One of the 7 Wonders of the Modern World)
(This bridge will never collapse)
You see this bridge...
- In a lot of movies. / - Right.
Like in "X-Men."
Magneto lifts the bridge
with his magnetic powers.
He snaps it in the middle.
If this collapses in disaster films...
That means that it's the end of the world.
This bridge is not collapsible?
That's right.
This is really amazing.
If you want to take a picture, take it by that hill.
That's the Battery Spencer.
- That looks so nice. / - It's more beautiful at night.
It looks amazing from above.
So nice.
(Charmed by the view of the Golden Gate Bridge)
It's too bad that we're the only ones seeing this.
(The day in San Francisco passed by too quickly)
- We have to go there tomorrow. / - Where?
- Napa Valley. / - Ah.
We will go to Napa Valley tomorrow
and visit a winery.
We can taste wine there.
- We're looking forward to that. / - That's pretty.
The place I'm looking forward to the most...
- Yosemite National Park. / - Really?
One of the best three national parks.
It's completely preserved.
Wow, stars!
- What is that? / - That's what we actually saw.
That sky is really unforgettable.
It's hard to capture stars on camera.
Is it over already?
I've never been there, so I'm curious.
Is the Golden Gate Bridge really beautiful?
The Golden Gate Bridge... It's a marvelous sight.
But from the moment they planned the bridge,
people said it'd be impossible to build.
Because they only have two columns.
The entire bridge is suspended on cables.
- Does it shake? / - Of course it does.
It has to shake for it to be safe.
It has to vibrate to the airflow.
That's what makes the bridge stand firm.
Since it doesn't have columns...
- You can pass freely underneath. / - That's right.
The bridges we know have continuous supports.
- You're right. / - So after the bridge was built...
It was good for cars...
- But boats could also travel freely. / - Convenience.
San Francisco developed
because of the Golden Gate Bridge.
- I've been to San Francisco. / - Have you?
But for me...
- The croquette... / - Croquette?
It sounds weird if you talk about croquette.
- Crab cake. / - Yes, crab cake.
Yes, croquette, crab cake...
The crab was the most memorable dish for me.
In Korea, it's steamed or cooked.
They have variety.
They cook it in butter.
- That was different. / - That lid.
Yes.
It was really savory.
We've seen enough.
- Let's take a vote. / - Let's.
Would you go to Northern California
based on the Cluck Cluck Tour?
Yes or no? Please vote.
(Cluck Cluck Tour planned a trip to Northern California)
(What will the judges choose?)
- Small things can be better at times. / - Yeah.
- In my opinion, we'll get over 70. / - Really?
- Over 70 is a good thing. / - Take a look.
What? Why did you look at it so fast?
- The thing is... / - Do you have to look so fast?
There's no need to pretend.
Just look.
They're going to be like this.
They'll act before they even look.
- Cue. / - This was your doing.
You acted like you really liked it.
Look at them.
It's a high vote.
How many votes do you expect out of 100?
To be honest, the first video you saw...
- Is just all the boring stuff. / - That's right.
That was the boring stuff?
Seriously, Northern California...
You haven't seen anything yet.
Okay then. Let's begin the second half
of the Northern California trip.
Let's watch together.
- We watch all of it now? / - We start right away.
This place produces the most wine,
and it's most famous in California.
- I want to go there. / - You can take the train...
And have lunch.
Then visit the winery, try some wine,
look around, take pictures...
- You can only say wow. / - It's marvelous.
There's no way to express this in words.
This should all be frozen.
We were lucky.
It's supposed to be frozen during this time.
There wasn't any snow so the water didn't freeze.
I didn't know that it would be this moving.
This trip is unforgettable.
That's amazing.
- Is that on camera? / - Yes, captured on camera.
Cluck Cluck Tour, day 2.
We will start from Napa Valley.
Should we move? 1, 2, 3.
(Starting to do it the old-fashioned way again)
(We will start the second half of Northern California)
They said that they would edit it well for us.
Where should we go today?
I planned everything.
Where are we going?
This is an intermediate course
to visit the suburbs of San Francisco.
- Since you rented a convertible yesterday... / - Yes.
I rented a proper one today.
It's not a small car like yours.
They must have rented a proper car this time.
(Surprised)
(Rent and insurance for 1 day, $92)
We're entering the Golden Gate Bridge.
The Golden Gate Bridge in the fog looks amazing.
I feel like I can
high-five everyone in this convertible.
(Wine train)
I told you we put the boring stuff first.
1 hour 10 minutes is perfect.
- Good job. / - Good job.
This is the Napa Valley wine train.
It's written here.
It's 50 times bigger than Yeouido?
It's not 4 times, it's 50 times bigger.
Napa Valley wine train. It's written here.
It's the sacred place for wine.
The most famous place.
- It's the most famous? / - You take the train...
And eat food there. You can also go to the winery
to try some wine, look around and
take pictures.
It looks very old.
- It looks vintage. / - It looks luxurious.
(Wine train and winery tour, $333)
It's a winery tour on the wine train.
You can enjoy wine and food there.
It feels like there's a party in this train.
It's crowded and noisy.
Everyone looks so excited.
This would be paradise for people who love
wine or alcohol.
It'd be a train ride to heaven.
Wow, that's insane.
They already gave us some Champagne to drink
before our meal.
That Champagne looks so good.
Enjoy some wine.
Let's have fun.
Cheers to Napa Valley.
Can we drink on TV?
My face turns very suggestive when I drink.
You might have to censor my face.
Will I be the only one on TV?
Did I go on this trip by myself?
My face turns very suggestive.
It might be inappropriate for TV.
I'm warning you beforehand.
(What will become of Jihun's destiny?)
Your face is already pink.
It has started already.
I can't drink all the booze they give me today.
I'll just taste.
(No alcohol, good circulation, pink boy)
(Amazing)
Jihun!
Isn't that computer graphics?
I'll get revenge for you!
That's unbelievable.
(We can assure you that it's not computer graphics)
Our mains are here.
They serve you dishes like that?
You have a course meal with wine.
Then you go to the winery for a guided tour.
And you do tasting there too.
We're eating salmon and steak
on the train.
(Appetizing)
(Steak on wine train)
(They each try a bite)
I shouldn't have come here with you.
Why?
- I should be here with a woman. / - I'm happy with you.
Are you really happy?
(He's complaining he's here with a man)
In my opinion,
you have to look outside while eating your food.
(Show off)
Later on. You know steak this thick?
- This thick. / - I want to eat that.
Just wait.
(Something you've never seen)
What's wrong?
We would go crazy over that.
We're used to this.
Things like that are common in the U.S.
- It's good, right? / - It's to die for.
They're so bad at making it look appetizing.
That's me when I'm eating the tastiest food.
That's the face for the best food.
I should try the salmon.
The salmon will suit your taste.
(How does the salmon taste?)
Isn't this better for you?
- It's the best, right? / - I prefer the salmon.
Eat the salmon on the wine train.
Salmon was good. That place does good salmon.
The salmon is good.
The atmosphere is really good.
- We're here. / - Let's go.
Let's go.
I'm getting drunk.
Your face is too red.
(Suggestive pink boy is here)
What do we do?
One glass of Champagne?
I turn like this with only one glass of Champagne.
- He's just like Minah. / - One glass?
Same for her.
What will we do?
Pink boy, get with it.
- Let's consume some wine. / - I'll have it all!
(Winery)
This is the winery.
The weather is a little foggy,
but the fog, mountains,
and the vineyard look so good together.
If you come in summer...
- It'd be so good. / - It's magnificent.
There's a valley and a road.
The winery lines the road on both sides.
There is a picture of it.
If you come to a winery,
you can see that building.
It's this building here.
This is our guide.
- Hi. Good morning. / - Welcome.
Let me show you around the winery.
It's a beautiful day and
we have exciting wine to taste.
This is like a door leading to an unknown world.
This is so amazing.
(They can only make exclamations from surprise)
- Goodness. / - Wow.
Wonderful.
(This is the place where they age the wine)
- We reacted a lot here. / - One barrel costs...
In terms of currency,
that's $20,000 to $30,000 worth of wine in there.
This barrel yields 300 bottles of wine.
Present?
If one of these makes 300 bottles
and say 1 bottle costs $100...
- That's 100, 1,000, 10,000... / - Always calculating.
- One of these is worth $30,000. / - Really?
I wanted to bring a barrel home.
There's no end to the barrels lined up.
You should've bought one of those.
This is so...
Cluck Cluck Tour went to a nice place.
There are over 400 wineries there
and they're all like that.
The cellars are filled with wine.
- That's why it's 50 times the size of Yeouido. / - Right.
Let me try this.
Not this one.
I can take it.
(How about a tasting instead of the oak barrel?)
I feel like I'm going to get drunk already.
I'm drunk on the smell of wine.
So, let me show you some of the beautiful wines
that we make here at Robert Mondavi Winery.
I'd like to start with a white wine.
The name of this wine is Fume Blanc.
Wine tastes better if you listen
to the explanation and talk...
- In a quiet place. / - Very true.
You can taste it better.
I was resentful of how little I could drink.
(Focused and serious)
(Show off, the eyes, wine tastes good)
Now taste again.
You need to taste again to know the flavor.
(We're looking forward to pink boy's wine tasting)
Pink boy, go, go.
- Pink boy, go, go... / - Pink boy.
- It's good. / - It's tasty.
This refreshes your palate.
- It makes you salivate. / - Right?
It stimulates your appetite.
I like this Fume Blanc very much.
Isn't she waiting for us to finish?
- Is she? / - She's waiting for you.
Our elder is waiting for you to finish.
So you can throw it out if you can't drink?
But it was too good to throw out.
- Why throw away good drink? / - They're nice wine.
You're going to get wasted.
You're going to meet a new pink boy.
This is a very special wine for us.
I saw what kind of grapes it used
but it's not written on the bottle.
They blended it exquisitely.
You should continue to make the wine
contact with air to age the wine.
It will taste more mature.
It comes to life.
I've never seen anyone do this with wine?
He's shaking the wine like soju.
- He's shaking it like soju. / - It adds depth to the flavor.
I guess you've never had wine before.
You only have to shake it gently.
(What will pink boy do?)
I don't know.
(He tastes it again)
(Pink boy saw a lot of people do things like this)
You're trying too hard.
Sommeliers do it like this.
(We apologize for the image being too suggestive)
He turned red again.
(Cabernet Sauvignon Reserve)
- That must be so nice. / - I want to try it.
I know.
That's so interesting.
If you go there in the summer,
you can see the grapes for yourself.
Then you can taste the wine
that's made from those grapes.
That's nice.
- Lamb meatballs. / - It's lamb meatballs.
(A bite of meatball first)
(And then a sip of wine)
(Eyebrows going up again)
It goes well together.
Mmm.
Talk after you swallow.
It's sour. Why is it so sour?
- What's in it? / - Balsamic sauce.
I think I'm too drunk.
(Focusing)
Why's everything so sour?
(He's out of it)
- Should we toast and head off? / - Let's leave.
- Cluck. / - Cluck.
Cluck.
Cheers.
Did she just say cheers in Korean?
- She learned it from us. / - That's cute.
- We taught her. / - "Cheers."
This looks really nice.
- I've never been to Yosemite National Park. / - Same.
I really want to go there.
With the grandness of nature...
When we stand before it...
- We become small? / - We become very small.
I wanted to experience that.
Where the trees are thick
and there are streams or waterfalls.
- I want to feel that. / - Sounds great.
(Yosemite National Park)
This is the real start.
- Is this the start? / - It's the highlight of this tour.
Wow, what's that?
Isn't that a Winter Wonderland?
I feel like I'm being influenced by this nature
and endorphins are being released.
Look at the trees in the grandness of nature.
This place is just a landscape painting.
They have concerts there too.
- You're right. / - Really?
- Like Kenny Loggins... / - Really?
- And Michael McDonald / - I've seen it before.
That'd be amazing to have a concert there.
They have a lot of video concerts.
That's incredible.
1, 2, 3.
Pop.
(Awkward)
You didn't edit it, did you?
- You made us look like fools, right? / - Embarrassing.
Seriously.
Check out the trees.
This is the size of a pine tree.
- This... / - Let's try hugging this tree together.
I can't reach your hands.
- It's so big. / - Jihun, where are you?
- But it's just a normal tree here. / - I'm here.
- Am I cute? / - What?
I think I hear something strange.
I hear something echoing.
There's a place we need to visit first
in Yosemite National Park.
We're going to see a waterfall.
- Waterfall. / - There's a waterfall there?
Listen carefully.
- Splash, splash. / - I hear it.
- You can hear it, right? / - Yeah.
There's a waterfall over there.
You can see it through the trees.
Let's go.
- That's 720m high. / - That's really incredible.
What?
It's like a 300-story skyscraper.
- 300-story? / - 300-story?
(Let's go see the waterfall)
Can you see the waterfall?
Girl's Day.
They keep teasing us.
They keep competing with us.
It looks amazing.
- Let's take a photo in front of it. / - Okay.
(The sun shines through the thick forest)
I can feel the difference in the air on my skin.
The sound is getting louder.
(Here is the magnificent scenery made by nature)
(Yosemite Falls)
It looks amazing.
(Its magnificent view attracts many tourists)
It's so huge.
It's jaw-dropping.
We can take the picture here.
We can make us look like drinking the waterfall.
- You're right. / - I'll take the photo of you.
- Do we have to do this? / - Wait.
Just hang on a second.
The waterfall is actually really far away from us.
We used to do that in grade school.
- Is this a prank? / - Wait.
Just a minute. You look great.
Open your mouth wider.
- It's painful. / - Lean further back. There you go.
There you go. Perfect!
There it goes. It goes into your mouth.
- I'm done. / - Did you really take a picture?
- Hey. / - Of course I did.
I got fooled.
It was hard.
Hang in there. You look great now.
It was a video?
- Doesn't it look quite real? / - That was good.
Let's take a normal picture here. Come up here.
Okay.
(They look friendly)
Do we look too close?
(They should let others take photos for them)
What is this?
I went all the way to the end.
I got close to the waterfall on my own.
I'm here to show you exactly where
the Yosemite Falls flows from.
The water is falling from above.
All the way down.
Do you see the mist?
It's so moist.
You filmed a cosmetic commercial.
- Feels nice. / - It's so nice.
(I will keep my skin bright and moist)
Moisture fully charged!
- I'm so hungry. / - Me too. Wait.
I wish I could teleport down there.
1, 2, 3.
Now let's go.
(Yosemite Falls, "M" hotel restaurant)
Where are we now?
This is where we will have lunch.
This place is amazing too.
Is that inside the park?
Yes, it's a hotel.
Oh, my God.
(Its beauty is indescribable)
- I wish I could stay there once. / - It's pretty.
- It's so pretty. / - It's a 100-year-old hotel.
(This hotel is)
President Obama stayed here with his family.
Really?
And Steve Jobs had a wedding in this hotel.
When it's peak season, you can't make reservations.
Fortunately, we were very lucky.
It's off-season now,
so we could make a reservation.
It's so popular but we're here since it's off-season?
- Let's go eat. / - Let's go in.
What a relief.
Yura. Minah.
- I'm sorry you couldn't come here. / - I know.
We didn't record anything for you guys.
You didn't even think of us, did you?
(They're done looking at the building)
The restaurant was awesome.
Why is it so big?
- Fake candles. / - It was really grand.
It looks very elegant.
The high ceiling makes the atmosphere
so nice because it's so high.
We were overwhelmed by Yosemite Falls earlier.
Now we are overwhelmed by the restaurant.
With this size, it's impossible that they have bad food.
(The food is here)
- Look at how big it is. / - What is that?
Is that a sandwich?
Wow, seriously.
- The visuals... / - The serving size...
That was incredible.
Americans have such huge serving sizes.
Please describe the food properly this time.
(Onion soup goes well with the cold weather)
- Look at how great it looks. / - Chewy cheese.
- There was bread inside. / - It was really good.
- Please. / - Please, this time.
- Please show some reaction. / - Express it well.
Please make it look tasty.
This is the best men can do.
- That's the best we could do. / - Was that it?
Is it over?
We really enjoyed it.
That's a face of enjoying the every little bit of it.
It's a little lacking.
- So what is in the soup? / - One more time...
- So... / - This time?
Of all the food I've tasted in the U.S.,
the onion soup is the best.
- It's the best? / - This is the best.
It's over.
(That's your best effort?)
The bread is in here with cheese to bulk it up.
It's delicious.
Should we try the trout?
This looks like a really nice restaurant.
It's trout steak this time.
I have never tried trout steak before
but it was the best fish dish I had
in any restaurant
I've ever been to.
Pink, pink.
Just like my face when I'm drunk.
(He takes a bite of the pink trout steak)
It's not fishy at all.
It tastes very clean.
The meat is so chewy.
Compared to salmon,
it tastes cleaner
and less oily.
It's the best.
- No. 1? / - No. 1 for me.
- Please. / - Please.
(This is the best they can do)
I can't stop eating it.
Look at this.
That's our best expression.
It means the food makes them speechless.
There's no need for words.
You just need to keep eating.
Does the skin have more nutrition?
Look at this.
You're really good at separating the skin.
Did I uncover it too well?
Goodness.
Are you lonely these days?
(This is who Jihun is)
You're red even though you didn't drink alcohol.
You can be pink without drinking alcohol.
Did someone spike the trout?
- Let's try the cheese steak. / - Yeah.
This is so...
This can be photographed
and be on the menu right away.
That is America.
(Why does he pick it up?)
Girl's Day, are you watching?
Why do you keep saying that?
Since you're a really big senior,
they'll be uncomfortable.
When they were in...
You can stop now.
Let's just enjoy the food.
You debuted before they started school.
It's all done now.
You cut it up well.
Jihun cut up the food really well.
Let me try it.
- Let's eat. / - This is meant to be...
The most popular dish here.
It's not that expensive.
That's a good reaction.
- Good. / - I tried.
It's not too expensive.
It looks so delicious. Suddenly it looks delicious.
It's the same price as any local restaurant.
The trout is better.
Is it?
The trout does look better.
- Seriously that trout... / - They don't match.
The best fish of my life.
- Now... / - What?
Let's pick what we think is the best dish.
- Best dish? / - My best dish.
Let's choose one each.
I'll give you the choices.
1. Onion soup.
2. Cheese steak sandwich.
3. Trout steak.
Now choose.
1, 2, 3.
(1. Onion soup, 2. Cheese steak, 3. Trout)
- No. 3! / - No. 3!
(Trout steak wins 1st place)
There's no need for words.
The trout is the best.
Though it's hard to get here,
some people visit this place.
Those people must
order this trout dish.
It's really good.
- Can I take the last piece? / - Sure.
Let's go.
The atmosphere there is great.
- It's just... / - Just...
- Even the ceiling. / - It's just a different world.
Just nature.
- So vast. / - The hotel itself...
Isn't this place really amazing?
This place...
I can't express it in words.
This place makes me feel small...
Being between huge rocks like these.
This is the biggest rock in the world.
This is a rock? It's not a mountain?
Only masters of rock climbing attempt this rock.
While climbing, they hang there and take a break.
I heard that's how they climb this rock.
In February only,
when there's a sunset,
you can see the fire fall here.
What is that?
It's the sunset.
Only at a certain time, it reflects off the wall like that.
- I thought it was lava. / - Me too.
- I thought it was lava. / - Fire fall.
It's called fire fall.
I think I can't see it properly
because we're too close.
Let's look from further away.
- Should we? / - Let's step back.
We're surrounded by huge rocks here.
This place is really incredible.
It's so cool.
It looks like it's made
by a meteor crash.
I'm so glad I get to experience this in my life.
You can shoot
a music video here.
That'd be so nice.
If you have a camera,
you can film a movie or a music video there.
I love this song.
I'll be walking around lonely in the reeds here.
(Pant)
Are you filming for a video game?
This is somehow embarrassing.
Was it this song?
Hang on a second.
I won't lose to Choi Jungwon.
What is he doing?
Right now, I'm a puma.
- It looks cool. / - That's from the 1970s.
- There were lots of music videos like that. / - I apologize.
Why did you have to do that at such a nice place?
- They did it. / - The music video.
That's actually like a music video.
That's just like in karaoke rooms.
This was really common in the 1990s.
Why are you blowing your nose?
You two play in a cute way.
Doing this in Yosemite...
It can end up looking really cheap.
What on earth were you doing?
That is so...
I'm pretending there's a slope there.
- This is legendary. / - I'm acting there.
It looks like I'm really going down, right?
What is that?
Who knew it'd turn out like this?
(El Capitan)
(Tunnel View)
There's a tunnel over there.
Check out the tunnel.
- The tunnel... / - Once you're out of the tunnel...
How many times in our lives do you think...
- Tunnel View! / - We can see something like this?
I don't know how many times I've said wow
here at Yosemite.
You can really feel the nature.
Being influenced by the grandness of this nature,
my body is releasing
lots of endorphins.
Look at the trees
in nature.
It's just
like a landscape painting.
Shouldn't this be hanging on a wall?
The rocky mountain over there...
Doesn't it look familiar?
I'm sure you can figure out what it is.
This is where the famous computer wallpaper
was photographed, you silly.
- Your eyes aren't sharp enough. / - It's really pretty.
It's this place right here.
If you look in the phone, they have this emoticon.
- You saw this in person. / - There's a Yosemite emoticon.
Really?
Steve Jobs
really liked Yosemite National Park.
You have to
take photos in this spot.
(Tunnel View, who takes better pictures?)
This is the highlight.
I can't wait to see this part.
Camping.
I think this is the best.
I want to eat this.
- Rib eye? / - Yes.
The meat here are dry-aged.
This one and that one.
It looks so fresh.
They only sell organic food here.
This could be a weapon.
Is that a sweet potato?
We bought wine from a winery and
bought meat before going there.
It was awesome.
Now it's time for the grand finale.
It's dry-aged steak.
- Let's put salt on it first. / - He's cooking it?
- Look at the size of the meat. / - It looks delicious.
So you're today's chef?
I'm Baek Jungwon.
Baek Jongwon?
Baek Jungwon.
Oh, Baek Jungwon.
I know what I should do.
We bought potatoes and sweet potatoes.
Let's cook them in a Korean way.
If we wrap them with foil and put them in the fire,
they will be ready when we finish the steak.
Are you sure it's a sweet potato?
Let's begin.
You know in Korea, a dry-aged steak
costs hundreds of dollars, right?
- How much was it? / - How much was it?
Over there it was...
$50? It was definitely less than $100.
Shouldn't we cook this too?
- PyeongChang Olympics. / - The vegetables...
You know the small cabbage?
I'll light the flame.
PyeongChang Olympics.
Wait...
You have to cook it on a pan with olive oil.
Put Brussels sprouts on aluminum foil.
- Add olive oil. / - They look cute.
Season with salt and pepper.
Then cover it with the aluminum foil.
I've never been out of breath cooking steak before.
- Grilled potatoes are good, right? / - Yeah.
We shouldn't flip the steak too often,
according to Baek Jongwon.
(A common meat grilling scene at a camp)
I was in charge of the vegetables.
Jungwon was in charge of the steak.
(He places it next to the steak)
Jihun, look.
(Wow)
(The 38-year-old men are surprised)
Cook on this side then that side.
- Then the sides, right? / - Right.
You need to grill it roughly.
Looks so good.
(It looks breathtaking)
The sun set while we were cooking.
It looks cozy.
It looks delicious.
- If you go there with your partner... / - It was so good.
It does look delicious.
It's sweet.
It looks like it's steamed.
(Pink boy looks out for his friend)
It tastes really healthy.
This is so...
Let's cut it.
Very well aged.
This is the finest beef steak.
- Let's cut it. / - Let's cut it.
That steak was amazing.
- Is that a steak? / - It's...
This is the finest beef steak.
It looks really...
The absolute best?
It doesn't make sense. I've never seen such a steak.
It smells amazing.
Does it?
It's insane.
(Just looking at it makes them happy)
Straight to my mouth.
I want to show them the taste.
This is really good.
- That was his best reaction. / - It's the best.
That was the best.
- It must be really good. / - That was so good.
See? You can't help doing that.
It was really good.
I want to show them the taste.
This is really good.
After having this, I can't eat what I had before.
That's why this is served last.
Nice.
(They drink the wine they bought from Napa Valley)
The wine tastes even better than yesterday.
It does.
Who would have imagined...
- You could camp in Yosemite? / - Who would?
I didn't even know you could.
Even Steve Jobs couldn't do that because...
- You had a great experience. / - He's too famous.
Since we're in Yosemite...
- Let's make American dessert. / - Let's cook it.
Okay.
That looks amazing.
- I always wanted to try that. / -  I know.
You see it in movies.
- They cook it on a campfire. / - I know.
- They make s'mores. / - Yes.
Why are the marshmallows so big?
- Earlier... / - Look. Look.
Isn't it rice cake?
It looks like rice cake.
I have never seen this.
How does this happen?
It's all melted.
- Crispy outside and moist inside... / - Amazing.
Crunch.
This is the best one.
This is the best.
That looks the tastiest of all the food.
That's the best reaction so far.
This is the best food I've had here in the U.S.
- I know. / - I mean it.
I've never tasted something like this before.
I'm going to roast these at home now.
(A taste you want to take back home)
Should we have the ultimate experience of feeling small?
- Should we? / - Yeah.
Let's look up at the sky
and be immersed in the stars.
The stars that were hiding
are starting to reveal themselves.
Jihun, you sound like a poet.
I sometimes write poems.
Tears welling up in your eyes.
Can you really see that?
- What is that? / - What?
- Is that real? / - These stars were always there.
It's just that we couldn't see them.
(It's a beautiful gift from the sky)
I'm so envious.
It can't be described with words.
I wish the people watching this...
They might not feel this 100%...
I wish they can even feel 10%.
- 10%. / - Even 10% will be enough.
I feel really small in the face of nature.
This was the
most satisfying trip for me.
I told you.
That's why we came to Yosemite
on the last day of our trip.
San Francisco,
Pier 39,
Napa Valley Winery...
Anyone can go there.
But being here like this
in the grandness of nature...
- Having time like this... / - You're right.
- It's not easy to do. / - Very true.
Cluck Cluck Tour.
- Forever! / - Forever!
That's so amazing.
The winery and camping looked really good.
There were pouring stars.
If you look up at the sky,
you can't see stars immediately.
But if you wait for like 10 to 15 seconds,
you start to see them.
- Because our eyes... / - They're not used to it.
- Then over time... / - Like it's charging up?
You can't see at first.
I thought there were no stars at first.
But after 5, 10 seconds...
- There are so many stars. / - It's full of stars?
- It's full of stars. / - You're on the other team...
- But the camping looked really good. / - I'm jealous.
How did you carry up your luggage?
When you go camping...
They provide the tables and fire.
- They provide those things? / - Yes.
So you just need the food.
You can buy at a local grocery
and you can take the wine from the winery.
- That's good. / - Okay.
Cluck Cluck Tour went to Northern California.
It's time to find out how much the trip cost.
The total amount we spent for 3 days and 2 nights
in Northern California...
The total amount?
- Per person. / - Per person!
Per person?
$817.50.
Why's it so cheap?
- Cheap, right? / - Why is it so cheap?
Right?
Some of them are shocked.
- Let's vote. / - We'll stand up.
Let's say our final comments
and do the vote.
Rather than a fancy and fast-paced trip,
I prefer a slow holiday.
I love autumn.
So San Francisco...
If you want a slow trip
and you want to experience positive energy...
I recommend San Francisco.
Okay.
The trip that Cluck Cluck Tour planned...
Will you visit Northern California?
Yes or no? Please vote!
(Cluck Cluck Tour designed a trip to Northern California)
(What will the judges choose?)
We'll reveal the result together next week.
Next week.
Please look forward to the Southern California trip.
Please look forward to it.
We'll see you next week.
Thank you.
(Next week)
Everyone wants to visit Hollywood at least once.
On this trip,
we won't go to obvious places.
- Like we're the leads in a movie. / - The leads.
For California.
I'm so scared!
I'm the highest.
Let's go.
(Having fun, let's go with Girl's Day)
We're going to win.
We've won already.
("It's U" by Golden Child)