52 Tour!
- It's amazing here. / - It's amazing, right?
Look over there!
We should've come sooner. Just follow me.
Wow, check this out.
This was the inspiration for "Avatar."
It's so cool.
It's perfect.
Wow. Let's go!
(Unique observatory where you can see the whole city)
(Which team will win?)
(Numerous great tips on trips)
(Oh Nami, Lee Sookyung)
(So Yujin, Kang Raeyeon)
Travel is war.
Battle Trip.
Just like last week,
we have the trip planners who planned
the last-minute summer vacation trips.
- Welcome. / - Welcome back.
- It's good to see you again. / - Nice to meet you.
Last week...
- The whale shark was amazing. / - You're right.
It was impressive.
A lot of people asked me...
- How to get there. / - I see.
I think they'll make that into a Nami Tour package.
- I know. / - Starting with the whale sharks.
I'm going to Cebu again on my vacation.
- Again? / - Yes.
Actually,
I want to thank Nami.
Sookyung likes to stay at home all the time...
- But you showed her a new world. / - Right.
- It's great. / - I know.
Sookyung, do you want to go on trips now?
- Not at your home. / - Not my home?
A trip to your house doesn't count.
If you like to drink,
there are a lot of festivals.
A beer festival is held in Germany in September.
- It's Oktoberfest. / - Right.
- It sounds very fun. / - German beer.
- I want to go there. / - Sookyung.
How many beers can you usually hold?
I can't hold a lot of beer though.
Do you like to drink strong liquor then?
- Yes. / - This is the place.
- You should go to China. / - Right.
- Right? / - Definitely.
- We'll see. / - Is there...
A kaoliang festival in China?
- A kaoliang festival? / - Sookyung.
If they have a kaoliang festival,
people will black out there.
We have our 100 impartial judges
who will vote on today's trips.
- Welcome. / - Welcome.
If you can go on a long vacation in September,
where do you want to go?
Raeyeon, you are a travel expert.
- She's an expert now. / - Yes.
I'm not an expert but I like to travel.
And I like to go on a long trip.
Actually, this was my first time to go on a short trip.
I once went on a 13-month-long trip.
- 3 months? / - It's 13 months.
- 13 months? / - It's more like a migration.
Where did you go?
- Europe? / - I traveled around North America.
- That's so cool. / - It's like you immigrated there.
- When I went to North America... / - She's a master.
I kept moving around for 13 months.
Do you come to Korea sometimes?
- No, it's not like that. / - 13 months?
How long do you usually go on a summer vacation?
About 30 to 40 days.
I usually take short trips in the summer.
- But I don't like winter. / - Since she's a freelancer.
Right, I can do that because I'm a freelancer.
Then, can you recommend a good vacation spot?
When people ask me
what was the best travel destination,
I always say the Rocky Mountains in Canada.
It's amazing.
I think the Rocky Mountains is the best place
and Jiuzhaigou and Huanglong in Sichuan
are like mini versions of that.
- The colorful place? / - That's right.
That place is very famous on the internet.
It's so beautiful.
- It really is. / - Jiuzhaigou?
Anyway, most importantly,
like we had Kim Minkyo in Thailand
and Sandara Park in the Philippines,
we have Kang Raeyeon in China.
I think it will be very special today.
I have a question.
- She said Chengdu. / - Yes.
We've been to Chengdo though.
Is there a difference between
Chengdu and Chengdo?
- Please explain it to us. / - Or is it the same place?
Back in the day, Beijing used to be called Peking.
But now, we only use Beijing.
Just like that, Chengdo is actually Qingdao now.
Qingdao is Chengdo.
- And Chengdu. / - Chengdu.
It's pronounced Seongdo in Korean.
- Seongdo. / - But in Chinese...
It's Chengdu. It becomes Chengdu.
- She was so cool. So cool. / - My gosh.
- I'm immersed already . / - I see.
Then Chengdu is the Chinese pronunciation.
That's right. Chengdu.
- Learning can be fun. / - Exactly.
Four areas in China are knows for delicious food.
They are Beijing, Shanghai, Guangdong...
- And Sichuan where we'll head to. / - That's right.
- The Sichuan cuisine is one. / - Right.
For the Beijing cuisine,
although it's not exactly the same,
it's similar to Chinese food in Korea.
The Shanghai cuisine has more seafood
as it's closer to the ocean.
Since Sichuan is hot and humid,
the Sichuan cuisine tends
to be spicy in order to help them stay healthy.
Even the instant black bean noodles we eat...
- Sichuan-style noodles are spicy. / - They're spicy.
But it's a tasty kind of spiciness.
You can look forward to that delicious spicy taste.
Do you ask your husband for his opinions about this?
He likes it the most when I ask him...
- About food. / - He does?
- He gets excited to talk about it. / - He does.
He would recommend me restaurants to visit.
He'd tell me the restaurants I must visit.
He gives me tips on which dishes to order there.
- I'm so jealous. / - He has a lot of data stored.
- His data is outstanding. / - It's vast.
He tells you what to eat and where.
Let's check Chengdu in Sichuan on the map.
- It's big. It's huge. / - From Incheon to Chengdu...
The average flight time is about 4 hours.
- That's about the same with Cebu. / - Yes, it is.
- You made it sound like it was far. / - Right.
It took us 3 hours and 30 minutes.
In "Records of the Three Kingdoms,"
is it Shu Han?
- That's right. / - The state Liu Bei founded.
- That's right. / - Korean travelers...
Don't have much information on the city
as a travel destination.
But amongst Chinese travelers,
Beijing was ranked 1st as the destination
they'd like to go during holidays.
And the 2nd place was...
- It was Sichuan. / - Right.
I heard that the difference in the votes was quite big.
- No, that's not true. / - Not at all.
The locals love to visit Chengdu.
- You made her feel competitive. / - That's why...
- Over 200 million people visit. / - Each year.
- 200 million people? / - How many are Chinese?
- About 190 million people. / - It's about that many.
- A lot of Chinese people go there. / - The locals?
- There weren't many foreigners. / - Exactly.
- Everyone was Chinese. / - That's true.
- It's loved by Chinese travelers. / - Within China.
- That's right. / - That's a great city.
UNESCO chose Chengdu
as the first culinary city in Asia in 2010.
That proves that it's a city where
there's a lot to see and eat.
But you would need a visa to go there, right?
When you go to China,
you'd need to apply for your visa.
- I'll tell you a great tip. / - Okay.
For example, say that you travel far, like to Paris.
If you're making a transfer in Chengdu...
- You don't need the visa. / - When you transfer.
- When you make a transfer. / - For how many hours?
- 5 days. 72 hours in total. / - That's amazing.
So you only need to pay for one flight ticket...
- And you can visit two countries. / - That's right.
When you're going somewhere far,
don't set your flight dates
so you can visit the places we'll show you.
Anyway, I get the feeling this will be fun
because their trip will be totally different from Cebu.
- That's right. / - I think it'll be hard for you to choose.
Give us a highlight. We showed the whale sharks.
- Pandas represent China. / - Pandas.
Sichuan is the birthplace of those pandas,
so you can look at those pandas,
check out great food and night markets...
Night markets there are amazing.
If I were to make a comparison,
that place is similar to Samcheong-dong in Korea.
It's outstanding.
You'd find something new every day.
What's the name of your team? For the tour?
1, 2, 3. Zhendehao Tour!
Let's check it out. That was a bit weird.
Am I allowed to be on a popular TV show like this?
I've never been on a trip for a TV program.
But you travel a lot.
Whenever you go on trips,
I always see that you can't be reached for
specific dates on your profile.
Whenever people text me, they always ask this first.
"Where are you?"
- "Are you in Korea?" / - "Are you in Korea?"
- She's really free-spirited. / - I'm so jealous.
You're living a happy life.
I'm delegating everything to you.
My gosh, that's a lot of pressure.
The theme is the last-minute summer vacation.
- A trip over the weekend. / - Last-minute vacation?
For people with limited vacation days.
They use the weekends...
- To go somewhere close. / - Somewhere accessible?
- Places with direct flights. / - That would be better.
We'd go there on a night flight, have fun for 2 days...
- And come back at night. / - Friday to Sunday.
Destinations we can go over the weekends.
Then should we use my expertise?
(The master of trips to China)
Can I do that?
What she said reassured me. That's so reassuring.
You're the best at that.
- The outfit looks great on her. / - It does.
- Where have you been to so far? / - In 2004 and 2008.
I went around China for 70 days in total.
Despite that, I only saw two-thirds of China.
- That's how massive China is. / - You traveled a lot.
I wanted to think of a new destination.
I thought about Lijiang in Yunnan Province,
- I've never been there. / - But there's no direct flight.
- Really? / - It doesn't suit the theme.
- I checked the places with direct flights. / - Right.
- Have you been to Sichuan? / - No, I've never been.
Actually, I've been to Sichuan
but as soon as I landed in Chengdu,
I just spent a night there
and couldn't look around the city at all.
I only went to Jiuzhaigou and Huanglong.
(It's known as the greatest paradise on Earth)
- That's the place. / - Isn't it incredible?
I checked out the city in Chengdu a bit.
- There's a lot to see. / - The city?
I know nothing about that.
- Really? You'll just follow me? / - Sichuan...
- Yes, I'm going to do that. / - You only know how to eat.
Yes, I can enjoy the food to the fullest.
In other words, she's like Sookyung.
(Criticizing 2 people with 1 comment)
Their trip is different from Nami's. They're very close.
- They communicate very well. / - Exactly.
- You guys talked really formally. / - Yes, they did.
You can't get enough, right?
- The spicy Sichuan cuisine? / - You can't get enough.
- Yes. / - Right?
- This is awesome. I'm in. It's Sichuan. / - Got it.
(Sichuan)
(Chengdu in Sichuan)
(Chengdu is the center of Sichuan)
Pandas are the most famous Chinese animals.
(The one and only habitat for pandas in China)
- They were so cute. / - It was amazing.
- Look at them. / - I want that.
- Spicy food. / - That looks really spicy.
- What's that? / - That looks so delicious.
(Chengdu in Sichuan will introduce the spiciest food)
Let me research about the food since Chef Baek...
- Is my husband after all. / - That's true.
I'll look into what we can eat there.
- Let's get tips from him. / - Right.
Besides, he went to Chengdu for a show not long ago.
He went there to check out restaurants.
- He said the food was great. / - What did he say?
- A lot of the places didn't get to air. / - She must feel...
- So reassured. / - You know how he is, right?
Whenever I start something, he'd help me at home.
"You must know how it tastes to not look ignorant."
- He doesn't want you to look silly. / - Right.
- He'll educate me. / - Right.
- So for the food during our trip... / - This is great.
I'll ask him about some good restaurants.
I'll be the local coordinator and guide you.
- That's great. / - It will be perfect.
We must pick the name of our team.
Let's use Chinese for that.
You know the term you always say to me?
In China, you always say, "Zhende."
You always say that.
- Good, "hao." / - Hao.
- Then... / - Hao, hao.
This is how you say, "really good." Zhendehao!
Wait, that means "really good" in Chinese?
- It's not bad. / - That sounds good.
- It kind of sounds like "swag" in Korean. / - It does.
The CG looks great on you.
Our trip to Sichuan will be "really, really good."
Lots to see and lots to eat.
(Hello)
- What is that? That's a baby panda. / - Hello.
- Hello. / - A stuffed panda just moved.
I wonder what could top this?
Sichuan...
(The 3 stages of their sightseeing will lure you in)
So cute.
(1st stage, Chengdu Panda Base)
I'm so happy right now.
I've been mesmerized.
- That looks amazing. / - It looks magnificent.
It's time to eat.
I'm hungry.
- I'm getting hungry. / - That was so good.
- I'm not lying. / - That stuff makes your mouth numb.
That's so tasty.
I'm salivating.
What is that?
Oh, I ate it again.
Wow, super spicy.
- You added too much. / - Are you alright?
- That was really good. / - That's dynamite.
- Doesn't that burn your stomach? / - Not at all.
- It might ruin her stomach. / - Not one bit.
- It wasn't that spicy. / - I can't eat spicy food.
- The spiciness goes away fast. / - I can't eat spicy food.
Where are we right now?
This is Sichuan.
(Day 2 of the Zhendehao Tour)
(Chengdu in Sichuan)
(4-hour flight, 1 hour behind Korea, currency is Yuan)
(220 voltage used and tourists must apply for visas)
- We've arrived in Chengdu, Sichuan. / - In Chengdu.
We're on a trip! Here we are!
(The warning for their excitement has been issued)
- This is my first time. / - You...
- What do you mean? / - It's my first trip alone...
After giving birth.
- That's so true! / - I'm so happy right now.
- Look at you. / - I'm free!
- That's right. / - You can't help but jump up and down.
- I've only gone on family trips. / - It's hot and humid...
- But I'm happy. / - You are?
I'm still happy.
- Let's get a taxi. / - It's late.
- People ought to travel. / - Of course.
- This is so awesome. / - She's genuinely excited.
- Go, go, go! / - Go, go, go!
For the past 5 years, I gave birth to 3 kids.
- That was my first time... / - The bus looks so cute.
Going on a trip with a friend without my kids.
3 kids over 5 years? You're a real patriot, seriously.
(It's a bright morning on their second day of the trip)
(A place where the past and the present coexist)
(Chunxi Road, Myeong-dong of Chengdu)
(What is the Zhendehao Tour's first itinerary?)
This is a landmark in Chengdu.
- My goodness. / - That over there?
- Pandas are everywhere. / - That shopping mall...
Is as big as several soccer stadiums.
(Peek-a-boo)
What? Shopping is first on our itinerary?
- No way. / - Raeyeon.
When people think about Chengdu in Sichuan...
- They think of pandas. / - My goodness!
Chengdu in Sichuan makes you think of pandas.
- We'll go see pandas. / - She wore panda earrings.
- You'll go see the pandas first? / - Yes.
If we buy the tickets at the Panda Base...
The line will be long.
But we can buy tickets from there in advance.
This way, we won't wait in line there.
- Right. This is a great tip. / - It's over there.
- These kind of tips are great. / - There it is.
- The bus looks like a panda. / - The panda bus.
It's so cute.
- The bus looks like a panda. / - That bus is adorable.
Mr. Driver, you can't doze off here. Excuse me.
You can't doze off here.
Let's buy tickets for the shuttle bus...
- And the admission tickets here. / - Sounds great.
(They buy admission tickets to the Panda Base)
(She speaks Chinese like a pro)
The round ticket for the shuttle bus
and the admission ticket cost 73 yuan per person.
We won't have to wait in line. This is awesome.
- Right? / - I bet the line there will be long.
- Are we going to see pandas? / - We are.
I really wanted to see them.
This is awesome! This is so awesome!
(30 minutes by bus from Chunxi Road to the habitat)
(The park preserved the ecosystem for wild pandas)
Pandas are the most loved animals by the Chinese.
- Pandas. / - We came here to see the pandas.
We came here to meet them.
This is the Chengdu Panda Base.
- Here. / - Yes.
(They're wearing panda hair bands)
Pandas are breed only in China.
That's why Chinese people
are proud to have pandas in their country.
They give pandas as gift to other countries.
- They rent them out for long terms too. / - Right.
- Aren't they pretty? / - Right.
(Pandas in Korea are also from China)
It's very early in the morning...
- But there are a lot of people. / - Seriously.
We didn't wait in line.
- Because you bought them earlier? / - Yes.
- We could enter right away. / - I see.
It's very early in the morning.
- But there are a lot of people. / - Seriously.
There were more people earlier.
Here it is.
(Raeyeon gets the map first)
It's quite big.
This place is for those newborn baby pandas.
- We can see baby pandas. / - My goodness.
Let's start with baby pandas.
It'd be nice to see them in the growing order.
You know what? We've never seen baby pandas.
Right. We only see big ones.
Except for when it's on the news
that a baby panda is born.
Yes! Let's go!
I'm so excited.
The pandas...
It's summer here.
If it's too hot, they don't come out.
That's why you should come here in the morning
to see more pandas.
That's why even though we came here early,
the park is really crowded.
That many people go to see pandas.
It was packed with people.
- That was 7 a.m. / - Right.
I feel like we'll get to see many pandas today.
I hope we do. We came all the way here.
There are newborn baby pandas.
Let's go see them.
In this park, there are these twin pandas
that were born in 2018.
- Twins? / - They must be so cute.
They were born this year.
Would they be as big as this?
I bet they're tiny like dolls.
(How will wriggling baby pandas look?)
Wriggle, wriggle.
My goodness.
(Oh, my heart)
- Why? / - What is it?
- Why? / - Are they that cute?
Just take a look.
- They are so cute. / - We weren't exaggerating.
Where are they?
- Where did they go? / - I can't see them.
- Wait. / - Where are they?
How tiny!
- They're as cute as dolls. / - They're like dolls.
- Seriously. / - Aren't they the cutest?
- They don't look real. / - They're alive, right?
Aren't they the cutest?
They're moving.
(The twins are welcoming the Zhendehao Tour)
- My gosh, unbelievable. / - They're so cute.
They're the cutest.
- So cute. / - Look at its legs.
- It's so adorable. / - Seriously cute.
- Look at the paws. / - I want to touch its paws.
- It's so cute. / - I really want to touch them.
No way, they're so cute. They're the cutest.
- Its paws are the cutest. / - It's so cute.
- Look at that. / - How cute!
- It's stretching its body. / - It's stretching.
- Pandas are so cute. / - They're too cute.
Hey, gosh. Look at that.
- That one can't roll over. / - Bye.
Show us your face.
It's saying hello.
- Look. It's waving. / - Bye.
- Gosh, it's so cute. / - It's so adorable.
(The hosts and guests fall in love with the baby pandas)
Now, let's go see grown-up pandas.
- Get bigger. Good luck. / - Bye.
Get bigger.
(Surprised)
We can't talk here. No talking.
The panda is eating. It's having breakfast.
I guess it came out.
(Snap)
(It almost fell over)
He surprised himself.
(Gosh, that was embarrassing)
I see. This one...
It was rescued. In 2006, it was rescued from the wild.
- So the date of birth is unknown. / - Gosh.
And this is a male panda.
The date of birth is unknown.
The panda was just out there and having fun.
- How relaxing. / - People don't get to see him often.
- But we were lucky. / - The weather was great.
The weather was cool.
I guess it's delicious. That must be delicious.
(He puts on a cute act in front of these ladies)
It's itchy, isn't it?
It's itchy.
He's climbing up.
Those two are going to meet soon.
Is he climbing up?
- It's rare to see pandas move. / - Exactly.
On that day, it was a bit cool.
They climb really well.
(I was here first! You go back down!)
- He got poked in the eye. / - "Panda Theater."
- What is this? / - These pandas were so funny.
What's going on?
(The boss and the subordinate have a fierce battle)
(The subordinate chases the boss up the tree)
- He keeps climbing up. / - He climbed up.
- They're goofing around. / - Oh, no.
But they have such cute bottoms.
What if they are kissing each other?
- No, they're not. / - They're fighting?
- It's only big enough for one panda. / - They're slow.
- It's stuck. / - Because they're big.
(The subordinate closes in and gets the upper hand)
They are fighting.
- They're having fun. / - I guess that's a good spot.
- I guess so. / - It's stuck.
It got stuck. No, what will it do?
Their fight is so cute.
- It looks flustered. / - It's stuck.
That one is stuck. Oh, no.
- Its legs are in the air. / - They were dangling.
- Oh, no. / - Oh, dear.
- Oh, no. / - It's stuck. My goodness.
How cute. Its legs are in the air.
He chased him away.
Later on...
(How dare you? I'll get you later)
He's so relaxed.
He kicked him out in the end.
Watching them makes the time fly by.
That's the charm of pandas.
- They're charming indeed. / - Right.
We saw pandas...
- In different age groups. / - Right.
Now, let's go see the dyed pandas.
Let's go see the pandas after the hair salon.
- Pardon? / - Lesser pandas.
- What are red pandas? / - Do you know them?
Wait, that master was a panda too?
(Red pandas are known through "Kung Fu Panda")
(How will they look in real life?)
I thought we wouldn't see them.
Aren't they raccoons?
I heard it's hard to spot them.
There it is. Can you see it? Look over there.
- My goodness. I can see it. / - You can see it, right?
- It's my first time seeing one. / - Huh?
- Isn't that a raccoon? / - It's really cute.
- That's also a panda? / - Yes, it is.
Really?
- I thought it was a raccoon. / - It looks like a raccoon.
How far will you climb up?
(Dangling)
My gosh, all these people are worried about you.
(Laughing)
Goodness.
I thought it was going to fall off.
This one doesn't look chubby.
- Oh, my. / - It's so cute.
I didn't know it was a panda.
By the way, the color is quite unique.
They're not locked up like in a zoo.
The whole park is their base.
It's as if the people are locked up.
So you never know where they'll turn up...
- Inside the forest. / - That's so cute.
- Seriously. / - That one is intriguing.
- Its tail is so straight. / - So this is red panda.
This is our first trip.
- You said you would... / - Yes?
Research the restaurants.
Since we're in Sichuan...
- We'll enjoy spicy food. / - Okay.
It's the first stage of the spicy food.
- Like in different levels? / - Yes.
- Let's go eat our meal first! / - Go, go!
- Go, go. Let's go. / - Let's go.
(30 minutes by car to Kuan Zhai Xiang Zi)
- I'm hungry. / - If we continue on this alley...
We'll be at the restaurant you told me about.
This restaurant name means "Come enjoy our food."
- Really? / - So funny, yes.
(Sights, Food)
(Food)
(Dandan noodles)
- Dandan noodles. / - Dandan noodles are delicious.
- That looks good. / - Doesn't it usually have soup?
- They're stir-fried in Sichuan. / - Right.
- Originally, the dish is... / - This isn't a soup dish.
People say that when in Sichuan, eat dandan noodles.
People say that.
So, the spiciness level...
- Level 1? / - Level 1? Okay.
I'll trust you with food.
Because Mr. Baek has your back.
He explained the origin to me.
I was recording him to listen to it.
- It's a video. / - Yes.
When you go to a restaurant...
- What's he doing? / - My daughter...
He's dressing a doll.
I've never seen him like that.
He's busy dressing a doll.
You can't ask him this stuff when he's busy like that.
- He loves it when I ask. / - Does he?
Dandan noodles means to carry...
Dandan noodles.
That's why it's called dandan noodles.
How well they use the chili oil is very important.
The use of chili oil is very important.
Dandan means "to carry."
In the past, the vendors carried
the noodles and the ingredients to sell them...
- On the street. / - Dandan noodles.
Also, suan la something.
- Oh, suan la fen. / - The sour...
- It's dumplings with sauce. / - I like that.
(Finished ordering)
Good? Like this.
(Chewy boiled noodles)
Even if you can't speak Chinese...
- If you order what I showed you, / - Chili oil.
- That'd be enough. / - It'll suit our taste.
(Dandan noodles, $3)
(A charming sour and spicy dish, suan la fen)
(Raeyeon's recommendation, dumplings)
Finally, dandan noodles are here.
- Chili oil is at the bottom. / - Chili oil is important.
- The sauce is at the bottom. / - Yes.
- It's getting red. / - That's really delicious.
- It's so good. / - It's really red.
- It doesn't look too spicy. / - It's really delicious.
- It kind of looks like black bean noodles. / - Yes.
- It does. / - Here we go.
(How will the original dandan noodles taste?)
(Slurping)
I can smell the mala sauce right away
but I'm not repulsed by it.
It looks bland.
It doesn't look good but it's full of flavor.
That looks really good.
It's really good.
It's tasty and spicy.
It looks really good.
(Dandan noodles have a strong flavor)
The peanut sauce neutralizes the spicy flavor.
Even if you can't handle spicy food...
It's red but not spicy at all.
(Dandan noodles are slightly spicy)
- Is it like mixed noodles? / - Yes, it is.
It's like black bean noodles.
Goodness.
It's delicious.
Try the suan la fen.
- Suan la fen. / - Suan la fen?
Suan means "sour" and la means "spicy."
Suan la fen. Fen means "glass noodles."
- I tried it before. / - It's like kimchi stew.
Kimchi stew is a bit sour.
It's like kimchi stew.
Kind of like spicy meat soup.
It's health food.
(Suan la fen, $2)
That's interesting.
- It goes down so easily. / - Yes.
This is great for stimulating your appetite.
This glass noodles didn't get soggy, did they?
- They're like that. / - This is the original texture.
It's very similar to glass noodles we know.
(Familiar, yet strange look and texture)
I thought it'd be really spicy.
- It is the level 1. / - Yes.
It's not super spicy.
This is great for people
who are trying spicy Sichuan food for the first time.
(A good starting point for beginners)
- Is it spicy? / - It is, but it's sour.
It's less spicier than instant noodles.
Dumplings.
Boiled dumplings.
(Staring)
You have to eat dumplings in China.
I'm hungry.
This shows that we're in Sichuan.
You can tell right away.
"This is Sichuan."
(This is Sichuan!)
- I see. / - The sauce.
- You dip the dumpling in the sauce. / - Chili oil.
It's Sichuan red oil dumplings.
You dip it in sauce and eat it.
(Gosh)
(Yujin, who's in charge of food, is nervous)
I'm angry.
Why don't people know about this?
- She's angry. / - It tastes so good.
- That sauce is so good. / - The dumpling is good too.
- The skin is delicious. / - The pork inside.
- No vegetables? Just meat? / - Yes.
- Without sauce. / - It's so good.
I love meat dumplings.
That looks pretty inside.
- It's so good. / - Goodness.
The skin and the stuffing go so well together.
I think I can eat 100 of them right now.
- Seriously, I can. / - Right on the spot.
(It makes me angry)
The dumpling tastes perfect with the sauce.
This is no. 1 out of the 3 dishes.
(Who are you by the way?)
For your daughters?
(They dropped by a souvenir shop)
- It's a panda wearing a mask. / - It's so cute.
- Isn't it cute? / - Yes.
It's wearing blush.
- It's cute. / - It is.
- This is the Zhendehao Tour. / - Yes.
If something was fun, we'll take this panda out.
"Really good!" We'll express it with the panda.
Zhendehao Tour's spiciness level 1.
- Open it if it was delicious. / - Okay.
- Alright? Be honest. / - I am.
- 1, 2, 3. / - 1, 2, 3.
Should I call it harmonious?
It makes me angry.
(What will be the fate of the panda?)
- So if you like it, you open the lens? / - Yes.
Really good.
(Really good)
I'm so happy.
- What will we do? / - Now that we ate...
Have you ever had your ears cleaned?
- Ears? / - Yes. Do you do it yourself?
Yes, I do.
Here, there are professional ear cleaners.
They clean your ears.
- Do you think it's weird? / - I've never done it.
It feels so good.
After we do it, don't ask to do it again.
(Sights, Food)
(Sights)
(Kuan Zhai Xiang Zi)
- That was good. / - It was delicious.
There are more people.
- You're right. / - There are more people.
This is Kuan Zhai Xiang Zi.
Kwan means "broad," zhai means "narrow,"
and xiang zi means "alley."
This is like Insa-dong in Korea.
- Doesn't it look great? / - Goodness.
- It looks amazing. / - Nice.
It looks historical.
Let's go there together someday.
That place is really amazing.
(Experiencing old China in the city)
- This is like paradise. / - Really?
Because we can...
Shop and eat great food here.
(Kuan Zhai Xiang Zi is a popular place full of people)
What's great about this place is
that everything has a fixed price.
So you don't have to barter.
Bartering is tiring.
You don't have to do that.
- That's great. / - It's all set out.
- Because it's a designated tourist area. / - Right.
(China's old traditions have been preserved here)
- That's an instrument. / - It really looks like China.
(There are so many things to see)
- Are those noodles? / - Yes.
Awesome.
- He looks hot. / - What?
- Look at his face. / - So cool.
Goodness, what's that?
There are lots to see, along with the food.
Yes, it's fun to watch.
As you walk along, it's so entertaining.
We just walked down the wide street.
Now, when we turn left, and it's the narrow street.
It has a different atmosphere.
- Wide and narrow street. / - That street is really narrow.
We took pictures in the narrow street.
(Where are they off to next?)
Ta-da.
- What is that? / - Ta-da. We're here.
- Just on the street. / - Just like that.
There are so many on the street.
This is the place.
Is this where we get our ears cleaned? Outdoors?
- It was outdoors? / - They're...
Normally outside like this.
- Sit down. / - I'm taken aback.
People are passing by.
He'll clean your ears.
I'm scared.
- Are you scared? / - It's hot.
Yes. I've never done this before.
- Oh, my. / - He's so cool.
- He's very serious. / - Yes.
This kind of gives you goose bumps. It's not hot.
- He has a lot of tools. / - Yujin got scared.
I was really scared in the beginning.
(She's touched by the famous ear cleaning)
I can hear it.
Isn't it nice?
What?
- Isn't it nice? / - I shouldn't speak loudly.
(Laughing)
- It's like ventriloquism. / - You can talk.
If I do, my jaw will move
and it'll affect my ear cleaning.
When I take my kids to the doctor and
when they get scared of getting their ears cleaned...
I scolded them. But this is scary.
I understand how they feel now.
Can you ask them
if anyone bled while doing this?
Never. And they've been doing this for 12 years.
Relax. 12 years.
- What's that? / - What is that?
- Is it acupuncture? / - He's doing something.
- He said it's a massage. / - Wait a minute.
- Seriously, inside the ear... / - Wait.
He's massaging the inside of the ear.
You can feel all that.
(The inside of the ear is massaged through vibration)
He's not budging.
(It's my ear but I can't control it)
- She can't quit now. / - He's already started.
I just heard a drill in my ear.
(Fascinated)
- It looks interesting. / - It trembles.
- It feels really good. / - Doesn't it tickle?
It feels really good.
It seems like he's done with one ear.
(He's getting ready to clean the other ear)
His expression doesn't change.
She seems like she has given up.
I think I should go get a neck massage after this.
I'm straining my neck.
Once you try it, you'll love it.
It feels really good.
I love it.
(She looks uptight even from a distance)
He stuck something in my ear.
(Peaceful)
No, no, no.
My goodness.
(Anyway, the extreme ear cleaning is over)
I love it.
(Her soul is cleaned away together with her earwax)
Thank you.
So, how was the earwax cleaning?
To me, it's obvious. 1, 2, 3.
(Really)
- Really. / - Then, let's keep this one closed.
Let's open this one. Good.
I'd recommend this for a special experience.
I'd recommend this for an experience
but right after, you have to go get a neck massage.
I admit some people might not like it
but I love it. I like it so much.
It's nice but for those who try it for the first time,
they might not like it too much.
- Okay. / - They can be nervous.
- I understand. / - Just relax if you do it.
I like how it turned out in the end.
It's very interesting.
- She looks very relaxed. / - She does.
(They walk around the narrow alleyways)
There is an alley here as well. There are stores.
I love this street.
Do you know the sauce for mala hot pot?
- I know. / - They're selling the sauce here.
This is very spicy and this is a little spicy.
I'd like the one that is a little spicy.
(They purchased the soup for hot pot)
(Only 10 steps away from the store)
What is this?
This is a plum tea.
- Would you like to try it? / - Yes.
- Try it. / - It's interesting.
This was really good.
- The plum tea? / - Yes.
All the staff tried this and said it's really good.
- This is exactly what I wanted. / - Is it?
- It's not too sweet either. / - No.
After you eat a lot of greasy food
in a fancy restaurant,
you get a small glass of plum tea.
It's not too sweet. It has a clean taste.
- I really like this. / - I really like this too.
This is a chrysanthemum tea.
If you put this in the water,
the flower blooms in it.
If you serve this to the elderly...
- They will love it. / - Exactly.
Saying, "This is chrysanthemum tea."
- It's so pretty. / - It is.
- You're shopping a lot. / - We did a lot.
What is this?
(Let's see)
The one in the front is pudding
and those are rabbit heads.
- What? / - Rabbit heads?
- It has teeth. / - Yes?
There were all kinds of heads.
- Rabbit heads? / - They are the teeth, right?
Yes, they are.
(Culture shock)
(What did they find?)
- Hey, look at that. / - It's a pig.
It's a pig's nose.
Why are there spring onions in it?
There is only one nose...
- Per pig. / - Only one.
It's a limited edition.
A pig's nose?
(Should I try it?)
- How about we share it? / - Should we try it?
- It looks interesting. / - It could be chewy.
My gosh, I can't believe I'm trying a pig's nose.
- Take a picture of me. / - 1, 2, 3.
- Looks good on her. / - They wanted to take pictures.
They look good with it.
Look at that.
Thank you.
So, this is how it looks when it's sliced.
(They boldly take a piece)
I think some might not like this.
That's not true. Everyone will like it.
- Really? / - Everyone will like it?
It tastes like pig's head.
It's a lot more chewy than the pork hocks.
Some people only like the chewy part with pork hocks.
It's like a collection of the chewy parts.
I heard it's way chewier and tastier than...
- The chewy pork hock rind. / - You're right.
It's the pure chewiness itself.
- It's tasty. / - Is it?
Yes.
I think it's worth trying.
This is definitely worth a try. And you should...
Ask for the sauce.
You want the spicy sauce.
- Spicy sauce. / - So that's the sauce.
It's similar to the instant noodle base.
Is it similar to the spice we eat with lamb skewers?
It's a little different. It's less salty.
Right?
How was the pig's nose? 1, 2, 3.
- Really good! / - Really good!
Yujin opened it too.
- It was really tasty. / - It's so chewy.
It suits perfectly to my taste. It's so chewy.
(Really good)
- I'm hungry. / - We've been sightseeing a lot.
- It's about time to eat. / - Level 2 of the spicy food.
(15 minutes by foot to the mapo tofu restaurant)
This is the typical dish of Sichuan.
I asked my husband for the recommendation.
I'm very confident.
(She's confident)
You won't be disappointed.
It's a food trip.
I'd like to go on such a trip too.
(Sights, Food)
(Food)
(Mapo tofu)
- I smell something extraordinary. / - Me too.
Of course, we should try mapo tofu.
We're in Sichuan.
- Exactly. / - Is this restaurant famous for it?
That's what I heard. It's my first time here as well.
I was told I must visit this place.
Thank you.
Are we ordering mapo tofu only?
No, we should order something else too.
I heard there's something I must try here.
Do you what it is?
You mean the one that was written on the sign
in front of the restaurant? Fuqi feipian.
I heard that and mapo tofu
are the representative dishes of Sichuan.
I was recommended to try something else as well.
- Kung pao chicken. / - We had that at your house.
Yes.
Okay. Let's try the dishes...
Mr. Baek recommended.
What is fuqi feipian?
Fuqi means "a couple" and
feipian means "sliced boiled intestines."
It's coming.
(What's their first dish?)
- It's served. / - This is fuqi feipian.
It looks amazing.
- So this is it. / - Yes, it's fuqi feipian.
Fuqi feipian.
It's one of the 100 traditional Chinese dishes.
- Chinese people must love this. / - Yes.
My family always eats this on Seollal.
(Typical dish of Sichuan made with different meats)
It looks delicious.
(Fuqi feipian, $5.70)
I can't wait to try.
It looks like intestines.
This is like the meat in the intestine soup in Korea.
- This is tripe. / - Tripe.
There is the beef heart.
When you thinly slice meat like that, it's called "pian."
- So it's sliced meat. / - Yes.
- It looks delicious. / - Amazing.
- It's red. / - That oil was incredibly good.
- It was so delicious. / - Fuqi feipian.
(Fuqi feipian)
(How does it taste?)
I'm a Chinese living abroad.
We eat this for Seollal.
This is one of the dishes we always eat on Seollal.
But we don't eat it with this spicy sauce.
Ours is made with garlic, soy sauce and vinegar.
But they made it spicy here in Sichuan style.
So you haven't tried this spicy version?
I have, but this is the first time
to try the original Sichuan-style one.
I see why he recommended it. It's so good.
This sauce is...
Now I feel the spiciness.
(Coughing)
- It hits you late. / - It's like spicy instant noodles...
With Cheongyang chili in it.
But the spiciness...
- It's savory as well. / - It's not just spicy.
It has a texture of whipped cream with the first bite.
- It's so soft. / - The chili oil is so good.
This is a good restaurant.
The chili oil was soft and tasty like whipped cream.
- Chili oil was? / - Yes, chili oil was.
And then the spicy flavor hits you.
It's very well put, saying it was like whipped cream.
- It's has great flavor and... / - It does.
- It tastes so airy. / - Exactly.
Sichuan dishes can be too much
because of the spices.
But anyone can eat this dish.
When it's too spicy, eat this.
It goes so well together.
(What's their next dish?)
(It's stir-fried chicken with chili peppers and nuts)
They say Korean people like Sichuan dishes.
- This goes well with rice. / - You eat this with rice.
At first, she said we didn't need rice
because we ordered so much.
- Right? / - But we finished all in the end.
(Kung pao chicken)
Cheers.
(What does kung pao chicken taste like?)
- Oh, my goodness. / - It's what children would like.
(This is what children would like)
- Anyone would love this. / - Anyone would love this.
It's not just sweet. It's sweet and savory.
It's a little spicy but it's tasty.
Yes. It's delicious.
How is the meat so tender?
The best thing about this dish is the nuts.
(It's made with nuts)
I have to eat this with rice.
- It looks so delicious. / - You eat that with rice.
- It looks so good. / - It must be good with rice.
I'll copy you.
You must eat this with rice.
(Wow)
- Sichuan has so much great food. / - It was so good.
(What does kung pao chicken taste like with rice?)
(She talks with her eyes)
It's here.
The main dish is here.
There's more.
- The mapo tofu. / - The mapo tofu is here.
- It's mapo tofu. / - Mapo tofu.
(Spiciness level 2 of the Zhendehao Tour)
It looks different from what we've seen.
It looks like soft tofu stew.
It's nothing like the mapo tofu we have in Korea.
- It's totally different. / - It looks like a stew.
The main dish is here.
I need some rice.
- You should eat it with rice. / - You need rice.
You definitely need rice.
Look at how beautiful this looks.
(Appreciate the beauty of mapo tofu)
- What should I do? / - Let me try it first.
Just mix it quickly.
(Rice covered with mapo tofu)
Sichuan mapo tofu has a lot of
chili peppers in it.
And minced meat.
- It has minced meat in it. / - This is so hard.
- It looks amazing. / - It tastes great with rice.
I'll have some Chinese food after this.
This is like torture.
I admit that the food is great there.
(Mapo tofu on rice is ready)
(What does mapo tofu taste like in Sichuan?)
It tastes so clean.
It's completely different from what we had in Korea.
This is nothing like that.
And this has different spiciness
from what we had in fuqi feipian.
This isn't smooth.
It comes in clean and gives you the taste of tofu,
then the spicy flavor hits right after.
It tastes very arrogant.
It tastes confident.
"I'm mapo tofu."
"What are you going to do about it?"
It tastes like that.
- "I am mapo tofu." / - "It's me. It's me."
When you go to Chengdu,
you have to taste this mapo tofu.
- You're right. / - I think this is excellent.
- It really is. / - I...
It feels like...
I did what I was supposed to do today.
Right, you did a good job today.
Thank you for taking me to this restaurant.
- Really? / - And tell your husband...
I appreciate his advice.
It was amazing.
- So, are we going to make a wish? / - Yes.
We have to see the statue.
We have to get ready early.
(Now it's time for the nature of Chengdu)
I'm overwhelmed.
- Even the path is pretty. / - Isn't it so pretty?
- The ear. / - Amazing.
This is huge.
Look at that.
- Bian Lian. / - Bian Lian.
That's right. It's Bian Lian.
It's convenient food.
(They conquer the taste of Chengdu)
This is the best Sichuan food.
This place is really popular.
It looks so good, right?
(Pleasure for your mouth, thrill for your body)
My ears are hot.
Wow. Let's go.
(Day 3 of the Zhendehao Tour)
This is second day of Zhendehao Tour.
Today, we're going to...
The Leshan Giant Buddha. I talked about it yesterday.
- There's a statue of the Buddha. / - Our first stop.
You might have seen it on TV before.
There's a huge statue of the Buddha.
It's called the Leshan Giant Buddha.
It was famous before
but it became even more famous
because Xi Jinping became the president...
After making a wish there.
Making it even more famous.
It's become even more famous.
And there's an interesting thing about this place.
Let's say we made our wish there.
If our wish is realized,
we have to visit the place again.
- Why? / - We have to go back there...
To say thank you.
- To thank the Buddha? / - So if we go there now...
We can visit the place again later.
I hope Raeyeon will get married next year.
I'll make a wish like this.
- Will your voice get heard? / - If you get married...
Don't whisper and just say it.
(This is the biggest stone-carved Buddha statue)
I'm so hungry now.
We should eat something first.
You're in charge of that.
Right, so I prepared something simple.
- I'm sure you'll like it. / - Is there a good restaurant?
- Can we have breakfast first? / - Of course.
- Let's eat first. / - Let's do that.
- Quickly. / - Let's go.
(First, they go to eat breakfast)
What are they having for breakfast?
What are they eating for breakfast in Sichuan?
We're having jianbing for breakfast.
It's a kind of crepe
that you can try anywhere in the streets of China.
(Excited)
(On thinly spread wheat-flour batter)
- Is that it? / - I've seen it before.
- Is this jianbing? / - Yes. It's jianbing.
It has egg in it.
- It looks delicious. / - You can add...
- Anything to it. / - You can choose what you want.
It's a popular street food.
And it's good for breakfast.
- My gosh, there's a lot. / - It looks great.
I love watching videos on this.
- Really? / - The video of making jianbing.
It's very popular.
Let's order one that has chicken and pork in it.
And should we get one with beef in it?
I'll have one with a lot of meat in it.
- This one has the most meat. / - Really?
People in their 30s love meat.
- That's right. / - People in their late 30s love it.
(Place an egg on top of the batter)
(Beat egg gently)
It's like toast in the morning.
- It looks good. / - Turn it over.
- They're turning it over. / - Is that black sesame?
Yes, sesame seeds.
- Black sesame? / - You can add anything you want.
(Raeyeon's choice is beef jianbing)
- You can choose the topping. / - I see.
You can add beef, pork, and chicken
in one if you want.
It's like a Chinese burrito.
- That's right. / - It's like crepe.
- Right. / - Crepe.
(Family set jianbing, $3.30)
It looks delicious.
(Beef Jianbing, $2)
This is our first meal of the day.
It's jianbing.
Jianbing.
(Their first meal of the day)
I really wanted to eat this.
(Cutting the jianbing in half)
What is that? Is it fried shrimp?
They added something like nacho chips.
- To make it crisp. / - Right.
- It was good. / - I loved the texture of it.
The meat was tender and the chips were crispy.
- Great combination. / - I saw them sprinkle something.
This is so good.
It has egg, meat
and vegetables in it.
- Yes. / - Nutritionally, it's a perfect breakfast.
- It's the best. / - It's like a hamburger...
For breakfast. It's simple but filling.
- But this is much healthier. / - Right.
Exactly.
It looks delicious.
What is this crispy powder?
- This powder? / - Yes.
They make it with pork or beef.
- Okay. / - They make the powdered meat...
And add it on rice or porridge.
So they added it like seasoning in here as well.
It's sweet.
- Do you like it? / - Yes.
The powder tastes so good.
One jianbing is big enough for a woman.
Right. We could've shared one together.
We are actresses, so it was way too much for us.
(It's a delicious and hearty breakfast)
After we finish this, we will take a train.
Really?
We have to take the train.
Let's eat quickly so we can make it on time.
- You can also take out the food. / - Right.
Yes, takeout.
We had it at a mall near the train station.
You can buy it before getting on the train.
(It's so delicious that they can't even leave)
(Sights, Food)
(Sights)
(The Leshan Giant Buddha)
We have to see some attractions now.
- You just keep eating. / - Right?
(They arrive at the train station to see the Buddha)
So, we're going to the Leshan Giant Buddha now.
And we have to take a train.
It takes about 2 hours. That's why...
- We hurried out early. / - Do they sell food there?
We just had jianbing for breakfast.
And you want food again?
I just want some snacks.
Since we're in Chengdu,
it'll be fun to take a train to go to the suburbs.
(1.5 hours from Chengdu station to Leshan)
(30 minutes by car to the Buddha)
(Leshan is located in south-central part of Sichuan)
After 2 hours,
we've finally arrived
at the Leshan Giant Buddha!
I'm so excited.
I've got a treat prepared for you.
- Really? Why? / - We're going on a cruise ship.
On the cruise,
you can see the entire statue.
From the boat.
It's a stone-carved statue of the Buddha on a cliff.
It's the biggest statue of the Buddha in the world.
Go, go, go.
In the Tang Dynasty,
they had a lot of accidents there.
- Like ship accidents or floods. / - Ship accidents.
So they carved the statue of the Buddha
wishing there would be no more accidents.
- Like a guardian? / - Yes.
But it took 90 years to make it.
They made it for 90 years?
So the workers died before the statue was completed.
True, true.
(Leshan Giant Buddha Cruise)
(30-minute course, $23.40)
(They run cruise ships during summer and winter)
The Leshan Giant Buddha will be on your left.
- Left? / - Yes. Over there.
You'll see it once we go around the corner.
- Look at those people. / - I'm excited.
- What's it like? / - We'll see it just after a turn.
We're at the best spot to see it.
I knew it.
(After 10 minutes, they are in front of the statue)
It's right here.
I can see it. I just saw its foot.
(The Leshan Giant Buddha shows up)
This must be it. I think we're here.
- My gosh. / - Gosh, this is it.
It's enormous.
- It was really big. / - It's huge.
- It's as big as a mountain. / - It's the mountain itself.
- They carved that out? / - My goodness.
- It took about 100 years. / - It's like a mountain.
On a single toe,
you can sit five adults.
- On one toe. / - Yes.
- Gosh, it's so big. / - It's really big.
It's as tall as a...
- 25-story building. / - Even the size screams "China."
(It took over 90 years to complete)
(It remembers 1,000 years of history)
(It's the biggest stone Buddha in the world)
I'm overwhelmed.
I feel overwhelmed.
- No wonder she feels overwhelmed. / - It's very big.
(There's a saying that compares it to a mountain)
"This mountain itself is the Buddha..."
"And the Buddha itself is the mountain."
- I see. / - This is amazing.
It's magnificent.
It's awesome.
We came all the way here. I'd like to see more.
- That's why... / - Do you know what I mean?
- That's why... / - Yes.
I'm taking you here.
After a 15-minute walk,
we'll reach the ear of the Buddha.
But I heard it takes 3 to 4 hours.
The route going all the way down to the feet takes
3 hours.
It takes only 15 minutes to get to the ear.
(After 380m of hiking, they can see the Buddha)
The Leshan Giant Buddha.
This is the way to the Leshan Giant Buddha.
I'm nervous.
(Gulping)
Are they all stairs?
- It only takes 15 minutes. / - Right.
- It was the perfect course. / - They're all stairs.
You ate so much. You need to work out a bit.
- Luckily, it's not that steep. / - No, it's not.
It's hot.
I'm sweating so much.
(It's hotter than they thought... They're sweating a lot)
(Spaced out)
She suddenly became quiet.
That's not it.
I was making a wish while climbing the stairs.
The more I get to know you, the funnier you get.
- She's so extreme. / - Yes.
- She's either silent or talkative. / - Right.
(The stairs look endless)
- I see the ear! / - Ear, ear.
- It's the ear. / - You can see it.
I can see the head and eyebrows.
(It looks enormous even from a distance)
This is amazing.
- This is amazing. / - The camera...
Can't capture its greatness.
You should be there to feel its magnificence.
(The Buddha looks even more magnificent up close)
Seeing the whole figure from a distance was great,
but seeing it from up close is also amazing.
This is amazing.
When I saw it from a distance earlier,
it was surreal as if I was watching television.
Seeing it from up close, it's even more surreal.
- Don't you think so? / - I agree.
(It's unbelievably huge)
I'd like to remove those weeds.
- It's so big. / - Right.
- It's so different. / - Look over there.
They're queuing.
(This is just as incredible as the size of statue)
They're queuing there to walk down safely.
There are too many people.
- To walk down to the feet? / - Yes.
It's a queue to walk down.
(It's a walking route that takes 3 to 4 hours)
- It'll take a whole day to see it. / - Yes.
Many people walk down the stairs...
- To receive good energy. / - To make a wish.
There are a lot of people doing that.
(The path makes their wishes come true)
(They make wishes as well)
They're making a wish.
Alright.
- It's time to rate. / - Yes.
The Leshan Giant Buddha of the Zhendehao Tour.
Let's rate it.
Alright.
1, 2, 3.
Really good!
- It's a must-see. / - It is.
I liked seeing it from a distance but seeing it up close,
you get a greater sense of feeling.
It has a mysterious energy.
Yes, we got positive energy.
I'm glad I came up here.
If you have time, it's not bad to walk down for 3 hours
but even if you don't have time...
- It only took us 15 minutes. / - Right.
It didn't take so long for us to climb up here.
I hope you don't miss this.
(The Leshan Giant Buddha is the biggest stone Buddha)
We're not getting the full effect because
it's not in person.
Look at the size of the people compared to it.
It's huge.
(2 hours by car to Chengdu)
- Are we now in Kuan Zhai Xiang Zi? / - Yes, we are.
There are a lot of great restaurants here.
As you know, today is our last day.
We're going to a very special place
for our last dinner.
(Sights, Food)
(Food)
(Hot pot)
(There's a typical Sichuan dish)
(It's loved by young and old, male and female)
(It's one of the spiciest dishes, hot pot)
I love Chinese hot pot.
Fresh lamb is delicious.
Lamb is amazing.
- It was incredible. / - Fish is also delicious.
Fish fillet in hot pot is the best.
(Raeyeon orders a lot of food)
How would you like your broth?
There are different levels of spiciness.
Would you like it mild, medium or extreme?
- Medium? / - Medium.
Medium or a little bit spicy?
Medium? Do you think medium will be alright?
(They order medium spicy broth)
Medium spicy.
(I hope it's not too spicy)
It looks like there's a performance down there.
There's a dancing dragon.
Shall we go have a look?
(They decided to watch a show before the meal)
This is so nice.
- Yujin seems truly happy. / - She's so excited.
She's so excited.
(You can watch traditional Chinese performances)
That's pouring tea.
(Here, you can have a meal and watch a show)
It seems like the Bian Lian is starting soon. Let's go.
Let's go down and watch it.
- We need to watch it nearby. / - What is Bian Lian?
The show where they quickly change face masks.
It's a mask changing show.
- Bian Lian is really interesting. / - It's fascinating.
It's really interesting.
It's fascinating.
(He changes masks in an instant)
Bian Lian originated from the Sichuan region.
(It's a mask of a cartoon character)
There are a lot of places where they have Bian Lian.
(It's so cute)
(It's the highlight of the show)
(He interacts with the audience)
He pretended to kiss my hand,
then his mask changed.
- In front of your eyes? / - Yes.
It's like magic.
(Startled)
Yujin easily gets scared.
I get scared very easily.
(It was a success)
(The highlight of Bian Lian)
(It's a fire show)
You can watch this show for free, right?
Yes, but you have to be there on time.
(It's time to treat their mouths now)
(Red soup and white soup, $11.40)
Let me make the sauce.
The sauce is the most important for hot pot.
We're in Sichuan,
which is a place known for spicy food.
- Peanut sauce... / - They don't have peanut sauce.
- No, they don't. / - I'm so sad.
I don't know what I should do now.
- But I will... / - I eat a lot of peanut sauce.
Don't worry.
I can make a great sauce.
This is sesame and corn oil.
Let me add the sesame and corn oil.
There must be a perfect recipe for it.
You can pour everything in if you want.
I prefer to add a lot of garlic in it.
- I love garlic and spring onions. / - You need cilantro.
I'll add a spoonful of oyster sauce.
People have different tastes.
- But most people like it this way. / - What is it?
- It's black vinegar made of rice. / - I like vinegar.
Vinegar in the sauce makes it easier
for Koreans to eat the dish.
- I should learn this recipe. / - This is a Taiwanese way.
(The hot pot is starting to boil)
I can smell it.
(White soup, red soup)
Let me start with the hard ingredients for the broth.
It's for the broth.
Let me put radish in.
Can I try the soup?
- Try the soup. / - Okay.
When we eat shabu-shabu in Korea,
we cook porridge with the soup.
But Chinese hot pot is made of oil.
So you can't drink this soup.
It's only to blanch the ingredients.
It coats the ingredients and adds a spicy flavor to it.
After some time, the oil is all gone.
- Try it. You'll be surprised. / - Okay, I'll try like this.
(Yujin tastes the soup with her chopstick)
How is it?
Oh, my.
Is this the medium level of spiciness?
This is medium.
This is only medium spiciness.
Why don't you try it?
- I'm okay. / - Really?
What?
It really was okay with me.
Didn't you suppress it?
Strangely, I can't eat Cheongyang chili...
- Or spicy rice cake. / - It's so strange.
But this was okay for me.
The spiciness is different.
It's completely different.
- I'm scared. / - Isn't that right?
You must be strong when it comes to hot pot.
I came to Sichuan to eat this.
(Worried)
Cheers. Our last drink.
(It's time for them to eat properly)
Let's enjoy the food.
Pick an ingredient you want.
And sway it in the soup.
- What is that? / - It's lamb meat.
- Lamb meat? / - It looks so delicious.
- I'm really hungry. / - Yes.
I'm going to eat this in a wrap.
In case I get surprised by the mala sauce,
I'm going to try the ones in white soup first.
Me too. I will also try the white soup first.
- Dip it in the sauce. / - Wrap it.
I make a thick sauce.
- I don't dip it, I wrap it. / - That looks so good.
I wonder what the sauce is like.
It's good.
(The white soup is also okay for Yujin)
Is that all oil?
No, white soup is just meat broth.
It's meat broth, so you can eat it easily.
It's really delicious.
It's time to try the mala hot pot for me.
- Raeyeon. / - It's dripping.
- It's dripping. / - Look at the oil.
It's coated with oil.
- It got coated on the way up. / - That's right.
She'll eat it after she dips it in the sauce.
(She also takes a big mouthful this time)
(I bet that's really spicy)
That looks so good.
It's art.
With beer.
It's okay. It's really okay.
- Really? I want to try it too. / - Yes.
I'll try now.
I'll try the meat first. The meat is here.
(Yujin tries the red soup)
- It's hitting her. / - She can taste it.
Did something happen to you?
It's no joke.
You seem really okay
when it was so spicy for me.
Can you think of it as a spicy shabu-shabu?
- The spiciness is different. / - Yes.
- Aroma is important in this dish. / - That's right.
It's not spicier than Cheongyang chili.
It's not that kind of spiciness. It builds up gradually.
I continue to eat more because I get greedy
thinking that it won't get any spicier.
It's delicious.
- It makes you angry? / - It makes me really angry.
Why do I have to eat this?
- Honestly, I'm going to eat more. / - Eat some more.
I'm going to eat more.
- These are bamboo shoots... / - Yes.
- Bamboo shoots. / - With shrimp inside.
They put shrimp wontons in bamboo shoots.
- Inside there? / - The texture is amazing.
- That looks so good. / - It was so interesting.
(How does the bamboo shoots with shrimp taste?)
Let's try it.
- Isn't it good and interesting? / - It's good.
(She is in awe as soon as she eats it)
I've never tasted something like this.
(She's mad again)
The inside is so tender
but the bamboo shoot doesn't taste like
the ones we usually have.
It feels like we're eating salmon roe. It's popping.
No one will never know that it's bamboo shoot
if you don't tell them.
It's crisp when you bite into it.
You can tell it's bamboo shoot as you eat it.
You really have to order this.
- Why? / - A lot of people miss this.
- Okay. / - It's a unique taste.
I'm going to try this next.
I'm going to make this in a wrap.
I've dipped it.
(She's impressed)
I think I can manage the spiciness now.
I'm completely fine right now.
Can we try a spicier level then?
Can we try a spicier one?
(It's hard to hide her shaking eyes and hands)
I think I can try it.
How can she...
(It makes you doubt your very eyes)
How will she...
- That's just the next level. / - You have to look inside.
(Unbelievable)
Really good!
No way.
Yujin.
This isn't a joke.
You should eat it like that since you're in Sichuan.
It's different to putting Cheongyang chilies in.
I'm starting to sweat from my head already.
- That's amazing. / - Look at Yujin's face.
- Nice reaction. / - It's free to order...
The next level of spiciness.
(Forced smile)
She can't stop laughing.
(What am I going to do?)
What level is that?
- It's the last level. / - It's level three.
It's the spiciest level.
Raeyeon is amazing.
It will taste the best if you put noodles in there.
(She's caught)
That means it's spicy for her.
It's spicy!
- Wipe your mouth. / - Wait.
I'm fine. I'll explain.
(She starts to show off when it comes to hot pot)
It choked me when I breathed but it's not spicy.
Touch my throat, it's not hot at all.
- I'm totally fine. / - It's really hot.
She's showing off. She's a show-off.
No, it's not spicy at all.
(Yujin just tries it)
She tries it.
This isn't a punishment.
Tell me.
This is really funny.
My ears are hot.
It's because you picked your ears.
Level 3 isn't that bad.
(It's time to evaluate the level 3 spiciness)
- 1, 2, 3. / - 1, 2, 3.
- Really good. / - Really good.
Undoubtedly, it's really good and unique.
- I really enjoyed it. / - Yes.
It's really, really, really good!
They ate all of it.
- There's nothing left. / - We ate all of it.
- We ate all of it. / - We ate all of it.
We still have some time left until our flight.
- We still have time. / - That's right.
We can't give up this time.
- Let's go to the Anshun Bridge. / - Okay.
It's like the Venice of Sichuan.
There is a river, pretty coffee shops and bars.
We'll spend some time there
to make us feel better and go to the airport.
- Okay? / - Okay.
We took a late flight.
It was early in the morning the next day.
(Sights, Food)
(Sights)
(Anshun Bridge)
- The night view is amazing. / - It's so beautiful.
This place was really nice.
It's too sad to just go to the airport like this,
and we still have time.
We came for the night view.
The night view is amazing. This is Anshun Bridge.
- It's so pretty. / - Isn't it so pretty?
"Pretty" isn't enough to explain this view.
(Anshun Bridge feels like it's representing China)
It's really beautiful.
It feels like it's representing China.
- Isn't it amazing? / - Yes, it's so nice.
There's nothing that's a waste of time...
- In Chengdu. / - That's so right.
(It's time to end the Zhendehao Tour)
- It was really nice, right? / - Yes.
It was really special for me.
This trip was the first trip I went on with a friend
after I got married and had babies.
- It felt like a dream. / - Yes.
I was just really happy.
I really enjoyed it especially because I was with you.
Do we have to cry now?
Are you trying to make me cry?
I liked Kuan Zhai Xiang Zi where we went first.
- Yes, the alleys. / - We went shopping there.
Watching the street vendors and watching the people.
It was a short schedule but there was a lot to do.
- That's right. / - Yes.
- Everything went well. / - That's right.
- The mapo tofu was intense. / - Yes.
It was good.
It was the food that made me realize
that I was really in Sichuan.
Hot pot is also a traditional food in Sichuan.
Right.
I was really happy because you reserved
such a nice restaurant.
It was fun.
It was such a special time.
The person who ordered to add more spiciness
was you, not me.
It was amazing.
I didn't know they would add so much.
- It's still spicy. / - I was...
Don't even talk about it. It still hurts my stomach.
Let's go to the airport. Let's go.
I have to go back to my kids now.
Kids, wait for me.
(The End of the Zhendehao Tour's Chengdu trip)
(The trip was as plentiful as we expected)
Our team had the whale shark
but they had the adorable pandas.
I thought the panda was a doll.
- It was so amazing to see it move. / - It was wriggling.
- Pandas aren't just... / - It's so funny.
An animal in China.
- They're symbolic. / - That's right.
Since pandas are continuing to disappear,
they do artificial insemination for them there.
- Pandas are increasing. / - Then...
- They send them back to the wild? / - Yes, they do.
While we were watching it,
you went to Kuan Zhai Xiang Zi twice.
You went there to eat once,
and to sightsee another time.
You can go there every day.
- Really? / - Even if you go there every day...
You can't see everything nor eat everything there.
Is there anywhere else
you would like to recommend in Chengdu?
This place used to be Shu Han from
the "Records of the Three Kingdoms".
Wuhou Temple has Liu Bei's grave.
If you go there,
they have everything about
the "Records of the Three Kingdoms."
- You'll enjoy it if you like that. / - It will be like...
- The sacred place for men. / - Yes.
I think it will be really interesting.
There's a street called Jinli
that looks exactly like Shu Han.
There's a street like Kuan Zhai Xiang Zi.
There's a lot to see there.
There are so many places to see.
- I can't introduce all of it. / - Because it's so big.
Can't you just come with us whenever
there's a China special?
I wish I could do that.
I enjoyed it so much.
- It's so nice. / - Let's see the final expense.
Last week, 52 Tour spent $285.
- It was for 52 hours. / - Yes, $285.
For 2 nights and 3 days, the final expense...
- In Chengdu is... / - What's the final expense?
- The airfare is excluded. / - For one person is...
- For one person? / - Including the accommodation.
The total came to...
- $269. / - Really?
- It's cheap. / - Wait a minute.
Aren't the prices cheaper in the Philippines?
Sichuan is also cheap.
- China is also cheap. / - But Sichuan...
China is also cheap.
Are you ready to vote?
Would you go to Chengdu according
to the Zhendehao Tour?
- Please vote. / - Please vote.
(They planned a last-minute summer vacation trip)
(What will the judges choose?)
Will it be 52 Tour's Cebu trip
that had an uncommon course?
Or will it be Zhendehao Tour's Chengdu trip where
they had both amazing things to eat and see.
It's so close.
What will the judges choose?
Please.
(Cebu vs. Chengdu)
- Let's just make it a tie. / - Oh, my.
I don't know why I get so nervous.
- Why am I so nervous? / - It makes you nervous.
- I don't know what to do. / - First win.
I think we're going to see the first digit.
- The first digit. / - First digit.
- I think it will be high. / - Both trips were really nice.
- It's the first digit. / - They were really nice.
It's 7.
- It was nice. / - It's 7.
They are both 7.
The first digits are all 7.
- We will win. / - Show us the results.
- 52 Tour. / - You surprised me.
- 52 Tour. / - What will be the result?
- 52 Tour. / - 52 Tour.
52 Tour.
(76 vs. 78, Zhendehao Tour won)
We won.
China won by two points.
- We won. / - We won.
(It was so close)
This is...
- This is amazing. / - This is amazing.
- Congratulations. / - Thank you.
I will really go and see the whale sharks though.
You should really see it.
It was unexpected.
Both trips were nice,
that's why it was so close at the end.
- Kim Iljung was with us today. / - Yes.
How was it for the last 2 weeks?
I really enjoyed it.
Before my family went to the U.S. to study,
we went to Cebu.
But we only stayed at the resort,
so I think my children will really like the whale sharks.
My wife also likes spicy food.
So I want to go to Chengdu to eat that with her.
Since I'm thinking about my family...
I really miss them but 3 weeks have passed already.
- Already? / - I don't know what he means.
A special is prepared for next week's Battle Trip.
- Is it another special? / - Really?
- It's expected now. / - Yes.
We had a married couple special...
- Early this year. / - That's right.
Next week, we will see two couples
who have amazing chemistry that went on a trip.
- Please look forward to it. / - Alright.
Please look forward to the married couple special.
We will come back next week.
The world is your school. Life is a journey.
Battle Trip!
Thank you.
(Next episode)
(Episode 2 of the married couple special)
- This is nice, right? / - It's lovely.
I think you've gained a lot of weight.
Thank you.
You're the best.
Sapporo television tower.
How is it?
(A tour full of innocence, Kim Yuna and Kim Hyungkyu)
This isn't corn.
Wait a minute. I didn't eat it yet.
(A sacred place for lovers, an eternal pledge)
It's so unrealistic.
You can't get this in photos.
I want to store it in my eyes as much as I can.
(Battle Trip)
("'Bout You" by Super Junior D&amp;E)