um so this is part 2 of a video I was
talking about all the things that were
wrong on my trip to Korea and I'm just
gonna tell you guys about this specific
event that happened with my whole self
you haven't watched the first video you
should probably watch it and get the
background information that led up to
this point or you could just watch from
here and just I don't know two weeks
into my trip my friend from Norway left
she's gone so I already have like places
on Airbnb that I'm looking that I have
saved in like a list and I'm considering
moving into it's 14 out of my twenty
fourteen or what's twelve twelve days
out of my twenty eight days stay in his
room it's a Sunday I got back to my room
I needed to do laundry so I washed my
clothes then I hung them up to dry a lot
of places of Korea don't have dryers
same with Japan
you gotta air dry important detail the
way the rooms are set up my room his
room there are screen doors and there's
a balcony a shared balcony that connects
in both our rooms out there is a washing
machine and also the things that you
hang your clothes on like you have to
pull a string and it lowers and then
like you hang your clothes on each
individual like rack and then you like
pull it and it goes back up this big old
metal thing so pull it down I put all my
clothes on I lift it back up this is my
first time doing laundry in two weeks so
like I have a decent amount of stuff on
there I hang up my clothes and then he
asks me asks me if I would like to have
dinner like he's gonna make some black
bean noodles and he asked me if I wanted
to have some and I've been waiting for
years to try black bean noodles so and I
didn't know how to make them myself so I
was like yeah sure
so cool I'm hanging up my laundry he's
making a black bean noodles you
finishing them we sit down at the
kitchen table we eat the black bean
noodles everything's normal just have
regular conversation about like his job
whatever else we have conversation about
the finished dinner and then you know
this is normal he goes to his room he
says good night I said good night go in
my room I sit down I start watching a
movie now I'm sitting on my bed chilling
my headphones in I hear a knock and I
thought I was tripping at first then I
heard a knock again so I was a nod
I heard a knock so I pause the movie I
get up answered the door he's standing
there so yeah what's up he started he's
being weird again
like the first night when he told me I
was too loud he's being weird and I can
tell like something's bothering him and
he's just like you know scrap again so
with scratching um you have two more I
know you've been here for like two weeks
and I know you got two more weeks here
he's like I have a suggestion for you
again broken English so he's like I have
suggestions for like the rest of your
time here and I'm like okay so now I'm
thinking I'm like what did I do now like
Dan I was was I still being loud I wish
I'd been trying my best but I guess I've
still been like oh I did something wrong
and now he's being he's nervous to tell
me so I'm I'm waiting for him to tell me
what I did wrong so I can fix it and
he's just still not getting to the point
sighs I'm just like it like you know I
don't just like what's up like what's
wrong and he's just like little uh I
wanna hang out like I wanna hang out
with you and I'm hoping like we can eat
dinner every night and like we can go
explore the town so we can go shopping
and we can eat food and we could try
food together and I want to sleep with
you and done it at a time just isn't
night night and then I was like whoa
whoa whoa and once he said that my eyes
stopped like I stopped listening to
everything else like I don't even know
what he was saying but like I stopped
and I was saying there is no way there
is no way that I just heard what I think
I heard as a female and a younger female
and a female who's traveling on the
other side of the world I don't know I
just frozen like okay I was like his
English he's got broken English he
doesn't always use the right vocabulary
like I'm just trying to give him the
benefit of the doubt so badly because
I'm just like there's no way this is
happening like you know being in the
situation like I was saying where I was
kind of scared at that point I was just
like trying to make the situation in
without escalating the situation so
instead of getting him upset or anything
I was just kind of like I don't mind
like one day when I go to like
Myeongdong again like you can join with
me or something like
like I said I'm not trying to make him
angry I'm not about to be like everybody
else probably I would have blown up I
would've the distance distance in this
okay but you have to be smart about
these kind of situations because I'm in
his home I don't have any weapons I
don't know where he keeps the weapons I
told you about this like nervous thing
he's got I don't know if he's gonna like
go off on me just anything so I'm not
trying to set this man off so I was just
saying you know we can maybe go shopping
one day knowing good and well that I'm
not doing anything with this man ever
like no but I just need him to get out
of my room so I'm saying what I need to
say to get him out of my face so I was
just kind of like you know we can go
shopping one day and then he was like no
but I wanna like no but I wanna sleep
with you and so in that moment I was
like okay this is real
we got like Kayla this is real it's time
to act like he really said that you
weren't trippin you didn't miss hear him
it wasn't his broken English he really
he said what he said I was like okay so
I was just like oh no no like I have a
boyfriend and he wouldn't be comfortable
with that I can't no no thank you you
know all this stuff so after I rejected
him he just I'm sorry you know I'm just
a man you know how men are
I'm just a man you know I I have a wife
and you know she lives so far and I
don't see them very often all this like
he's talking and giving me all these
excuses and I'm grossed out like I just
feel so oh just thinking about it like I
it was so disgusting like it's so
disturbing I just feel so violated and
I'm just saying I've been in the house
of this man and like in his house just
thinking about all the things that could
have happened to me in that moment in
that time that I've been there and I'm
just like I'm terrified right now
freaking out inside and he's still
talking
you know blaming it on him being a man
and I'm just like oh my god please leave
me alone cuz get out of my room I'm
scared and so he's just talking you know
I'm just a man and you very you're very
pretty and just I thought you know all
these things I'm just like you're done
he's just like forget it forget I ever
said it we could just and I'm like yeah
yep mm-hmm and so he's just saying okay
it's okay and I'll say it okay and so he
say and he reached out to shake my hand
like do we have a deal like it never
happened type thing and I'm just saying
because how he reached out his hand I
the last thing I want to do is touch him
right now but like I said I'm scared I
don't want to set him off so I go in
shake his hand and when I shake his hand
he's just kind of like he shook it you
know everybody knows like the standard
like handshake is only gonna last a
couple seconds and then it's done like
not even a couple seconds it's just like
shake done but he held it and he all
different like a little too long and
then he finally like slowly let my hand
go as he let my hand go he just kind of
like slowly brung it up to himself and
like kind of like held it like I don't
know if it was kind of like a oh my god
like her touch like I'm chill um I
couldn't tell if it was that kind of
thing or if it was like um he just
regretted the whole situation and now
he's thinking to himself what did he
just say I don't know either way it
completely creeped me out holding my
hand for too long and then just like
holding it and slowly turning and
walking away then he walks arisen at
this point
lock the door he walked out I locked the
door I go to the back door I locked the
door I pulled the shades down and I sit
down and it's like it's like 9 o'clock
at this point so in America it's like
5:00 a.m. so it was like 14 hours ahead
I don't know it's all I know is it's
early in the morning and nobody's gonna
be woke on my side yet I'm freaking out
I'm just like oh my god what just
happened I sit down on my bed and I'm
trying not to freak out because like I
said I don't want him to freak out he
already was panicking at the thought of
like me giving him anything less than 5
stars on Airbnb god knows what he'll do
if he knows that I'm freaking out
because he just did something
inappropriate and he can get in like
actual trouble for this like I did not
want him to know at all so I just kept
quiet I don't my bed I put on my
headphones and I start texting my sister
I'm like you know I need you to wake up
so I messengering her on my computer I
mess up I'm like wake up please wake up
oh my god Dale please wake up
need you emergency like wake up we go
Center like 15 texts and then I feel
like two minutes I was just saying she's
not gonna wake up it's it's early over
there so so I facetimed her
i facetimed her and then she woke up and
she answered the phone and she was like
what are you doing like what are you
doing and immediately when I saw her and
she talked to me I just busted out
crying and I don't think holding my
mouth and I was from and I started
typing to her because I don't want to
talk cuz he can hear me in his room so I
start typing her I'm like oh my god I
tell her what happened like he just told
me he's just tried to sleep with me and
like I'm just telling her what happened
- she was like oh my god so she has to
call my mom on a separate phone on her
boyfriend's phone she calls my mom and
she's telling my mom what's happening
that I'm telling her through this I'm
texting her and she's talking to my mom
on the phone and so they're just like
kaeleen do you get out of that room you
need to pack your stuff you need to go
I'm like guys I literally just did my
laundry an hour ago every all my stuff
not only is it wet but it's scattered
all over the place and it's hanging up
on this thing like I can't get my stuff
I just have to go like I just had to go
oh I took my little backpack and I put
like a couple clean pair of underwear
that I had leggings maybe in a hoodie
that were sitting out on my bed grab
like little things that I needed
toiletries that I had on the counter and
I just had to go and I had to go
silently of course I got a little
backpack of stuff I held my laptop in my
hand cuz I wasn't getting off FaceTime
and I just left and so I went to the
staircase of the apartment complex and I
just sat there with them and I was like
I don't know what to do I don't know
where to go it's not like I have any
contacts there it's not like I know
people in Korea he's the only person
I've talked to accept the the employee
who works at the gym downstairs like I
said I'd been going to the gym almost
every day so I would see him everyday
and say hi and I've had small
conversations with him in Korean so I
was like he's the only person I can go
to so I did guy said it was about 9
o'clock
gym closes at 10 o'clock and I went in
there and I saw him and immediately like
when I walked in like
oh hey and I was just saying hi and I
got my laptop and ice and I go to him
and I'm like can I sit down he said sure
so I sat down I'm talking to my sister
you know I'm not in a mindset where I
can just try to be having conversations
in Korean so I just went straight to
Google Translate and I was like I have a
situation basically I needed your help I
don't want to stay in that room upstairs
can you help me find somewhere to stay
for the night and he wrote on my
computer like I get off at ten o'clock
can you wait for me at the coffee shop
it's probably like 9:30 at that point
upstairs because Jim is in the basement
then on the on the first floor of the
lobby there's a coffee shop said can you
just wait for me up there I get I'll be
off in like a little bit I said okay
took my laptop stolen face on my sister
I went upstairs and I waited and at like
1006 he came in the coffee shop it comes
in the coffee shop he sits down with me
and he's like okay so like what's going
on so now I tell him what's going on
like I said in Google Translate I told
him what happened I told him everything
that happened and I could see like his
facial expressions as he was reading it
like not really understanding that first
and then I kind of click to him God got
like the translations a little off I
don't know but you see you could see in
his face like the concern and then he
was a he asked like he asks you for sex
and I was like well he didn't come
straight out and ask me for sex he just
said I want to see with you know I don't
know it's 2018 if you want to be in some
denial world where like he may be just
mean cuddling I don't know that's not
what I take it as maybe he did just me
cuddle in the bed with me because he's
lonely but the chances of that in his
mind what were the chances that that was
not gonna lead to sex in his mind like
either way both to me in his mind were
gonna be sex so I was like he didn't
come straight out and say sex but you
know who are we kidding yes he was gonna
help me find a place to stay so first
thing was first I needed some cash and
he knew I told him my debit card wasn't
working so he was nice enough to take
to the banker he took money out of his
account and I gave him my American cash
to treat in exchange then he helped me
find a hotel that was up the street now
mind you guys I have my book back on I
have a hoodie and I have one these
slippers like bedroom slippers that are
too big for my feet so like I'm trying
to walk in like they're too big it's
just and it's cold I don't know why was
that cold in Korea at that point but he
has long like this big old jacket and
like I just have one like my hoodie like
my light pink hoodie that I bought in
Korea and so I'm cold
I can't walk properly because my feet
it's just irritating so we walk a couple
blocks up the street to the hotel and
apparently they were all booked no more
rooms so we had to think of something
else so at that point he was a you want
me to just order a cab and I was like no
no it's fine
you think like you're obviously coat is
fine so he ordered he got a kind of
caught a cab back and then there is his
motel so we go inside and he's talking
to the clerk it gets me a room he also
had paid for the room I was just kind of
like I'm like okay so how much was it
how much do I owe you and he was like
don't even worry about it all this stuff
and I think no no and you just like know
like really don't worry about it like
you let me know if you need anything
give me its numbers like you let me know
if you need anything all this stuff he
was so nice and I was just say thank you
so much I guess he could see in my face
that like I was on very on the verge of
tears the whole night and I guess he
just felt really bad for me I got my
room key I went upstairs to my room and
that's when I called my mom and them
back and I was letting them know what
happened like where I was that I was
safe all that stuff fast forward I slept
for maybe like 3-4 hours maybe motel
wasn't the best in and the guy who
helped me let's just call him Jim guy he
knew it was like not the greatest motel
but you know and I had to take what I
can get so I was very uncomfortable in
the motel room I was like scared at this
one I'm uncomfortable like I'm scared
I'm alone I feel vulnerable I'm just
kind of laying on top of the covers in
the bed legs to myself don't want to
touch anything call my family again and
we're talking about what I need to do I
need to figure out how to get my stuff
out of his room
and I don't know what I'm gonna do
because I don't want to go back up there
I don't trust I'm scared I was terrified
I don't want to go back up there and see
him just strike I can just at this point
I'm just I'm getting really stressed on
this trip it's almost like 11 ish so
it's almost time for me to check out the
room basically I know at this point that
I don't have anywhere to go so I need to
pay for another room in this hotel and
then I'll figure out what to do like I
need to go pay for another room go get
some food and then I'm gonna figure out
what I'm gonna do how I'm gonna get home
I need to like call err trying to get a
flight home all that stuff so that's
what I do I go downstairs and first of
all this exchange of information like
this conversation with these people at
the front desk it was how because they
weren't understanding what I was trying
to say
I need another night they kept trying to
like get me to check out and I'm like no
I don't have anywhere to go I need
another room and they weren't
understanding and it was just um I was
trying to like Google Translate but the
Wi-Fi was so bad in the motel that like
it just wasn't loading and even when it
did load she wasn't understanding what
the translator was saying and I was just
oh my god so finally she understood what
I was saying she gave me the key to the
other room I went to the new room they
gave me they couldn't even let me just
stay in the same room they had to give
me a new room for whatever reason so I I
just moved my stuff to the next room and
then I went to go get food I came back
got a whole pizza that will ask me like
I bought a whole box of pizza so it
would last me and I wouldn't have to
keep leaving the room at this point I'm
just irritated with everything I'm
frustrated nothing seems to be going
right right on this trip
and I was in the room I couldn't the
electricity wasn't working and I
couldn't figure out why the electricity
wasn't working and I didn't want to have
to go downstairs and try to explain to
them my issue because they weren't even
understanding me trying to get another
room I would say how they gonna
understand me trying to talk about
electricity and I could not for like
half an hour figure out why the
electricity wasn't working at this point
like my computer had been dying my phone
is probably dying I can't charge all my
stuff and I was just like irritated and
finally a clip to me that's not how we
do it where I'm from but in this motel
at least you get the ring key and
there's a little keychain there's
something on it that's tingling for me
you actually have to put it slide it
into a slot that's by the front door
you do that the electricity comes on and
I forgot because when I got there the
first night the guy from downstairs had
to come up and like did it for me and so
I didn't remember to do it the second
time and so finally I remembered that
that's what I had to do so I put it in
there and then like I was charging on my
stuff oh I was becoming like an
emotional wreck at that point not
emotional wreck but I was just very very
stressed at that point yeah so me and my
mom had started looking for rooms and
stuff because now I need a new place to
stay a new Airbnb to stay until I can
figure out what to do with my stuff I
need to get my stuff out of the room so
I'm sitting there and I'm just saying
we're literally trying to go over all
the ways I could possibly get my stuff
out of the room and I don't know just
nothing was making sense to me like I
was just saying I none of these sound
like good ideas none of them telling
anything I want to do so I was like you
know I'm just gonna call Airbnb the
whole time I was very reluctant to call
Airbnb because I knew that they were
going to contact him and I didn't want
him to know that I had contacted them
until I had all my stuff until I was
completely laid out of that situation so
at this point I was sitting on the bed
and I was like I don't know what else to
do
I don't I went on the website and I
reported it like report this host and so
maybe like 20 minutes later I wasn't
expecting them to reach out to me this
quickly and it was great because I was
glad they did but like 20 minutes later
I got a call I answered it and this guy
is just kind of like you know what seems
to be the problem and then I busted out
crying again I was like my host asked me
to sleep with him
and that's when I busted out crying and
then here's that or like you can't hear
like the his voice just like completely
run from like oh this is like a real
situation so you say I'm so sorry that
happened you know like let me let me put
you in like contact with let me transfer
you to to something something team like
I guess there's a team that handles like
the real situations so you transfer me
to some other lady and she's talking to
me about the incident you know
did he touch you what happened Baba and
I told her what happening and then I
said don't say anything to him yet cuz
my stuff is in his room and I don't want
him to do anything to my stuff and like
I still got to go up there and get it
and I don't need him being upset with me
or any you know she said okay you're
right she's like but I need you to get
your stuff out of there girl like you
gotta go get that stuff under she was
telling me that I need to go to the
police that's what she recommended I
need to go to Korean police and have
them escort me up there and I was like I
don't know it just it just didn't seem
to me like it was the best idea for me
to go to the police it was just gonna be
just like so much for me I don't speak
Korean like that not like that I don't
know the Korean law like it was just all
it just seemed all bad to me so I'm
telling her I was like okay I'll figure
it out and I'll call you back and I'll
let you know when I get the stuff under
there after I talked to her it was her
name let's just say it was Alice after I
talked to Alice from Airbnb I got a call
from somebody else it's a guy from
Airbnb he's telling me you know I heard
what happened
we're gonna take care of the situation
for you we're gonna reimburse you for
you stay at the motel and we're gonna
find you another place to stay for the
remainder of your time then turned so
that's like around the same cause they
were like they were gonna take the money
from my other stay and use it to pay for
the new plates so I'm just the old thing
god that's like one less thing that I
have to worry about like I know I don't
have to sit around and look for places
like I can worry about other things
they're gonna find a place for me and he
told me he would call me in the morning
and give me the address of the place and
like it was just already gonna be taken
care of in like I was just gonna be able
to wake up and move into the new spot I
was in perfectly you guys are great
thanks so much after I hung up hung up
the phone with him I text the guy from
the gym and I was like are you working
well I use that are you okay first of
all that was the first thing he said
like are you okay and I was like I'm
fine like you know I really just wanted
to give him the money back because now
that I pay for the second room I knew
how much the room cost and I wanted to
pay him his $40 and he was like yes I am
working but I'll be off at this time do
you want to meet me at the coffee shop I
was just gonna drop the money off and
like go but he said to meet him at the
coffee shop so that's what I did I meant
the coffee shop he got off work he came
in there and so he basically just wanted
to know the update on the situation and
I was telling him everything they think
I should go to the police and have them
escort me up there and he basically told
me that he also didn't think it was the
best idea for me to get the police
involved
just for a number of reasons he was also
telling me how he can't really be too
too involved like he would go up there
with me but he can't because he works
there and if it becomes like a big
situation he could lose his job I
understand and I respect that and I'm
like yeah yeah yeah you're right out so
I'm scared and I'm like about to cry
again cuz I'm like I have to go up there
I have to go I have to be the one at the
end of all of this after all this I
still have to go up day and get myself
like I'm scared I'm scared I'm sitting
in a coffee shop with him and oh my god
while we were sitting in a coffee shop
we were facing the window and he was
like oh and then you pointed and I was
like what and I looked and it was my
host and he was coming from I don't know
maybe like the grocery story he's about
to go into the building upstairs and
like I know my god I hate I forgot about
this I hate it so quickly behind the
pillar in the cafe like oh my god I was
terrified and just seeing him I was just
so reminded of how afraid I was to go up
there he said that he would go with me
but he could only go so far into the
building and then he would wait for me
like downstairs or something
well I'll go up we'll get my stuff and
so basically after talking to my mom and
my stepdad we decided that the best
thing for me to do is to get a trash bag
to run upstairs
keep them on FaceTime run into the room
lock the doors throw all my stuff in the
bag and then get out and so that's what
I had to do but I was scared because my
stuff was on the balcony or nothing and
I knew that I was gonna take a long time
for me to pull this thing down get all
the clothes off individually pack it up
and especially being on the balcony were
like he has access to me at least if I'm
in the room like I can lock both doors
but if I'm on the balcony he can come
out from his
and I was just so terrified but I had to
do it he went with me Jim guy went with
me to a little convenience store we got
a trash bag we went up there well I went
up there he waited downstairs I went up
through the trash bag computer in my
hand I quietly walked in the room I said
my computer down and then I just started
throwing stuff I just start throwing
everything in the bag
everything packing my big suitcase up
throwing everything else and I went out
on the balcony I slowly pulled it down
and I was just praying like just hoping
like please do not come out here just
picking up all my stuff putting in the
bag my family is still in facetime like
my mom was in the background crying I
didn't know at the time she told me
later and she didn't want me to like
freak out but she was in the background
crying why my stepfather was like
talking to me like trying to keep me
calm while I was packing up the stuff
and then like finally like I packed
everything up I took the key to his room
sat on the desk and I quietly walked out
the room once I don't close the door oh
boy all that luggage I had I was moving
boy I was gone first thing I did was
like run down the stuff I ran down like
three flights or something cuz I just
didn't know I didn't want to wait for
the elevator on the ninth floor because
I didn't want him to like I don't know I
was just so scared and paranoia it's so
bad I just ran down a couple of flights
then I took the elevator down there so I
got down there and the gym guy was still
there
I'm so sorry like I know it took a while
and like he was waiting for me he helped
me take on myself like I had like
suitcases at this point I have all my
stuff and I have suitcases and now I had
this big old trash bag full of stuff
because I couldn't properly you know
like when you go on a long trip you have
to pack it a certain way that everything
fits and like I just when everything is
jumbled it's not gonna fit so I have way
too much stuff now it's heavy so he was
nice enough to help me walk me back to
the motel with all my stuff like helping
me carry I got there and I said like
thank you again to him I paid him back
his $40 that he used to pay for my room
for the first night I thank you again
like so much for the last time like
thank you you know it was kind of and so
now I'm at the point where I'm like
thank God like this is over it's over
I was just oh my god it's over so I
called the people from Airbnb and they
tell them I got my stuff it's cool you
can do whatever it is you got to do
because I'm safe I'm out of the room all
my stuff's out the room do you thing
like I don't care what you do do you
think I mean there's just like okay cool
like well handling I was a very cool
that was the situation with my host
that's what happened to me there's a lot
more to the story my trip in Korea that
is but for this video which is just like
what happened with my host that's really
kind of like it you know that's that's
the teeth we're only two weeks into my
six-week trip