what's up guys are y'all diggin the
curls I got someone to be after this I
did curls I don't know how I feel about
it
I look like teenager so this video is
very long overdue it took me a while to
get to a point where I was ready to talk
about it but of course this is a travel
page so I feel like I need to talk about
my experiences in trouble right I'm
gonna redo this video I'm gonna try to
keep it as brief as I possibly can but
it is a long story and there are a lot
of details and there was a lot that went
down so it is gonna be a longer video
but I promise I'm gonna try to keep it
as like straight to the point as I can
so so if you've been following my
channel for a while you know that back
in April I went to Korea I went to Korea
for five to six weeks and before I got
there I was super super super excited
I'd always wanted to go to Korea I was
saving up for it I was just really
excited for his trip during the time I
was in Korea a lot happens not only just
in Korea but just in my life in general
at that point and then I got me to a
point where I felt really broken down
and I wasn't posting on social media
actually I had to take a social media
break and I ended up canceling the rest
of my plans for solo trips for the rest
of the year
things I just got them really really
really bad and now that I'm at a point
now where I'm feeling better you know
emotionally physically spiritually
everything I'm finally ready to tell you
guys what happened because only a few
people know the story there are two
parts first I'm going to talk about the
trip in general everything that went
wrong and then I'm gonna focus in on one
specific issue that occurred when I was
in Korea and that's gonna be a whole
separate video like with the details
about that like situation the first
issue I encountered very first issue I
encounter I miss my flight to Korea and
I was very embarrassed when it when I
realized it happened I wasn't gonna tell
anybody but for the sake of the story
just to let you guys know the first
thing that went wrong I missed my flight
to Korea so I had to pay extra $250 when
I got there to get another flight that
day to Korea so I just got to take that
I take that out so I get there and I
meet my host he meets me at the bus stop
when I get off the bus and you know he
shows he walks me to the apartment we go
upstairs shows me to my room now the way
the apartment is set up you walk in
there's bathroom medially on your right
there's my room his room the kitchen
that's it it's a small apartment he
lives there by himself he was telling me
he has a wife and two kids they live in
California they're going to school over
there he sends some money you know all
this stuff cool whatever I had the idea
to get a pocket Wi-Fi a pocket Wi-Fi is
basically a hot spot it's a hot spot so
I went online and I found this website
and I ordered one for the full month of
my stay in Korea so cool put it in
ordered the hot spot everything was good
you use my debit card and cool once I
ordered it they told me I could pick it
up the next day but their little stands
are only set up in airports so I had to
go to the airport to pick it up I can go
to Incheon or I could go to Gimpo
Airport I decided to go to Gimpo because
it was a little closer to where I was
staying it was still like an hour by the
metro to get there but it was the closer
one so I chose Gimpo Airport so only
ones day I get up I'm like okay I'm
gonna go pick up my pocket Wi-Fi then
I'm gonna do this distances and this for
the rest of the day I get there and they
told me I couldn't get the pocket Wi-Fi
what and they told me I couldn't have it
because I didn't have my passport with
me and I was really serious like I knew
all my passports before I know it by
heart
I know it but she was telling me I
couldn't get it because I didn't have
the actual physical passport with me so
I was like fine I'll take another I'll
take the El so I was just like okay fine
I'll come back tomorrow it's no big deal
that's for two the next day I go back
take another hour ride Metro up there to
Gimpo Airport I get there and I come see
the lady and she tells me that I can't
get the Wi-Fi pocket Wi-Fi because I
don't have a credit card for her to put
on file and I'm confused at this point
because I'm like I was here yesterday
and you guys just told me anything
Passport why didn't you also tell me at
that point that I needed a credit card
second of all why do I need a credit
card when I already paid for the Wi-Fi
like I already paid for the service at
this point I'm imitating cuz I've
already come up here twice and you guys
didn't tell me on your website that I
needed a credit card to have them file
or that I needed to have my passport
with me so I'm just like okay it's fine
like I'll just cancel so I sent the
email to the people I told them what
happened I was like you know bah bah bah
bah you guys said I need credit card
whatever
at this point I would just like my money
back like the next day the guy emails me
back and he's like you know we actually
stay online that you do need a credit
card buh buh buh buh bah like have a
nice day something like that but nowhere
did he address the fact that I asked for
a refund so at this point in my mind I'm
thinking that I just get scammed I'm
like I would say uh this website that I
put my debit card and throw into I'm
just not sure there's I start to panic
I'm worrying a little bit so I go online
and check my my bank card statement like
all the transactions and I see a
transaction on there for like 30 bucks
or something and I cannot remember what
it was from and I'm like I didn't do
that so without really thinking it
through I called my bank and I told them
I need them to cut off my debit card now
this is what I need you guys to not
judge me I'm telling you I was panicking
and I didn't think it through
you know I later realized that that
wasn't me who spent that it was that
forever21 I thought I like body and cash
I don't know I just didn't think I use
my debit card at forever 21
once you cancel a credit card you can't
just like magically cut it back on they
have to send you a whole new debit card
and the issue is I wasn't at home at my
house to get the debit card so at this
point I don't have access to my online
like my bank account I don't have access
to it all I have now is the cash that I
came to Korea with but I didn't think it
was gonna be that big of an issue
because we weren't there yet we're not
there yet no story okay so let's just
say that's three things so far I missed
my flight to the whole pocket Wi-Fi
incident was really irritating me that
blew me and three cut off my debit card
so I'm like huh all right one of the
things I noticed when I first got to
Korea and started exploring or two
things I noticed one everything there
was a lot more expensive than I thought
it would be I had heard by watching
other travel vlogs and channels that
shopping and like stuff in Korea's cheap
people I went there with the impression
that things were gonna be cheaper there
which is not true but it's also group
activity it just seems like group
oriented so when people go to do things
they don't really do them by themselves
so like when you go out to eat at a
restaurant the prices are set up in a
way that you're expected to split the
cost with your friends so a lot of
places that you'll go
eat you might have to pay like $18 or so
for like chicken in a side because
you're expected to come there with like
three friends and you all split the cost
so like $6 each and you split the food I
can't eat okay I eat a lot so I'm eating
that whole $18 meal by myself plus
having to pay the $18 so I was like okay
well this trip is gonna be a little bit
more expensive than I thought it was
gonna be it was not that big of a deal
to me I was like I'm just gonna have to
reconsider some of the things I had
planned and I might have to eat in my
Airbnb you know cook at home a lot more
than I thought I would have to that was
one thing I noticed it's a lot more
expensive than I thought
and to like I was saying everything's
like group activity oriented there
weren't as many things to do as a single
solo traveler as I thought there would
be karaoke rooms in like Lotte world and
like I said just the restaurant
experiences a Korean barbecue just a lot
of things seem like you needed Thai
friends to do that those are the two
things I noticed so as I was getting
into the trip I was feeling lonely like
I was having a good time and I was
enjoying what I was doing but I was
lonely I was missing my family and my
friends and it didn't help that I was
kind of going through like my
relationship at the time was kind of
rocky it was on the rocks that was that
little gray cloud was looming over my
head the whole time I was in Korea also
because that happened before I even left
so you know those emotions and those
feelings I was also dealing with at the
same time I don't know how many of
issues I just listed but that's what's
going on so far and we're not even like
a week into the trip I think it was like
the fourth night in the Airbnb that I
was staying in my biological clock was
off okay so it's daytime in America it's
nighttime in Korea so my body's just off
so every night I would end up cooking
dinner late so my host actually would go
to bed early he would go to bed around
nine o'clock and he would always wake up
around 6:00 a.m. on like the fourth
night I was cooking in the kitchen and
he actually had to come out and he told
me like he apologized to me he was
telling me I was being too loud in the
kitchen now I apologize and I felt
really bad I had made some noodles on
the stove and it's a gas stove so when
you know you cut it on if you have a gas
stove
no you put it on and they don't like
that it's not that quiet I mean it's not
that loud but for us to have been in the
small apartment that we were in and for
him to only have a sliding door a glass
sliding door that to separate his room
from the kitchen I can understand why
you know it would be a little noisy like
me trying to cook in the kitchen at the
time he has to come out and he was
apologizing he was like I'm sorry you
know I just can't sleep it's a little
bit noisy and I was like okay I'm sorry
you know that's my fault
I'm so sorry bah bah bah bah so you know
I just got my stuff together and I went
in the room and you know I didn't think
it was that big of deal
I felt really bad but I didn't think it
was a huge thing like I said I'm so
sorry you know all this stuff and so I
went in the room and then um I was ready
to go to bed out of that point I like
cut the lights I was like I'll just shut
up completely like I'll just go to bed I
won't make any more noise I'll just men
go to sleep three minutes later I hear a
knock at the door and I'm like oh so I
get up answered the door and he's
standing there and he starts like
apologizing and he's just like rambling
and he thinks it's way more of an issue
than it really is and he was just like
I'm so sorry like I've never had to say
this to a guest before you know stuff
like that he's I'm reading the situation
and obviously his personality type is
he's panicking like he thinks it's so
like I said it's not that big of a deal
but like he was like panicking like oh
my god I've never had to do this before
like everybody always gives me good
rating ba ba ba ba ba so I'm like okay
obviously he thinks I'm gonna give him a
bad rating on Airbnb and it's not even
that serious like he's just rambling ba
ba ba ba
and I'm just sitting there like oh my
god okay I just want to go to sleep at
this point but he's still going and like
he's doing this nervous thing where he's
scratching his head and I can see that
his hair is like thinner in the area so
obviously it's like a nervous hi blade I
just and I just noticed that like he's
like scratching his head while he's
talking he was like nervous and he's
giving me these vibes like I hate to say
but like the weird kid in school who
everybody's worried like if something's
gonna happen you know the jokes are like
the person shooting up the school like
I'm like it might be just got
like that's him he just got he's
freaking out like I don't know what's
gonna happen type thing also I think
it's important to note that he's a
professor out of college and he leaves
he would leave every day for like an
hour to an hour and a half but he would
just leave for a little bit and then he
will come back after work and then just
be there all day just all day sitting in
his room by himself and he was telling
me like he reads books a lot he writes
his own text books and stuff like that
so he's really just like a hermit kind
of like he just sits in his room he
doesn't interact with people outside of
his Airbnb cus I suppose when they come
yes back to the him rambling he was
rambling just apologizing and he was
just like you know everybody always give
me four stars yada yada yada I mean five
stars yada yada yada
and then like word bomb and I guess he's
just saying you're just so pretty and
the lava and the lava that line he's
rambling and while he was talking I
caught that and I was just saying hmm
What did he say
I thought I was tripping at first like I
was like that has nothing to do with the
situation they just threw me off
completely it completely I cannot I'm
talking too quickly it threw me for a
whole loop and I was like nah I'm
tripping like I don't know I don't know
but at that point I just wanted to get
back in the bed so I was like it's okay
like I'm sorry I'm sorry I woke you up
that's my fault or have been waking you
up every night I don't know I'm sorry
you're sorry we're sorry let's move on
like it's fine and I really had to like
get him to calm down cuz he was gonna be
at my door forever I was like it's fine
I'm sorry you're sorry it's okay music
okay I was like okay okay so he went to
the bathroom then he went back to his
room good night good night cool I get
into bed I'm like what the heck but
before I go to bed I email my mom and
you know I just I a mail her like every
day and I tell her you know what I'm
doing that I'm safe just that kind of
stuff so I remember emailing her and
telling her and I was like I'm pretty
sure like in explaining the event to her
that pretty sure he called me pretty
it was weird and then I went on with it
because I didn't seem like a big deal to
me at the point at that point the next
day I was in the kitchen cooking he came
back from work there must have been like
12 o'clock he came
back when in his room dropped his work
stuff off came out and started having a
conversation with me and we're just
talking you know just stuff in journal
and then he brings up last night and
then he apologizes again you know it's a
more relaxed environment at this point
I'm just so you know it's fine and we
start talking about like my by body's
time being off and you know like how
guess in the past I've been too noisy
and neighbors have complained so he's
got to let them know you know like he's
got to control the noise cuz it's
obviously a very sound sensitive room oh
we just started having a normal
conversation and then he'd mentioned
something about the gym and I had been
going to the gym almost every day at
that point maybe it's like the fifth
sixth day I'm there and he mentioned
okay right right right
he said something about my body he said
you have a body like Miss Universe and I
never I've never heard in all my years
I've never had anybody telling me I look
like Miss Universe only was I like hmm
but then I was a hmm because why are you
commenting on my body like and then it
hit me in that moment that what I heard
last night was real like he did call me
pretty last night and I'm like this is
weird because and I know I'm gonna get
some crap for it in the comments but I
just didn't like it didn't it doesn't
register to me that I don't ever assume
that when I go places that people are
attracted to me like I it just never
crossed my mind that I would have this
issue with this man he's an older Korean
man he's got to be in his like 50s or
60s and it just threw me off and I was
just like he's attracted to me like you
already hear things about Koreans like
in lighter skin or Asians in general
Asian culture it's like me lighter skin
is just the whole thing threw me off and
I was just like okay this is maybe weird
at this point it's like maybe something
I should look out for so I'm like after
that conversation ended I was telling
myself I maybe just need to avoid him in
general like I'm just gonna stick to
this trip and I'm gonna try to avoid
interacting with him as much as I
possibly can just because it's just
getting awkward at this point like he
stays in his room all day I feel like I
can't like do simple things like play
music or like just move around the house
I just feel like I always got to be
super quiet and now like when we talk
he's just like awkward and okay so
that's what I decided to just just kind
of try to avoid them I think it's like a
weekend to the trip I was so lonely that
I went on Lonely Planet and they have
this forum where you can go meet people
who are travelling similar in similar
places as you and you can like meet up
with them so I made a post I met this
girl from Norway she was also in Korea
at the time so long story short we
message each other we decided to meet up
in Seoul and we were gonna spend the
time that she was there and so together
before she left she was only there for
like a week before she was going
somewhere else one day I started getting
dressed and I was gonna head out the
room to go meet her
Amil dong and my hosts came in again
every day around the same time he came
in and he saw me getting ready to go and
he starts having a small talk and he's
like oh where you're headed and I'm like
I'm gonna be my friend and million dong
and he's like oh wow like can I go he's
like super excited for whatever reason
just kind of like him writing himself on
the trip like I knew I have this gift
from my niece that I need to take back
in exchange like and it's right over
there can I go with you but I'm you know
like no you can't go late it was just
awkward but I was like you gotta go drop
off to give like it's whatever I was
like I guess okay so I messaged a girl
in I'm waiting my host wants to come so
like push the time back like 20 minutes
you know it was so weird it was so weird
to me out and I haven't even met this
girl so me trying to explain that
situation to her was just like very
awkward I was like um yeah cuz like I
said like we're I think she was 26
like we're younger okay too much detail
whatever so he ended up coming with me
we got on the train and we're on the
train that trains very crowded created
and sold trains very crowded and we were
having a conversation and he started
talking to me he was talking to me about
his family California hitting him
teaching again and then he asked me it's
important
he asked me no he said you are the first
and he just kind of paused and he's
stopping he's like trying to think of
the words because his English is choppy
like he speaks he speaks English but
it's broken English he speaks it well
enough that I can understand or like I
would speak Korean and we would have a
conversation like his broken English my
broken Korean like we could communicate
but he doesn't always know what he's
saying
so he was trying to find the words and I
would say the first black person you met
and he's like yeah yeah yeah and then
you stopped me saying no no and then
he's like I recognized and I was
recognized like I wasn't understanding
and so he was like like I look and
you're very pretty but like I realized
he was trying to say I'm the first black
girl who's ever been attracted to like
he's seen a bunch but he's never been
attracted to before and I was saying oh
and at that point it became awkward for
me because I was think this is again
it's weird it's inappropriate and I'm
like the conversation say every time he
makes a comment like they're getting
more and more inappropriate and I'm also
just like because we're on the train in
public and I'm like if anybody else
around me suits English they know how
weird this conversation is likewise his
old man older me and sorry well as his
older men having this conversation with
me right now and I'm very visibly like
clearly late I don't know I just like
why are we having this conversation like
why are you doing this right now I just
came to visit oh really don't have these
conversations with me I was just saying
oh okay he asks me after that he was
like do you and like pointing around our
all the Asian people like do you I'm in
Korean people say oh putting around all
the Korean people you think do you
recognize these people
and I would say am i attracted to Asian
people I was like yes I find Korean boys
to be cute like I don't discriminate and
then after that I change the topic
because like I said it's weird it's
inappropriate so I meet up with a girl
from Norway he's still with me he's
following me and leader with a girl from
Norway and then we decided we wanted to
go do something
over him youngdong and he was like well
the place he needed to go was over there
and so I got got kind of awkward because
they it was clear we didn't want to go
with him over to this department store
that he wanted to go to say he said okay
you know it's fine like you guys go
ahead and I'll just see you back at the
house like I'm just gonna go head her
back after this and I was just like okay
like I wasn't gonna fight him about it
or anything I wasn't gonna be like oh no
no it's finally just music like no go go
home bye like okay cool
so that's what he did and so like the
first conversation me and the girl had
formed Norway the first conversation we
have is she was like what's that about
like I thought he was coming with us I
was like girl I don't know he's strange
and I started telling her all the things
that had been happening because I met
him like he's a hermit doesn't come out
of his room all he does is sit in there
silently all day how his wife and his
kids are like somewhere else and then I
started telling her about like the three
incidents since in the comments that
he's been making that she's like yeah
it's weird and choose that you need to
like nip that in the bud I was it you're
right and so I started thinking like
okay then I probably should be moving
out of that room soon I was actually
just move out she'd just find another
air B&amp;B and just move out I was fine um
sure yeah
so I hung out with that girl for like
five more days until she had to go to
Nepal she went to Nepal and so after
that I was back to being by myself so
this is where the story is about to get
trapped in half I'm just gonna say that
I did two weeks into the trip I did end
up having an incident with the host so
if you want to hear the details about
that story you're gonna have to go to
the other video that's cuz it's just
gonna be too long so yeah yeah so I'm
just gonna put that on the list as one
of the things that we're wrong I'm gonna
go on talk about the other things