BAM so after the situation when my host
kind of finally like ended I let Airbnb
know that I had all my stuff out of the
room and at that point I really just
needed to worry about getting a flight
home they were gonna find me a room and
I need to worry about getting a flight
home so that's where I was I was still
in the motel for the second night and
then in the morning I was supposed to be
moving to my new room I just went to
sleep and I was like in the morning like
I didn't even feel like repacking my bag
the proper way just anything I just
didn't feel like doing it so that's what
I did I went to sleep my stuff scattered
everywhere in the motel room I went to
sleep woke up in the morning and I woke
up a little later than I probably should
have checkout time was 11:00 maybe I had
gotten up at like like 9:30 I don't know
but I woke up and I hadn't gotten any
call from Airbnb the guy who was
supposed to find me a room I had no
calls no messages nothing I started
talking to my mother I'm like this guy
didn't find me a room he didn't do
anything like like now I have nowhere to
go he didn't come through so now we're
back on the internet trying to find me
places to go and now I'm panicking
because like it's almost time for me to
check out I have nowhere to go
now I have all this luggage but I have
all this luggage basically I wasn't able
to find a place to go before it was time
for me to check out so I ended up having
to stop looking I had to pack up all my
stuff I ended up having to go back to
the coffee shop like taking all my stuff
it was hard enough with gym guy helping
me and now I'm by myself and I didn't
know where else to go I had to go walk
back a couple blocks to the coffee shop
and I sat in there with all my stuff and
I'm talking to my mom on FaceTime now
and I'm just like my mom found a room
that I could stay in it was very nice
room and it was only available for two
nights and I don't think that's fine
like I just need somewhere to go for
right now when I get to the room I'll
call Air China I'll book my flight home
I don't care how much it costs I really
just want to go home now and she's
trying to convince me to stay like don't
let this ruin you trip all this stuff
and I'm trying to tell her like mom I
know I know I know because she knows me
like she knows how much I love traveling
but I'm just saying my mom
really done I'm really over I just
really like to go home I don't care how
much it costs I just want to go home do
you like okay fine so she picks a room
for two nights and she's like okay it's
booked mind you guys I couldn't even pay
for the room because my debit card is
not working so I couldn't pay so my mom
and I'd to pay and I was gonna have to
pay her back I'm sitting the cafe with
all my stuff and the host
luckily responding very quickly after we
ordered the room the room won't be ready
until 3 o'clock because there was
someone in it she has to clean it first
so I'm like that's fine cuz like it's an
hour away anyway I was like okay I'll be
there like right at 3 o'clock late got
nowhere else to go so she's like okay
cool so I sit in the cafe for a little
bit longer then I get on the Metro know
me trying to get to that room I had
gotten lost the the Metro trip was hell
was on my luggage like some some parts
had I had to do transference because
like I said it was like an over an hour
away or so some places had transfers
some parts didn't have escalators some
dead even using the escalator was a
hassle some didn't have elevators it was
hard for me to get through the turnstile
it was just so bad then even after I got
off the metro I got lost and I couldn't
find the building and nobody knew what I
was talking about
it was either like I was asking people
for helping either they didn't know what
I was talking about or like they didn't
understand my Korean so like even when
they didn't understand my Korean they
didn't know what building like nobody
knew where this building was and I was
your friend so I kept walking back and
forth oh that way
Oates that way oh it's over here on the
lake oh this is what and I just was all
this luggage and like my feet were in
such pain I was in so much pain and I
just I was so miserable I ended up not
finding the room until about five
o'clock it was two extra hours that I
was out there lost walking around just
miserable I kept having to stop and sit
down
only benches because I was just in so
much pain arms hurt like and I'm a
trooper yarm and like I've done sports I
was in physical pain back hurting
everything carrying my feet hurt I was
just
never dealt with anything like that in
my entire life and I finally found the
room I was just like Haley you literally
just have to make it up to the room at
this point carried the bags got to the
room logged into the Wi-Fi I had like
missed calls and messages from my host I
guess she was worried cuz I told her I'd
be there three o'clock and it's five
o'clock at this point and I still hadn't
checked in or like let her know what was
going on
probably message early yes I got lost
but I'm here now like it's fine and I
was just sitting there and I was sitting
to myself I believe cried I can't
remember I just sat there crying because
I remember to this moment like sitting
there thinking this is the worst day of
my life and I just felt so much hate and
anger toward my host because I blamed
him for everything like from the
beginning even before that night with
the incident I was like he made me so
uncomfortable in my room that he was
just like ruining my trip to Korea in
the first place and I was just so angry
I was so angry the only thing that made
it better at this point like was
cheering me up was that this room was so
nice it was just loft and I'll insert
the clip here it's like this nice Korean
lost obviously very expensive I had to
park in the back like a big old window
with the view of a park there was lots a
world right there I was like oh my god
I'm gonna get to go to Lotte world and
just the view is beautiful there was
like a little park with a with a trail
outside around the lake and I thought
I'm gonna go running like it was very
nice and I was happy I was like the only
thing cheer me up at that point at this
point I still need to figure out how to
get home so I called air China but I
have to wait I have to wait until
nighttime because the time difference
between Korea and I guess China or
wherever their office is located when I
was calling during the day it wasn't
open I had to wait till like 12:00 a.m.
before I could call and they would be
open so I did whatever I did that day 12
a.m. comes I get on the phone I call it
air China I'm on hold for like 20
minutes and I'm not gonna for nothing
I'm trying to go home I'm not hanging up
twenty minutes go by I'm on hold and
finally a guy answers in like okay I
need a flight home how much is it gonna
cost for me to get a flight home early
and he's just saying oh it's gonna be
and I'm like how expensive and you say
oh yeah it's gonna be pretty expensive
I'm like okay and I'm like okay well I
flew into Seoul and I'm supposed to
leave from Busan but now I need to leave
from Seoul how much is it gonna cost for
me to switch airports oh it's gonna be
expensive but I'm like men
leg-oh I'm like sir I need you to give
me numbers like I mean I'm trying to go
home he doesn't know what I've been
through I'm like I need you to tell me
something I need to know like I'm trying
to buy this ticket home I don't care if
it's expensive how much is it and so
he's like okay I'm gonna have to look it
up give me a number and I'll call you
back and I was like excuse me like what
I already sat on the hole for 20 minutes
and it's 12 a.m. not that it's not even
12 a.m. now because pie like 12:30 I
don't hold for so long then talking to
him it's like 12:30 and I'm like oh like
and I'm not understanding why he can't
just google it or like look it up in
their system and tell me like isn't that
how it works and I'm just saying call me
back and I'm like fine I give him my
phone number and I'm like okay and I
hang up and I'm waiting and I'm waiting
and I'm waiting and he doesn't call me
back and I knew he wasn't gonna coming
back cuz I go my god so I pick up the
phone is probably like 1:00 a.m. now and
I'm like I'm calling and I'm on hold
again
finally this lady answers and I was like
Hello psyche I was talking to this guy I
told him I just want to know how much it
cost to book a flight home early and
she's like ok kind of oh goodness
every time I talk about I get upset
because I was like she giving me
attitude like kind of like what's your
point because I was saying I was talking
to this guy and this is what we talked
about and she was just like okay and I
don't say okay so what he never called
me back he said he was gonna call me
back and he didn't so y'all better
figure it out like now I'm about to
start I'm just not just out of character
for me like y'all better giving me some
information I mean I said on hold for
this long
he says I'm coming back and he didn't
like figure it out basically and she
said okay give me a second I still don't
hold for like five minutes she comes
back to the phone and she's like he
still hasn't figured it out yet like
he's still looking basically she has no
information for me he's still looking
but it sounds like it's late over there
if you want I can just give him me your
email and I can have him email you the
information instead of calling I was
like you know what okay I gave her my
email I was like they're obviously not
gonna help me like they're trying to did
not come through for me at all at this
point I'm at cuz everybody heard him
come through for me I was like okay I'm
obviously gonna have to wait this trip
out because I can't go home they are not
cooperating with me I don't know what
else I'm supposed to do so that was just
that and like I knew they never did
contact me I was never able to get it
early play home I think I cried myself
to sleep that night cuz I was talking to
my mom and I was like now um like I have
to get a whole nother room because this
room is gonna be up like I've tomorrow's
my last day here in this room and then I
have to move out cuz she has another
guest coming now have to buy a whole
nother room because I thought I was
gonna be able to go home within those
two days that I was supposed to be
staying in that room and now I can't so
I practiced I cried myself to sleep
again that night because I was telling
my mom how stressed I was I wasn't
understanding why life was being this
horrible to me
but everything was going wrong I'm such
a good person I'm a nice personally what
is the problem my trip to career that I
saved up for for so long and I looked
forward to for so many years just all
bad if on the map
this is soul
this is what like my first one was this
is where my second room was like an hour
way by metro and that's where my third
one was well I wasn't trying to stay
with any other host because I wasn't
trusting people not gonna happen I
wasn't staying with anybody and the best
for microphone was way up there it was
like an hour and some change away again
once I checked out of that room I had to
go super super far with all my luggage
again to get to that room but when I got
to the room I absolutely loved it like I
love this stuff so so so much at that
point I just wasn't feeling in like I
wasn't feeling I wasn't gonna be able to
go home and just say after everything
had happened like on top of that I was
running out of cash at this point I only
had so much cash to say I don't want to
get robbed in a foreign country so I
only bring so much cash and I take more
out as I need it so now I've got a whole
nother big issue to deal with I don't
feel like telling anymore
I swear I'm never telling the story
again after this like I don't want to
have to talk about the story ever again
it's so long so horrible because I was
running out of cash the room I was
standing I could only buy certain
groceries um so every day I was eating
like the same thing like ramen spaghetti
and like eggs for breakfast in like some
bread so like for like five days that's
what I was eating and I was like really
getting tired of it okay okay when I
first got there well when I first got to
that room like that night I called my
bank I had to wait for a night time
because I had to wait for the offices
and the u.s. to be open I called my bank
and I told them what happened basically
I cut off my car I shouldn't have done
that because I was in Korea and I
couldn't get to my new debit card they
were like we already sent it to your
house and I thought I get that I need
you guys help me I need food like I need
money I need to get some cash out and
she was like I'll tell you what cuz I
had to talk to a manager cuz they're not
supposed to do this they had to cut my
debit card back on for me for an hour
and I was supposed to get to an ATM get
some money out sounds like okay I made a
wholeness of all these places
that had ATMs that I could think of that
I could go to within the hour and I was
going to get some money out so I was
like okay cool
so soon if I got off the phone with the
lady I hung up and I started my timer
for an hour and then I had to go out I
ran downstairs I went to the 7-eleven
across the street didn't work I ran down
to the grocery store down the street
there were like a bunch in that area
none of them work so my last resort was
to get on the train I had to go back to
Gimpo Airport which was a little closer
now I was closer to Gimpo Airport now
and that's where everybody online was
saying like yo you'll definitely find an
ATM here that worked for American credit
card it's a debit card whatever so I was
like that was my last resort so the
commute there already took up some time
then I had to run find the ATMs I went
there nothing was working so I called
the lady I called the lady back at the
bank I'm sitting in front of the ATM I'm
like it's not working do that I don't
know what's wrong it's on it's activated
I'm sitting right here looking it's
activating I'm like okay well I'm I'm
using it and the ATM is now working and
it's just I don't know I didn't know she
didn't know what the problem was but it
just wasn't working I was like okay I
don't know I guess just my debit card in
general just doesn't work in Korea I
mean not at the ATM's at least I could
buy things with the debit card but I
couldn't take money out of an ATM so I
said I'm so sorry I know you guys are
not supposed to do this in the first
place but I need you guys to help me and
she's very understanding I was just like
you please just leave it on for one more
hour for me and I will run back get on
the Metro I'm gonna ride back to my
house I'm gonna go to the grocery store
and I'm going to just use my debit card
to buy some groceries that's all I'm
really worried about at this point just
having money to buy food like I just
need to be able to eat and she's like no
problem sweetheart like you know that's
fine I'll leave it on for you for one
more hour I said okay thank you
hang up the phone again 60 minutes gotta
go get back on the metro I was oom there
the way it was set up my building was
here like two blocks down was a grocery
store
there was a metro stop right in front of
my body there's also a metro stop right
in front of the grocery
so I got up and I came up right at the
metro stop right in front of the grocery
store and when I came up the steps I
looked and the grocery store was closed
it was too late because remember I had
to I had to start this whole process
when it was already late it was probably
like 10 o'clock at that point because it
was daytime over there in the US and the
grocery store was closed and when I saw
that and she was so nice enough to keep
my debit card on I felt defeated again I
was just done I was done I was saying
now I can't eat she cut the debit card
on for me I was it was bad so I was oh
my god so I turned around and I like
kind of like molten rock the two blocks
home and then 7-eleven across the street
from my building so I go in the southern
lemon I pick up a couple things I don't
get too many things if I know like I
don't know if it's all gonna happen to
have a car take it up to the cashier put
this stuff down he brings me up I give
him the debit card and wouldn't you know
it didn't work so at that point I was
just like I'm sorry so I just take my
debit card and he was like trying to
figure out what's going on see don't
even worry about her like I'm sorry I
grabbed my debit card I put the food
back and then I just I just went home I
just went to the my room and I set up
there and that's when I got to the point
where I was like I give up I give up and
I was texting my boyfriend I was like I
gave up like I don't know what I did but
I give up I'm defeated like I give up
and I was just sitting there crying and
crying that's when I decided I don't
care I'm not doing anything for the rest
of the time here like I give up I
yeah I don't want to do anything for the
rest of my time here I literally would
just want to sit in this room and just
hope that the days go by quickly I got a
ten more days then I gotta go to Busan
and then I can just go home and I don't
want to do anything he was telling me
like don't do that you're okay you're
stronger than all this stuff I was ain't
no no don't care don't care I don't care
so couple days went by and I did just
that like I didn't leave the room like I
was just sit in my room and like I would
talk to him I would talk to my mom and
my sister probably just like watching
youtube videos or like movies if I was
over Korean at that point I was like I'm
never coming back to Korea I don't want
to learn Korean anymore cuz I didn't
want to spend any extra money on the
Metra I wasn't going out exploring and I
was just like so depressed I cancel one
of my rooms in Busan I was like I'm
literally gonna fly to get to Busan stay
in the room I supposed to say in and
then leave like I really wanted to just
be done with the church so I just sat in
that room for a few days and didn't
leave the room didn't go exploring
anymore so just nothing I just sat in
there
I wasn't posting on social media I don't
think it was just a lot of crying
involved a lot of depression involved it
was just really bad I had stopped doing
vlogs at that point I wasn't posting
anymore I still had a lot of footage
that I was supposed to be using but yeah
I wasn't gonna do anything with it yeah
couple days and I and my mom contacted
me and she they came up with an idea she
said I'm gonna send you some money
through Western Union I didn't know what
that was I'd never heard of it but yeah
basically she found out a way to wire me
some money I tried to use like Apple pay
and everything in like it turns out my
bank didn't work when I tell you guys I
was trying everything since the
beginning of this trip I was trying to
make my situation better every step of
the way and every time I had an idea
just wouldn't work so my mom finally was
like Western Union okay cool she sent
you the money already like all you got
to do is find a bank they use the
Western Union you can go pick it up does
it okay so I look up all these places I
think it was like a Friday maybe or a
Saturday and of course they were all all
the places were closed a crowd
and I texted her and I just talking to
her when I recorded this the first time
and I was a do nothing because I texted
her when I saw that they were all
clothes all the places were closed I
just busted out laughing and I think
like mentally at that point I was
delirious like it was so bad that I like
lost my mind I mean like nobody will
really understand because probably
because I'm sitting here telling the
story with a smile on my face but I
really like lost my mind and I was just
sitting there like I'm going I'm going
to need a psychiatrist when I get back
basically this trip has done so much
damage to me mentally emotionally like
the break-up just like everything going
on in my life right now
I'm gonna need a psychiatrist when I get
back like I was not okay
mentally at that point I was in such a
dark place it was so bad and I just
busted out laughing yeah I texted her
like hahahahaha all caps and I was like
it's follows Mom like I can't get of
course like she knew like when we got
back when I got back we talked about it
she was like I knew like when I texted
her hahaha that was like a Saturday I
think so then Sunday had to go by and
then Monday I found on the bank I ended
up having to open a bank account in
Korea which was a whole struggle in
itself so I had to set up an account
long story short finally I got that done
the guy was like irritated with me or
something cuz he didn't want to have to
do all that work to open up an American
a bank account friend American citizen
but you know I got the money that she
sent me it was plenty so I went to the
grocery store bought all this food I was
like oh my god I can eat now I can't eat
so I bought all this food and then I
took it walked back to my apartment with
it all I was very heavy and then I only
had a couple days left in that room at
that point so you know I was feeling
better so I went out and I explored a
little bit those last couple days in
Seoul I went out and did some things and
it was time for me to go to Busan well
that's what I did I packed up my stuff
thank the host and I took the food too
when I got to the room I didn't realize
that the room that I had booked didn't
have a stove or anything so all the food
that I brought over there was useless
and I basically ended up having to throw
it away which was crazy because not only
did I like have to carry all my luggage
and everything Plus now groceries and it
was like heavy so don't say I did all
that for nothing but now I have to throw
this food away and I'm gonna have to buy
new foods with a little bit of money
that I already have there go just
everything getting all bad again I was
just mad so when I was in Busan I was
only there for like three four days or
yeah I didn't do anything because I was
so over it at that point except my
second to last day I did go to the beach
and I was so happy I did because it was
so pretty it was so nice yeah that was
the only day that I really went out of
the area other than to like get food I
went to the beach and I came back and I
was like I'm finally gonna get to go
home I went home I still had the two two
day trip because I had to spend the
night in Beijing Airport I was out of
money at that point so I couldn't eat in
Beijing like I ate but the mill the only
meal I could afford cuz the airport is
expensive was only enough to keep me
like fed for a couple hours and so I
basically like I was really really
really hungry in the airport and so bad
and I just didn't have any more money I
was like out of money I survived the
plane ride and I got home and then I
went out so the pickup area with all my
stuff and finally my mom pulled up and
she just kind of stood up she got out
the car and she looked at me and she
just kind of like hey poo like that's
what she called me she's like hey Pooh
you okay
she's just like the concerned mother and
look like it was like a smile but like
she knew and she was like oh okay and I
was a no
I'm not and I busted out crying and she
just came and held me and it was just so
sadly just thinking about it like I just
I really didn't know I was just thinking
like wow on that trip in the last room
and so that thing and I was like is this
where people are when they are like
suicidal I was in such a dark when I
tell you guys I never had like suicidal
thoughts but I was just like like I
don't know I just couldn't imagine the
feeling that I was feeling being any
worse and I was like I'm not even at a
point where I want to die so for people
to want to kill themselves it has to be
just so bad I just feel so bad but yeah
when she got out the car and she was
like are you okay and I was just like no
I'm not busted out crying came and
helped me we got in the car and I went
home now was Korea now in that moment
that wasn't like the last of my
struggles cuz I said I had to deal with
stuff when I got home and so like things
just were like getting worse and worse
and worse but that's like another story
for another day that I probably will
never end up sharing with YouTube but
just know that the that was Korea that
was my trip to Korea when I got back of
course I wasn't telling people that when
they asked me how Korea was I was just
saying it was cool didn't want to talk
about it I only told a couple of people
who I haven't really happening and if I
did tell I was just kind of like oh you
know I ended up being kind of bad my
host was a pervert and I had to move out
you know nobody knew what happened but
now you guys know and like I said I
cancelled the rest of my solo trips for
the rest of the year may or may not have
some next year I don't know I have ended
up going on a couple trips but they've
all been like trips with my friends and
like trips with family but like as far
as solo traveling goes I'm just kind of
like chillin on it for a while also
because that trip took a lot out of me
mentally physically financially like I
budgeted I think like $3,000 I ended up
spending between like four to five
thousand dollars on that trip like in
total four planes for like housing
everything it was just way more than I
wanted to
and so I was like like we chillin for a
little bit now you guys are basically
caught up and I went on like the social
media break and then finally I came back
with like the slipping slide video it
was a lot I never won it like I said I
never want to have to tell the story
again I hate this story I hate talking
about it but that's what happened and
just know that I've been there it's like
happy and bubbly as I like like to be
only energetic I've been going through
stuff too and I'm just saying like it's
not gonna stop me from traveling I know
that there are things that I have to do
differently now in the future in order
to avoid situations like this like not
cutting off my different car not staying
with the man and taking X amount of cash
just things like that I learned a lot
from that trip it broke me down but I
learned a lot from the trip and I'm not
gonna not travel anymore just gonna do
things differently so this video is long
enough I don't want to talk to too much
more like that that was the story and it
is what it is
that's everything that happened to me in
Korea so yeah oh my god I can't believe
I made thank you guys so much for
watching if you made it through this
entire video especially like you
literally watch the whole thing thank
you for listening to my story it was a
lot for me to do anyway thank you for
watching I love you guys and I gotta go
so I'll talk to you guys later goodbye
my social media down below in the
description box all that good stuff and
I'll see you guys