what's up guys it's Rachel and this week
I'm in my bedroom as you can see today
I'm just gonna sit down and talk to you
because I got an interesting story it's
about my recent mistake if you've been
keeping up with my videos you guys know
couple weeks ago I hurt myself in a
swimming pool yeah I got a few scratches
on my face so I went to a pharmacy to
get some ointment but oh can I get some
condiment yeah condiment I asked for
ketchup sand mustard for my scratches I
still can vividly remember the confused
look on his face so whoops but it's okay
because people make mistakes all the
time and I don't think it's a bad thing
but it'll be great if we could avoid
making them right so today I decided to
talk about common mistakes foreigners
make in Korea and how to avoid them
I really wanted to make this video
because I know many people make these
mistakes not because they don't respect
Korean culture but because they simply
just don't know and that is because you
guessed it every culture is different if
you grew up in a different culture how
could you possibly know how we do things
are all different culture by culture so
even if you make these mistakes peers
are not gonna get offended they know
you're annoying Korea they they'll
understand but if you do these over and
over and over again people around you
might think huh you you don't even want
to try so I'm making this video in hopes
that these tips will help you better
understand Korea and Korean
okay so without any further ado here are
common mistakes Koreans not foreigners
week in Korea let's go I find that a lot
of people have this misconception about
Korean drinking culture and I'm always
like no no no and it is believing that
it is a rude thing to turn down drinks
and you have to drink if you want to be
friends with them
and it is so not true you should not
drink more than you can handle
accepting every soldiers job people
offer you it's not gonna make you a
polite person it's just gonna make you
drunk and that could lead to alcohol
poisoning which is really dangerous yeah
it's nice of you wanting to be polite
and you respect them and you want to be
friends with them good but hear me out
when I say this anyone who makes you
drink more than you want is a jerk
anyone who makes you feel bad or put you
down because you didn't drink as much is
a jerk and when you see this type of
people just say bye-bye don't even care
about what they think of you it's just
not worth it
so remember you don't have to drink more
than you want more than you can and it
is definitely not gonna make you a rude
person the next mistake I'm about to
tell you is gonna sound totally the
opposite of what I just said it is
refusing a surger shot what Rachel you
just but you just sit why all the whole
the whole a whole the whole hello hold
up let me explain so you're in a
restaurant with your Korean friends and
they offer you a soda or beer I say just
take it take it
just don't drink it unless you want to
Koreans always make sure everyone's
glass is filled
it's considered as good manners in Korea
no Wendy glasses a few refuse they won't
necessarily get offended but you don't
raise question rights to that oh you
don't want to hang out you don't you
don't wanna be my friend let's see their
purpose of offering you drinks is not to
make you drunk that's a sign of
friendship that's like saying oh we're
hanging out as a group yeah it's nice
because no one has to feel left out when
we make a toast and obviously you don't
have to drink just raise your glass do
the toast and put it down and drink your
sprite or coke or water whatever you're
drinking you don't have to consume the
alcohol and when your glass is not empty
if you are not gonna offer you no more
next I want to talk about table manners
in Korea when you go to a restaurant put
the utensils on the table for your
companies before they do it for you
because it's a nice thing to do Oh in
the water to fill their water cups for
them so if they are taking care of
spoons and chopsticks you could be
filling their water cups or vice versa
this is a manner if you do nothing but
just sit there like a king or a queen
the one's gonna blame me or anything
it's more like holding the door for
someone else so if you are eating with
an elder I recommend you to do this and
if you are on a date and want to make a
good impression I recommend you to do
this also after the waiter served stuff
food just hold on for a moment just
don't jump right in I know I know we're
hungry I know it's painful to watch my
food on the table like my beautiful food
sitting on the table staring at me but
uh it's considered as good manners
to wait until the other person starts
especially if the person is older than
you if you want to make a good
impression
wait for the other person to start or
suggest them to go ahead usually we wait
until the oldest person at the table to
have their first bite but if you're not
sure if you are older or younger than
the person I think it's best to wait or
suggest them to start together by saying
let's dig in or enjoy your food next
common mistake is calling people by
their first name when you meet someone
you learn their name and you start
calling people by their first name
Ohr so hi it seems like there's nothing
wrong with it but in Korea we rarely
call people by their first names unless
you're the same age and you're close to
them if the person is older than you
you're supposed to add words like unnie
bodoni huh
after their first name according to
their gender and age I made a video on
how to use these words appropriately
I'll put a card up here click it check
it out if you want to learn more about
it I think the safest way is to ask the
person how he or she would like to be
called and finally it never hurts to
learn the correct body language
oftentimes I see many foreigners doing
this making this gesture when they come
to Korea is a sign of respect but is it
really is it really being respectful to
Korea
oh I don't think so because you know
what this is not even Korean gesture
this is from Buddhism they might say oh
but I didn't know and I'm interested in
Buddhism don't some Koreans believe in
Buddhism okay first of all if you're
interested in Buddhism then do you go
around in your country with this and say
how are you how's it going good morning
No
then why here Korea is not even a
Buddhist country we do have a freedom of
the religion and it's something to think
about if you want to show respect I
really learning about the culture should
come first
I think bowing might be the best choice
in this case I also made a video called
Korean body language 101 where I talk
about the most common Korean body
languages you should know before coming
to Korea
if you want to know more on this hit on
over and check it out a lot of videos to
catch up on right yeah stay connected
with me okay guys that is it for today's
video hope you enjoyed it and if you did
remember to give rapid thumbs up if you
don't follow me on Instagram or Twitter
all the links will be in the description
below and I'll see you next week
peace out love you and goodbye
[Music]