hey you guys what's up bitch okay today
I have a big news for you me and my
sister are moving out of this place by
the time you watch this
we'd be already moved into a new
apartment so yeah this would be the last
time you're seeing this background and
who trusts me finding the new apartment
was not an easy game at all I used these
Korean USD websites
Kabam in Japan and there you can search
our locations budget and options like
parking space where pet friendly cinema
and they show apartments that fit all
your conditions you can see pictures of
their place and also you know oh my god
yeah I'm so ready to move out I can't
kill a bug that's a problem you can
tweet oh my god I'm scared
ah okay
focus because you can do this huh you
can see pictures of them please and also
read a short description about that
place but I realized there's a huge gap
between what's written on the website
and what the actual place is like yeah
after checking out a few places I
learned that you can't just believe
what's written the description as it is
I realized they were using their own
special language very deceiving but I
cracked the code now I know what they
are really saying when they sing
together
oh yeah and I thought this was pretty
amusing so let me give you some examples
you will enjoy fresh air around
it's located on the remote mountain road
the homeowner is very kind
he's nosy very quiet neighborhood feels
peaceful around here it's located at a
dead-end street and it's freshly
repaired now in a good condition it
needed to be repaired
it feels safe around here because the
neighborhood is bright even at night it
gets very noisy at night because of all
the loud drunken people around here see
what I mean
yeah technically we are not lying but
man they are like these conversational
Wizards with all their magic words and
you know what pictures on their web
sites can be very deceiving too because
I realize they use one of those fisheye
lens the ones that make the place look a
lot larger so I highly recommend you to
actually look around many places and
compare them before choosing one but I
know what the big question is did we
ever find the perfect apartment
well I'm pleased to tell you after days
and days of searching and searching and
searching we finally found the perfect
apartment for both of us I have so many
good memories with this house except for
its box but it's time for a new time
this place was okay but it's just a big
studio with no brooms
so me and my sister are so excited to
have walls again that way even when one
of us is sleeping the other one to just
go to a different room and do our own
thing like turning on the lights or
watching TV show but anyways that is it
for today's video
next time I'll say hi from the new
apartment unless the bug kills me with
its poison I lost sight of the bug but I
know it's in the corner right there how
am I gonna sleep
anyways maybe I could make up apartment
or video once I close in let me know if
you want to watch it with your comments
down below and yes as always thank you
so much for watching and I'll see you in
the next one peace out love you and
goodbye
that looks like a spider yeah that's a
big spider oh my god
if it comes this way I'm going to faint
[Music]