hey you guys what's up Rachel here hi hi
hello today I want to talk about making
friends in Korea because it's me every
new year you mean new people and come
friends with them but if you're in Korea
chances are remember it's so hard to
make friends and trust me when I tell
you this my friend in Korea you're not
gonna be able to make as many friends as
you want and movie that came out to
negatively so let me rephrase that
mmm you're not gonna be able to call as
many people as your friends as you want
better because in Korea the word friend
only applies to the people who are the
same age as view so basically to call
someone as your friend you must have
been born in the same year with them let
me give you an example when you guys
share a story of a little boy making a
special bond with the grandfather next
door you'd say it's a sweet story right
well I also think oh it's a seat story
and they're so adorable together let's
say the boy comes up to his mom and say
oh he's my friend
you guys still think oh it's so sweet
but you know what I you think ha that's
rude that's inappropriate yeah talk
about cultural difference right so what
Rachel if I'm not the same a cute the
person I want to be friends with it
can't be close with them it can't build
a strong relationship with them no no no
of course you can so instead of calling
someone close to you as your friend
in Korea there are other ways to call
someone who's older and number than you
okay I was born in 1989 so if you're
younger than me
and if you're a female you can call me
on me Rachel with me
and if you're a male you can go me buna
reach on them yeah and I said be my
talking and I could call you all by your
names let's say you were born prior to
1989 which means you are older than me
then I'm your tuning you can call me by
my name if you are a female I should
call you on me and if you're a male I
should call you oppa and yes it's Bo
power from Psy's Gangnam style actually
these on me oppa do not win 10 words are
how we call our brothers and sisters in
the family so if we are not a same age
even though what we may not be able to
be friends in Korea you call each other
like your family you will be my brothers
and sisters I don't know I think it's
pretty damn cool and I think it's so
sweet
okay and that is it for today's video
I'm gonna go now thank you my brothers
and sisters Korean style comfort
watching my to this video if you liked
it give it a big thumbs up leave a
comment below and I'll see you in the
next one peace I love you in goodbye
[Music]