we're not gonna let them fork with us
what's up guys it's Rachel and this week
I'm gonna talk about how to avoid cult
recruiters in Korea because it's getting
hard not to notice them they are
everywhere these days and honestly I
think it's becoming a serious issue in
Korea these days I feel like three out
of ten times I'm outside walking around
someone is bound to come up to me and
try to talk to me and it's annoying
because I know who they are
cult recruiters that's who they are and
you guys know I normally talk about good
and positive things about Korea so this
video might feel a little different but
you gotta learn both good and bad sight
about things you're interested in
because we are not living in bubble
sorry
it's an ugly side of Korea for sure but
they do exist so I want you to be
prepared so in this video I'm gonna talk
about how they approached us and how
they try to trick us and what we can do
about it honestly I don't know if I
should feel scared for posting this
video because I'm like exposing their
tactics here and calling them out but uh
I feel like this is something I need to
do because it's so easy to get tricked
by them and they can really mess up our
entire life
and I don't want that to happen to
anyone ever and why our hero for doing
this because I'm basically saving your
life nah yes I am okay so let's begin
they usually approach you pretending
like they are asking for direction or
they might ask for your time to take a
simple test or a survey introducing them
as students or researchers who are
studying mostly psychology they might
ask you to take MBTI test Enneagram they
might have you draw a simple drawing and
say they'll interpret your
whatever they say their goal here is
simple they want to meet you once again
they don't give us shirt about the
direction or the test regardless they're
gonna thank for your time and they're
gonna start complimenting you and
eventually they'll ask your number and
set a plan to meet you next time
they will desperately plan for a hangout
coffee or a meal or just a quick meet
with you by making up whatever reasons
so if you bump into these type of people
run but if you didn't notice who they
are here and if you didn't run you'll
find yourself hanging out with them well
here's their next move they'll bring out
their wingman by saying oh hey by the
way my friend was just in the
neighborhood and I kind of invite her to
come hang out he said okay and you'll
probably say yeah okay that's cool
because you kind of like this person and
you don't want to be an asshole
sometimes they put on an act and pretend
like they bumped into their friend by
accident oh my gosh how are you it's
been so long
Oh me I was just hanging out with my
friend here do you wanna join for a
second hey do you mind they plan this
they're all cultural coders now you are
their fish so now here we are you became
their fish and now I'm gonna tell you
how they treat you and drag you down if
you took their test they're gonna give
you the result of course it's all bull
shirts they made up mostly the results
sounds very negative and they will point
out your weaknesses and bring out your
insecurities this is to make you feel
vulnerable so that it's easier for
to make you emotionally rely on them and
they're gonna start to manipulate you
acting like therapist and encourage you
to open up and then they go get they
they will ask all about your past and
make you think about why you feel what
you feel all the shirt but remember they
are not licensed therapists they are
working fakers what they are doing there
is collecting information about you they
appear to be good listeners
of course because they are collecting
information about you which they will
use against you in the future but
because they seem to be so into your
story right now it's so easy for you to
spill out everything you might even cry
while doing this because you are talking
about your insecurities and it's easy to
get emotional and they will convince you
that you can make a change that you can
solve the problem you are having right
now that you can be a better self and
finally be happy by joining them with
the Bible study and they start to
present themselves as these nice people
saying bull shirt made of stories like
helping out people like you in the past
and those people are so much better and
happier now and helping others gives
them the meaning of life yada-yada-yada
it's all bullcrap but now that you
shared all your stories and opened up
you kind of feel close to them and they
seem to be real nice people who care
about you and you feel like you can
really change and you want to be with
them
so now you are invited to their Bible
study they're gonna ask you to do a few
things before your next session and
honestly they're instructions sounds so
hilarious
because obviously it's all bull shirts
but you're pretty vulnerable at this
point so you might actually follow what
they tell you to do so please pay
attention to this now so you can
remember how ridiculous this sound okay
here we go
don't tell anyone anything the fact of
the matter the fact of your study
together don't tell anyone
don't search about this on demon there
are a lot of haters you need to study
about yourself you solve your problem by
gaining Bible study group and consulting
with us they're so lucky to get this
opportunity for faint
you know it's expensive this is all free
for you on doing that says a volunteer
work I'm donating my talent and it makes
me happy never ever talk about any of
this to anyone okay now it's the
important part we're not gonna let them
fork with us well they said don't ever
tell this to anyone right do the
opposite number one talk about this to
everybody literally everyone around you
don't keep a secret blab on this free
service you got you might not be able to
see it but people aren't you have fresh
eyes and they'll be able to figure out
how shady it all is talk to people
please give people around you a chance
to save you from that shirt home number
two walk away this is what I do usually
it's literally just walking away when a
stranger approach to you I don't do this
intentionally but I'm a naturally
terrified person I guess so startled
when someone tries to talk to me and I
just go to my direction right away
because think about it what could
possibly a stranger have something to
tell me don't get me wrong I'm not a
monster if someone asks me for direction
I try to help but if they ask me
something more than that like my time or
my
number I'd say no a because I think it's
shady and B I'm actually busy if I'm on
the street walking from point A to point
B it means I'm in a rush I'm on my way
to meet someone or I have to be
somewhere right now I don't have a
luxury to hang around the street I know
it sounds a little sad but it works to
keep the bad people away from me number
three don't expect to make friends on
the street we can't be that naive
you just can't everyone has an agenda
you know being friends with a random
person on the street it sounds almost
like a fairy tale and we know life is
not a fairy tale it's a scary world man
they're a cult recorder is trying to
fork you up find a better place to make
friends go to school go to church go to
parties and fun events join clubs just
don't expect to be friends with total
strangers on the street you just met
because they might not be the people who
you think they are
okay guys these are the stuff I wanted
to tell you today and I feel like I
should mention this before I go these
tips are actually information shared by
people who managed to get out of the
cart for obvious reason they don't want
to reveal their identity but I came
across these horrible and sad stories
shared by them on the internet a few
days ago and I thought I should share
this with you as well because I really
care about you hope this video was
helpful and I really hope you don't fall
into their pool shirts when you visit
Korea they are fourth up their workers
who manipulate people who are
emotionally vulnerable so please feel
free to share this information with the
people around you I think it's important
for everyone to know what they do and
how they trick us so that we can be
prepared and be able to avoid them okay
now if you liked this video please give
it a big thumbs up subscribe if you
haven't already and if you don't follow
me on Instagram or Twitter or the links
will be in the description below and
I'll see you next time peace out love
you in the bike
[Music]