[YKICKY STUDIO]
[Today's blind date place]
[With 1.98 won per second, you can help yourself at ON restaurant ]
Hello I am a freelance model Jung Sunyoung
[Q. What is your ideal type of boyfriend?]
I like someone who is somewhat like a bear?
a little big and tall
Hello
Hi
I am 25 years old and I'm Jung Minjun
I am a college student and I live in Incheon
[Q. What is your ideal type of girlfriend?]
I like people who are
cute and feminine
Nice to meet you
Yeah you too
[Jung Sunyoung]
Was it hard
[Jung Minjun]
to get here in the rain?
[Pretense or Honest?]
[a merciless dramatic blind date!]
Here's your rule of '2FACE blind date'
[Rule1 : There is a like it/hate it button under each foot.]
[Rule1 : If they press 'like it' button, one heartcoin will turn on.
[Rule1 : If they press 'hate it' button, one heartcoin will turn off.
[Of course the partner doesn't know whether the button is pressed!]
[Rule2 : Each participant starts a blind date with three heartcoin]
[Rule2 : When all lights are off on one side or
[Rule 2 : less than three lights are left altogether, ]
[Rule 2: The blind date is forced to quit]
[Rule 3 : it will be successful blind date, If it lasts for 30 minutes.]
[Rule 3 :  If dates are forced to quit before that, it's a failure.]
[30 minutes of blind date start]
Oh no it's fine
It's not humid so that's good
Yeah it is
How old are you?
I'm 25
And you?
Me too
Oh we're the same age
Yeah
You don't have to use polite language
Oh yeah
I will later
Did you eat yet?
[Sunyoung pressed the 'hate it' button]
No not yet
[Q.Why did you click dislike all of a sudden?)]
I hesitated
but he was not really my type
and ripped jeans and a T-shirt was a little off for a
blind date
where did you come from just now?
From Sinlim
Oh Sinlim, with your family?
No I live alone
Oh really?
Yeah
That must be hard, I lived in Sinlim too
There is this place called Culture street?
Fashion culture street?
I lived there with my friend
Why?
I was at school
and I wanted to be less of a burden to my parents
but it was not easy
Right, help yourself
Yeah, you too
Do you want something in particular? Help yourself
Yeah
[The other person doesn't know whether I pressed the button.]
Is there a knife here?
I don't think I can eat now
[Sunyoung pressed the 'hate it' button]
[[Q.Why did you press 'hate it' button all of a sudden?)]
I clicked dislike because it was so awkward and
I wanted to not be there
You can ask me anything if you want
sure after this
What hobbies do you have?
I like cooking
That's really nice
I really like cooking
Do you know this thing
called air-frier?
I got it too, it's really good for a diet
I put a lot of sweet potatoes
It's a lot cheaper these days
I'm not into it a lot
but there's a lot you can do with it
you can cook really easily
so I recommended it
You're not here to advertise right?
No, I don't even for there
[Q. You had a conversation about a air-pair conversation all of a sudden]
It was so funny,
talking about that in a blind date
but it was kinda cute
I thought that we were that much running out of topics to discuss
Have you been to Borame park? It's nice
Really? I have never been there
Never?
Yeah
It's great there are lots of Pikachus
if you play Pokemon Go it's a great place to be
Borame Park?
Yeah
I went hunting too when I was living in Sinlim
for Pikachus
[Q. Why did you have a conversation about 'Pikachu' all of a sudden?]
It was a huge thing a while ago
It was really famous for having lots of pikachus
since she said she lived there too
I thought it would be something to talk about
Do you play it these days as well?
Not these days
Anything else you like?
I like taking pictures
Pictures?
I like it a lot
-Me too
Do you like taking pictures?
-Yeah
Really?
I ordered a camera recently
You like taking pictures yourself?
Or being taken?
I'll take a picture of you sometime
-Thanks
I like taking pictures
and she likes being taken
it's not easy to find someone who likes to be taken pictures
I clicked the like button then
[15 minutes after the blind date]
Do you like interior design too?
Yeah
Really?
I like simple designs
I clean all the time
Oh me too
Really?
-Yeah
You need to clean well when you're living by yourself
When I was living by myself
I had wet paper towels
I clicked the like button when he said he liked cleaning
not because he likes cleaning
but he tried to find something in common
and that was sweet
[21 minutes after the blind date]
I have a question
What do you think about girls and guys being friends?
Do you think they can be?
It is somewhat random
I do have friends who are girls
like watching a movie during the day
Movie?
Yeah
I don't do that when I have a boy friend
Right sure
but when you don't -Yeah
when you are not dating anyone you don't really have anyone to go to the movies with
When there is, you do what they say
If they say 'don't' I would say 'okay'
Not doing the thing they don't like is the best policy
to avoid fighting
Do you fight hard?
I hate fighting
I don't even fight with my friends
So I'd just say 'okay fine'
'I'm sorry I won't do it again'
I don't really get mad easily
Not really
Unless someone hits me from the back all of a sudden
right a girl friend doesn't do that usually
I'd let my girl friend hit me from the back once or twice
I guess we had that in common, we both didn't like fighting
I thought that we wouldn't
so I clicked like
[26 minutes after the blind date]
I ride the bike at night if I feel like it
or take a walk and go to the fish tank
I like fish a lot -Oh really?
Yeah I go to the aquariums all the time
I come from Busan
Me too
Really?
Where?
Seomyun
That's a little far from where I'm from
Where?
Jangsan, do you know?
Yeah I do
A little over Haeundae
I lived in Jadong
You are also a Busan person
You don't have the dialect at all
People made fun of it so much I changed it
They were calling me a village boy, but Busan is not a village
Nonsense -Right?
They called me names yeah
It's great to see a Busan person
I think I don't know your name
What is your name?
Jung Sunyoung
Jung Sunyoung?
I am also Jung, Jung Minjun
I'm sorry I didn't ask
Slipped my mind
[Q. Do you think Sunyoung pressed the 'hate it' button?]
I think she would have clicked dislike
In the beginning I was talking
and I didn't even ask her name
Was that bothering you?
Not at all
I knew that I didn't know his name
but he was trying so hard
I didn't want to lead the conversation
to make him feel bad
[30 minutes of blind date ends]
You reached 30 minutes
Thank you
I didn't know it had been 30 minutes
[Q. How's your feel after the blind date?]
I didn't like how I was leading in the beginning
But I liked it when he was trying
I wanted to know him more
So if we can see each other again, it would be nice
[Q. How's your feel after the blind date?]
I liked how time passed quickly
and it felt like it was not enough
so I think we can have a longer time next time
and have more conversations
[2FACE Blind Date]