YKICKY STUDIO
Hello, I am Choi Sulgi and I'm 26 years old
I am attending graduate school right now
I still have a year left until graduation
[What is your ideal type?]
I like someone who looks neat
sofr rather than sharp
Hello
I am Hyun Jongwu and I'm 22 years old
[What is your ideal type?]
I like someone with a nice smile with the eyes with a cute personality
and who can fit right in a hug
[Hyun Jongwo]
[Choi Sulgi]
[Pretense or Honest?]
[a merciless dramatic blind date!]
Here's your rule of '2FACE blind date'
[Rule1 : There is a like it/hate it button under each foot.]
[Rule1 : If they press 'like it' button, one heartcoin will turn on.
[Rule1 : If they press 'hate it' button, one heartcoin will turn off.
[Of course the partner doesn't know whether the button is pressed!]
[Rule2 : Each participant starts a blind date with three heartcoin]
[Rule2 : When all lights are off on one side or
[Rule 2 : less than three lights are left altogether, ]
[Rule 2: The blind date is forced to quit.]
[Rule 3 : it will be successful blind date, If it lasts for 30 minutes.]
[Rule 3 :  If dates are forced to quit before that, it's a failure.]
Your name is?
I am Hyun Jongwo
Hyun. Jong. Wu?
Yes. And yours?
[30 minutes of blind date start]
Choi Sulgi
Sulgi? Yes
How old are you?
26? okay
and you?
I'm 22
What?
Why?
22? -yes.
Oh okay
Do I look much older?
No, no it's not that
[The other person doesn't know whether I pressed the button.]
-Oh...
[Q. Why did you press the button as soon as you heard age of the other one]
We have quite an age difference
I was just a little surprised so I clicked the unlike button
What do you do usually?
You are a student then?
Yeah, I took a semester off
and the military?
Do we have to talk about military here? -I'm sorry
Oh, okay
[How about a unfulfilled blind date partner ?]
I usually meet someone older or of the same age
if he was not done with the military yet
I wasn't sure if I could do it
Oh no, I just asked because you were so young
Yes I still need to go to the military
[Finally press the 'hate it' button]
[If one more light of  Sulgi goes out, blind date is forced to quit]
help yourself
did you do many blind dates?
Not many just a couple?
I don't know
I haven't done much either
of these kind of blind dates
are you good at talking like this?
Yeah I'm usually friendly
just a little bit awkward
What do you do usually?
just normally? -yeah
I am working these days
What kind of work?
I'm going to graduate school these days
and I had a class with elementary school kids today
so I teach them
You're a teacher?
Oh no just
a class about theater
in a camp during the vacation
so I was doing that
What kind of theme?
We were making a short scene
with fairy-tales in English
like a musical
Today the kids wanted to do
10 more minutes
I was really proud that they asked
[What is the reason you pressed the 'like it' button]
I like kids too
so I thought we had something in common
that's why I clicked the like button
[10 minutes after the blind date]
Is there
a specific type of person that you like?
Someone who is not faking
and who is cute
Any celebrity that you like?
I'm really into this show 'Secretary Kim' these days
Park Minyoung? -Yeah
I like Park Seojun
He's really wow
You admit that he's pretty cool
Even when for a guy
and Park Minyoung too
Have you watched Mr. Sunshine?
Yeah that too
[No way]
[Sulgi pressed the 'like it' button]
We liked the same TV shows
I like TV shows
so I thought that we had something in common
The script is so well written
and the acting is excellent too
Definitely, Mr. Sunshine is great
What is your blood type?
What do you think it is?
B?
Nope
O?
Wrong again -AB?
Yeah
I thought so, you were friendly
Yeah AB types are cool
What is?
What kind of aspects? -I like AB types
Yeah these people are cool
Are you type B? -No
A? -Yes
Yay
I'm not timid or anything
That's just a stereotype that
[Sulgi pressed the 'like it' button]
type As are timid
I'm not sure you remember but you clicked the like button when you were talking about blood types
Did I?
I wonder why
No I know why
He laughed a lot
-He did? -Yeah
hmm
After a topic there was a silence
Another topic...
[Sulgi pressed the 'hate it' button]
We had a lot of silences and every time I felt like
I had to start a conversation
and I clicked the dislike button when I thought that It would be nice if he could start a conversation
we had a few bumps with the silences
and I think she didn't quite like me for that
[15 minutes before the blind date]
It's so hot,
it's the first time that Korea is this hot -Yeah me too
But every year it's so much hotter
Like every year it's a new record -Yeah
-I seriously feel like
[What destruction]
the world is coming to an end
All of a sudden?
Yeah -We're talking about the end of the world now?
Don't you think that it will though?
Mmm
Think about it, is it too weird?
They say they found water on Mars
Will it be faster to live on Mars or for Earth to end?
Oh wow I never thought about it -Really?
What do you think?
I think about it a lot,
I feel like there would be other galaxies so
-so there would be an Earth elsewhere?
Something like that?
So there would be something similar to humans
or even better
[Jongwo pressed the 'hate it' button]
Am I here on a blind date or at a lecture?
I was thinking about that so it was a little awkward
What is your dating style?
I do everything for them -Oh wow
Not only just things but I am full in
when I'm in a relationship
So after a while they say that I am more like a friend
That's exactly the same
for me too
I do many things for them
and at the end they say that I am like a mother
Yeah something like that
I like taking care of people
When she said
[Q. What is the reason you pressed the 'hate it' button]
'like a mother'
I know that she meant she took care of people
but I hope that a girl friend is like a girl friend
that would be better
[When one of the two lights goes out, a blind date is force to quit]
How lenient are you
with your boy friend?
-As in?
If they meet a friend who is a girl, or if they go drinking or clubbing?
I don't think I'd say okay to clubbing
I like clubbing...
I go there often when I'm with friends to listen to music
Do you go often?
Today too?
No not often
See?
I understand that it's fun
but he was not really finishing his sentence
and he felt a little too young
I think the last time I went out was last week?
[Sulgi pressed the 'hate it' button]
Is that too often?
Oh how often do you go usually?
[The blind date failed.]
I was a little surprised
that she was so upset
I shouldn't have mentioned it
Thanks
Yeah thank you
[Q. How was your blind date today?]
I was a little nervous
and I wonder what she didn't like about me
and what she did like
I think he's a really good person
but I guess it would be better for him to meet someone with more similarities
[2FACE Blind Date]