Julian right Julian Julian yes you got
it yes you're you you're the one that
loves to sing so big question what is
your ideal first date wait I don't think
I'm the one that actually likes the same
but that's okay oh my gosh how do you
think you get to know someone without
actually seeing them in person if it's
through a conversation over a phone then
you get to know them that's why I really
love telemarketers when they give me a
call
because then we can jive and have a
great conversation from there but when
it comes to photos you just swipe to see
who you think is the most attractive and
I don't think that's necessarily the
best way to get to know someone but
[Music]
hello how are you I'm good how are you
life is beautiful what's your name and
do you have any siblings
hey yeah my name is Liz and I actually
have three younger siblings nice yes hi
I'm Victoria I have two younger siblings
that are eight and ten years apart for
me and I like to play tennis
I'm Sabrina but people call me SAVs but
would like to see you oh yeah you know
different I want to be different
most of my days they do jumping jacks
sort of how are you hi my name is Liana
and I love food and what do you mean by
you do jumping jacks favour us on this
week this week you know I don't know the
secret menu yeah hello my name is
Jonathan and I love singing in the
shower
are you a shower person I am a shower
person are you morning or night quick
morning shower yeah I'm a morning shower
person too and then my name is mcleach
by the way being Hispanic I'm Hispanic
nice there's a lot of me it's hard to be
vegetarian in both of our culture's I'm
Keanu like well all my friends call me
ki so oh I like that yeah we were like
key to your heart that's like basically
how you're gonna remember me above me oh
I love how you said that Kiana I love
food I've two older brothers who they
like individuals that are men that walk
into the place when they want to ask you
out on the date I mean they don't get
involved in my business like we're
really distant are you close with their
siblings super close that's why I'm kind
of like a child but also mature at the
same time but mostly a child
gosh I feel really bad I'm going to do
Courtney I was unable to really get to
know her right away and then Coco you
know I've dated people before that had
rough siblings and that usually didn't
turn out right so those are the two
reasons why my deal first date I like
things really super chill so going to a
coffee shop going on a hike I love
hiking that's that's exactly what I love
too yeah yeah well my favorite is we
start off with something small like a
hike yes and then if it's cooler than
that then it's like oh do you want to do
an activity like rock climbing wait I
climb - oh god you're joking Irie like
the beach I love the waters so and I
haven't been in a while so I think that
would be really cool I think the best
part of the day is just to talk so I
really like seeing places I like walking
around somewhere so I do love art
museums do you like single dates or
let's say there's a group setting of the
date ooh I've never done like a group
date I've never done a double date so
that could be something fun to
experience okay all right Julian right
Julian Julian yes yes you're you you're
the one that loves to sing so big
question what is your ideal first date
wait I don't think I'm the one that
actually likes the same but that's okay
oh that's okay my ideal first date I
would love to do something where we can
talk but also where we're doing
something kind of active like mini
golfing or bowling I think anything food
related I love like anything like grief
or anything did you know you live longer
if you eat Mediterranean foods so they
say we really didn't so you're gonna be
able to like to live a very long life
anything outdoorsy is pretty much really
like my ideal date sounds like a lot of
fun to do that sounds fun that's cool
[Laughter]
you're a vocal director do you have
students as well yeah yeah okay okay all
right oh they're all really great I am
okay so the first one yeah and I
apologize again is Breanna the energy I
guess is just different that's it we're
just two different energies
I'd like my cleat I like like Jana I
hope I I hope I've picked the right one
I Liz what is your a deal-breaker when
it comes to dating I think it's about
extending generosity to other people and
giving them an open and safe space yeah
someone doesn't provide that then that's
a deal-breaker for me I want the person
that I'm gonna be in a bishop whatever
um to be able to give me that
independence it would be someone you had
like low emotional intelligence if it
was someone who that was way too
dependent on me and a relationship okay
so we can not complete one another but
we can come together and like build each
other up I think a big deal breaker for
me is someone who isn't honest if you're
not vegan I don't want to date you
I'm joking I'm joking okay I'm vegan but
that's not a deal-breaker right okay why
did you say that but I love how you play
see that's that's what's so special
about you is that you love to I
complained about you yes furry okay this
is sound big but kayani
and the reason why is because we're here
to like have a relationship but I would
love to be her friend I think she would
be so dope as a friend
probably Jill as well
Victoria out oh god maybe I do like
Victoria this this is you're pressuring
me
I mean I'd love to keep traveling I love
traveling overseas but I also would like
really love to have a family someday
so I guess those are - what do you mean
by someday like have a family some daily
yeah like how many years out do you
think um probably my next five whatever
I'm doing I want to be helping people
and I know that when I'm helping people
and proud of myself oh my gosh yes I'm
currently a student I'm a third year
undergrad so right now I'm studying
education so my goal is to become a
teacher one day it's oh gosh I think I'm
gonna hopefully I'm right with my notes
I feel I apologize but I'm gonna go with
the bliz I mean I've never been on a
blind date
like literally or otherwise you know so
I'm a little and by little I mean a lot
nervous um also really excited do you
want to see each other or do you want to
see each other later like right now
right now hi hi we did that hug and the
hug was I was like oh my gosh there's a
little hard at first because it's like
very us so much at one moment this is
exciting this is moving away now and
then I'm moving back you have your socks
by the way oh thanks and so I took a
step back to hopefully give her that
space you could also show me the moves
that you have when it comes to
when it comes to climbing climbing yes
hopefully after this we can exchange
contact information if she's down of
course it's all about if she's willing
because I would love to figure out if
there is chemistry you know based on
just traversing
[Music]
you