I'm Alexa nice to meet you just like
Amazon huh I get that so often Alexa
yeah
like Amazon you got it I'm just playing
it's like that thing I can buy yo Alexa
flavor this all I'm nervous
if I'm being honest I feel like I will
yes I'm pretty good about picking up
inflections of like voices and
everything and I can tell if somebody's
being honest with me or not by their
voice so I feel like I'll do really well
with that
[Music]
what's your name
imma go what's yours I'm Alexa nice to
meet you nice to meet you
that's really cute names oh thank you
okay I'm 18 how are you I'm 23 okay do
you have any goals in the future
ah yes one of my biggest goals right now
is to be able to have enough money to
buy my mom her own house I would love
that
my name is Alexa oh wow that's my mom's
name really no no oh are you in school
yes I'm studying to either be a marine
biologist or a psychologist where do you
go
I go to Biola it's a Christian College
that's cool so you're Christian yes very
much so we're just a little bit very
much so so are you like working are you
going to school or something
um I'm working on getting work yeah so
tell me a little about yourself what do
you what do you do right now I'm a
full-time student okay I love all the
arts so painting photography stuff like
that how about you I I'm actually really
into airplanes
I'd say photography I do a little bit of
camera shoots and stuff like that
so I guess we have something in common
here yeah what's good hi my name is
Tyler I'm gonna ask you a question
really quick this is really important if
we went to Yogurtland would you put
chocolate on your yogurt or fruit
because that's like
important to me I put both okay you're
already a freak I can tell this is crazy
how are you I'm awesome okay you can
tell your voice you sound like really
energetic yeah I'm super outgoing and
everything oh goodness gracious I'm
gonna have to get rid of JD because I
just didn't feel like a connection there
but the one after Caleb also just didn't
really feel like a straight connection
there
[Music]
I'd say my ideal date would be I don't
wanna be too cliche but long walks on
the beach but also I always wanted to go
on a ferris wheel with one beautiful
girl mine would be probably driving
around and Polly ended up on the beach
pretend I know about constellations and
stuff so I'm gonna tell you straight off
the bat like I suck at planning do you
know like those retro like Dining's yes
like with the colors and the lights and
stuff uh-huh I think they'll be really
good okay okay all right so so bear with
me here I put a lot of thought into this
okay so so I'm working on getting my
pilot's license I'm thinking you and me
we go we go we hop into a little private
plane at the airport right we take it we
fly up the coast of California and you
know there's little islands off the
coast right we could go and kind of fly
over to one of the little islands
obviously you're in a photography you
bring your camera get some nice shots we
definitely need to share memes with each
other because my main game is crazy so
like if you don't have good taste and
means we can't be a thing like this is
not gonna work Oh trust me I have an
entire folder I don't know laughter I
think laughter is really really cool I
like to do like impressions and stuff
like that so like by Penta that's soaked
oh my gosh what is your name all right
so I'm gonna have to get her no let's
see let me go initially I felt kind of a
connection but after that I just kind of
it kind of went away a little bit and
then whoever the third person was and
it's cuz initially he just immediately
said he was bad at planning and I like
someone who's really good at planning
and stuff like that cuz I love being
creative and all that kind of stuff so I
[Music]
think for me personally if someone's not
vocal if you're on a date or whatever
explaining who you really are or how you
feel it goes very far in a relationship
I would say was it some Christian like
you know excessive drinking or like
smoking um like a little bit's fine like
if it's excess yeah a little bit hard
the smoking and drinking thing you know
I wouldn't want to date someone who's
he's a partier you know
weekend that's just not really my scene
let's go Z I feel like I need someone
who can like twerk you know like that's
what I want I want even if you can't do
it that way I want you to try like want
someone we can have fun I want to
continue from where we last meant off
what would you say is like a really big
talent of yours I guess I can sing but
like I'm not very confident with it oh
cool I mean I'm not like horrible but I
haven't really been public about it I
guess hook you up
um okay first one's gonna have to be
Tyler he was talking about twerking and
everything I haven't tried it so I don't
know if I can do it but he also didn't
seem like he was very serious about a
relationship and then I'm gonna have to
uh Caleb no particular reason just
wasn't really feeling it anymore I guess
I want to be able to say that I can own
a house but hopefully by the time I'm 30
you know have my family set how many
kids do you want
hopefully by like a boy and a girl to be
honest and then maybe like three or four
dogs so yeah I'm totally with that oh
yeah and I want the boy to be a little
older than the girl see I want it the
other way around bully the boy oh my god
for me something that's really important
I'm trying to become a pilot and I
joined the Navy to try and achieve that
goal and I'm still working there and
that's something I feel like from my
partner I want them to be the same
mentality that I'm and you can't be in a
relationship where one person is
motivated right and the other person is
doesn't really care I've got a lot so
I'm a musician actor but I'm also
studying political science and I want to
be President of the United States so
obviously you know being with somebody
that's like committed but also like
supportive and I can learn a lot from
them that that really means a lot to me
what about you I'm leaning towards
psychologists so I can help teens with
mental disorders
everything like that there's a lot of I
think genuine connection you really like
care about people you know because then
you can look beyond where they are and
like see them for who they truly can't
be and I think that's super special yeah
I'm cutting one okay um I'm just gonna
have to cut off Sam the vibe that I'm
getting just isn't as strong as the
other two that I've been getting so no
prompt here so I want to know a little
bit about you tell me about yourself
what you're Abhi's I like to dance
wait wait wait stop there stop there
dance are we talking like salsa or
breakdancing here cuz I'm okay with both
more so hip hop than anything okay
that's cool what else do you like so you
like dance you like to sing I was
singing on my way here to every Sunday
that's awesome that's cool but what
about photography I'm kind of curious
about that do you like portraits
landscapes um my main focus I guess you
could say is portrait um I love shooting
animals as well like wildlife yeah you
love taking a photo on me then
haha so what's the hardest thing that
you've ever been through and how did you
get through it and how did it affect who
you are uniquely today one of the
hardest things I've had to go through
was probably middle school beginning of
high school because I struggled with a
lot of depression and self-confidence
I've overcame it by like I'm starting to
love myself I'm super outgoing and I
help people so helping people yeah yeah
yeah that's amazing I would definitely
say like you have to embrace who you are
because it's unique and what you bring
to the world is different than any other
person in the other individual
and it makes you who you are today you
know yeah I think I have a decision all
right so I'm gonna have to go with
Joseph that last question that he asked
me it shows me that he can actually get
really deep when he needs to be and
that's the kind of stuff that I'm
looking for like I want someone who I
can have a ton of fun with but I can
also be super serious with when the time
comes so that kind of said it over the
bar and that's what I'm looking for
so
[Music]
I'm definitely more used to like talking
to people like face-to-face and being
more real so solo we're in a nutshell
yeah as what is all about yeah I'm good
are you oh well oh no well I didn't
really envision you looking like
anything but I'm really happy you're
cute thank you thank you and yeah I know
this kind of goes somewhere I guess well
I got a girl
what Oh what thing I was really good
you're awesome though
wait dude this just happen dang I do I
love the only one that does though here
why are you guys really yeah oh dang I
told my girlfriend like all about it and
everything and she said it's solving a
cool
[Applause]
I thought it was like a prank on me I
was like okay like and then everyone
else was like I surprises me and I was
like guess not
that is weird because I totally went
into this thinking that I was gonna end
up with somebody who was single and like
looking but I mean I'm not hurt or
anything I'm just kind of confused as to
why he was here but I mean it's whatever
I'm happy he has a girlfriend I guess
cuz he's he's actually a genuinely like
really cool person and he had everything
that I was looking for so he must have
had everything that she was looking for
so I hope that they're happy and
everything
[Music]