excuse me hey real quick starting a
conversation with a beautiful woman can
be very frustrating and even terrifying
for a lot of guys but it's actually a
whole lot easier than you think if you
keep the following three things in mind
and all the opening lines that I'm about
to give you have all been 100% tested to
be tried and true in giving you the best
reactions from women I'm an artisan from
the attractive man and I'm going to show
you how to start a conversation with a
beautiful woman
we've done all the testing we know what
works when you start applying the
following three techniques to all of
your interactions with women I guarantee
your results will skyrocket number one
approach within three seconds when you
see a woman that you want to talk to
make sure to start approaching her
within three seconds from the time that
you take that first step no more than
three seconds should go by do this no
matter what because it short circuits
your brain's ability to come up with
excuses and which you know a lot of
excuses can come up I'm sure you know
that I know that they come up from me
too and it also just conditions you to
take action it's like you see beautiful
woman and within three seconds you take
that step towards her instead of doing
what most guys do see beautiful woman
and think about it analyze it and
eventually tuck themself out of it it
also conveys confidence when you walk up
to her right away which is a really
important attraction trigger for women
I'm sure you know that so next time you
see a beautiful woman that you want to
approach count to three and when you get
to the number three start walking
towards her okay take a step and then
taking another step even if you bail
before you get to her cuz maybe her
boyfriend shows up or she jumps onto a
bus or maybe you just chickened out okay
that's still a success because you're
training your mind and your body to take
action you're conditioning yourself to
every time you see a beautiful woman
that you just go if you do that fifty or
a hundred times eventually you're that's
going to be a habit you're gonna see
beautiful women and just be compelled to
walk towards them and that's a pretty
good habit to have number two open
strong coming in with a good opening
line can start the interaction off on
the right foot so it's really important
now for fun flirty opening lines that
get her laughing are great however
there's no problem with just keeping it
simple especially if you don't know what
to say or you're feeling a little bit
tongue-tied here are some examples of
some great opening lines I really like
banter openers because they're a fun
flirty way to start an interaction going
especially in the nighttime environment
like a bar lounge or club or part
or maybe even a concert hey have you
noticed that you and I are like the
hottest people in this entire place it's
true so I figured we have to at least
meet
[Music]
hey are you shy or something because
I've been here for like 25 minutes and
you haven't come and said hi to me yet
or buy me a drink or anything so you
must be shy because people are there to
have a good time so if you can get the
girls bantering back and forth and
laughing and being playful then of
course it's really good now my favorite
way to start a conversation especially
during the daytime is to use a direct
opener because people are busy so using
something indirect beating around the
bush a it doesn't show any attractive
qualities and B it wastes a lot of time
so I like to just show my intent and my
interest right away because that shows
confidence it shows that I must believe
that this girl is also attracted to me
and it can create as long as you do it
the right way it can create sexual
tension so for example I might say
something like hi I just saw you here
and I thought you
the matter
Shawny another favorite of mine is the
intro opener which is where you just
introduce yourself it works really well
at nighttime at bars parties and meetup
groups or you know any type of social
gathering really where you just
introduce yourself and that shows a lot
of confidence it shows that you don't
need a reason or an excuse to go talk to
somebody
hi I don't believe we've met yet I'm
Matt make sure to say that confidently
with strong eye contact and a warm smile
now feel free to modify these openers
based on the situation or the you know
the type of girls you're approaching or
your individual mood or your own vibe
whatever what's most important is to
keep in mind that ninety-three percent
of communication is nonverbal therefore
your body language and how you actually
deliver you know your opening statement
is gonna matter a lot more than the
actual words you say this is exactly
what I mean by that and to learn how to
spark sexual tension immediately which
is extremely powerful then make sure to
watch my YouTube video on how to spark
sexual tension immediately and there's a
link to it down in the description
number three don't get caught up on the
opener remember like I said the actual
words that you say when you first
approached her really aren't all that
important compared to the overall vibe
that you're giving off later on when
you're a little bit more advanced it's
nice to come back and kind of practice
some of these different types of openers
but in the beginning when you're first
starting off
keep it simple man it's totally fine to
just say whatever is on your mind
because that will get you in the habit
of going for it instead of always
second-guessing yourself and developing
that habit will get you more women than
any pickup line ever could now of course
there's other ways to start
conversations with women as well such as
being indirect or using an observation
something you see about her or a
situation something in the environment
the problem with those is it's harder to
keep the conversation going because she
doesn't know the real reason that you're
talking to her which is probably because
you're attracted to her so use the
examples that I gave you in this video
or something similar especially during
the daytime be direct don't be afraid to
show your inch
right away and of course like I said it
all depends on how you do it there's a
needy supplicating way to do it that's
gonna repel women and then there's a
really badass more attractive way to do
it that's gonna build sexual tension
right away
and of course it's gonna work much
better what's key is that after you show
interest in her you slightly take it
away by challenging her if you show too
much interest too soon it seems needy
and it pushes her away you have to also
be a challenge so to show you how to be
more of a challenge and get women to
actually start chasing you I created a
video called how to get women to chase
you and there's a link down in the
description and also on the right side
of the screen so go ahead and click that
right now and watch that video make sure
to also subscribe to this channel for
more dating tips and click that Bell
icon or notifications also if you're
interested in live coaching if you want
us to take you in feel and show you
exactly how to meet an attractive and
tracked women then check out our
bootcamp schedule and also schedule
yourself a free consultation with us my
name is matt artisan from the attractive
man and i'll see you in the next video
[Music]