what if I told you that height money or
status isn't the only way to win over a
girl in fact there are five key
questions that you can ask her that will
set you apart from every other guy out
there
I'm Renee slansky for the attractive man
team and in this video I'm going to
reveal to you the five top questions to
ask a woman on a first date that will be
begging her for you to take her on a
second one it's my job as a dating and
relationship coach to help you come
across as the most confident and
desirable man you can be so if you want
to know how to do that make sure you
subscribe to our YouTube channel and
give us a big thumbs up all right men it
is time to beat the rest of the pack and
jump up on top and be the alpha dog with
women and if you want to know that and
all you need to do is ask her these five
simple questions are you ready let's
jump in number five are you okay
are you comfortable or would you like to
go somewhere else
the first thing a woman will be
instinctively doing is actually working
out if she feels comfortable in your
presence literally guys within the first
five minutes we are asking ourselves two
questions the first question is am i
attracted to you and the second question
is do I feel safe around you as the
weaker sex we want to make sure that as
soon as we go on a date that we feel
that we can trust you to protect us and
make us feel at ease this is why it is
so incredibly important to just ask her
that don't leave it up to getting an
Oscar does she feel comfortable in that
environment if there's too many men
there does she feel intimidated by the
amount of men there is she cold all
these little things that you can
actually ask her will help her put her
mind to ease that you actually care
about the way that she feels that you
care about her safety and that you
actually want to do something about it
to make it a memorable and nice date for
her guys be the hero from the first date
take control and actually show her that
you're able to step in and make first
safety and security your number one
priority and not only that asking her if
she feels cold or hot gives you an
opportunity to take
you'll Jack it off and actually put it
around her shoulders and it makes you
come across looking like a gentleman
which is basically what we want to know
number four can you let me know as soon
as you get home safe but this one is one
that will have you in the good books
with her why because it shows that you
are once again concerned about her
safety that you were following up after
the day and that you genuinely care
whether or not she actually did arrive
home safe not only that it actually
makes us feel like we are a damsel in
distress and you're the hero
that cares about us and wants to protect
us it makes us feel incredibly feminine
which is what we want to feel when we're
on a date we want to know that we can go
on a date with a guy and actually know
that if anything happened he would step
in and rescue us number three where do
you see yourself in five years okay this
is a great question because what it does
is two things firstly it actually gives
you an indication whether or not this
girl is on the same page as you
because remember going on a date isn't
just about impressing her you want to
make sure that you're actually
impressing a woman that you know you
want to invest into you because she
actually wants the same things as you
secondly it also communicates to her
that you are a future thinker you're a
man with a plan and that plan could
possibly include her hence why you asked
her that question trust me guys before
we've even met you have already decided
if you're going to be our future husband
and what our children are going to look
like this is how we work within the
first 10 to 30 minutes of getting to
know you we are racing through all these
scenarios in our head which includes you
to work out if we want to be attracted
to you keep dating you so if you can
actually put our mind to ease in some
sort of way by asking this key question
what it does is it gets us excited
because in our mind we think well hang
on a second he is a man that's asking me
this question
maybe it's because he is a man that is
actually serious about finding a
relationship now I know that we as women
jump into the future and it's hence why
I coach women to stay in the present but
if you can use this to your advantage by
talking about the future it gets Ramin
even more curious and wanting you even
more number two have you ever been
hold that you look like insert beautiful
celebrity now this is a little bit
tricky the last thing you want to do is
go and compare her to someone that she
looks absolutely nothing like don't go
and say that she looks like Beyonce if
she is clearly Asian or on the flip side
don't go and compare it to some sort of
celebrity that was really kind of trashy
no one was to be compared to Britney
back in 2007 this is about sending her a
compliment now if you can't actually
find somebody's famous or somebody of a
really sort of high status that she
would actually be flattered by then what
you need to do is you need to pick out a
small detail and compliment her on that
for example have you ever been told that
your smile is actually really sunny or
have you ever been told that your eyes
change color in different lights guys
hands down if you say those sort of
things to her and actually asked her if
she's ever noticed what it does is you
send the signal that you're a noticing
something special about her and B that
you're assuming that she doesn't know
that so what you'll do is you'll
actually feel really kind of beautiful
and special and she'll also feel really
humbled by your compliment and number
one are you a family type of girl don't
okay this is a question that is going to
hit her right in the fields why because
a man who asked about family is a man
who probably wants to get married is a
man who probably must have children
equals a man that is jackpot that is how
they think guys honestly so if you're
able to talk about her family her
desires for a family and also listen to
what it is that she says you're going to
come across as somebody who's really
sincere someone that is forward-thinking
and future planning and it also means
that you're probably going to have
really genuine qualities that make
someone that is a family guy a great guy
in general now chances are if you're
dating at a certain age then children
are going to come up at some point
whether she's got children you've got
children or neither of you do this isn't
about lying and pretending that you want
children there are certain ways to
actually talk about things but still
keep her interest for example if you
know that you're not really wanting to
start a family with someone if she asked
you are you wanting to have
children you might want to say I'm
pretty sure that I don't want to have
children because I know that the right
woman will be enough for me or if you
actually do eventually want to have
children then what you can do is you can
really kind of draw her in by saying
yeah I know that I want to have children
one day
but I think I'll know for sure when it's
with the right sort of girl
you're basically planting seeds of Hope
into her brain that yes it is a
possibility that you want to be a part
of her future or that she's going to be
a part of yours and so that is really
going to get her going into overdrive of
actually starting to envision that
herself
guys these are just five simple
questions that you can ask her to get
her court but if you're someone that
really struggles with conversation then
what I want you to do is download a
completely free conversation cheat sheet
it is full of ways to be able to talk to
women in such a way that you do come
across as a confident man
everything from conversation starters to
knowing how to flirt and have that fun
vibe to escalating it and also to making
sure that you never run out of things to
say all you need to do to get that is
simply click on the image on the screen
or click the link in our buyer and that
will go straight to your inbox now what
I want you to do is I want you to tell
me some of the questions that you have
asked women on a first date that you
really felt works for you and got her
hooked why because Sharon is carrying
and we're a community here and we want
to make sure that we don't leave any
bros out of the code alright guys I
really slansky for the attractive man
team until next time bye for now
[Music]