Have you ever picked up guys yourself?
Yes,
I have
We gathered a group of 20 people to participate in a blind date
They each chose one person out of the line-up
Blindest Date
I chose him
I chose him because
I have a pretty big personality
I’m really outgoing and bubbly
so I want someone who can ground me
He seems calm and rational
so I chose him.
Hi
You seemed liked you have a calm personality
and I wanted to meet someone who is the opposite from me, so I chose you
Thank you
Chooser: answers the given questions
Chosen: if the chooser’s answer is not the answer he’s looking for, the lights go off
[Preference]
[Cooking vs. Eating out]
I’m answering, right?
Yes
I prefer cooking
so you want me to
eat out?
I think that it’s great to
cook and eat at home
and if you were to cook for me, I’d love to return the favor
but since I’m a terrible cook
It’d be better to
- eat out?
- eat at a restaurant, yeah
let’s eat good food.
you can just do the dishes
At home?
can somebody please turn the lights off?
[Stay-at-home Dates vs. Going Out]
Dates at home.
Do you also like dates at home
Or are you completely against it?
I think I have this thing where
going to someone else’s home
might be an invasion of privacy
and homes should be kept private especially in the beginning of a relationship
so I chose going out for dates
Even if it’s your girlfriend’s place?
Yeah
and same goes for my place
I’m a bit opposed to
frequent visits at home
but despite that, I think
the only person who I’m close enough to invite over to my place
besides my best friends, is my boyfriend
Dates at home are really fun,
If you’re at a bar with a group of friends, and they want to pick up another group of guys to drink with,
would you actively participate?
I’d actively participate.
Isn’t that a group activity?
Why should only one person do the pick-up while others hide in the back?
I thought the same
To be honest, I’ve never done anything like that,
Or blind dates, group blind dates, I’ve never been on one.
So I can only imagine but
I like people who can have fun in those situations
Whatever it may be
If there’s someone you like, you go for him
If you don’t like that person, you leave
I like women who
are able to do that
Have you picked up guys yourself?
Uh, yes I have
I saw someone who matched my type so closely
I get red very easily, even just by a sip
So I pretended to be drunk and I asked him to play darts with me
Did you have fun playing darts?
I mean, my goal wasn’t to win the darts game..
It was like, ‘I’m going to win you over,’ huh?
Okay
[Halfway Point]
what if he reads my lips?
I’m gonna talk like this
He’s a bit different in real life, as to what I imagined he’d be like before meeting
He’s even better looking in person
and I was surprised because he said he’s never been set up on a blind date or picked up girls at a bar
her first impression
as soon as I saw her,
she looked like a very smiley version of Suzy
She’s very good looking,
very friendly
She’s the type to command the room
Confident
I find her attractive
[Values]
Maintaining your virginity before marriage is important vs. not
virginity..
no,
Not important
Why did you want
me to say that virginity is
- not important?
- yeah
usually ‘virginity’ seems like a responsibility given only to women
I don’t think it’s important at all
I actually think it’s better to experience more relationships
and I like women who’ve learned from those experiences
I think past experiences in love and passion are good influence for us today
Ah, based on those experiences,
We’re able to have a mature relationship
Mature…
Can I just say it?
We’re all adults here
You’re right
Okay, I’m going to say it with confidence
For mature sex
Right
Right, because sex is only between boyfriend and girlfriend.
And you know that saying, if you just save it, it just goes to shit
Right, because you don’t know what you like
So you do know a lot about yourself.
Yeah, I think I know very well.
I have something I wanna say, but I’ll just stop here.
[I take a lot of interest in gender issues vs. I do not]
If it’s ‘a lot of interest’ versus not,
I think I’m more ‘not’.
Not a lot, no.
How do you determine whether someone takes a lot of interest?
For me, the news articles,
When there are issues like women’s protests, I usually look up articles from each news source
Even if it’s not to this extent,
I’d say having awareness of the problem
Being able to examine different POVs to an issue?
Being aware of different points of view?
It’s such a current issue that recently it becomes the subject of conversation
Do you not take much interest in the issue?
Just to the extent of reading the news when I see it come up?
I don’t actively seek news articles
When you hear something like ‘what’s wrong with men?’ where do you tend to side?
I hate phrases like ‘men should be like this’
Or ‘women should be like this’
I just focus on the person.
So there isn’t much different between men and women besides the biological?
Besides the stereotypes
And rigid prejudices,
I don’t think there’s much difference
Between men and women besides those.
[Work is more important than family. Yes or No?]
No
I think family is more impotant.
you cold-hearted man
I think,
I don’t want there to be career breaks (for my significant other)
I don’t want her to give up a part of her life for children
I prefer someone who places her own life as a priority
Even for someone who dates me and maybe we end up getting married,
I want that person to place herself first, before me
And that’s the same for me
And it goes the same way for me
I’ll also always place myself first
Over the other person.
I want to have a relationship where we go together in that way.
I know that I’m the type of person to focus more on the family
when I have a family of my own, so I’d probably focus more on the home
So I really shouldn’t get married
[Depending on the circumstance, teachers can physically punish students]
Nope.
They shouldn’t
Don’t teachers have the right to educate students?
And
Don’t some parents spank their children when they discipline?
These were the two thoughts that came to mind
And you could say that the parents transferred the right to discipline to the teacher
So in that sense, wouldn’t it be possible?
I also grew up in a generation where physical discipline was possible,
And my parents raised me very strictly,
But I still think that teachers cannot beat students.
Hm so if,
Let me give you a hypothetical
Let’s say at school, a student curses at the teacher
And ends up slapping the teacher’s face
In that situation,
Would ‘spank/hit the student’
Not be one of the possible choices of action?
No, it is not.
If I were in that situation, I would just leave the scene
Or leave the evidence
And solve it by law
I would never, do the same
I wouldn’t go into physical violence
Let’s say, what if there was a clause in the school’s regulation that
Physical punishment can be given in certain circumstances,
Would you say that’s wrong, too?
No, not in that case.
The parents who sent their kids to that school would’ve seen and agreed to those regulations
And it's a matter between a group that shares the same values,
So I’m not in the place to say
Whether that’s right or wrong.
[Final Decision]
[Do you want another date? Send O or X]
How was it for you today?
It’s my first blind date, ever
I felt kind of nervous
for the first time in a while
I enjoyed it
I just,
I feel like I didn’t speak very eloquently today
I kinda feel like an idiot
Probably gonna go laugh/cry in the corner when I get home today
So yeah.. but
It was fun!
Unlike somebody over here,
I’ve been on a blind date before, so.
[If you sent an X, your light will turn off]