hey it's Matt artisan and in this
training video you're gonna discover the
most powerful most effective opener of
all time that works in nearly any
situation to trigger deep sexual
attraction instantly without coming off
weird or needy or gimmicky or like some
kind of cheesy pickup artist now when
you use this magic sentence that I'm
about to share with you I guarantee you
you'll stay out of the friendzone it's
literally impossible to fall into the
friend zone when you say this now pay
attention to all the techniques because
they are all really really powerful but
make sure you pay attention to the last
technique that I share with you because
that's the one that's responsible for
nearly all of my success now I know that
triggering attraction instantly might
sound a little bit unbelievable heck I
didn't believe it either I thought
there's no way you could trigger
attraction instantly in like three
seconds because I wasn't able to attract
women in three hours
I wasn't always one of the best dating
and attraction experts
I used to flat out suck with women it's
probably worse than you are right now
watching this video I remember one time
that my best friend introduced me to a
group of women I didn't have to cold
approach them he introduced me and
within a few seconds just like it was
like every time I spoke something awful
would come out of my mouth
it was just like verbal garbage in just
a few seconds I said something so stupid
that they all scattered I remember
another time me and that same best
friend we're at the mall and we wanted
to meet girls and there was a girl that
I had my eye on but I couldn't build up
the courage to approach her I just
couldn't do it I was like frozen I felt
paralyzed maybe you can relate and then
lo and behold she starts walking towards
me I'm thinking oh crap what do I do
she was probably gonna ask me for
directions or something like that maybe
he asked me where Starbucks is I don't
know I never even had the opportunity to
find out because before she actually
approached
before she got all the way to me I
looked the other way and I altered I
just bolted down the escalator and I
don't know I felt so pathetic I felt
weak
my best friend Jason he didn't make it
any better he he was laughing at me you
know I can look back at the situation
now and it's kind of funny but at the
time I remember how awful it felt and
it's because I had no idea how to
approach I didn't know what to say I
didn't know how to say it and I just
felt weak and powerless and it's a
pretty crappy feeling so in this video
I'm going to show you how to overcome
all that now before we get into the
three simple steps or techniques that
are literally going to skyrocket your
results you need to understand this one
fundamental truth that emotions are
contagious that's right the way you feel
inside is projected outward and other
people unconsciously pick up on that
think about this have you ever seen
somebody even just out of the corner of
your eye you might not even be looking
at them and they could be a complete
stranger way off in the distance but you
see them yawn and then all of a sudden
you start feeling tired or maybe you're
feeling a little down you're not in the
best mood but then your buddy comes in
with some great news he's excited he's
smiling he's happy and all of a sudden
your mood just elevates and you start
smiling and you don't even know what
he's happy about you have no idea but
you start feeling much better or it
could be the opposite maybe you're in a
great mood and somebody else is in a bad
mood and they suck you down to the their
level the point is you must understand
that how you feel internally is
projected outward and other people pick
up on that unconsciously so if you want
to get a girl to desire you and want you
instantly I'm talking about within
seconds of meeting her there's three
crucial things that you have to do so
imagine this scenario you're walking
down the street and you see a beautiful
girl walk out of the Starbucks and
catches your eye and your jaw just drops
because she's absolutely stunning she's
like your perfect type what do you do
what do you say to trigger attraction
how do you get her to like you how do
you get her invested how do you make her
watch you because you don't know you may
not be her typical type that's okay you
can still get her you can still win her
over you can still attract her and she
can be yours but you have to do these
three crucial things number one you have
to own your space if you walk up to her
or let's say it's a group and you're
hesitant because you're not sure if
they're gonna like you yet you're not
sure if they're gonna accept you to be a
part of their group if you walk up there
with that type of hesitation that's
gonna kill attraction before there even
was any attraction that's gonna kill it
because here's the deal you're if you
walk up to them looking for approval
looking to see whether this is okay or
not 9 out of 10 times it's not gonna be
okay
there because they're looking at you to
see how they should react to and I used
to be guilty of this I used to walk up
to a group of girls and if they gave me
a good response then I'd be like all
right yes I'm in I'd feel good but if
they gave me a bad response or even if
they just looked at me a little funny
like huh who's this guy then I could
start feeling this almost pain in the
pit of my stomach and I started cowering
unconsciously because I felt like Oh am
i doing something wrong they don't want
me here I should leave and I just wanted
to get out of there as soon as possible
oftentimes I force myself to stay in
just to learn which is really good I did
learn a lot that way but I would just
want to leave as soon as possible and
then sometimes you'd go it would it
would finally they would realize okay
this guy's not a total weirdo and it
would go okay thankfully it's not like
that anymore I worked on this and how
you do that is you have to feel good
about yourself internally you have to
feel like you are supposed to be there
like they're your best friends yes I
know they're complete strangers but you
need to walk up to them like you are
supposed to be there
like you are meant to be there because
when they see that because they're
looking at you to determine how they
should react then they're gonna say okay
this guy is cool he's confident he's
acting like he's supposed to be there
therefore I guess he's supposed to be
here talking to us now oftentimes girls
will give you a really weird face when
you first approach them whether it's
daytime or nighttime doesn't matter I
see this all the time I call it the what
the fuck face because they're looking at
you like like that like what the heck
what the fuck what is this guy gonna say
cuz they don't know you they don't know
how to react yet they're gauging your
reaction how you interact to decide how
they should react so during that phase
the first few seconds depends on the
situation some girls right when you
approach they're gonna be like hey
what's up and they're not gonna give you
that face other girls are gonna give you
that face for a few seconds and other
girls give it to you for a minute and
it's harsh they're just like huh
sometimes are folding their arms or just
judging you so what you got to just be
cool and just go with it and just own it
because if they can see that they know
what they're doing they know they're
kind of like just by giving you that
face they're challenging you but when
you can own your presence and own your
space and just say yeah I'm here I'm
gonna talk to you I'm gonna say what I
have to say I don't really care about
your reaction you can like it you can
dislike it it doesn't matter to me I'm
gonna do it either way when you have
that type of energy and that's what
you're exuding and it's gonna work most
of the time you're always gonna run it
and you know once in a while you run
into that girl if you're just not into
anything and she's just having a bad
night but for the majority the vast
majority of women just by owning your
space whatever it is that you're gonna
say we're not even talking about what to
say yet but just by owning your space
they will accept you and the attraction
starts to build because they see you as
a confident man so this also has to do
with your posture to some degree you
can't be slouching over you need to
stand there
like a powerful man standing as tall as
you can and you need to be close to them
if you are if it's a daytime situation
and you're standing more than arm's
distance apart then it seems like you're
afraid of her like you're afraid to get
close to her now I'm not saying you need
to be right up in her face because that
can be pretty weird as well especially
in that type of daytime scenario you
need to be about arms distance away or
even slightly closer invading her
personal space
just slightly well what I see students
do all the time
first when they first start learning
this on our boot camps is they're way
too far away and they seem like they're
scared of her and when she feels that
like oh this guy's afraid of me it's not
logical she doesn't consciously think
that but it's unconscious there cannot
be attraction if she thinks that you are
afraid of her so you need to walk up to
her like you know her like you're like
you're somebody that's already in her
life and then she will accept you
because she'll feel that she'll feel
that you're comfortable with her you're
comfortable talking to her complete
stranger that will make her feel
comfortable
on the flipside if you're completely
uncomfortable and you're looking down
and you're fidgeting and you're far away
from her she's gonna feel uncomfortable
because emotions are contagious she's
gonna feel uncomfortable and there's not
gonna be any attraction so just to recap
own your space stand close about arm's
distance away from her or even slightly
closer I mean like an inch or two closer
can work really well for a daytime
scenario at a nighttime scenario even
closer than that because it's loud it's
okay to be a lot closer to people I'm in
a club even more so because it's really
really loud you might have to be up on
her and your cheek might touch her cheek
because you have to speak in her ear
because it's so loud in that type of
environment which is one benefit of
clubs it's kind of kind of is a bad
thing because it's so loud you can't do
a lot of talking but the good thing is
you can get really close and build that
and break that physical barrier and
build that physical connection very
quickly in those type environments so
you have to remember to accommodate
change your you know your approach a
little bit per the environment so own
your space get close stand up and act
like you are supposed to be there this
next technique can literally make or
break your approach it's called the look
and it's based on how you feel
internally yes it has to do with eye
contact and having good eye contact
strong eye contact not looking away
because if you look away you kill the
cute you killed the tension for example
if I say hey you're really cute right it
looks awful
so yes it's based on eye contact and
maintaining that strong eye contact but
it's much more than that
it's very very subtle but this subtle
difference makes a huge impact and it's
gonna make her literally start getting
aroused for you no matter what the
situation even if you're in a bookstore
or somewhere that's completely not a
sexual environment you do this for her
she will start giving a tingle in all
the right places
trust me so it's called the look because
what you're doing is you're expressing
your desire for her through your eyes
and through your facial expressions
you're allowing yourself to just feel
certain emotions whatever natural
emotions you feel towards a beautiful
woman when you see her and allowing
yourself through your body language
through your tonality and through your
facial expressions and more so your eye
contact allowing yourself to communicate
how you feel towards or what you're
feeling inside internally so first of
all you can't try to hide it a lot of
times we're taught seemingly it seems
like at a very young age to hide our
emotions hide what we're feeling
especially for aroused if we feel
aroused towards a woman that we
shouldn't express it because that's
weird that's creepy and I agree to an
extent if you're going up to a woman and
you're like yeah I want you yeah I want
to fuck you and you say that or even if
it you're not saying that but you're
expressing it through your body language
like hey baby what's up like a cat call
you know you know the stereotypical
construction worker type thing you
that's not gonna work that's creepy
that's weird that's not what I'm talking
about I'm talking about allowing
yourself to feel whatever it is that
you're feeling let's call it desire and
expressing that desire to her
not necessarily verbally it can be
completely unbearable it's nonverbal
it's through your tonality your eye
contact which I call the look and
through your just you your your body
language so if you rush through the
approach this isn't gonna work because
you're not allowing yourself to feel
anything you have to take your time you
have to pause so the way you're gonna
look at her you're gonna look at her
with desire but I want you to think a
very specific thought I want you to
think how you are gonna give this woman
the utmost sexual satisfaction the
utmost sexual pleasure the best sex of
her life if she's so lucky if she's so
lucky to win you over that's what I want
you to think when you think that you
start exuding sexuality you start you're
not hiding your sexual interest in her
you're not hiding your desire your
showing your desire towards her without
hiding him but it's not again it's not
this needy desire it's not saying I want
you so much
I need you I need to have sex with you
as soon as possible no you're saying I
would give you the most sexual
satisfaction if you are so lucky you're
communicating that through your eyes and
it's going to be communicated through
other things your body language your
tonality your facial expressions but
right now we're focusing on the eyes
you're looking at her with desire so
it's a very strong gaze but it's not
bug-eyed its softening your gaze subtly
looking at her like you have a secret
and of course the secret is you're gonna
rock her world so it's gonna be a little
bit of a smirk you're not gonna have
this huge smile on your face like yeah
yeah we're gonna have sex now you don't
know that yet
to meet your standards as well but you
have this secret like you have a gift to
give her but you're not gonna tell her
what it is yet that's gonna give you
this sly devilish smirk so again how to
accomplish this look you don't want to
try to manufacture it artificially and
and try to make the perfect smirk and
the perfect squinting and all that now
all you need to do is allow yourself to
feel what it is that you would feel
naturally if you're talking to a
beautiful woman right your tonality
would lower a little bit if you're
taking your time allow yourself to feel
sexy allow yourself to express your
desire towards her and allow yourself to
feel and think that you would give her
the utmost sexual satisfaction if she
was so lucky so let's go ahead and look
at an example right now so let's start
with the approach first this is how most
guys do it that makes her smile it can
work it can definitely get you a date
but it's not nearly as powerful so this
is what most guys do they come off very
nice so they'll see a beautiful woman
I'll come up to her there'll be about
this far away first of all they'll be
far away and they'll say hi I just saw
you here and I thought you were really
cute I just wanted to say hi right seems
seems good seems like that would work
and it can work like I said but watch
the difference okay see a beautiful
woman get a little bit closer and say
hey real quick this is totally random
aiyah I just was walking by and I just
saw you and I had to tell you that you
are absolutely adorable do you guys see
the difference so so far we've talked
about how to approach having look how to
showcase your desire how to stand how to
own your space now let's talk about the
actual words to say so this technique is
called being direct versus being
indirect which is obviously the opposite
so be direct simply means you're telling
her why you're approaching her you're
being honest you're being sincere
you're being powerful you're not being
apologetic about why you want to talk to
her you're owning the fact that you like
her or at least that you're attracted to
her you don't know if you like her yet
you don't know her but you're owning the
fact that you're attracted to her your
only your manliness being indirect would
be the opposite it would be beating
around the bush not telling her why
you're talking to her or giving her some
fake reason to talk to her something
you're probably not even interested in
like asking her some kind of question
that you just don't care about the
answer
that would be indirect and that shows
that you're not honest that you have to
hide your intentions and really that
you're just a weak man who can't own his
masculinity so obviously that's not
gonna work as well can it work
absolutely it can work but if the reason
you're walking up towards her is because
you're attracted to her then tell her
that don't use some weird lame excuse
now if she's right next to you already
and you don't actually have to approach
her she's already there just maybe
you're at a bar and she's happened to be
standing next to you and you use some
other reason to approach that's totally
cool but if you're gonna walk up to her
make it effort towards her which I
recommend you do that all the time
because it shows that you're bold it
shows that you're confident when you
approach in a direct manner it shows
that you're honest that you don't need
to hide your attention that you're a
true man so obviously those qualities
are really good very attractive so it
can build attraction very very quickly
instantly she knows oh you're a real man
you're not hiding your intentions you're
like Here I am
I'm attracted to you let's talk that's
very powerful when you incorporate the
look and having a very powerful presence
and only in your space then you are
gonna be approaching her like no other
guy has ever approached her it's
literally just gonna sweep her off her
feet she's gonna be like wow I can't
believe this is happening all these
other guys come up to me
they're like hey what's up og MACO cool
or they maybe during the day they go up
and say you know ask for directions
which is a fine way to start the
approach but if you stay on that level
it doesn't work you have to be direct so
this is gonna set you apart from other
guys especially in daytime scenarios
yeah women get hit on at night but
usually the psych hey beautiful hey
gorgeous what's up damn you're so hot
it's cheesy it's pathetic
it's needy when you go up to and use the
look and you own your presence and
you're just comfortable it it's gonna
work really well it's gonna separate you
from other guys and it's gonna make her
feel desire right away she's gonna be
turned on instantly she's not just gonna
like you she's gonna be attracted to you
whether you're her typical type or not
so before I give you some examples the
right way to do it and exactly what to
say let me give you a couple other
really important techniques when you
approach and these can make a big
difference of whether it goes smoothly
or not number one is time constraint
people in a hurry so give a little time
constraint it's not it's not a fake
thing it's true you are in a hurry even
if it's just to meet more girls you are
a busy guy so convey that that you're
not going to take up too much of her
time so you use a time constraint next
is acknowledging the reality here's the
thing if you just walk up to a girl and
you're like hi you're cute that can work
definitely
but in daytime situations especially
people are doing other things it's not a
social type of you know most daytime
scenarios are not social situations like
a party or a club or a bar or that's at
the vent day time you know people don't
really talk to each other people don't
talk to strangers that much so when you
go up to her and you're just like hi
you're cute it's a little bit too much
too soon she's like whoa what's going on
and you didn't create any sexual tension
now I don't have a lot of time in this
video to go over all the details of
sexual tension but understand this
sexual tension is the difference between
whether she gets really
really sexually aroused or not and you
can do it instantly you can do it right
away so and I'm gonna give you an
example just a second so bear with me
but you want to acknowledge the reality
especially in daytime situations because
people are busy people are doing things
you want to show that you're aware of it
okay so for example let's say she's
walking really fast
she seems like she's in a hurry instead
of you saying hey you're cute you would
say hey listen I know you're in a hurry
and then you would say the direct opener
which could be something like I think
you're really cute or I just saw you
here and I wanted to say hi to you or I
find you absolutely adorable I just had
to tell you and there's obviously
there's other complements you could give
her too and that's what being direct is
it's giving her a sincere honest
compliment it's not about telling her
she has nice shoes yes that could be an
honest compliment if you think her shoes
are nice but that still doesn't convey
your interest in desire so that's what
direct is conveying your interest and
desire while also giving her a sincere
compliment who doesn't like a compliment
as long as it's not done in a creepy
needy way so other situations you might
find herself in or you might see a woman
in during the day as she could be on the
phone
you better acknowledge the reality if
she's on the phone he can't just go up
to her and say hi I find you attractive
she's good okay well I'm on the phone
asshole that's really rude so you got to
think okay I got to tell her hey I know
you're on the phone but also acknowledge
the fact that it's kind of rude to
interrupt someone and here's the thing
when you acknowledge that you know it's
rude she won't think it's rude anymore
it's pretty cool huh let me repeat that
when you acknowledge and you know you're
doing something wrong or you're doing
something that's rude or not normal
she won't think that anymore but if you
don't say it she's gonna be thinking
they got this guy's really rude
if you say hey listen I know it's so
rude to interrupt somebody on the phone
but I had to tell you that you are
absolutely stunning
that could work now maybe it won't work
every time she could be on a really
important phone call
but in my experience
that works at least 50% of the time
where the girl says okay hold on one
second hey I gotta go I gotta go
and then she'll talk to you you can have
a normal interaction okay or maybe she's
with a friend you could say listen I
know you're with your friends but I just
wanted to say you are absolutely
adorable okay so that's acknowledging
they're acknowledging the reality saying
listen I know you're in the situation
right now or you can even say I know
this is really rude or random I like to
use the word random because really any
daytime situation where you approach a
woman during the day it's random because
women don't get approached during the
day almost never I've I can't tell you
how many beautiful women I've gone on
dates with and I've asked them how often
does that happen where a guy approaches
you the way I did and it's almost always
never or maybe it's all once two years
ago some guy did it but it wasn't as
charming as you I get that all the time
I've never had a girl oh yeah that
happens a lot some girls might say yeah
I get hit on a lot but it's guys
hollering at them it's guys yelling at
them damn girl damn you're beautiful but
it's not guys confidently approaching
them owning their space looking at them
with desire and communicating their
interest verbally and non-verbally that
doesn't happen to women during the day
it just it just doesn't so the point is
you can tell her I know this is random
because you know this doesn't happen to
her much so that's another way to
acknowledge the reality so you can say
hey listen I know you're shopping and
this is totally random but you are
absolutely adorable I just had to tell
you so notice that versus what most guys
do when they first start practicing this
and they first start approaching women
during the day they go up and they say
hi I just saw you here I thought you're
really cute and they're overly excited
smiling too much talking too fast and
they just seem like a nice guy a
friendly guy who's a little nervous and
the girl will usually give that guy a
good response because he's being nice
that's it you're just the nice guy same
words but completely different reaction
and she's gonna feel something
completely different so I'll give you
one more example let's say a girl is I
don't know let's say she's in Starbucks
and you know it's kind of quiet and most
guys would go up hey real quick I just
saw you here and I thought you're really
Q I just want to tell you you know kind
of whispering and being a little bit
clout a little bit quieter and singing
about that fast that's gonna make her go
oh thank you wow that was really nice of
you you just made my day that's gonna
make her feel good which is another
benefit of being direct by the way is
making the girl feel good you're making
her day it's pretty cool to just see a
girl who maybe was having an average day
or even having a bad day just completely
light up it's awesome and it becomes
even somewhat addictive because every
girl that you want to approach you know
worst-case scenario you're gonna make
her day it's pretty cool so the right
way to do it or a way that's gonna be
much more effective and create sexual
tension it's gonna make her feel your
desire is gonna be more like this hey
real quick
listen I know you're busy I know this is
completely random but I just had to tell
you that you are absolutely adorable and
to at least say hi hi and then go from
there that's gonna work much better why
because you're allowing yourself time to
feel the emotions inside you and to
convey it through your eye contact
through giving her that look of desire
and looking at her like you know you
know you know the secret that you can
give her the utmost sexual satisfaction
and you're taking your time allowing
those emotions to build up and conveying
it and just owning your words owning
your presence owning your stance being
unapologetic about it it's gonna work
really really well she's gonna feel it
she
gonna feel attraction towards you right
away she's gonna want you and that's how
you should be approaching that's how you
should approach if you want her to be
sexually attracted to you and feel
emotions very powerful motions towards
you right away
because here's the deal if she doesn't
feel anything if you're just going up to
her and you're saying something just
generic something that's flat
emotionally or even if it's something
direct but you're not communicating your
desire through your words through your
eye contact and your body language she's
not gonna feel anything she's just gonna
feel like oh that was I was a nice guy
he was friendly no you want her to feel
the tension build up in her body that's
gonna work thousand times better she
will call you back I guarantee you
she'll go on an instant date right there
on the spot if she is able to if she's
not working or completely busy in that
moment she will want you so I want you
to approach like that got it so what do
you do after the opener what do you do
after you say hi to keep the
conversation going so you know exactly
what to say how to keep the attraction
elevating and increasing more and more
with every word you say and how to take
it either to an instant date right then
and there to the bedroom to a long-term
relationship whatever it is that you
want how do you do all that well I've
created a special program called the
language of Attraction where you'll
learn how to become a fascinating
conversationalist
that can spark attraction and create a
deep connection with the words you say
and you'll never run out of things to
say because you'll always know how to
steer the conversation and you'll get
proven openers that work in any
situation to get the conversation
started in the best most attractive and
confident manner possible you'll learn
how to make her see you as the prize so
that she starts trying to earn your
affection how to be more fun and playful
in your conversations through banter
teasing role-plays and more to set
yourself apart from the boring guys in
her life and if you're an older guy I
show you how to make this work for you
as well and I'll give you the exact
questions to ask her to make an impact
and create a deep connection with her in
a matter of minutes and I'm gonna give
you a whole lot more including actual
exercises to become an amazing natural
conversationalist so click the link
below to see the special offer I have
just for you because I want to honor you
for watching this entire training video
so just click the link below to get the
details