when you first approached a girl if you
make her feel even a little bit creeped
out she's going to lose interest you can
be a totally nice normal awesome guy but
if you don't follow certain rules per se
you're gonna scare her away most girls
myself included can name forty different
scenarios in which a guy has approached
and for no particular real reason she
felt really uncomfortable and had to
leave so I'm gonna cover five mistakes
that most guys make and give you some
demos to really show you what I'm
talking about
so that you do not become the one
labeled as the creep hey guys it's
Nicole with the attractive man team and
in today's video I'm gonna tell you how
to approach and flirt with a girl
without being creepy approaching someone
new and flirting with them can be beyond
nerve-racking we've all been there an
important thing to remember is that when
you approach a girl she's gonna feel
really nervous to meeting anyone new can
be a little bit awkward intense so if
you can do something to alleviate that
awkward tension then you're golden but
if you're the one creating it you're
definitely going to be labeled as a
creep the first and most common mistake
I've seen guys make is that they take
forever to approach after making eye
contact you can guarantee any time I'm
out with my friends we're gonna come
across at least one guy who will make
eye contact with one of us maybe a few
times and then he just doesn't approach
or he takes like 15 minutes to approach
or something crazy like that if you
think you're being fun and playing
hard-to-get creating that will they
won't they vibe across the bar you're
wrong all you've done is created the
vibe that you are a stalker and you've
made her feel uncomfortable that she has
to be in the same room as you
it's really important that you approach
quickly after making eye contact you can
glance once or twice maybe even three
times and then you need to approach if
she's looking at you that many times
that's like a guaranteed cue that you're
she's ready for you to approach and
you're welcome to do so you cannot wait
around or else you've lost your chance
so the second mistake I'm gonna cover
was actually inspired by a question that
my neighbor asked me he's a single guy
and he's in the day
and he asked what if you can't make eye
contact with someone across the bar what
if it's too crowded or you just can't
catch their glance what do you do in
this scenario this is a great question
it's definitely still okay to approach
but how you do it can make or break your
chances with someone this leads me to
the mistake that most guys make is that
in this scenario they tend to get too
close too soon you have to approach them
across the bar it's easy to have to get
close to them and make them feel really
weird so I'm actually going to do a demo
for you to show you just how awkward and
creepy this can be from the outside
looking in this happens a lot in bars
where someone will approach me from
behind and they are so close it makes me
feel freaked out so Aaron's gonna
demonstrate that so you turn around and
they're just right there like you can't
even see who is in front of you you see
right there nose it just it's really
awkward and it makes you feel like
threatened like he's taller than me and
he's bigger than me and he's a really
really close so you want to maybe stand
look back I think could be a little
closer than arm's reach since you're
going through a crowd but you need to be
able to see you so he could have brought
up and approach me like the normal way
hi
so that's comfortable he touched my arm
gently and not weird and now I can see
his face and engage in conversation with
him and it feels much more natural by
the way if you're not subscribed yet go
ahead and click that subscribe button we
put out awesome new dating advice videos
every single week and you're not going
to want to miss any of them so now
you've approached the girl nice work
but what happens next can really
determine how the interactions gonna go
you have to have something to say to her
other than hey my name is so-and-so it
can be a flirty line it can be a comment
about the weather I mean that's kind of
boring but literally anything that you
can say to get the conversation going to
spark something is going to make a
difference
hi hi my name is Anna Nicole nice to
meet yo sirisha and then he immediately
dropped his head really awkwardly in for
like the longest five seconds of my life
didn't say anything where are you from
I'm from Austin are you from from the
past Texas how long have you been here
I've been here for about a year and a
half and needless to say this
conversation died out pretty quickly
after you introduce yourself you can and
should make a flirty comment you know
maybe something vegetable she's wearing
or something you noticed about her
anything to really get that flirty
energy going will make you see him
really interesting and also will avoid
any of that awkward silence that just
creates the weirdest conversational
tension don't make this mistake always
have something to say you can also use
your surrounding this topic cues if you
really don't know what to say to someone
you can kind of look around you and make
comments about things maybe you're at a
coffee shop and you can make a comment
on someone's order or maybe you're at a
bar and you can make a comment on
something interesting you see there's
always something funny drunken happening
anything like that will really expect a
conversation that is relevant to both of
you so it's easy to get that good
conversational dynamic going now the
fourth mistake that a lot of guys make
is making too much eye contact now I
actually have not really personally
experienced this but my best friend
recently went on a date and she says
this has actually happened to her a lot
where the guy you know they had a good
conversation started and then he made
some comment about maybe she had pretty
eyes or something about her face and
then didn't look away would get really
creepy and old and weird after just a
few seconds it's not cool
look away naturally literally anything
around you just don't stare directly at
someone's eyes for a really long time or
you're gonna really creep them out
the fifth mistake a lot of guys make is
too much or unwelcome physical contact
now this absolutely differs from girl to
girl and you won't know immediately when
meeting her so you have to pay attention
to her body language and the signs she's
giving you about what's welcome and
what's not but a lot of guys make the
mistake of having way too much physical
contact too soon and it will just make a
person feel really tense and
uncomfortable so one mistake that guys
kind of make pretty often is their
insert there's either too much touch or
not enough touch so I'm going to show
you a couple of examples of too much
touch that makes you feel creeped out
and weird and then an example of no
engagement at all physical you know a
physical engagement at all and show you
how it looks so the first example is
going to be this happens all the time in
bars or even other places it's too much
and it feels really weird so Aaron's
gonna demonstrate that really quick so
yes hey how's it going okay so this is
like it's bigger than me first of all
it's overpowering and weird like you you
feel like trapped all of a sudden so you
are in this scenario it's just not
comfortable you don't feel good and you
don't want to like engage more because
you feel already uneasy you wanna take a
step back from him as opposed to
engaging with him so avoid that a simple
way to approach a girl if you want to
touch is just a quick light tap on the
arm or anywhere on the arm hand whatever
you can shake hands something like that
that gift that physical action going but
not in a way that makes her feel
threatened so another problem is if they
don't touch it all at first it kind of
creates a weird like they're not sure of
themselves I'm not confident a weird
vibe so he's gonna approach me and just
say how I can show you how that looks hi
hi okay so see it like this happens all
the time the guys will approach and the
like look like they're gonna shake your
hand or something and they put their
pocket instead and you're like all right
left meeting in and it's really weird so
just you always shake hands or something
just some kind of interaction if you
really want to get that conversation
going it really sets the tone so you've
seen the wrong in the right way to touch
a person that you've just met if you
touch a girl lightly on her arm and the
conversations going well and she smiles
and you know everything seems fine she
doesn't flow away it's probably a good
go to that you're okay to do that again
but if someone pulls away it doesn't
necessarily mean that they're not
interested especially if the
conversation is going really well it
just may mean they're not quite ready
for that level of interaction yet so
keep the conversation fun and playful
and flirty and you can try again a
little bit she'll let you know when
she's ready for that she may even
reciprocate first just to let you know
she's no longer feeling nervous around
you on the other hand if you make a
light playful touch even if the
conversations going well and the girl
pulls away or seems uneasy all of a
sudden it's a pretty good cue that she's
just not really into it the thing is if
a girl really is into a guy that she's
talking to that's pretty much always
going to be welcome it's a pretty normal
thing
it's affectionate it's nice its playful
it's fun so if she does back away and
seems a little uneasy it's probably your
cue to make an exit and don't waste your
time with that person because they're
not that interested so I've covered the
five mistakes that most guys make when
approaching a woman and talking to her
and flirting with her that can really
make them come off as creepy a lot of
these things are really easily avoidable
but they are kind of based in a lack of
confidence or nervousness and things
like that if you really want to gain the
confidence necessary to approach a girl
you should download our confidence cheat
sheet right now there's a link below and
also in the description and it includes
18 proven ways based on science and
psychology that you can boost your
confidence fast and effectively that way
you won't have all these nerves when
approaching a beautiful girl and if you
really want to know how to interact with
a woman and get some really personal
advice
instruction check out our bootcamp
schedule which is also in a link below
thanks I'll see you in the next video
bye
[Music]