I'm
he has mastered the art of seduction
to be assertive a woman
we turn on two three six something you
know what works what does new person
keep your text short as possible short
as possible I go through my text use I
mean I don't spend a long time on a text
but I'll send a text look at it as
anything I can eliminate that's not
necessary
everything that you send should be
necessary especially in the beginning
this is a quick excerpt from a talk I
did about texting at one of our 7-day
workshops in Las Vegas and here's the
deal man
texting is absolutely crucial in today's
day and age so in this video I'm gonna
go over some basic principles about
texting that most guys actually don't
know and the best way to use texting and
most guys actually get this completely
wrong and even do the exact opposite and
how many texts that it takes to go for
the date and how I like to go for the
date and the mindset if she doesn't text
you back which is absolutely crucial
because most guys freak out and they
start being all meaty and obviously
that's going to turn away the girl and a
simple principle to not be needy over
text and before we get started I want to
make sure you grab your free copy of the
texting cheat sheet click the link down
in the description below to get twenty
word forward texting scripts to get the
date and get her wanting you so that you
always send the perfect text message
every single time make sure to grab your
copy now because it's totally free and
packed full of tons and tons of awesome
texting tips okay so let's get back to
the video a lot of you guys have gotten
pulls this week and a lot of you guys
even use texting to get dates this week
first of all what is the point of
texting instead of a date some guys get
that wrong
okay go just to build rapport and just
to like be on our mind all the time and
yeah that is a little bit the point as
well but the main point is to get a date
you might have to do things like spike
up the attraction a little bit show some
good qualities that would make her want
to go on a date with you I like to just
get the date if it's possible so get a
girl's number I usually go for the date
within the first three texts usually the
second or third text
first text is going to be just something
so that she just to start the
interaction again start the interaction
I'm not going to go for the date on the
first text because it's just too quick
little too quick but second third text
start starting to transition into a date
I'm starting to either hint at it or
actually set it up and I'll give you
exactly how I do that I like to do that
because I want to see where she's at if
she if I can give the date really
quickly then hell yeah I don't have to
waste time doing a bunch of texting to
do that I used to do that a lot like
text text text a lot of it was for her
experimentation to just see what works
and what doesn't work written two
different books called turn her on
through text which all you guys will get
a copy of as well if you don't have it
already so what I recommend is go for it
quickly and then if that doesn't work
then start adding in some fun text to
show her that going on a date with you
would be fun one of her biggest fears is
going on a date with a guy who's just
completely boring she's stuck with him
for a few hours although she can always
leave anytime she wants but she wants to
make sure that it's fun she wants to go
on a date with a fun guy so if you can't
get the date quickly and she doesn't
reply with an alternative I mean she
might be just busy that doesn't mean
that it's not gonna work out but she's
like oh I'm busy tonight how about
tomorrow night then just keep setting up
the date figure out the logistics of the
date and then you're good to go if that
doesn't work and she just doesn't reply
when you go for the date or she says oh
sorry I'm busy and doesn't give you an
alternative that's when you got and go
into fun okay and I'll give you some
examples of that so you don't want to do
is be boring and I don't like texting
all day long all that all that bullshit
either because for me I'm a busy guy
like I said I used to do that but I'm a
busy guy now
I don't even text that much anymore if I
need to build up some attraction I'll
send one or two texts to do that and
then go for the date again if it's still
not working working working move on next
next and here's the thing if you had a
solid initial interaction then you don't
really need to do much through text
if you're not getting a lot of dates
through text it may not be your texting
your texting is pretty fun playful then
it could be because your initial
interactions aren't very solid now
remember it's never going to be a
hundred percent it is partly a numbers
game you could have a solid interaction
and it still doesn't turn into anything
why who knows maybe she gave you her
number she didn't tell you that she has
a boyfriend had that several times where
girls say hey actually I have a
boyfriend can you delete my number
can you stop texting he's getting pissed
happens or she just doesn't tell you
that she just never replies or she's
kind of dating somebody and then she
gives you her number thinking well he's
not my boyfriend yeah you know you give
out my number and then two days later
they become exclusive or a week later or
whatever or she wants to just wait it
out to see you don't know so don't take
it personally even if you like think you
had such a solid interaction right it's
not going to work every time that's why
have a lot of numbers I always tell guys
have 7 to 10 numbers girls that you're
texting that will help you avoid getting
needy if you only have one 2 girls and
you think it's on and maybe it starts
off on and then it's off after that they
just stop texting you back you know
maybe they both got boyfriends at the
same time maybe ones out of town the
other ones super busy at school who
knows we don't know what's going on in
their life what a lot of guys what will
happen for a lot of guys they start
getting needy through text and then they
they shoot themselves in the foot and
then the girls lose interest because
they're like god this guy has no life
this guy has no other options it's kind
of unattractive I don't want to be his
only option I know it sounds a little
counterintuitive but a girl doesn't want
to go on a date with a guy who can't get
dates with girls she doesn't want to
feel like she's the hottest girl he's
ever gone on a date with that she can't
gig or that he can't get girls like her
and that's what neediness shows so if
you don't have that many numbers go out
and meet more girls go out and meet more
girls thanks for watching man and again
I want to make sure you grab your free
copy of the texting cheat sheet because
it contains 20 word-for-word
texting scripts to get the date and get
her wanting of just go down to the
description right now click the link and
I'll send it directly to your email and
I look forward to seeing you in another
video
no no that would be bad I'll make you
all making my Miami girlfriend for the
next five minutes then then it will be
okay
yes okay are you giving me a tour Hoff
yes