you've got our phone number now what do
you do well in this video I'll break
down exactly what to text a girl to get
a date fast because I typically send
only three to five messages to get a
date and I'll even give you those exact
messages in just a second the key is
that you have to stand out from all the
other guys that are texting her because
if she's an attractive woman
then she's getting bombarded by messages
from guys every single day so I'm gonna
show you exactly how to stand out my
name is Madison international dating
coach I've mastered the art of
encouragement to be assertive
we've done all the testing you know what
works now I'm about to give you the
exact texting sequence that I use to get
a date with a girl but first I want to
give you a free texting cheat sheet that
you can download and use right now for
free
after years of sending thousands of text
messages I compiled a list of 20 of my
best texts that I personally use in
there you'll discover my simple texting
sequence to get the date fast you'll
discover the single biggest mistake that
most guys make when texting that kills
attraction and is the reason that most
girls stop responding inside I'll even
show you what's a text her to turn her
on so just click the link down in the
description to download those texts
right now just follow the link and I'll
send it straight to your email okay now
let me help you with your texting I'm
gonna give you five texting tips and
examples and number five is the exact
texting sequence that I use to get a
date first I want to clear one thing up
right now texting is a lot easier when
you had a solid interaction in person if
there wasn't any attraction or
connection when you first met her
there's not much you can do through
texting to fix that assuming that you
had a great face-to-face interaction or
maybe you got her phone number off of
tinder or Bumble tip number one has to
do with timing timing is really really
important don't text too soon or too
late
yeah well the twos enough not to look
anxious yeah choose enough not to look
anxious but I think three days is kind
of money yeah but you know why maybe
I'll wait three weeks
don't wait that long if you need a girl
at a bar text her the next day in the
afternoon because the longer you wait
the memories that she have has of you
start to fade and remember women are
getting bombarded by guys messaging them
from tinder or just randomly on social
media and if you wait too long she might
already be into another guy I only text
her the same night if I think there's a
chance that she might come over maybe
after she drops off her friends and I'm
just gonna text her what I'm doing for
example when to go grab pizza to kill
the hangover or milkshakes at 2:00 a.m.
Rock and if she replies and says
something like
I wish I could have a milkshake then of
course I'm going to invite her this
works well because sometimes she just
needs to get away from her friends then
she's totally willing to come meet up
with you later alone now if you meet a
girl during the daytime don't wait more
than three or four hours to send your
first text unless you had a really great
interaction and maybe there's a little
bit longer than normal then you still
might be on her mind the next day but I
typically only wait three or four hours
to send my first text if I met her
during the daytime
now what about replying to her texts how
long should you wait to reply back well
the key here is to be random don't
always text her back right away but
don't always wait too long either don't
just stop whatever you're doing to check
your phone and text your back in fact
keep your phone on silent and only check
it a few times throughout the day this
way sometimes you're gonna text your
back right away because you happen to be
looking at your phone or she just sent
you a message right before you look at
it most of the time it's gonna be a few
hours but sometimes it might be the
longer than that maybe the whole day or
not till the next day because you're a
busy guy that keeps things a lot more
random and it prevents you from
overthinking things or playing games
just be a busy guy live a cool and
interesting life and texter randomly
because a girl that you just met
shouldn't be the most important thing in
your life by the way make sure to
subscribe to this channel for more
dating tips because I want to help you
attract your dream woman next don't over
text when I'm coaching guys and I check
their texting interactions I usually see
20 or 30 texts back and forth without
them ever asking or going for the date
don't do that
remember the goal of texting is to get
the date like I said before I go through
the date usually within 5 texts because
why do more work than what is necessary
plus if you're texting her all the time
it shows her that you're not a busy guy
and that you don't really have a lot
going on in your life and women like
guys that have other things going on in
their life other than them and keep your
text short and sweet before you send it
out look it over one time and see if
there's any unnecessary words and delete
them don't send 3 or 4 sentences when
you could have said the exact same thing
with just one sentence next I
you to be slightly more playful in your
text here's why because when she sees
that you're a fun playful guy she'll
realize that going on a date with you is
gonna be interesting and fun instead of
boring but if you're sending her a bunch
of boring text like hey what's up or hey
what are you doing then she's gonna
assume that you're gonna ask her a bunch
of boring questions on the date so just
make things a little bit more
interesting than the average guy instead
of saying hey what's up or hey what are
you doing
say what kinda trouble are you getting
into this weekend just adding the word
trouble makes it a little bit more
interesting another example instead of
sending a ping text like hey you could
send hey you just popped into my head
what kind of weird voodoo magic are you
using a text like that can actually make
her smile which causes her to associate
positive emotions with you whereas a
text like hey doesn't do anything and
remember there's a lot more examples in
the free texting cheat sheet next text
like a man what I mean by that is cut
out unnecessary questions now of course
you do want to ask her questions by the
way I like to ask interesting questions
like if you could have any superpower
what would you have or if you could
travel anywhere in the world where would
you go that can create some fun back and
forth what I mean is that you want to
avoid questions that imply that you're
not sure if she actually likes you or
not or that you're unsure if she
actually wants to hang out with you
instead of texting wanna hang out
sometime
which implies that you don't know if she
wants to hang out with you text her a
command statement that assumes she wants
to hang out with you something like hey
let's meet up Saturday night I know this
great place this shows her that you
assume that she's attracted to you and
wants to see you again which is
basically showing confidence and it's
also good to be specific as to when and
where you want to hang out instead of
just saying hey let's hang out sometime
send hey let's hang out tomorrow night I
have a really fun idea or you could tell
her what the fun idea is and tell her
the exact location cancel all plans
tomorrow night I know a great band
that's playing at Crazy Charlie's let's
go it's gonna be fun it's specific and
it's a command instead of a question now
I want to give you the exact texting
sequence from start to finish
I use when I get a girl's number and
then go for a date first when I get her
number
I usually text her something that
includes a callback something that
relates or calls back to the initial
interaction that we had if it was at
night then it's usually something fun
that we joked about or something maybe
that I teased her about for example
maybe we did a fun marriage roleplay and
then the next day in the afternoon I
text her hey wifey I cheated on you with
the housekeeper don't be mad if we met
during the daytime which is not as
playful of an environment compared to a
bar I might recall maybe her reaction to
my approach especially since women don't
get approached nearly as much during the
daytime something like so crazy meeting
you today it was cute how you dropped
your phone when I said hi or maybe she
didn't drop her phone but she just
seemed a little nervous then I might say
so what expected running into you
earlier it was cute how nervous you got
when I said hi notice also how I didn't
use the word nice because nice is so
overused instead I use the word
unexpected or so crazy or so random
meeting you and then after she replies
send a fun yet challenging text
something like make it or break it
question would you rather be poor and
traveled the world or be rich but could
never leave your city I like that one
because I like to travel and I like
women that like to travel so I encourage
you to pick something based on equality
that you wanted a woman but don't make
it too complicated don't ask her about
her hopes and dreams and passions in
life because that's just too intense and
too personal keep it fun and save those
kind of questions for the date by the
way you should be qualifying women in
your initial interactions with them as
well because a woman wants a man that
she has to work for a little bit that
she has to win over that she has to
chase she doesn't want a man who just
Falls for her for no reason other than
it looks and I like the
make-it-or-break-it part because that's
what makes it actually sound like a
challenge there's other ways of course
for example if you like adventurous
women you could text her tell me this
are you adventurous it's short and sweet
and it causes her to invest just a
little bit and it creates the frame that
you are screening her that your test
her to see if she meets your standards
then after she replies there might be
some fun back and forth there's a lot of
examples remember how to keep it fun and
flirty in the texting cheat sheet make
sure to get that and then just find out
when she's free find out what her
schedule is like just text her waiting
you're free this week or if you want to
be a little bit more fun and playful you
could add in besides missing me in
doodling hearts on a piece of paper
what are you doing this weekend and then
just go for the date if for example she
said she's free on Sunday then just text
her okay listen I have a super fun idea
keep Sunday night open I like that
because it gets her wondering what the
super fun idea is right it sounds like a
surprise and of course some girls will
just go for that others will want to
know what the fun idea is in which I
usually just text something like cool or
that you probably haven't been to first
meet me at handlebar be there at 8 p.m.
try it out man because it works really
well it's simple and it's not gamey or
gimmicky remember women want a man with
a plan who go for what they want and for
more text that you can use remember to
download the free texting cheat sheet
with 20 proven texts for getting the
date and making her want you in there
I'll show you what to text her if she's
not responding and I'll even show you
what to text her to turn her on so just
go down to the description click the
link and download those text just follow
the link enter your email and I'll send
it right to you and if you like this
video the make sure to subscribe to this
channel for more dating tips on how to
attract your dream woman my name is matt
artisan from the attractive man and i'll
see you in the next video
[Music]