if you were not comfortable with your
ownself would you change your look
[Music]
takagi Selena
you know a pencil is phasing in the
kisser
[Music]
no idea I'm going my house
I took Hermia crombie on y'all come and
join it work in English okay yeah it's
better it's better yeah
[Music]
it's a famous Russian
sonica Dardenne doesn't the khaki why
did you choose waiting instead of
leaving because since it's a special
place probably we traveled there for a
long time just for this specific
restaurant that's the longest wait you
were like willing to wait that's a good
maybe 20 minutes it was it's a really
good it's really good nice how does that
like that long I actually vote okay I
think I'll be willing to wait like
couple hours
hmm I'm not that patient occasion
I mean if it's like that famous that is
you know I think it worth it if it's
pretty special
Jordan can't Santa
it's okay
I prefer texting less meeting up if
possible okay so you prefer meeting up
more than yeah I prefer face-to-face I'm
completely on the same page I prefer
meeting up in person I don't really like
texting or calling I'm kind of
old-fashioned so calling or face-to-face
yeah
[Music]
so then I'm Alan Cohen turquoise
that's the reasoning behind it if I'm
just not in the mood to have sex can't
really do it for me I chose no because I
think consent is important between any
kind of relationship you know one-night
stands
consent that's just a must so I don't
want to force my partner I mean at all
my partner to force me yes and to having
sex in any kind of situation are you
good
have you ever had a experience where a
girl wants to have sex with you but you
didn't want to yes I had to shave my
ex-girlfriend ah with your ex-girlfriend
enemies my big issue
ah when she was in the mood for sex she
was kind of expecting me to get intimate
and she thought it was like like a
switch yeah except a finger right what
it takes more than that angry
[Music]
Budi step on that cows also take a
report over here in Zion Hyundai
take a bunch of boo-boos engagement day
because I have told officials it washes
off the window although I can tell she's
quite nervous she seems really nice I
like the way shipping for answer to the
question with the restaurant waiting
into life I can tell there she might be
a really patient which is always good in
a relationship she said she would wait
one hour I would not wait that long but
if she wanted to them I would wait with
her
[Music]
turnin up doesn't exceed
so what do you think Korea's a diverse
beauty standard yeah no I don't think so
there is a very very straightforward
standard I think it is true that a lot
of people feel pressure to comply to
that beauty so why would you not change
that if you know they feel pressured I
think the question asks do we need to
change it I don't think we have to
change it like this agree disagree why
when I came to Korea this was one of the
biggest shocks that I experienced the
Korean really strict purity standard and
the pressure that the girls have here
the girl is nice to girls mostly yeah
they feel like they should change their
look I think they should try to accept
their natural beauty if it's completely
up to me and I was in power to do so I
would say yes more diversity is the
better but if some I don't know
non-korean come and say Korean standard
of beauty is wrong like me
I'm a non-korean yeah and I say that I
don't think I don't think you and I both
have the right to point and say it's
wrong so what kind of person you are if
you are not comfortable with your own
self mm-hmm would you change your look
or would you try to accept it I think I
would try to change it you know mm-hmm
if I'm not comfortable let's just say I
want bigger lips I don't think I would
mind getting a plastic surgery or
occurring through a procedure if that's
going to make me happy just for myself I
respect that
[Music]
I think I know your answer John and I'm
content articles that was expected why
do you think that's not acceptable
well the question is just an ordinary
cafe I don't think it's necessary to
hire somebody based on looks unless it's
that kind of a cafe where they hire
good-looking people I am really against
hiring someone just based on their looks
I know it's really common let's just say
if you're the owner it is kind of true
if you hire a good-looking people I mean
I hate to admit it but a lot of people
come to see them your profit
that's true but on the other hand if
they hire someone based on their
personality someone who's really
talented or just good with people I
think that can do the same they can also
attract customers I will try to give
everyone the same chance I know this is
a very cruel question well let's just
say there are two people and have
exactly same exactly same personality
but one is better looking than the other
he's cruel question a lot of people who
hate me for my answers but yeah I get a
logically thinking logically thinking
yes of course hmm I was big the
better-looking one right and it said I
think it said anyone that's life that's
the reality and the statistics even yes
that good-looking people make better
money mmm but definitely that's that
doesn't make it right though yeah yeah
[Music]
turn in content ah ah why would you say
you're not okay I think I tend to be a
little bit jealous
she's getting TM from God ah ah I see so
let's just say you can look at all my
DMS whenever you want would that make it
better
[Music]
no I would not want to be I'd not want
her to say that you just want to avoid
it if it's possible yeah yeah so you
would be okay with your partner
imploding revealing pictures I'd be okay
with my partner uploading photos as well
as it's tastefully done mm-hmm and
Juvederm each other's jealous that they
would get with the ends from girls no
not really I think I'll be okay it's not
my right to invade his personal social
media I don't want to be that person to
restrict him okay yeah
[Music]
Tony it died Mira hmm so you're a family
person I would like to say I'm a family
person why did you want somebody who's
willing to make sacrifice for family I'm
a family person so I want my partner to
be the same I think it's definitely a
choice to have a family right get
married have children with that choice
comes responsibility as a parent I think
you have to make sacrifices we talked
about posting pictures on Instagram
mm-hmm what if your family your husband
asks you to take off some pictures from
Instagram it's for the family could you
do it I don't know how my photos would
affect the family in the first place I
don't think there's anything wrong with
posting photos of female body so I think
I would want my husband and my children
to understand I should be proud of my
body and my career hmm I don't want them
to feel ashamed so I guess the answer
would be no I think I don't agree my mom
who's revealing photos should be ashamed
I think they should be very proud yeah
[Music]
how was it for you you know it was very
interesting I was little bit nervous
because my first okay
ah yeah I didn't really know what to
expect
the questions were quite deep right I
think we got to know each other quite a
bit in just a really short time yeah I
think so too
probably I don't think my best friends
would know how I would answer like these
questions yeah just don't talk about
this character right it's not a common
topic
[Music]