The dads are watching! My Daughters' Men season 4!
I hope the daughters start beautiful relationships before the
year ends so they can be happy next year and be full of smiles.
The couples start planning what to do for Christmas when the year is ending.
Who do you guys want your daughters to spend Christmas with?
I heard who you spend Christmas with determines
who your real girlfriend or boyfriend is.
If you were close to someone and they disappear on
Christmas, it means you guys weren't really close.
Will Seok-hee be with her family?
She can hang with Yo-Han, and they can come over afterward.
Together?
You've really opened up a lot.
What are you doing for Christmas?
Christmas? I don't have any plans.
Well I'm busy.
I'm sure you guys know, but Joo-yeon had a blind date
and Soo-bin had a blind date too.
- From last week, was it Joo-min? - Yes.
I don't know where he's from but anyway...
The camera is zooming in on you right now.
He had a really nice body and looked sharp.
I'm worried that Soo-min is going to fall for another guy.
Jae-young, how do you think today will go?
I'm sure they talked a lot.
Yes, I'm looking forward to this week.
This sounds like Seok-hee and Yo-Han.
This has to be them.
This is so obvious who it's from.
Your body looks like a piece of art.
Your face looks like a piece of art.
You don't try to kiss anymore.
He's holding back.
My mom thinks it's for real.
The mothers think it's for real.
Even when you tell them no.
- If she's talking about the body... - It's Soo-bin.
- It's obvious. - Soo-bin.
Since Joo-min has a nice body.
That means she saw him shirtless.
- Why? - They must've done that.
- Did they go to a pool. - He must've danced to a song
That's so old.
Isn't that the countryside?
That must be an old train station.
Old stations are pretty.
Who is it?
I told you it's Soo-bin! It's Soo-bin and Joo-min.
She's hiding?
It's cute how she's shy.
I'm embarrassed.
- Hi. - Hi.
Why won't you look me in the eyes?
Is she still shy?
- She must be shy. - I heard that's a good thing.
Yeah.
it means she likes him.
I recently went to Da Nang.
Oh yeah.
- Do you remember? - Of course.
- I saw you the day before I left. - Yeah.
Hold on.
They met without the cameras, right?
After the blind date, Joo-min asked to meet with Soo-bin before he left for Da Nang.
So they met the night before he left.
Do you think he went to Da Nang alone?
Oh my!
That's scary.
- I thought it wouldn't be awkward. - I feel really awkward right now.
Stop looking at me! I'm embarrassed.
It's because you're pretty.
You look pretty today too.
It's because he really thinks she's pretty.
The guy has to like the girl like that.
I like this guy.
What's this?
A camera.
I'm going to take the best picture of your life today.
Her body is leaning towards the guy.
- For real. - I think you're going to be bad.
I'm kidding. I think you're going to be good.
I took pictures for the whole 2 years I was in the army.
- Oh he was a photographer. - There's such a thing?
He was enlisted in a nice place.
I got you a gift from Da Nang.
Really?
- From Da Nang. - A gift?
It's from Da Nang.
He must've gotten her that Vietnamese thing.
It's the thing you said you wanted to eat. Bananas.
The dried bananas.
You asked me to get some.
- You told me the night before. - I didn't know you really would.
It's really good.
And this is...
Open it.
What is that?
- Is it Ado Dai? - Bananas?
Chocolate?
It's chocolate.
Say ah.
- Is it good? - Yeah.
You're not going to give me one?
- I'll get it myself. - It must be so sweet for them.
The two have gotten a lot closer than last week.
- They met before Da Nang. - Meeting on their own must be big.
Of course. And Soo-bin wants to be genuine.
She wants to know how she feels without the cameras.
Right.
Isn't this place pretty?
- Yeah, it's really pretty. - It has a nice vibe.
- Do you want to look around? - Shall we?
- Let's go inside. - Let's go.
There's a place like that?
The history.
Wow, it's really pretty!
They're memories.
I love that old school vibe.
- Doesn't that make you want to cry? - Look at the uniforms.
Old school vibe.
Yeah.
Have you had ice bars?
- Ice bars! - That's so cool!
I think I've seen that before. It opens only on one side.
- A hand isn't going to pop out, right? - No.
- What? - It's my second gift for you.
- For real? - Yes.
There's another gift in there?
Really? I had no idea.
- Really? - This is crazy.
It's a mood lamp.
That's going to be pretty.
You said you have a hard time falling asleep.
So have this on when you go to sleep.
Thank you so much.
Yay, this is great.
- But did you know? - Know what?
There's a last gift.
- There's more? - Yeah, look for it.
What's the last gift?
You're very eager now.
That means Joo-min really likes Soo-min.
He bought her several gifts, not just one.
That means he's that much more interested in her.
He prepared everything because he didn't know what she'd like.
So he was thinking about her the whole time.
He thought of her whenever he looked at something.
Jung-hoon is touched too.
Look for it.
- You didn't hide it here, right? - A scavenger hunt is a good idea.
That's dirty. Don't touch it.
They've gotten really close.
Where is it?
It's this thing.
It's right here!
Yay! I found it!
What is that? I think it's going to have a card!
She's good at finding stuff.
- What is it? - Is it a necklace?
- A bracelet? - A ring.
It's a perfume!
I love purple.
- Really? - Yeah.
I like scented things.
I love perfumes too.
Scents are powerful.
There's a person you think of when you smell it.
Of course.
I got it for you so you can put it on whenever we meet.
Okay?
Okay, I'll put it on whenever I see you.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
From a girl's perspective,
do you feel burdened if a guy gives you gifts before you start dating?
I think he prepared gifts that aren't burdensome.
Rings would be burdensome.
Oh, gifts that aren't too much...
Do you think you can walk on it? Get ready.
Ready.
Go.
Hold on.
They can walk on it because the trains don't go on it.
It's a strange feeling.
They say the love is stronger the less you fall.
Do you want me to hold you? Wait...
I can't get my balance!
I'm trying to stay focused.
She's doing really well in heels.
She's like a model!
Did Soo-bin do gymnastics?
That's how models train.
- Should we take a picture together? - Okay, let's take one together.
They're going to put it on timer and take it together.
Yeah.
A picture on the train tracks would be really pretty.
People used to take pictures like that a lot.
One, two, three! And then run.
I'm here.
Come closer a little bit.
A little bit.
I'm walking on it really well!
Okay that's good.
She discovered a hidden talent.
Hurry!
Get your pose.
I think he's going to casually grab her hand so she doesn't fall.
- This is hard. - Your hand!
I do this all the time!
They grabbed hands.
Did it take it?
This is fun.
This guy is very charming.
- No, this is too much. - This isn't right.
But he still grabs it carefully.
They took it several times.
This one turned out nice.
There's a place like that?
That looks fun!
Where is that place?
So Joo-min showed his body here.
Oh here! You're right!
He took off the top of his suit.
That's cheating!
It was him!
- Look at her smiling! - She's shy!
I can't look at him!
You can wash clothes on his abs!
So-Jin is funny!
- That's crazy. - What's crazy?
Oh yeah, you said you were in a competition.
That's so cool.
Why is she staring so intently?
She's driving me crazy.
She's staring too much at it.
Your body looks like a piece of art.
- Really? - Yeah.
Your face looks like a piece of art.
He said her face is like a piece of art.
I'm embarrassed.
That's enough! Put your suit on!
Put your suit on.
This is cheating.
Soo-bin couldn't look at him in the eyes.
But now that he's shirtless, she can look at him.
She's only looking at his stomach.
My goodness...
- Why? - What do you mean?
Keep it off.
You think you can handle it?
She likes it.
So-Jin loves it.
It has an advantage because you don't have to swim.
- It's better for first timers. - Oh really?
Swimming and standing by yourself is really hard.
Look at his arm muscles.
Who cares if he has a nice body. He's shaking.
You're right.
We're all feeling inferior right now.
If you put people like us there, we'd get up very fast.
We get back up because our bodies are round.
This is really hard.
Put your arms out straight.
Seeing how Soo-bin was on top of the train tracks,
I think she'd be good at getting her balance.
I think she'd have good core strength.
Go Soo-bin!
Soo-bin is athletic.
She needs to let go and go straight up.
You can't get scared.
- Look at her balance. - I hope she doesn't fall.
You're really good!
So she doesn't get pushed back.
She's good!
She should straighten her back.
She can't let go of the rope.
That's how strong the water is?
The water is super strong.
He didn't get to protect her.
He should've jumped in after her!
Are you okay?
She's mad.
- She looks worn out. - How cute.
I think she's going to let go.
It's time for her revenge.
I think she's going to pull really hard.
Oh no!
They fell together?
It's fun even if you fall.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
But you looked good even when you fell.
How annoying.
I guess he looks good doing anything.
She thought that looked good?
That looks fun.
You get really hungry after you play in the water.
For real.
- It's the best. - Yeah.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- Good work. - You too.
This is really good.
It's good.
There's a climbing wall next to us.
You want to do that?
Let's try it and fall a couple times.
- Climbing isn't going to be easy. - It's not easy.
It's okay, I'll catch you if you fall.
I'll catch you from the ground.
- Really? - Yeah.
I'll catch you even if my arms break.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
I'm strong. Don't worry.
This is a workout date too, but it's very different from Seok-hee and Yo-Han.
- That's the place. - Climbing sounds fun!
Let's go.
That's where the climbing wall is.
Yeah.
They're going to try that?
It's really hard.
- You put the safety equipment on. - But it's still hard.
- Let me get a feel for it. - It's a whole body workout.
You need a strong grip.
It really must work out your arms and legs.
- They're putting on the safety equipment. - They need it.
I'm nervous.
I want to try stuff like that too.
- Want to place a bet? - A bet?
- Let's pick the punishment. - Yes.
What should it be?
Compliment each other for 30 seconds nonstop.
- Got it. - Got it.
- Deal. - Deal.
Get set, go!
I don't think I can do this.
This is really hard.
Why is she so good?
Soo-bin, can you slow down?
He's like Yo-Han with muscles.
- Right? - Yes.
He's a little weird too.
I grabbed the wrong one!
Oh no!
- She lost strength in her wrists. - Of course.
I don't think I can do it.
The guy needs to make a decision whether to be on her pace or...
- He's not going to be. - No.
What if you really reach the top?
He's good!
No!
Don't reach the top!
No...
Is he done?
Wow, he did a good job.
This is annoying.
I almost had it. I was close.
You did a good job.
You did well but...
Hurry up and compliment me.
Since 30 seconds is too long, do it for 20 seconds.
It's embarrassing.
And you run out of things to say.
There's nothing to compliment me on?
That's cruel.
Talking about the appearance is too boring.
Are you saying you've heard enough?
- What about my personality? - There's really nothing.
They're close enough to joke around now.
- I'm kidding. - Okay.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, here I go.
- I'm going to time you. - Okay.
Get set, go.
First, you're very handsome. You have a nice body.
I can't do it!
- And... - This feels good.
And your tan looks very sexy.
And you're a lot nicer than I expected from your looks.
I'm sure there's another side to you, but you're very nice.
And you're kind.
And you have a good personality for someone who's so handsome.
I feel good now.
And you're good at climbing and surfing.
- And you're even a good student. - She's totally into him.
Did you know that 20 seconds was up a long time ago?
- Oh really? - You did it for longer than 30 seconds.
- She can't look at his face at all. - She can't.
How can she not look at him at all?
- Yeah, how is that possible? - She likes him a lot.
It's because she likes him a lot.
I'll tell you that you're pretty a lot.
Soo-bin, compliment your dad for 20 seconds. Get set, go!
What if she cries?
"Why are you doing this to me?"
So where are we going next?
We went in the water and climbed the wall.
What's next?
Next is the sky.
He must be serious!
The clip isn't just for reference?
They really went to do it?
That looks really scary.
I don't think I'll be able to jump.
No you can do it.
What do you think about Joo-min? Be honest.
He has a nice personality and has a lot of talents.
It seems like he can take care of Soo-bin.
It's nice to see, and Soo-bin looks really happy.
But I don't think they go well together.
Why not?
I don't think he likes him!
He's jealous.
Her dad is jealous.
A text from the daughter's man!
We're getting a lot of those these days.
For real.
What is that?
This is what Jung Woo-sung said in a commercial.
"Go! Leave me!" With the leaves falling.
I think it will suit you.
She's enjoying it too now.
She enjoys my bad acting.
Here I go.
Nothing has been working out ever since I met you!
Yo-Han is the only one who would say that directly.
You're right.
I think Seok-hee would've beat him if he said that to her.
Didn't she learn jiu-jitsu?
Oh yeah! She did learn it.
Let's find out who it is through the clip!
- What? - It's Joo-yeon.
I never expected this.
- All of a sudden? - I'm 33.
- Me too. - Really?
They must use the informal tone now.
- Is it okay if I go to the bathroom? - Sure.
He got up to go to the bathroom at the restaurant.
That's how it ended last week.
- I thought you went to the bathroom. - Yes.
I thought you went home.
He looks like a different person.
This is actually my restaurant.
He's the owner.
We came so I can make you the food myself.
- Really? - Yes.
- You're going to cook? - Yes.
Would you like to watch me cook?
Yes.
- He's showing her who he is. - It's a great move.
It's an open kitchen, so you can watch me.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- I'm going to the kitchen? - Really? Okay.
That's cool!
- I'll get you a glass of white wine. - Nice.
And I'll make you a welcome dish.
She'll have a glass of wine and wait for her food.
Guys look the best when they're working.
I don't think she can drink that much.
Please give me a plate for salad.
- Do you like it? - It's good.
It's really good.
I was only going to have a sip.
I hope you don't get drunk. You said your face gets red.
He's sweet.
- Please pace yourself. - Okay.
This is an appetizer that people eat in Spain.
This is called pan con tomate.
What's that on top?
- It's tomato salsa. - That sounds good!
And this is Italian reggiano cheese.
This makes him look more mature even though they're the same age.
You can eat it in small bites.
I'll make the salad now. Please shake it.
This is really good.
The gentleness is spreading on his face.
- The guy? - Look at Jae-young.
He's totally into it.
Do you like avocados?
I love them.
She's acting cute.
This won't do.
- She's showing off her charm! - Showing her neck!
What does it mean when the girl reveals her neck?
It's like showing your delicate side.
It's like this. You stay like this and...
do this all of a sudden and tie your hair.
There's no need for So-Jin to reenact it.
You're making So-Jin really comfortable.
We're going to eat together at the table when I'm done.
I didn't want you to be bored while you were watching so I got you the wine.
Joo-yeon looks cooler with her hair up.
I used to do that too once.
- Putting your hair up? - Yes.
I've prepared you the welcome dish.
Guys like it when girls tie their hair like that.
- This is the herring egg, caviar. - I know.
I've seen it before.
She must be happy.
Caviar.
This is Spanish style salted octopus.
I love octopus.
He's making all of the dishes like that?
It's because you eat the food with your eyes.
He has a good sense of art.
- He's good at explaining. - That's pretty!
That looks good!
He looked a little cold earlier, but he looks very gentle when he cooks.
- His cold image disappeared. - Yeah.
He's being so sweet. I wonder how the text came about?
- What did it mean? - I don't know.
- I'm going to face the back for a bit. - See?
He's being considerate.
He's caring.
- Just to let you know. - Okay.
I thought you were telling me to turn around.
Do you like meat?
Yes I do.
- Do you like pork neck? - Yes.
This is Iberico black pork steak.
That's really popular these days.
- It's Spanish pork. - Black pork who grazed.
Right.
- Where's your nose meat from? - It's like the fish ice cream.
The meat is really thin.
Wow, they're going to eat together now.
I think I'd feel bad eating something like that.
The pork neck sounds good.
- It looks so pretty! - That looks good.
The fact that a chef showed himself cooking
- means he showed off his best charm. - That's right.
People fall for singers when they sing on stage.
What about you Soo-geun?
Do you crack jokes in front of girls?
It was when I was doing "No High Note."
- How? - I lowered my voice and said, "Hello."
It's because people don't recognize me without my wig.
So I had to give them my voice.
I used to take girls to karaoke and sing.
Why are you even singing like Choi Min-soo now?
- Shall we eat? - Yes.
- What should I start with? - Start with the salad.
Let me put some on your plate.
How cute.
His attitude has changed.
He's gotten a lot softer.
This is really good.
- Is it okay? - Yes.
That's good.
You know how to eat.
I like girls who can eat.
That was out of the blue.
Don't you like to eat?
Me? Yes, I do.
But I can't eat a lot.
My digestion abilities have decreased.
Stop talking about sad stuff.
I'm at the age where I have to admit it.
No you're not.
I personally want to try that pork neck.
Kyung-hoon, make some for me.
She's falling for him.
She can eat.
I've never seen Joo-yeon eat that much.
You're right.
How do you feel after meeting me?
- Compliment him! - She should give him a score.
From when we first saw each other...
Do you feel more comfortable now?
I guess not.
Do you feel comfortable?
It was a little awkward since we didn't get to talk much.
It hasn't been that long since we've met.
He's not fake.
I feel more comfortable because I've shown you who I really am.
- After you've seen me cook in my space... - Right.
So I feel more comfortable now.
I've written down my thoughts and emotions that I felt after meeting you today.
He's romantic.
Wow, people still do that these days?
That's touching.
"Joo-yeon."
Why do you always want to act it out?
Just read it!
Why am I nervous?
Joo-yeon, it was very nice meeting you today.
Can I see you again where we can be more ourselves next time?
Be more themselves?
Somewhere uplifting and comfortable.
Most people just say it out loud, but writing it down is new.
It's something people used to do long time ago.
I really like this guy.
"Can I see you again?"
Doesn't that feel better than an actual "Yes?" Signing it with your body.
- Right? - We like it too.
My heart skipped a beat when they nodded.
Yes, we can meet again.
The food was very delicious.
- I had a lot of fun. - Me too.
Thank you for allowing me to cook for you.
Although it was a surprise.
I really enjoyed it.
I'm happy because you enjoyed it.
Joo-yeon's ideal type was her dad.
I think he has a lot of similarities with her dad.
- He's calm. - He's sweet.
I think he has a very similar vibe with you.
We'll have to see. I'm not sure yet.
He might get talkative all of a sudden.
He took off his glasses!
You're right!
- Joo-yeon. - He looks like a man of autumn.
- Have you been waiting for a long time? - No.
I haven't been waiting for long.
Aren't you cold?
- I put on a lot of layers. - You're dressed very warm.
It was raining in the morning.
There's a lot of butterflies going on.
This is making me feel very weird.
The background is really pretty too.
I'm okay.
We were at a very crowded place last time.
I guess he wanted to see her somewhere quiet.
We came to a place with not a lot of people.
It's very nice. The air is nice too.
It's pretty.
That will make anyone want to go on a date.
Seriously.
- In person, it's... - It's awesome.
- Taking a picture with the flowers... - I think it will turn out nice.
- Should we go down and take a picture? - Yes.
Could you take a picture for us?
Sure.
We should step back.
- Get close. - Close?
We're very close right now.
The lady is very...
They do that a lot when you ask them to take a picture for you.
- Put your hand on her shoulder. - I think he's going to do it right away.
Isn't he going to do this? Hover over?
This is great. Let's see what he does.
Put your hand on her shoulder.
You put in a lot of time on your hair.
- They're setting Yeon-ji up? - A double date?
I usually do.
You're majoring in English. He's really good!
He always got first place.
That must be fun.
Put your hand on her shoulder.
Hold on. One, two, three.
- They look good together. - They do look a little awkward.
You have to do it on the comfortable side.
- This is good right? - Yes.
- You press this button. - Okay.
Got it?
Should I take it without saying?
They look like a married couple from the 70s.
Yeah, it looks like a newlywed photo.
It feels really good.
To be honest, I don't really take selfies.
- I've never used this before. - Really?
Yes, a selfie stick.
- This used to be really popular. - Yeah.
I turned it on...
This is nice.
I took a year's worth of selfies today.
Really?
This could be two years' worth.
- Really? - I took a lot.
What about taking pictures for other people?
I do a lot of those.
They're starting to talk more.
What a nice view.
It's so pretty.
The air is amazing there.
It's refreshing just to look at it.
We need to go to places like that from time to time.
This is pretty.
We should've came before the leaves had fallen.
A lot of them have fallen.
That's why it looks prettier.
- If you catch a falling leaf.... - A small one, right?
they say your wish comes true.
He's surprisingly into shamanism. He believe in superstitions.
What the heck? Shamanism?
I haven't heard that word in a long time.
Shamanism...
Have you ever caught one? No, right?
I haven't.
Me neither...
People used to catch them and use them as bookmarks.
- Did you know that? - No.
Just kidding.
I wanted to catch one but there isn't any falling.
Do you remember that?
When Jung Woo-sung from the drink commercial from a long time ago...
- "When you're lacking something..." - That's where the text is from.
Of course.
- Do you remember him throwing the leaves? - He was angry.
Nothing has been working out since I met you! Go away!
But I can't throw leaves at you.
No, you can.
- Really? - Yes.
You can do exactly what Jung Woo-sung did.
Okay.
- What happened? - He must've grabbed a handful.
You know he had a serious face, right?
I'll become Jung Woo-sung today.
Here he goes.
Nothing has been working out since I met you.
Go away.
I said, go away.
I don't think he'll be able to toss the leaves in her face though.
But she told him to.
Where did he throw it?
Go away.
- He's a gentleman. - He's romantic.
He's sensible.
What?
What was that?
Are you sure that was it?
Kyung-hoon is surprisingly good at acting.
He's better than me.
It looks like the two have gotten more comfortable with each other.
- Yes. - They're joking around.
Joo-yeon usually don't suggest doing stuff
like that. It's because she feels comfortable.
- It means the two have connected. - That's right.
You got home safe that night right?
Yes.
- Did you get home safe? - Yes.
It's less awkward since it's our second time meeting.
Right?
- It's good, right? - Yes.
It's not awkward, right?
No. It wasn't too awkward that day either.
Really?
I was just pretending to be serious.
- He has a jokester side to him. - He does.
- You're not a serious guy? - No. I joke around a lot.
Then why were you pretending to be serious?
I can't be a jokester from the beginning.
I'm old.
Right?
It's not fun if he's serious all the time.
He has a sweet voice. He really sounds like Sung Si-kyung.
- What did you think of the food? - It was delicious.
It stayed on my mind.
There's a spice that you can't see when you cook.
It's the emotion of the chef.
If he adds the thought of wanting the person to really enjoy the food,
it gets relayed to the person for real.
- Isn't he a generator of wise sayings? - Yes.
He's almost on Kang Ho-dong's level.
Even when you cook something with the same recipe and same technique,
whether you add that emotion or not influences how the food affects the person.
Those things are fun.
That's why your mother's cooking is delicious.
They're the same age. And technically he's 3 months younger than her.
But he feels older than her.
A lot older.
And I don't think Joo-yeon wants to use the informal tone with him.
- She wants to lean on him more. - Because he's mature.
It's natural.
Where's that place?
A crafting experience?
I guess it's an experience hall at the park.
There's a place like that?
What are they making?
- Where should we sit? - You guys can sit right there.
You have to put on your aprons before we start.
You can help each other.
- Oh you put in your head. - Yes.
You're not going to do something funny, right?
"Come here, Joo-yeon."
- Turn around. - He's caring!
I've never put on an apron before.
Do I tie it tight?
It's funny when you tie it to yourself.
- So you're tied together? - You get dragged along.
A couple's apron.
You can take a seat. I'll help you with the materials.
You're going to make troll friends that look like this.
A lot of the couples make it too.
What's your status?
What's their status?
We're...
What the heck!
This isn't fair!
This one ended faster than last week's right?
You must've been very upset to do this.
People have their expectations. I didn't know they'd end it here.
They did that last week too.
He said "We're..."
Why do you sing like that?
What do you think he said?
I'm not sure.
"We're getting to know each other more."
Yes, getting to know each other.
I think he said something in Spanish.
Oh yeah! In Spanish!
Anyway, we'll have to keep watching.
We'll find out next week.
That's crazy!
Hee-chul loves this.
- This is crazy! - Viewers, please hold on to your seats.
Do you want me to bathe you?
Do you want to get slapped by my dad?
It's Seok-hee.
Yo-Han said that?
It can't be Seok-hee. She would've just slapped him.
That's true!
Let's see.
- Where is this place? - Where is that?
- It's Seok-hee. - I told you it's Seok-hee.
Yo-Han said something like that?
I'm sorry but why is Seok-hee always eating?
- That's what I'm saying! - Right?
She did the hair style in trend right now.
Where are you?
Hurry up. I'm hungry.
She said, "Hurry up, I'm hungry."
Why are you hungry when you're already eating?
It must be her friend.
- Isn't it one of her friends? - Ji-seul?
It's either Ji-seul or...
It's someone younger.
Yeon-ji?
- Yeon-ji! - It's Yeon-ji.
That's crazy!
I'm so hungry. I'm going to have some of this.
Me too.
They're really close.
They're super close.
Now I feel bad.
- It's good if they eat a lot. - They're so cute!
Have you watched the show?
- The show? - Yes.
I was going to watch it since you're on it, but
you know I live by myself and don't have a TV.
So it's hard for me to watch it.
- How long has it been? - Seriously. How long has it been?
We had our 100 days celebration last week.
- Already? - Yo-Han did something for you, huh?
A letter.
- He bought me something. - What?
Something.
- He bought you jewelry huh? - Yes.
He bought her jewelry.
You know the whole country knows you guys are dating.
How is it dating in the open?
For real.
It's uncomfortable and burdening.
Stressful.
It's like everyone's in the relationship together.
- The whole country is in it? - Yes.
She's right.
I bet.
People who date in the open always say it's not just them two dating.
There are a lot of things you have to worry about.
- Did you know about that? - I didn't.
But I bet so.
It can be stressful.
It can be hard to handle at that young age.
Yes, it's hard to enjoy it, and it's their first time.
Seok-hee.
Wow, Yo-Han is really...
What? Are they setting Yeon-ji up on a date?
A double date?
Kwang-gi would've been like, "No, no."
He would've said, "Yeon-ji, no, no."
He's handsome.
I've met you before right?
- We've met. - Yes.
- What? - They've met before.
- They've all met before. - Really?
He was there when we were drinking with Yo-Han.
You put a lot of time in your hair today.
I usually do.
Oh, they're all close with each other.
Guys usually don't have blankets over them no matter how cold it is.
It's because he's weak.
Isn't that hypothermia?
You're majoring in English.
You are?
- Yes. - He's very good at English.
He always got first place.
He lived abroad for a long time.
- He has the second generation vibe. - Yes.
There's no more sandwich?
Should we order more?
I want more.
She never does this with me.
She shares a straw with me.
I want to do that too.
Are you guys going to eat anything?
I'm hungry. Should we order something?
- Do you want some sandwich? - Yes.
I think you're the one who wants some.
- No... - Yes you do.
She does.
Her eyes were shaking.
Seok-hee gets shy when there's someone else there.
Isn't she adorable?
Eat.
Eat one.
Say ah.
You eat it. I think I can fit the whole thing in my mouth.
Try it.
- I think I can fit it in my mouth. - Don't do it.
- For real? - He made it look so unappetizing.
Are you sure your mouth doesn't have a hole?
- Yo-Han is adorable. - Yo-Han is very cute.
Does Yo-Han treat you well?
Sure...
He treats me well.
I need to try more.
You should be thankful that she's dating you.
- Yeah, Seok-hee is the best. - That was out of the blue.
I think you made a mistake bringing your friend.
One thing is for sure. No one is on my side here.
You need a friend like that who says the right things.
"You should be thankful that she's dating you."
- If he were on Yo-han's side... - Yeah.
That's why they're best friends.
Why did you call us here so early in the morning?
We said we'd do something I want to do this time.
- What is it? - Oh yeah.
- What are they dating? - What is it?
A double date.
Why did you call us here on your date?
We're all going to chill together.
- We're going to chill, right? - We're going to enjoy it together.
Enjoy it?
Is it something I'll enjoy too?
What does she want to do?
Something to do together?
What can you do to wash together?
Be careful.
- It's a real countryside. - It's refreshing.
What's to do here?
Is that where they have cows?
- Did they go to catch grasshoppers? - Are they going somewhere to eat?
It'd be funny if the 4 of them were going to eat like that.
- What is that? - It's a greenhouse.
They must have a hot spring in there.
I really wanted to come here.
- I was going to come here with Yeon-ji. - For a long time.
- You guys planned this? - Yeah we wanted to come here together.
He's cute. Look at him sitting like he's waiting for me.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Are you here to volunteer for the pound? - Yes.
Seok-hee has such a kind heart!
I'm so shocked that people would abandon their dogs on the road.
- I heard there's a lot of those. - Seriously!
Let me tell you a story that will make you angry.
I do a show in Ulleungdo Island.
People come there on trips and leave their dogs there.
On their trips?
Why would they bring them all the way to Ulleungdo Island to abandon them?
Oh my gosh!
There are so many people who abandon dogs.
Seok-hee is interested in volunteering.
- For dogs? - Not just that.
She volunteers at the children center and elderly homes.
- Can we go in? - Yes. Take these gloves.
Let's tie our hair first.
The city must run the pound, right?
Oh, it's run by an individual? That's amazing.
He must love animals.
They send them for adoption, right?
Let's go.
It's really tiring.
Hi!
They're so cute.
- I want to touch them. - How cute.
- You can come in. - Look at his face.
Hi.
They're so excited. They miss people.
You see the white pads?
There are sick ones too.
- How cute. - You can give me those.
How cute.
Cute!
Seok-hee is really good at that.
Even when she had a part time job, she'd volunteer to clean the bathroom.
Please move, I need to wipe.
- They love people. - It looks like it.
- He's peeing again. - Where?
Which one?
- Because there aren't pads. - How could you?
Where did he pee?
Over there.
My back hurts.
Straighten your neck.
Yo-Han really is tall.
He's really tall.
Yo-Han...
Oh my!
There's space to breathe.
Please move.
We cleaned everything, right?
Doesn't he look like a clown from the back?
- His pants. - Or the guy on wooden sticks.
Do we put them out in the corner?
Hold on.
He's so tiny.
Look at them embracing people.
- That's heartbreaking. - We'll go to a different one now.
- There's a lot of cute ones. - Don't you feel proud?
You guys can split up into two groups and take out the water bowls.
- Water bowls? - Yes, you just need to take them out.
- Should we go in here? - Groups of two?
Yes. Two people per section.
Their nails!
They're going crazy.
They're full of energy.
I think Yo-Han would fall if there are big dogs.
Yo-Han is scared of the dogs.
He is scared of dogs, but his love for Seok-hee is greater.
That's why he came.
- Just this one, right? - Yes.
How cute!
What?
They really did something amazing.
They're like a married couple.
From your perspective, does Seok-hee...
She takes care of Yo-Han.
Even though she acts cold, she cares for him.
It's like she's taking care of a kid.
- Like a mom? - Yes.
A motherly love.
I'll wash them with soap. You rinse them.
Wear the rubber gloves. You're going to hurt your hands.
They're uncomfortable.
- You're going to touch the poop. - I'll just wash my hands after.
Yeah.
Seok-hee is a good worker.
- No, you rinse them. - She's not wearing the gloves?
Put them on!
It's fine.
It has the dogs' poop.
Seok-hee must really love animals.
They have a cat house too?
They're a bit cleaner.
Cats are clean.
Yeon-ji and Hyung-tae are here.
Oh yeah, Yeon-ji has a cat.
My cat is the cutest cat in my eyes.
How cute!
Look at him!
Real couples volunteer together. And people who volunteer together can end up together.
My colleague also met his wife at a group like this.
He did?
Oh yeah, I bet no one plays with them.
Yeah.
I don't want to admit it.
It smells like the tuna can we have.
Should I leave this here?
Will they eat it if we put it in there?
That must be good.
I'm hungry.
You're hungry after seeing cat food?
- We need to go inside. - Oh, this was the water?
Have some water. You were thirsty!
You're cute.
They're attacking him.
It means the dogs are looking down on him too.
They think he's below them.
They know the hierarchy.
They've decided on the hierarchy.
For the last step, you'll bathe the dogs.
How should I hold him?
- Like this? - Is this where the text is from?
I think so.
Should we start from the top?
It must be nice to do that with the person you love.
In that kind of space.
You'll be blessed from the volunteering.
It'd be really nice if you have the same mind regarding that.
It must be nice to have someone bathe you.
No one bathes me.
Do you want me to bathe you?
Do you want to get slapped by my dad?
I mean just your face!
She didn't slap him because she had soap in her hands.
Because she needs to hit him with the shower head.
It feels good, right?
We can keep these on, right?
Do that thing dogs do.
- There you go. - He's doing it!
- This way? - No, the other way.
Seok-hee really opens her heart to the dogs.
Let's go. You're done.
Seo-beom, have you volunteered with your wife?
He does a lot.
I go on a couple.
My wife does a lot of them.
She must've learned from you guys.
We're going to walk the dogs now.
There are two dachshunds, and remember the malamute from earlier?
- Yes. - Right.
We're going to walk them.
You have to walk the dogs.
Dachshunds are really strong.
They're super strong.
- With those legs. - Yes.
- Hold on. - What's going on?
- A big dog! A husky! It's a malamute.
He's too strong!
The leash is tangled.
Come here. Your arm!
- I think that's the leg. - Your leg!
He's really strong.
- Really? - He's going to drag you.
You can go.
The dog is the one walking Yo-Han.
No!
He's the dog that pulls sleighs. He's really strong.
He has to run with him.
- Calm down! - The malamute is walking Yo-Han.
Yo-Han, no!
You can't go that way!
- He used the formal tone just now! - To the dog.
What is Yo-han's arm breaks?
Yo-Han, run with him.
Go!
Let's go.
Yo-Han!
Who's the owner?
He's going to fall!
It's like he's ploughing the field.
Ploughing...
His power is beyond your imagination.
I want to try
Let's go!
Say, "Let's go." Then he'll run.
You're really strong.
The malamute knows.
He knows she's done it before.
"This human is stronger than me."
Don't get tangled up.
It's okay.
How did they end up at the pound?
Our team recently rescued these two.
Because the breeding place went out of business, they threw them away in a box.
So we rescued them.
A breeding center.
How did Tansang end up here?
Tansang was found in the winter without his genitals.
What?
Because the owner hit him so much, his genitalia fell off.
He must've been in a lot of pain since it was cold.
How badly was he beaten?
It's very sad.
I bet the owner would recognize him if he saw this.
Yeah.
They wouldn't even feel bad if they were able to abuse their dog like that.
Of course. They're not normal.
He was really scared of people at first and was on guard.
Did he recover?
He's healthy now?
He loves people now.
- It looks like it. - That's great.
He followed me from the beginning.
You must be sad every time you get a new dog.
They come here with some pain in their hearts.
People shouldn't abandon them, and they shouldn't get dogs without thinking.
Of course. It's like raising a kid.
- Yes. - Seriously.
People have to think things through.
Not just out of curiosity...
Let's go inside.
Bye!
Bye Tansang!
It was a really good day.
Bye Tansang.
- Bye! - Take care!
I heard saying goodbye is really sad.
You end up going again.
It's hard to even watch the clip.
Yeon-ji likes animals too.
They can't talk, but I'm sure they were very happy too.
- The dogs? - Yes.
Bye!
This is sad.
I got attached.
It was a rewarding day.
It was sad but...
The dogs were so bright, so it was great.
- We can come back. - Yeah.
We should come often and play with them.
This is pretty close to our homes, right?
I really want to come back.
- For Tansang? - You really want to do it?
Yes, I really do.
It was a good date for everyone.
It'd be nice if you went on a volunteering date with your future girlfriend.
It's a better date.
You get close from the meaningful time.
They worked very hard.
- You're seeing a new side of her. - I'm proud of her.
You must be proud.
I think my kids will learn from this too.
It's not an easy thing to do.
I saw today that Seok-hee is a woman of actions.
They're a charming couple.
- We'll see you next week! - That's all for today!
Hello.
You look prettier in person.
They look very good together.
- He has a nice first impression. - That's good.
It's because his last name is Song.
- Do you know Ahn Jae-wook's hair? - Did that shock you?
He's joking around. Although they're dad jokes...
Want me to teach you?
- Let's ask them to take a picture! - Just stand there!
- He wants to take it together. - Just stand there!
I told you I was making a song.
A song?