KYDS Sub
The dads are watching. My Daughters' Men Season 4!
We're already on our 12th episode now.
We've become attached to the dads but also to their daughters and their dates.
I'm already sad because we don't have much time left.
Time went by so fast.
And stop trying to hook me up with So-Jin on this show.
For real--
So-Jin wrote me a letter!
- Hee-chul!
- Hold on!
- That's not what it's about!
Hold on before you talk about the letter.
It's supposed to be a secret letter.
Dear lovely Hee-chul, Merry Christmas.
Oh, it's for Christmas.
I'm very happy and joyful because you're here.
It's not like that.
I'll pray that we'll always be happy and peaceful together.
Let's have a warm winter together Hee-chul.
What?
Your face is red.
It's really not like that.
"Today is out 103rd day together."
It's already been 103 days?
That means it's been past 3 months.
We're secretly dating.
And isn't this what people used to say a long time ago?
A lipstick mark.
People used to do it a long time ago.
What does it say at the bottom?
The thing at the bottom?
You're going to say it out loud?
"You better take care of me."
That made this whole thing sound like a lie.
You ruined it!
So there's no misunderstanding, So-Jin wrote all of the MCs a letter.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Since we've read So-jin's letter,
we should read the daughter's text too.
- Yes.
- Let's hurry up and see it.
- What does it say?
- What a perfect timing for this text.
- This is perfect.
- Yes.
Look me in the eyes.
I got a feeling that you're my partner.
"Dear lovely Hee-chul..."
Stop it!
You're teasing us.
Partner means like school partner right?
- Or odd or even.
- Odd or even?
Doesn't that mean she went on a blind date?
It's Woo-ju.
- She should be going on a new blind date.
- Right.
You're right.
It's Joo-yeon.
Maybe Joo-yeon did a parody of something.
Let's watch the clip.
I'm curious.
- Is it a temple?
- Where is that?
- Is it a folk village?
- It's a folk village.
Who is it?
I told you it was Woo-ju.
Why is she going all over the place?
She's off to find a new partner.
I thought it'd be Joo-yeon.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Is that him?
What is such a beautiful woman doing in our village?
It's a deer?
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Is that her blind date?
- Hello.
Your hands are cold.
I picked this up on the way.
Thank you.
What brings you here?
Oh he's talking in an accent because he's a deer.
There are a lot of different characters at the folk village.
Why did I come here?
- I came for a blind date.
- A blind date?
So I'd like to formally introduce myself.
No way!
The deer is her blind date?
Hello.
A blind date...
He's going on a date looking like that?
I wish I could be your date.
Is it not possible?
- What a funny guy.
- I was flustered.
Could I come in for a second?
He sounds like Lee Sun-gyun!
"One vongole pasta..."
Could I come in for a second?
Sure.
It is you, huh?
- Is it the deer?
- Is it Lee Sun-gyun?
It really must be him!
It is you, huh?
It is the deer.
For real?
I had no idea he'd be her blind date.
I'm your blind date.
Really?
Oh, he doesn't usually play the deer character.
Hello.
I'm lying.
What the heck?
Were you going to hit me?
I'm just trying to loosen you up because you look nervous.
- I'll go get him right now.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
He's here. The door opened.
Hello.
His last name is Song!
He has a nice first impression!
- Hello.
You look prettier in person.
He said that right away.
He's handsome.
- You look even better in real life.
- No I don't.
Let me first introduce myself.
I'm Song Ki-ho and I'm the CEO of an interior design company.
An interior design company!
- They're Song and Song couple!
- You're right!
Double Song.
Like Song Hye-gyo and Song Joong-ki!
Song Ki-ho and Song Woo-ju.
- What do you think about him?
- I really like his first impression.
- He has a genius side.
- Yeah, he looks smart.
It's probably because he's a Song.
I'm Song Woo-ju and I'm a college student.
I saw you eating on the show.
- He has a really nice voice.
- He does have a nice voice.
He looks very smart.
You're close to my ideal type of woman.
- Really?
- Yes.
Thank you.
How old are you?
How old do I look?
28 or 29?
- 28 or 29?
- Yes.
We're the same age.
Really?
Nice to meet you, friend!
We're the same age.
Our last names are both Song,
and we have a lot of similarities.
What's are your hobbies or special talents?
Is it too boring of a question?
- I like listening to music and drawing.
- Really?
That's similar to mine.
- I listen to jazz or RnB pop.
- Jazz and pop!
- Do you know HONNE?
- Of course.
The music taste has to match well.
And matching tastes are important for Woo-ju.
- Aren't they really good?
- They're amazing.
I practiced piano because of HONNE.
- Their song is amazing on a rainy day.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
- The deer is here again.
- Hello.
Here is your order of black herbal tea and Shiquan Dabo tea.
- First...
- That's dried ginger, right?
- You know about them?
- I bought a bunch on home shopping.
- It's good.
- It's really good for your body.
Right.
It's good for your throat.
Have a good time together.
Yes, please leave.
- A man shouldn't slouch his shoulders.
- He's sitting right there.
You'd be intruding if you stay too long.
- I have to go.
- He's witty.
He can play along.
Let me say one last thing before I leave.
Please put background music to this.
She can't drink too much.
He must've watched our show too.
So I hope you'll serve her tea instead of drinks today.
Please be happy!
Good bye.
I was excited to see characters like him--
And...
He keeps coming back.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
But it's your guys' blind date today.
So the folk village has prepared hanboks for you guys so you can have a fun date.
There are a lot of events there.
You look happier now.
That was a little helpful.
You can make beautiful memories if you go around the village in hanbok.
I'll leave them here.
Please be happy.
The deer is playing the matchmaker.
He is.
- Shall we go out to look around now?
- Yes.
If it's the deer again, I'm going to...
No.
He looks good.
He looks good in hanbok.
- It's not easy to look good in hanbok.
- Seriously.
He's the type that parents like.
- I'm excited to see Woo-ju.
- Yes.
She looks pretty.
How pretty.
She looks like a fairy.
You're so beautiful.
Ki-ho fell in love after seeing Woo-ju in hanbok.
- His eyes were full of hearts.
- He looks like he's in bliss.
- He looked like he was in love.
- She's his woman in that moment.
She looks really good in hanbok.
She looks good in that color.
- You're so pretty.
- No I'm not.
- It looks really good on you.
- No...
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
- Have you seen Woo-ju in hanbok?
- Is it your first time?
Yeah.
- Doesn't she wear one on holidays?
- People don't do that these days.
- I was worried it might be cold.
- It looks like a historical drama.
The folk village is really pretty.
Am I speaking in a dialect?
- No.
- Really?
Are you trying to be polite?
You're not.
- I'm not?
- No.
You're good.
Thanks.
- They're speaking in causal tones.
- Ki-ho speaks in a dialect.
Isn't that a swing?
It's been a while.
You need to be careful getting on.
Let me help you.
You have to wear a swing when getting on that hanbok.
Wear a swing when getting on a hanbok?
You have to wear a hanbok when getting on that swing.
They look like Chun-hyang and Mong-ryong on a date.
This is fun.
You look like a painting.
He really likes her. He said she looks like a painting.
Do you really mean that?
You really look pretty.
This is really fun.
It will be dangerous if you go too high.
You're going high.
He's never been on that swing before.
He's falling backwards.
His neck must be hurting from staring at Woo-ju so much.
We might do a full spin if we focus too much.
What are such shabby people doing in a fancy place--
Is it the deer?
What are such fancy people doing at a shabby place like this?
There must be different characters there.
You look like you've been dating for a year.
He's a goblin.
This is good.
This is called odd or even.
I was right!
This is crazy!
This is where the text came from?
No way!
I have coins in this hand.
Do you think it's an odd or even number?
Please shake it.
Shake it?
Look me in the eyes.
Is it odd?
I got a feeling it's even.
Why did you make us get all excited?
It feels like it's even.
You got a feeling?
You and I are partners from now on.
But if it's an odd number...
If it's an odd number...
Ki-ho will be left alone.
We'll shoot the show together without him.
If they lose, Woo-ju's blind date will switch to that goblin.
Are you ready?
- I'll reveal it right now.
- I'll trust her this time too.
- You do?
- Don't be like that.
Didn't anyone tell you to be careful of who you trust?
- You'll learn today.
- It's fine.
- Will you go with even?
- I'll go with even.
You guys pick even, I pick odd.
Let me open my hand.
Woo-ju must be so anxious.
- It's odd.
- It's even.
What does that laugh mean?
Did he make it be even?
It's odd.
- It's even.
- What is it?
- It's even!
- How is this even?
That's right. You and I are together now.
- He's stopping him.
- How cute.
Then you're...
- It's even!
- You take this and leave.
All right, from now on--
It's nice to meet you. I'm the new blind date on "My Daughters' Men."
I'm the goblin from the folk village.
The folk village look fun.
It's changed since our time.
They got close fast.
They got close real fast.
They took the advantage that being the same age gives.
I think they both like each other.
The age is perfect.
It feels like we're going to get a second Song and Song couple.
- Let's go in here.
- Okay.
- The floors are toasty.
- They are.
There are a lot of places with toast floors today.
I saw that you eat a lot on the show.
I saw the part where you tied your hair and eat.
Did you?
- It was very attractive.
- Really?
It's obvious on Ki-ho's face that he likes Woo-ju a lot.
He said she looks pretty when she eats.
People say that but when they really see me eat,
they think I eat very messy.
No, no.
He looks like he fell for her.
He looks kind.
They call it "talking" these days.
That's right.
How long do you "talk" to someone for?
I think the number of times we meet is more important Thant the time length.
Meeting 3 times over 3 weeks is different than meeting 10 times over 2 weeks.
She's right.
I think on an average, about a month.
I get to know someone slowly.
So we need to meet often.
Can't you just start dating right away if first dates go well?
- I don't think the time is important.
- Yeah.
I think within a minimum of 5 dates...
Jae-young, did you have a "talking" stage when you were younger?
Yeah, but first impressions were important for us.
That lasts a really long time.
It determines everything.
I think it lasted all the way to marriage.
But the guy has to like the girl more.
That's right.
You share my theory.
It has to be like that.
It's a slang that young people use these days.
But the "talking" stage is the most fun.
- The excitement...
- And then move on to someone else.
That's how they get to your age.
What's wrong with my age?
It's a perfect age for falling in love.
I love marinated crabs.
Woo-ju likes marinated crabs.
It's hard to eat that on your blind date.
People usually don't because you have to suck on them.
You do and the smell lingers.
- Some time has passed now.
- Right.
Could we use the informal tone now?
Of course.
Yes.
I'll start first.
Okay.
You're chill.
- Shall we eat?
- Let's eat.
You look like you're having fun.
You've got to eat the crabs with your hands.
You know you have to suck on them, right?
Of course.
You know how to eat.
Look at his neck bone!
I'm sorry but I have to eat that for dinner tonight.
Tonight's menu is marinated crabs.
I can't believe I get to watch your mukbang in real life.
Woo-ju doesn't act coy.
That's why I like her.
Yeah.
I don't like it when girls go, "Oh my."
She eats a lot and looks pretty doing it.
This is good.
Let's squeeze out the meat and mix it with the rice.
- She knows how to eat it.
- Of course she does.
Yeah.
That's it!
We used to mix it in the shell.
That's it.
- I'm getting annoyed.
- That's a lot for two people.
That looks so good.
It's so good when you mix it with the rice.
It's the best.
And you top it off with seaweed--
Yes, there you go!
That's what I'm talking about.
- You're supposed to put the rice in there.
- That's right.
This is the best side dish.
Who said this was okay?
She's joking around.
Her sense of humor is the same as her dad's.
She's cute.
I always say "Stop crabbing around"
whenever I eat crabs with her.
We're really enjoying this.
We finished it already.
I really like that you eat a lot.
I stop myself when the other person doesn't eat as much as me.
I guess you don't gain weight though.
I exercise a lot.
He looks like he does too.
I should learn from you.
- They cleared it.
- Who said it was too much food?
- You can't help yourself.
- They inhaled it.
- I should eat marinated crabs tonight.
- They're really good.
There are some forbidden foods for first dates.
That's right there's a forbidden list of food for first dates.
Things that get stuck in your teeth or make your breath smell.
So I was worried that this would be considered a forbidden food.
How did you feel when I suggested it?
I was really happy.
That's good.
What would you say if the guy suggested getting marinated crabs?
I'd like it.
What's the most memorable first date food?
We had lamb together, and I really liked it.
- What about you?
- I had jajangmyeon.
I had chicken soup.
I met her through work so we had packed lunches.
We had chicken ribs.
We had seafood stew.
We had boiled dumplings.
How cute.
The fact that he remembers that...
It somehow suits him.
- Everyone remembers it.
- Of course.
That's Cheonggye creek.
I heard famous artists make those.
It looks a lot prettier in winter.
That's pretty!
Wow, I think they made that out of cloth, right?
Should we take a picture?
- Do you want to?
- Yes.
- Want me to take it for you?
- Are you good?
I am.
Really?
- Here I go.
- Okay.
I'll take one more.
Are you sure you took good ones?
Let me see.
But you can't see your face because the light is behind you.
- They look like a long time couple!
- For real.
You can't see my face at all.
You're really good at taking pictures.
I think they got close right away.
- Is it because they both like each other?
- Yes.
Let's write our wishes in first two lines.
And for the other two lines, let's write how we felt after meeting each other.
They're writing it in front of each other.
One, two, three!
I'll read it out loud for you.
Thank you for giving me a fun time.
You put a smiley face. I like it.
I want to see more sides of you.
He's asking her out on another date.
- Should we make it?
I thought doing stuff like this was cheesy.
But it's actually fun.
Yeah.
They're making the lanterns.
That looks really cool.
They're making wish lanterns.
Do they float it on water later?
I'm done.
I finished mine too.
- I think we did a good job.
- Yeah we did.
We have to pray. Hurry up and pray.
I wonder what they're praying for.
Hold on!
Let's do it together.
Wow, they're putting it in the water.
Bye!
I hope everything we wrote comes true.
It's already far away.
Should we get going now?
I'm sad too. How does one year go by so fast?
Seriously.
2018 is over now.
They spent time together in 2018 and are entering the new year together.
So I bet it's even more exciting.
What did you think about today?
I had a lot of fun today.
This is my first time seeing this in real life.
Thank you.
I thought a lot about where I should take you.
I'm so thankful that you're happy with the things I prepared.
No, I'm the one who's thankful.
If you had fun today,
why don't we meet each other again?
There it is.
He says things very nicely.
What will she say?
She didn't answer?
I think it's going to go well.
Do you think Woo-ju just sees him as a friend or...
I think Woo-ju is interested in him too.
- We got a text from daughter this time.
- Once again.
What's this?
My dad would really like it.
This sounds like Seok-hee.
She talks about me a lot.
Yeah, she showed you off last time.
I think she's talking about me.
Soo-bin also talks about her dad a lot too.
She does. Is it Soo-bin?
I think it sounds more like Soo-bin than Seok-hee.
Seok-hee wouldn't phrase it like that.
Joo-yeon's blind date is a chef.
You're right!
She said it after seeing a dish!
Oh, because he's a chef!
Joo-yeon thinks about her dad a lot.
That's right she does.
Where is that?
They're going on a trip.
- Seok-hee?
- It's Seok-hee.
It's Seok-hee!
Where is she going?
It looks like she's at an airport.
It's Kimpo airport.
Doesn't that mean she's going abroad?
I bet it's Japan.
You're going to break the suitcase!
He's worried about the suitcase.
Are they going to Japan?
Wow.
Seok-hee is always with that jacket and suitcase.
- She's going somewhere with Yo-Han.
- Where is she going?
Airport fashion!
His walk got better.
Seok-hee.
He does look good though.
- He's gotten more handsome.
- Yo-Han looks good.
It's so cold.
He looks good if he doesn't talk.
The first thing he said was "It's cold."
- Did you get a lot of sleep?
- No.
- How much sleep did you get?
- Where are they going anyway?
Are they going to Japan together?
Kimpo airport could mean it's somewhere in the country.
But you can also go to Japan, Taiwan, China...
- Oh, they're going to Jejudo.
- Alone? To Jejudo?
It's so pretty!
Jejudo is prettier in winter than in summer.
Seo-beom has changed a lot too.
Before, he used to get upset when he thought they were going on a trip together.
- But now...
- He's fine.
He's understanding.
We're in Jejudo.
The two look like they're on their honeymoon.
Just being there makes you excited.
You've gotten very used to riding in the passenger seat.
I'll get my license next year.
It's okay. I like driving.
I want to try it too.
They're renting a car.
- You have to rent one there.
- Is it this one?
It's not this one.
Is it this one?
- Yeah.
- It's nice.
- It's cute, right?
- Yeah.
Isn't this expensive?
But you might have to fold yourself.
Why?
Oh, it's low.
This must be a two seater.
- The color is pretty.
- I like the smell.
Did you see how she said that?
Dang, it's pretty.
Want to see something cool?
Yeah, what is it?
What is it?
You prepared something weird, huh?
It's a convertible.
What a girl crush.
It's opening!
I wish it'd open all the way.
What?
What's going on?
- How cute.
- She's shocked.
That must be nice.
The air is nice in Jejudo.
I've never been in a convertible before.
Me neither.
I didn't get to do that when I was younger.
I'm jealous.
Yeah.
What if people think we're weird with the top down?
Why would they?
It's refreshing and nice.
It feels refreshing even when it's cold because you're happy.
Seok-hee is super excited.
How cute!
The beach is really pretty!
I wonder where they went.
He looks sad all of a sudden.
Isn't it a day trip?
- You know they don't do that anymore.
- It's an overnight trip.
Seok-hee might kill Yo-Han if he tries to make a move.
I realized that when they did jiu-jitsu.
Yo-han's going to break a bone.
I realized I have nothing to worry about during jiu-jitsu.
Yongduam Rock.
This is really nice.
It must be a photo zone. I'll take one for you.
- The clouds are pretty.
- They're pretty.
Let's take it together.
- I'll take one for you.
- I'll take one for you too.
Let's ask someone to take it for us.
- Just stand there.
- Let's ask someone!
It looks like the roles have reversed.
He's so cute.
Let's take it together.
I don't want to take it alone.
Stand next to that warning sign.
You've got to take a thrilling picture.
- Let's take it together!
- You have to make it thrilling.
Let's take one together.
Yo-Han wants to take the picture together.
He should just stand there first.
- But he does listen.
- Do a good job.
Yo-Han might blow away in the wind.
One, two...
Yo-Han has gotten even more handsome.
I'll take one for you.
Let's ask someone to take one for us!
Why does he have to talk like that?
- Seok-hee hates taking pictures.
- She does.
I can't because I look fat.
No you don't!
You're not fat at all.
The water is really clear.
- Have you seen something like that?
- What is it?
I've never seen that before.
What is that?
- What is it?
- They're female divers.
They sell what they caught.
- Right?
- Yes.
They're super fresh!
- That's amazing!
- They have that in Jejudo?
That looks so good!
Did you catch these?
- Did you just catch them?
- Someone went in just now. Look.
She's catching some right now.
- What's this?
- Abalones.
And these are conches.
- These are horned conches.
- I want these.
They look the most safe, huh?
Want me to mix them up with abalones and this?
Yes.
$10 if you touch them.
$10 for touching!
Try touching this one.
Like this?
But my hands aren't that clean.
He looks like the perfect target to play jokes on.
He doesn't bite right?
- I think I know who you are
- Who do you think I am?
Who are you?
Want me to guess?
You're Jo Gap-kyung's daughter.
How did she know?
They watch this show.
What's your relationship with each other?
We're dating.
- You're dating?
- Yes.
She can say that comfortably now.
They're dating. He's her husband.
He's not my husband.
But he's going to be your husband.
- I'm not sure...
- Why not?
The old Seok-hee would've been upset,
but now she just smiles.
She doesn't seem to hate the idea.
Seo-beom, how would you feel if they wanted to get married?
Yo-Han as a son-in-law?
I'm okay with whoever Seok-hee wants to marry.
I'm going to try this one first.
- That's what real raw fish is.
- That looks so good.
The view must be great too.
It's good.
I don't think I can eat sea squirt.
Seok-hee knows how to eat.
Is it good?
Sea squirts are the best to get your appetite going.
I should try it too.
It's so good.
Why are you putting so much sauce?
Yo-Han is basically just eating the sauce.
He might as well just dip his finger in the sauce and eat it.
It's not my style.
The ocean is pretty.
That really is an open view restaurant.
This is a hot place.
- My dad would really like it.
- Like what?
This is where the text is from.
He loves them.
It's so good.
This is...
Look. He looks so happy.
Saying that her dad would like it...
She thought of you when eating something good.
Parents are supposed to think of their kids when they eat something good.
But she's thinking of her dad.
And I really love seafood.
Yeah, that's why Seok-hee...
It's not common to think about your dad at a time like that.
- Buddy, you finished everything?
- Yes.
- Did you enjoy it?
Which one was the best?
- The sea squirt.
- The sea squirts?
I'm happy you finished them all.
- It was good.
- Thank you.
- You guys should come back.
- Okay!
Come here on your honeymoon instead of going abroad.
That must be memorable for them.
Take care!
If I go to Jejudo with
my girlfriend, I just
want to hold her hands
and walk around freely.
At the hotel lobby?
I don't know why my head hurts so much today.
Wow, look how clear the water is.
- That's so cool!
- This looks fun.
What if he falls in?
It must be really hard to get his balance because he's tall.
And he's a klutz.
We're going.
Do I hold it like this?
Yo-Han does everything to try to be the man.
He said, "Why isn't this moving?"
We don't see sitcoms these days,
but this is a true sitcom.
Yo-Han is...
I guess I'm supposed to do it like this.
I'm driving right now.
- Is he driving it?
- He finds it really cool.
I can't help it. It's my first time.
Grab it shoulder width apart...
Then you should put your hands closer to each other.
I don't want to do this.
Seok-hee made fun of his narrow shoulders.
How hurtful.
Here we go.
This is fun.
It's a lot more boring than you expected, huh?
No, I really like it.
Yo-Han is awesome.
I've wanted to try something like this.
Isn't the ocean nice?
Isn't it pretty?
Let's go to that island.
You want to?
Don't laugh.
I'm trying my best right now.
The two are cute.
I got a cramp.
He got a cramp.
You didn't even row that much!
It's very tiring.
I want to try it.
How do I do it?
Hold it like this.
It's hard, right?
You see how I tired I must be, right?
What's with all the noises?
I'll do it. It's hard, right?
No, this is fun.
She's good.
Let's go.
Go where?
Somewhere.
She looks like Guan Yu.
It looked like the Green Dragon Crescent Blade.
With her hair flying too.
Just row in the direction you want to go.
I'm going to go where there aren't anyone.
There you go.
With the same strength.
You're good.
Seok-hee, you're really good.
I'm good at everything.
I've realized that you're not stronger, but as strong as me.
That was his last pride.
We're the same or similar.
I think I'm doing a good job right now.
We're going fast.
I'm going really fast right now.
They're moving fast.
That's like a boat.
For real, that's the only one moving.
One, two!
One...
Are you embarrassed of me?
One, two!
You can put the paddle down and get off.
Just get off.
Why are you grabbing the paddle instead of me?
This place is the most fun.
No rowing was the most fun for me.
Stop it!
Have you guys gone to Jejudo to go on a date when you were younger?
- I went for my honeymoon.
- Honeymoon?
A lot of people went to Jejudo for their honeymoon.
What did you do there?
A driver would come, and we have to do whatever he says the whole day.
You wished the night came faster, huh?
Yeah, I wished that we could just go to our room.
We don't want to ride horses and take pictures, right?
It's so funny hearing him say that.
Joo-yeon is adorable.
Is she that cute at home too?
Hold it.
She's like Demi Moore from "Ghost."
I bet she got a lot of butterflies.
That's nice. Where is that?
Oh, a guest house?
Bunch of people get together.
You save money and eat together.
And you share about the vacation spots.
Are we supposed to eat together?
- Yes.
- It's our first time at a guest house.
- It's our first time too.
- Really?
Thank you.
Is this how the culture is?
Yes, it's a party guest house.
We share information together too.
You get to know new people.
Tonight's menu is black pork.
That looks so good!
You guys are a couple, right?
- Yes.
- It looks like it.
How long have you guys been dating for?
We just had our 100 days celebration.
What a fresh new couple!
You have the best reaction.
That looks so good.
Thank you!
Look at his manners.
He always takes care of Seok-hee first.
- Who is she going to give the wrap to?
- Yo-Han of course!
Seok-hee!
If she had given it to Yo-Han,
it means she's changed.
A second wrap!
A person shouldn't change.
It's really good.
Yo-Han, please pick up a spoon.
He doesn't eat!
Hes always only using chopsticks even though there's a spoon.
He only eats a little bit.
Look at Seok-hee eat.
Seok-hee, that's enough!
Seok-hee!
It's cute.
Is Ms. Hong usually this quiet or...
No, it's because she's enjoying the food a lot.
You have to let her be so she can eat a lot.
He's her spokesperson.
Her lawyer.
Which place did you like the best from today?
I liked just being in the car the most.
He liked it when they're alone.
I wasn't into going on trips before,
but I've been on many since dating her.
I think it's really good.
You guys haven't been to Udo, huh?
Udo?
- Udo is really nice.
- Have you guys been?
Seok-hee...
It's different. You have to spend the night in Udo if youre in Jejudo.
The boat times are...
I'll tell you later when the last boat time is.
When the boat stops running.
We should exchange numbers.
He was going for it.
Let's do a toast.
Shall we do a last toast?
Thank you!
I'll take you to your rooms. It's this way.
Follow me.
I'll tell you the password.
One room?
It's fine now.
What?
That's not right.
They have separate rooms.
This is nice.
Their rooms should be farther apart.
There's a connecting room inside.
It'd be funny if they went through the wall.
But I trust Yo-Han.
Please don't lay down.
Why do you look like you've collapsed?
It's too big for one person.
It is really big.
You can cook there too.
Hong Seok-hee!
You can hear him.
- Who is it?
- Are you going to sleep?
- What?
- They should grab a beer.
- Yeah, they went all the way over there.
- No, why?
I know the password.
- What?
- He knows the password?
He saw the owner put it in.
Oh, I'm wrong.
That was dangerous. I'm going to report you.
It'd be funny if
she really did.
What if she takes him to
get a marriage license?
I'm an old man.
Where's that?
Did you sleep well?
No.
- Why not?
- We were supposed to get up early.
But it rained out of nowhere.
We were supposed to see the sunrise.
Oh, they were going to see the sunrise but it rained.
That always happens.
- What?
- It usually looks like that?
Wow, that's amazing!
You know the song I told you I was writing?
He's writing a song?
I finished it.
There's a piano here.
Finally?
He wrote a song.
Listen to it. You're the first one hearing it.
Listen to it and tell me what you think.
- Play it.
- I think you can listen to it.
But don't be so serious. It's funny.
But this is a serious song.
He plays the piano too?
I'm going to be serious.
Don't laugh.
Yo-Han poured his heart into it.
Let's listen to it.
It's okay...
Come on.
- I told you not to laugh.
- I wasn't!
- Don't laugh.
- I'm always smiling.
I want you to listen to it carefully, okay?
Play it.
It's okay...
This is just messed up!
This is messed up editing!
We're not okay!
This isn't okay!
This is really...
This is really wrong.
We really wanted to hear it, right?
This isn't okay.
Seo-beom, you're an artist too.
Can't you tell from the first line?
They lyrics are what's important.
He sat Seok-hee down and told her it's the first song he's written.
I wonder what the lyrics are.
"Is it okay to have that big of an appetite?"
What if it's something like that?
"Don't you get sick?"
"Is your stomach okay?"
"Your digestion ability is amazing."
We got a text from the guy this time.
Yes...
- "What's wrong?"
- "I can't stop!"
"That scared me."
I can't stop my love for you!
We ruined it.
I think they're talking about driving a car.
"I can't stop the car!"
The brakes are broken!
And then he stops the car, and she goes, "You scared me."
I think there's going to be a kiss.
"I can't stop my feelings."
Something like this. "I'm sorry I can't stop."
And then a kiss.
- "You scared me!"
- That's it.
Let's see how we were baited this time.
- What's your relationship status?
- Oh, it's Joo-yeon.
We're...
dating but we're not official yet.
- We're not dating yet.
- He's honest.
I see.
I hope your feelings grow through this experience.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
We need to get the water.
- It's already getting on my hand.
- We'll water it little by little.
- Little by little?
- Yes.
- I'm going to do it like I'm making bread.
- Like he's making bread.
This is what you do when you make bread.
Try doing it like me.
It really does look like I'm making bread.
This is what you do when you bake.
You're very fast.
Mine won't clump together.
He's doing it like he's making food.
He might taste it too.
This is pretty hard.
Use this one.
- It's going to be easy to work with.
- Why is it hot?
Did my affection get in there?
He said that directly?
He has such a nice smile.
Wow, this is so cool.
Are you done?
- Yes.
- Is it working?
- Are you bringing it back to life?
- It's alive again.
He's good because it's like making dough.
I'll put it in for you.
What a gentleman.
Let's see.
He's craft with his hands like a true chef.
Where should I put it? Here?
- Yeah.
- But it kept coming off.
It sticks. Try it.
It won't? I'll do it for you.
Wasn't he using a formal tone before?
Does your heart flutter if a guy uses a casual tone little by little?
Yes, it becomes comfortable naturally...
- Using a casual tone here and there?
- Yes.
Got it, kiddo.
- Did you guys have a good time?
- Yes.
- Shall we take a look?
- Sure.
But he keeps laughing.
It looked like things were going well.
You put bangs on him?
Do you know Ahn Jae-wook's hair?
Oh, I see. It's Ahn Jae-wook...
You can tell his age from that.
- You sound like him!
- You're good!
You could be a singer.
Please help me out.
Shall we take a look?
- You're not shocked, right?
- No!
It wasn't supposed to be that shape.
- But this is still really cute.
- It's cute, right?
- Good work.
- Thank you.
They hadn't decided to use the casual tone yet.
I asked So-Jin earlier.
I guess it makes your heart flutter when there's a causal tone here and there?
Yes. It becomes awkward when you say, "Let's use the casual tone."
So he's just putting it here and there to make her feel comfortable.
You use formal tones and say, "Did you eat? It's this way."
And then say, "Hey, be careful."
Like this?
You were accurate this time.
Hee-chul looks cool today.
You hit the nail on the head.
They went camping all of a sudden?
She's tired.
She must be really sleeping.
What are you doing?
Are you sleeping?
You told me to rest.
I was just laying here.
This must be it!
- He's shaking it.
- Isn't it too low?
- To the ground?
- Yeah.
- I wanted to hang it higher, but...
- You can't huh?
I'm short, so it can't go any higher.
You get sleepy when someone shakes the hammock for you.
It's like shaking a cradle.
- Are you shaking it?
- Yes.
- This is really fun.
- Is it really fun?
Isn't it too much?
He shouldn't shake it that hard.
That looks scary.
A hammock can cause a fight.
This is making me dizzy.
Let's look inside together.
Camping!
- This is...
- Yes?
I should open up the sleeping bag.
Oh, you're supposed to do it like this.
Are you supposed to go in like this?
Have you slept in a sleeping bag before?
At home when I was a baby.
- At home?
- Yes.
Joo-yeon has become cuter because she's with someone her age.
You're going to lay down right now?
- I'm not going to lay down!
- Hurry up and come outside.
We need to eat.
Why do you keep trying
to cook for me?
Because we're hungry.
This is warm.
I prepared some ingredients.
- Wow, you're going to cook?
- I bet he's good.
It's making me have high expectations.
- Look at the ingredients!
- That's camping food?
Isn't that a restaurant?
I'm going to make you two dishes.
It's Spanish style roasted chicken.
Spanish style roasted chicken?
They're eating a Spanish dish at a camping ground.
And Portugal seafood soup.
Portugal?
Let's eat.
It sounds good even if I don't know what it is.
- You have to be careful.
- Why?
Because...
Step aside for a second.
What is it?
I got ride of the scent with alcohol.
They're cooking very well right now.
If you put onions with chicken,
it tastes good.
That's right.
Chefs look the coolest when they're cutting stuff.
Let's learn the recipe.
We're going to cook the mushrooms slowly at the same time too.
Okay.
There's nothing Joo-yeon can help with.
Want me to teach you how to stir fry?
Yeah.
It's simple.
Did you hear her say, "Yeah?"
Joo-yeon is cute.
I think she's definitely seeing him more as a man.
- You just use your wrist.
- Okay.
- Only the left hand?
- You can use the right hand too.
- Can I use both hands?
- Yes. Grab it.
I bet she got a lot of butterflies.
One, two, three.
Do it lightly.
One, two, three! Lightly.
- One, two, three! Lightly.
- He's a man.
Yes, like that.
- One more time.
- One, two, three! Lightly.
Touching is natural whenever you teach someone something like golf.
That's why you're continuing with billiards lessons.
How do girls feel when a guy holds them from behind for the first time?
I think her heart is fluttering a lot right now.
He's teaching her and he looks very dependable all of a sudden.
I bet she felt like a baby learning something.
I think the two look really good together.
I think you'll be eating Spanish chicken dish soon.
Their honeymoon will be in Barcelona.
- Now, we'll cook the chicken...
- It's like they brought the restaurant.
It looks good already.
I marinated it beforehand.
Didn't you say your mom makes Spanish dishes?
She learned a few of the Spanish dishes.
Is there a Spanish dish you learned from your mom?
There's something I'd like to make for you.
- You just thought of one?
- Yes.
What is it? Is it a secret?
- Gambas.
- Gambas?
She knows how to make gambas.
Shrimp dishes are good.
Are you going to make it with your own recipe?
- Like how my mom taught me.
- Your mom's recipe?
- I want to try it.
- Really?
Yes.
Now, Joo-yeon is...
Her mom's recipe.
She must've learned from her mom.
My wife never lets me or my daughter into the kitchen when she cooks.
Because she's unwrapping the food she bought?
She's opening the microwavable foods.
"Oh, honey!"
That's not it.
She doesn't like it when we try to help her with her work.
Oh, she doesn't like it.
She thinks of it as her work.
Moms usually call their daughters so they can teach them.
No. She learned everything after she got married too.
- So she says they'll learn.
- Oh, since they'll learn eventually.
- She never lets us in.
- Not even for washing dishes?
No.
Then the first person she's cooking for is Kyung-hoon.
I bet it's her first time.
It looks like a cooking competition.
Be careful to not cut yourself.
Want me to cut some up for you?
Something like that!
He's considerate.
I think you can put them in the pan.
You can just finish those.
Good cooks get nervous in front of professionals too.
Not just for cooking, but when it comes to singing too.
Even the best singers get nervous in front of pros like Jo Yong-pil and Hong Seo-beom.
The whole point of gambas is having enough garlic oil.
Am I putting my arms around you?
What is this?
- I can't stop.
- You scared me.
This is where it's from!
That was very new!
He went like this.
It's annoying when it's between guys.
That's why girls like tall guys.
That made my heart flutter.
- Was that intentional?
- That was intentional, right?
Of course! He could've went around her.
Right? It was intentional!
Joo-yeon did get flustered.
She looked more surprised.
Because he came in out of nowhere.
That was really special.
But I think Joo-yeon likes it too.
She could go like this...
It's cute. Isn't it beautiful?
That was a legendary scene.
Put in the sliced garlic.
You can put in based on how spicy you want it to be.
It's going well.
- You cooked for me last time.
- Right.
So I wanted to make you this as a way of saying thank you.
Since you're always cooking for other people.
- Right.
- You never...
To be honest, it's been a while since someone else has cooked for me.
They're not looking at each other.
For real.
I think the arm move made things very awkward.
- Because it was so heart fluttering.
- I'm looking forward to it.
My dish is almost finished.
- Kyung-hoon.
- Yes?
Can you try the shrimp since I made it?
Yes, I'll try it.
Do you think it's done?
His hand!
His touches are natural.
I'm glad it's good.
- There's a dish like that?
- Seafood soup?
- Potatoes and sauce...
- That looks good.
- What's that?
- That's the one Joo-yeon made, right?
Which one would you like to try first?
That looks so good.
Is that rice?
It's warm inside.
The gambas is good.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's good.
Don't the potatoes look really soft?
It's cold even when it's not hot.
I really like eating it with the vegetables.
Joo-yeon eats a lot.
It's good.
I know I made it, but it's good.
- This is really good.
- I agree.
Get a big spoonful.
- I did.
- It's really good.
It's good.
I haven't eaten the one I made.
Why aren't you eating it?
Because these are good.
It's okay. I'm eating it.
He casually says things that make the other person happy.
They're eating the food that the other person has made for them.
They're the only two people in that space.
I really enjoyed it.
I enjoyed the gambas too.
I heard you can see a lot of stars here.
Do you want to go see them?
Okay.
We can blow up the air beds in the tent.
- Oh, with the wind?
- Yes, you just use the wind.
How do you do this?
Did you hear her voice?
"How do you do this?"
- You have to run.
- Be careful.
Oh you just put in air like that.
I think you're supposed to--
Run...
Be careful!
You have to keep doing that?
I've never seen that either.
- Want to go run a lap?
- A lap?
Yeah. Let's go this way and around the back.
Okay.
You have to run fast.
Come back from there.
That's cool.
That's simple!
An air bed?
That's nice.
Is it hard?
This is good enough.
Yeah.
- Want to try?
- Yes.
Can you hold it up for me?
Go!
- Just run?
- Run!
This is fun.
None of the air is going to go in.
Yeah, run and then tie it!
How much faster does she have to run?
- More!
- It's not working!
This isn't working. It's too hard.
Don't sit in the middle. Sit on the end.
- The end?
- Yes.
Like that and...
- Don't throw yourself on to it.
- No!
You told me to sit on the end.
- Don't throw yourself onto it.
- "No!"
She's full of cuteness.
That hurt.
How come I'm the only one who can't do it?
Sit down slowly.
Look.
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
- Slowly.
- Okay, got it.
You can't get your balance if you sit down quickly.
There you go. Slowly.
Get your balance.
But...
What? It's perfect.
Let's look at the stars now.
I smell the countryside and campfire.
I get what it smells like.
Have you looked at the stars laying down?
I don't think I ever have,
now that I think about it.
So today is your first time.
Were you waiting for a while?
This is nice.
But I can't hit you with them.
This place is a little far from Seoul so...
- There are stars.
- We can see the stars.
What do you think about Kyung-hoon so far?
I like him.
I like him too.
Right? He seems like a really good guy.
I think the two go well together
because he seems dependable.
Joo-yeon's cute charm is...
I think he's close to her ideal type.
They look good together.
I let the alcohol to go away on purpose.
You boil fruits with wine and drink it warm.
I've never heard of it.
This is good.
What did you think about our second date?
It was a lot more comfortable than the first date.
- It was comfortable and...
- Seriously.
Her cheeks are flushed already.
I feel like we've gotten closer.
We felt that too.
We really liked it.
We did a lot more together than last time.
And talked a lot.
Right.
It felt like we understand each other better.
- You're right.
- That's why we feel more comfortable.
- This is your second time seeing me.
- Yes.
What did you say about my first impression again?
This is her first time asking something like that, right?
I think there were more pure sides to you than I expected.
I thought you'd have a strong mentality and be really opinionated.
But when I met you, I saw sides that were opposite to that.
So I thought, "She has these sides to her too."
Yeah. He read her well.
What do you think about me as a girl?
This is the most important part.
I think I have to be careful with my words.
They're talking about their very honest feelings right now.
They're very serious right now.
When was your last relationship?
- Two years ago.
- Two years ago?
I think new relationships are getting harder.
Yeah, as you grow older.
I think she's thinking about it very carefully.
I used to think that I wanted to get married.
But after that phase passed,
it's been hard forming new relationships.
So I think I do observe the person more.
What about you? What are you like?
I also do think that I need to be in a stable relationship with marriage in mind.
Because of our age, right?
I think you always ruin things if you rush it.
I think things that start too quickly
end quickly.
If you like someone too fast,
those feelings go away quickly.
You're right.
Yes.
The topic is definitely different from what Seok-hee or Soo-bin talk about.
Completely different.
Because they're thinking about marriage,
they can't just easily say they like someone.
They're more careful.
Since they're older, they're very serious
and they want to go slowly instead of moving too fast.
I think they could get closer by talking about this.
I relate to it because it's
different from the time
you take to get to know
someone when you're younger.
When you're younger, you get to know someone based on feelings.
But now you think about if you can accept even the other person's flaws.
I'd like to see you more.
Let's meet again when we're both free.
That sounds good.
Okay.
I'm so curious!
- What do you think as her father?
- We'd like to know.
I'm sure it will work out if it's meant to be.
That's important.
Do you want her to get married soon?
No.
But we always have a special episode!
- We have one this time too.
- Yeah, we have one this time too.
We can find out then.
We're rooting for the daughters' lovely dating lives!
There are only two people I want to depend on.
We think they're dating by now.
What?
It's upsetting.
This is crazy.
What a man.
There was no reason to not like him through the clips.
I'm about to cry too because you're crying.
I'm happy.