Matt: There's one word that gorgeous
women rarely hear, probably because it's pretty
counterintuitive but it can actually boost
attraction, get a girl to start chasing you and
make her see you as a real man. Now that one
word and the concept that I'm about to share
with you can set you apart from all other
guys and get her to see you as the prize! My
name is Matt Artisan from The Attractive Man,
and this is one word that will make women chase you.
-Intro sequece-
Matt: Now what I'm about to share with
you is slightly controversial. I know that
some of you guys watching this video probably
won't agree with what I'm about to say but
first let me share a quick story I was in
Belgrade Serbia about five years ago about
to teach a boot camp and I see this gorgeous
supermodel looking goddess walking down the
street and naturally I run into when I approach
her by the way is exactly how to do that in
other videos here on the channel and everything
was going great you know she was into the
approach but she told me she's in a hurry
she said she has to go. Girl: I have to go!
Matt: No, what you have to do is tell me one cool thing about you, then you can go. Now I know that kind of
seems like a Dick thing to say you know girls
in a hurry and I tell her no he can't go yet
but her eyes lit up partly in shock you can
believe I said that but I was all like you
know that sparkle in her eyes like I could
tell she was more attracted to me probably
because she had never heard anything like
that before the truth is that the hottest
women are used to men throwing themselves
at them and they're used to getting everything
handed really to them right on to work for
anything and everything for free for example
when I lived in Las Vegas I did a really attractive
cocktail waitress and you get into the hottest
clubs for free get bottle service for free
like ten thousand dollar tables she would
get really expensive meals paid for her should
even get invited to expensive vacations just
because she was hot see when women get everything
they want at no cost then they start to expect
it and pretty soon they don't value it as
much doesn't mean that necessarily don't appreciate
it it just means they don't value the men
who give them everything for really without
them having to aren't just because they're
hot on top of that beautiful women almost
never have to work for a man being attracted
to her right may just flocked to her because
she's so damn good looking and you never have
to do anything to like earned his interest
these women are used to guys showing way too
much interest too soon and putting them on
a pedestal. So if you want to attract these
kinds of women who are used to guys just fawning
all over them because they're so damn hot,
and you have to do the exact opposite. Stop
putting women on a pedestal! Now before I forget
make sure to subscribe to this channel if
you're not already subscribed to it right
now and hit that bell icon so we can notify
you about upcoming videos. So you've probably guessed
what that one word is you know that will
set you apart from all those suffocating guys
who will do anything she wants and hopes for
small piece of the pie it's the word "NO". No
no no that's right just saying the word no
two beautiful woman who's used to getting
everything handed to her on a silver platter
is very intriguing you see men that don't
stick to their guns and sacrifice their own
needs wants passions desires get walked over
by women and are not respected for example
let's say you're or mission at this point
in your life is to write a novel so every
night you go down to your basement at some
peace and quiet to work on your novel but
your wife constantly keep pulling you from
it she's asking for help with the dishes or
clean the house or just to spend some time
with her or even have sex with her and it's
kind of hard to say no to that one but if
you keep on putting your novel side just to
please your woman and eventually just give
up on it and you realize all I just need to
focus on her am to please her and make her
my passion my mission she will not only lose
respect for you but her attraction for you
will die.
What's really important is that
you don't put a woman before your mission
or purpose in life. David Deida said in his
book "The way of the superior man" if a man prioritizes
his relationship over his highest purpose
he weakens himself deserves the universe and
she says woman of an authentic man who can
offer his full undivided presence even if
she says that she wants to be number one in
your life what you really want is to support
a man in his mission and purpose just one
man who throws it all away just for her once
in awhile she might even test you to see if
she can knock you off your course a good woman
will do this now she doesn't want to actually
knock you off your course she just wants to
feel that you are a real man that can stand
up to her and say no to her now course he's
probably gonna be a little displeased that
she didn't get what she wanted but should
be more attracted to you in the long run now
this doesn't mean that you should say no to
everything she wants or use it as some sort
of manipulation tactic just like in the novel
example you might say yes to her sometimes
it's all about balance you say no when you
really need it and I can apply at any point
interaction like with a girl in Serbia I said
a within a minute of meeting her now that's
not gonna work all the time if the girl wasn't
attracted to me she probably would just laughed
and walked away but the point is to be more
of a challenge with women so that they see
you as a real man instead of a suffocating
me little child.
And this isn't meant to be like
a harsh thing you don't actually have to say
the word no all the time no no no no you can
just make fun little restrictions every time
you also make a request I call this technique
restricted requests let's go back to my place
but no sex let's go get copy but only for
ten minutes then I have to go no touching
below the belt here but your number here but
no calling twenty times a day.
That's all you get no more.
Now obviously these are just little
one liner examples what women usually love
them because they leave them wanting more
when you put a restriction on something it
shows you that you're not that easy like you
know every other guy that she's used to because
it's no fun for a woman if she knows about
a shadow of a doubt that you're a hundred
percent into her in the old pretty much do
anything for her she actually wants to wonder
a little and she wants to even have to win
you over this is actually the basis of flirting
flirting is not just showing your interest
all the time it showing your interest but
then playfully taking away keeps are guessing
a little bit which makes things a lot more
interesting for women love to tax the color
girlfriends at all he did this thing it was
so sweet they really show that was into me
but they did this other thing and I'm not
really sure of using to me what you think
about that and they don't call it girlfriend
getting opinions love doing that if she knows
right away that you're totally in love with
her you'd go home with or even make your girlfriend
then the game is over for her the fun for
her is in the flirting so if you're the type
of guy that never says no to women and you're
not used to using restrictions then start
doing it you'll notice that her eyes light
up as she realizes that you're different in
all the other guys out there and she begins
looking back with you now if you really want
to know how to be a challenge I created a
YouTube video that's all about qualification
which is one of the best concepts principles
tactics whatever you wanna call it when it
comes to being a challenge you should be doing
this in all of your interactions through out
the interaction because it's one of the best
ways to get her to see you as the prize and
get her to start chasing you within minutes
sometimes even seconds of meeting so check
that out right now there's a link to the right
of the screen click that and watch a video
and make sure to subscribe to this channel
if you're not already subscribed, hit that
subscribe button and if you want us to coach you
live in person then check out a book camp
schedule and schedule a free consultation
with us. My name's Matt Artisan from The Attractive
Man and I'll see you in the next video.