I'm
he has mastered the art of seduction
to be assertive a woman
we turn on two three six something you
know what works and what does new person
and then dominance going for the date
like a man
here's another short clip from our
seven-day advanced workshop in Las Vegas
now I have a lot for you in this video
including three texts that I use to get
the date yep that's all it takes you
don't need to be texting her all day
long and I'm gonna give you examples of
what those texts are how to use
role-reversal to make her laugh and
associate you with someone she wants to
see again how to set up a date with her
right then and there on the spot when
you first get her number so that you can
bypass most of the texting and also a
huge mistake that a lot of guys make
that will make her stop texting you and
how to use a hook text to get her to
reply almost every time and also how to
use restricted requests to make her say
yes to the date and how to get her to
start thinking about sex before the
first date and before we get started I
want to make sure you grab your free
copy of the texting cheat sheet click
the link down in the description below
to get twenty word forward texting
scripts to get the date and get her
wanting you so that you always send the
perfect text message every single time
okay so let's get back to the video or
not hey when are you free this week I'm
free all week when are you free I really
want to see you I'll take you anywhere
you want to go like be a man you and
that just means take charge be in the
lead you are the leader you make the
decisions now you may have to find out
her schedule okay so that goes into the
second text okay so the first text
actually let's go back talk about the
first text ill okay so it's basically
like this still first text call back
humor second text find out her schedule
and then invite her to whatever you're
going to three texts to get the date
that works a lot of the time if you had
a solid interaction usually three Texas
three texts is enough to get the date
first text call back humor and then
something like again something from the
interaction like let's say there was
this crazy guy at the club with crazy
hair something like that
and you pointed him out it was just a
really creepy guy you pointed him out
and you're like I'm gonna hook you up
with that guy like let's say you created
some tension right well we've talked
about some bait bait-and-switch actually
use this last night with first girl I
talked to I said oh I said I was talking
telling her about the comfort zone
challenges that we were doing and I
showed her pictures of the comfort zone
challenges she's like wow that's really
cool I'm like yeah you should get out of
your comfort zone every day she'd do one
thing a day that that scares you or that
is out of your comfort zone I don't want
to make it sound like scary cuz I was
leading into a kiss so I realized that
scaring doesn't sound good so I was like
yeah out of your comfort zone do one
thing a day like what be out of your
comfort zone she's like I don't know
it's like what about kissing a guy I
said what about kissing a complete
stranger like making solid eye contact
and then I pulled her in I said I think
I think you should kick kiss a complete
stranger right now pulled her in and I
said what about that guy over there so
let's say you pointed at some really
funky weird creepy dude you can use that
his callback humor like you totally went
went home with mister and then maybe you
gave him like some nickname amazing
crazy pants hit some weird tacky
Nathan pants huh and that might go that
might be a little bit of a
back-and-forth depending on her answer
her reply second text second or third
depending again a reply would be
starting to transition into the date so
one option remember is finding out her
schedule if you have a pretty open
schedule there's no sense in finding out
her schedule if you only have one or two
days free that week why would you need
her schedule who cares about her
schedule it's all about your schedule
your busy guy tell her that you're going
to hang out with her on that date that
you're free that day that you're free
but if you're if you work 9:00 to 5:00
and you don't have that much going on
throughout the week then find out her
schedule so just I usually just say
what's your schedule like next week I
like
add on something playful some kind of
like role reversal or something that
indicates that she's like really into me
and it's something that's a joke like
what are you doing next week what's your
schedule like next week or this week
besides carving our initials in an oak
tree or besides classic one I always use
is besides missing me and doodling
hearts on a piece of paper or besides
coming up with our power couple name
it's a little reality TV reference I'm
sure if you guys don't understand what
that means
she will I usually do like the tongue
sticking out emoticon I don't use too
many emoticons too many lolz because
when you laugh at your own jokes when
you're smiling at your own jokes that's
what it implies it releases the tension
now I know texting there's really no
tension the can be can be it's a little
bit more advanced and then hopefully she
replies with an answer that gives me
some information about when she's free
and then just tell her what you're doing
on that on that day that she's free and
invite her the same thing that you would
do in person when you get her phone
number same thing get her phone number
hey what's your schedule like this week
I may not add that funny part we say hey
what's your schedule like this week she
says oh I'm working all week I'm really
busy week but I'm free this weekend okay
we can applies Friday Saturday so I'll
take the earliest day and say okay
Friday I'm thinking about going to
such-and-such bar they have this amazing
waterfall it pours from the ceiling it's
so epic I can't believe you've never
been there you have to go there oh my
god that sounds amazing she says okay
I'll tell you what I'm almost tempted to
suggest you come with me but you have to
promise to behave same thing for checks
it's not really the same thing so I'll
add in a little bit of a restriction
don't sound too overly eager I've seen
guys do this yeah you should come with
me or yeah we'll go together it'll be so
fun exclamation mark exclamation mark
exclamation mark and they think they
don't realize what that sounds like in
her mind it sounds like we should go
yeah I'm so
excited I can't wait I've never been on
a date with a girl before like that's
but it it can that's how she can
interpret remember the way you write or
think she's gonna interpret it may not
be the way that she does because there's
no tonality she puts the tonality on it
and exclamation mark will imply a
certain tone out I never use exclamation
marks in text I never use all caps
that's the same thing it sounds like
you're yelling dadada is fine because
that means there's something coming next
and it doesn't mean that you're gonna
say something next could mean that she's
gonna go next so that's okay stuff like
that especially if it's a hook hook like
you're never gonna believe what happened
to me after you left the club last night
that could be the first the first text
using nickname if there was one callback
humor if there was and you're never
gonna believe what happened dot dot so
first text scheduled and then I'm almost
tempted to suggest you come with me but
you got to promise not to such-and-such
got a promise not to embarrass me too
much you got to promise me to hold your
liquor but you got to promise that
you're not going to get drunk and be all
crazy gotta promise to behave gotta
promise to keep your hands above my
waist you know whatever something some
kind of restriction but people are more
likely to do something if there's a
challenge because you're not offering it
up so easily you're like wait a second
just like when you get the phone number
it's great put a challenge on that here
we got to keep in touch
wait you're not crazy are you you take
it back and she's like no no no right
she's got to prove herself no I'm not
crazy okay I'll take a chance on you I
don't know there you go
put it in sometimes we'll say put your
put your address in to put your email
social security number tax ID credit
card information go ahead all right adds
a little humor well I'll take her phone
save my name her phone and put a little
nickname sex God sex ninja the new crush
something like that so then when I text
her it's like wait what Matt the new
crush
I didn't write him save that it's funny
she's gonna exactly right you guys are
chuckling she's that's what how she's
going to react she seems like especially
if there was some kind of like sexuality
to the interaction if there's nighttime
I might add something more sexual sexy
man your future ex-husband so then the
other way to go for the date is if you
only have one night free and be very
dominant like cancel all plans we're
hanging out I have a super fun idea dot
and you don't have to tell her what the
idea is you can either tell her what the
data is especially if it's something
that you know she hasn't done before and
that is kind of cool like every I'll
used go-karting that's pretty cool fun
not too expensive most people haven't
done that I think I'm done that a long
time that would be compelling it's like
oh yeah not only am I gonna you know
she's thinking how am I gonna handle
this guy who I like I'm gonna we're
gonna do something fun you know how
could she say no to that so it's close
logistics so you can tell her or you
could just not tell her if she says
what's the idea what are we gonna do say
it's a surprise I can't tell you then
tell her what to wear you're gonna go do
something like hiking or something like
that make sure she's stressed
accordingly she shows up in heels and a
dress you're going like to do some
activity like go-karting I guess you
could do go-karting in that attire but
she might feel out of place so tell her
what to wear and it's very dominant to
tell her what to wear just I like to
just say wear skirt and heels I take her
to a bar even if I say I have a super
fun idea she gets her she's like what's
the idea I'll just say you're hanging
out with me that's the super fun idea
come on oh yeah I usually to wear skirt
and heels number one reason because I
like it I like that number two it's very
sexy and sexual and it plants a seed
like why does you want me to wear skirt
and heels we're gonna have sex
she starts thinking she might start
thinking about it and it's conditioning
her to please me with her sexuality
thanks for watching man and again I want
to make sure you grab your free copy of
the texting cheat sheet because it
contains 20 word-for-word texting
scripts to get the date and get her
wanting you just go down to the
description right now click the link and
I'll send it directly to your email and
I look forward to seeing you in another
video
no that would be bad I'll make it I'll
making my Miami girlfriend for the next
five minutes
it's a minute then it will be okay yes
okay are you giving me a tour huh yes