something that all girls can agree on is
the first few texts a guy sends her will
make or break her decision about whether
she wants to see him again so guys this
is really important you have to make
these count you can't just go
bullshitting your way through this text
thing and expect to get a good response
so I'm gonna show you a few examples of
big texting fails to help you so you
don't make the same mistakes hi it's
Nicole with the attractive man team and
in today's video I'm gonna reveal to you
how a girl actually wants you to text
her and ask her out after you've gotten
her number I'm gonna cover the do's and
don'ts of those first few texts you send
a girl so you can make sure you don't
send her running away and can get a date
fast to do this I'm going to show you
some text that I've received in real
life and break them down for you based
on the good and the bad and then at our
end of this video I'm gonna tell you the
number one way to ensure that you get
the date that you want so make sure you
stick around for that
okay so the first types of texts are
gonna want to avoid are the drunken late
night text or the meaningless text now
these can be one in the same sometimes
or they can be separate but the example
I'm going to show you is a guy who
managed to combine them both I'll let
you read that real quick hmm so you'll
know the timestamp of this it was 4:00
in the morning that I received the
letter M and an emoji what does this
mean
I have no idea this was a waste of my
time and it woke me up so this was not
endearing and needless to say I did not
text him back you're gonna want to avoid
junk text the beginning of a texting
conversation with a girl because it's
gonna make you seem like you don't have
self-control and like you may be our
little immature and also a meaningless
text is going to be a waste of your time
and hers if you're trying to gain her
attention and you send her something
that she doesn't understand or means
absolutely nothing to her she's gonna
move on just avoid these there's no
for them alright so the second type of
text you're going to want to avoid is
the kind that's gonna get you
screenshotted and destroy it in a group
text with her friends this can include
anything from really bad grammar and
spelling to excessive emoji or meme
usage unless you're 12 that's not okay
can also include inappropriate text or
unsolicited pictures I should hope that
you know you shouldn't send those things
but I still have to say it just to make
sure if your first text to a girl
includes a bunch of spelling mistakes or
a bunch of emojis it doesn't matter if
you've just told her she's the most
beautiful human you've ever seen in your
life
she's probably gonna think you're an
idiot that might be harsh but it's true
there's just no reason for it and if
you're sending an inappropriate message
even if you spend a lot of time with
this girl it's just gonna kind of give
the wrong vibe you may come across as
creepy you just want to avoid this
there's no reason for it so I'm actually
gonna show you an example of that if you
ever are bored and want to send some
pics I'm your guy though winky face haha
a little background on this is that I
met this guy the night before and we had
a great time together we kind of flirted
we spent like five hours together
actually it was a good encounter and the
next day he asked if I could hang out
and I couldn't so that was his response
to just asked for pictures I had a good
time with him prior to this but that
really gave me a creepy vibe it wasn't
cool I just met him yesterday I don't
know why he expected that this was okay
you just want to avoid messages like
this it's not a good idea
following this text which I will not
include for the internet because I think
there's a lot of rules against that but
he sent just a picture of his naked
torso and while it was a decent torso I
was completely turned off at this point
it's just not okay I didn't ask for that
just avoid these kinds of
at all costs okay so the third and final
texting don't I'm going to share with
you is actually one of the biggest and
most common mistakes that guys make
while texting it's the non-committal
text if you want to see the biggest
collective I roll from a group of girls
ask them how they feel about the we
should hang out sometime text this
basically translates to I'm gonna make
as little effort as possible to ever see
you again
and isn't going to lead to a date unless
the girl is desperate in which case hey
you might get lucky and good luck really
guys sometimes seem to have this idea in
their head that if they set a day in
time that is suddenly something serious
but no girl thinks this way they're just
gonna be thankful that you actually
could make a decision because a lot of
guys can't seem to for some whatever
reason I don't know why let's face it
there is always the chance that a girl
just gave you her number to be nice this
happens from time to time there's
reasons why I'm not sure but if you are
straightforward with your intentions I'm
going to see this girl again
you're gonna weed out these wishy-washy
people who are probably just gonna flake
on you anyway and that way you are not
wasting your own time and you're not
wasting theirs by the way if you haven't
yet go ahead and click that subscribe
button down below we have new videos
every week so go ahead and click that
Bell icon as well so you'll be notified
of when those are released anyway let's
move on to the types of texts you should
send a girl to make you stand out these
are really gonna help set you apart from
anyone else you may be talking to and
help you get a date now the first kind
of text you should definitely always
include in those first few texting
exchanges is a unique compliment no
don't get me wrong
girls love compliments you can tell her
she's pretty you can tell her she's nice
you can say any great thing but a lot of
times they can come off as a little
cookie cutter like something you could
say to anybody so if you can put in a
unique compliment that really lets her
know that you paid attention to her this
is going to make you stand so high above
anyone else she's talking to this can be
anything
I mean think about if you had a
conversation before you got her number
or something about her appearance just
something very specific to that girl
it's really going to be so endearing I'm
gonna show you a kind of funny example
of that really quickly I'll let you read
that mmm it was great meeting you
yesterday by the way you have the cutest
sneeze so to explain this text I met
this guy and we were having kind of a
quick conversation maybe 5 or 10 minutes
it was going pretty well and then I got
the worst allergy attack I'm telling you
I probably sneezed 20 times in 30
seconds it was really embarrassing and I
thought for sure I blew it I mean I
could not stop like we had to end the
conversation because I was just like a
red-eyed puffy just the whole thing it
was awful
so when I got this text from him the
next day I was so relieved and it was so
sweet that he kind of let me know that
he didn't care that I looked like a
crazy person because no one is cute when
they sees unless you were a baby panda I
mean come on seriously
it just wasn't cute but this was really
endearing if you can pull something like
that from a conversation or anything
about this girl she's gonna know that
you paid attention to something other
than her boobs during the conversation
and it's really gonna get you a long way
okay so the next thing that you should
do in every text conversation is
something I wish I could tell every
single guy you have to make actual plans
to see the girl make actual plans for a
date or if you happen to leave your
balls at home that day and you can't
call it a date you still have to make
plans let me show you a quick example of
a guy who did a really good job just
sending up a casual date with me who
drinks tomorrow night or early evening
Friday let's say a Valentino's so this
was great
meeting for drinks very straightforward
he gave me a couple of day option so I
can fit into my schedule he even picked
a place that was close to where I lived
on my side of town so it showed me that
he was listening to our conversation
girls just want a guy who
confident and sure of himself and able
to make decisions if you can set a day
in time to meet her you're already gonna
be 10 steps above half the guy she
probably talks to on tinder or Bumble or
whatever the youths use these days I
don't know but seriously just make plans
with the girl it's not that hard it's
really gonna set you apart and if you
make the plans this really opens it up
so that you are comfortable with the
situation you can pick a place that you
like that you have been to before so
you're not completely thrown out of your
element and you can really be your best
self when you're on this date all right
so I've covered a few of things that you
can do to really make yourself stand out
but now I'm gonna share with you the
number one way to make sure you can get
a date you're really gonna stand out
with this I showed you a couple of
examples of guys who seemingly did
everything right with texting good
compliments setting up dates things like
that but they actually lost out to the
one guy the one one who had the balls to
actually call me yes that's right he
picked up his phone and used it as it
was intended and called me this was so
shocking to me I almost dropped my phone
I'm not even kidding you this is so rare
than this happens which is why it was
this a surprise no this conversation was
not long it was actually quick and
straight to the point he just said hey
it was really great to meet you this
week I would like to take you out this
week are you free and of course I said
yes we set a time that's not important
all of that but this really displayed a
level of confidence encouraged that no
Gaea had talked to ever did this was
really impressive to me and it's kind of
nerve-wracking to be called honestly it
really puts you on the spot you have to
be quick with your thoughts and feelings
and ideas and all this it really is
nerve-wracking but even if you hate
talking on the phone or she hates
talking on the phone this is going to
really make you stand out it's gonna
seem like you have your shit together
even if you don't it's okay if she
doesn't answer she may not maybe she's
busy it doesn't mean she's not
interested and it's totally fine to
leave a text afterwards and just tell
her hey I was giving you a call to see
if you wanted to hang out this week or
see if I could take you out this week or
any number of things to kind of get that
flirting going but calling a girl is
absolutely the number one way that's
going to make you stand out above anyone
else she may talk to getting a girl's
number it's just the first step so I
really hope you follow these tips and
tricks and use them and go get yourself
an awesome date and if you want to know
how to talk to a girl once you're
actually on the date we have created a
free conversation cheat sheet that you
can download where we cover everything
you need to know and exactly what you
need to say to keep a conversation going
and spark a really good connection we
have everything from conversation
starters to techniques to make sure you
never run out of things to say to fun
games you can play to create a flirty
vibe and more make sure you click the
link at the right side of the page so
you can download it you'll want to keep
that handy oh and if you're not
subscribed already go ahead and click
that subscribe button and thanks for
watching bye
[Music]