hey guys it's Marie from Asian boss
thanks to the rise in popularity of
kdramas Korean men are often perceived
as tall good-looking and basically the
perfect boyfriend or oppa I'll pass the
term Korean females used to refer to
guys older than them often in a
flirtatious kind of way but what if
there was actually a service that allows
you to run out to all three of them to
give you a private tour of Korea
recently we came across one company that
does exactly that on this scientists can
rent an opera to show them erotic Korea
all for a small fee well today we're
going to see if we can rent an Appa and
get some insight okay let's see well he
looks kind of cute I guess
gonna flick it on him Adam is his name
okay so on his profile it says he speaks
perfect English and you can even choose
where to go or even customize where you
want him to take you I'm using a small
writing a person experience but kind of
excited at the same time all right looks
like we're all set let's go meet him now
oh hi are you my oh yeah I'm
alright
hugging yeah I don't know okay nice to
meet you
I am Marie I'm aremy okay so I don't
know this feels like a blindside so what
are we supposed to do I'll bring you
around one day and we can have a
conversation and maybe drink a coffee
yeah okay yeah let's go
[Music]
by you rather I rabbit you like it I
like the name
[Music]
with string would you like when they
lobbying lot there will do do you want
to order it try ordering it and then
Korean panel a pin lot there and done
tonight
[Music]
okay so we have to share because I'm
quite title on my money for Lucas okay
we have to like share it
first actually
[Music]
but yep I'd like to try cake first
okay eat first okay so when did you
start doing this job I started this job
in April this year I grew up in Korea
and then we moved to New Zealand and I
lived there for about 15 years I only
came back three years ago and then I was
looking for a job somehow I found this
oh my
so are you doing this that's a full-time
job or are you doing something else I do
a few other business businesses too and
I'm actually a mobile streamer and why
exactly did you start
oh my oppa I was doing a similar kind of
tour previously it was called era meat
war because I was bringing my viewers
from the mobile streaming when they come
to Korea I brought them around Korea and
we went for camping and stuff what kind
of services do you offer I bring you
guys around and show you guys some good
places and recommend and suggest we're
to go and what to do in Korea how much
do you charge we have fixed price around
70 to 80 dollars for 25 hours how often
do you get hired if I open up every day
I usually get almost full booking every
day that's a lot do Koreans ever hire
you a Korean guys or girls
we don't allow Korean girls or guys to
book us so it's really just a tourist
yeah so is full foreigner so shall we do
something else sounds good so we're at
Han River now and this is a tandem bike
so we have two seats here so I'll be
using this you can just hold this handle
and just do the pedals all right let's
try we might fall I apologize in advance
I will stop pedaling and you can just
follow your ticket Elise okay good are
you having fun
it's nothing comfortable though yes I'm
not scared at all
[Music]
so what are the things that you can or
cannot do anything involves physically
touching like holding hands and kissing
but we hug each other earlier was that
too much already
yes we broke the rules oh my god it's
any other client other than read right
across the line before not really this
because the tour is only for two and a
half hours it's quite short
have you ever dated a client after the
tour no I haven't our policy is very
restricted
we normally cannot exchange numbers
afterwards so yeah I never had a chance
who was your average customer our
customers are aged around 20s to 30s
usually there are more Asian than
Western people more Asians yeah because
I think Kay drummers are more well-known
in Asian countries then European and
Western countries so since your service
is called woman oh my oppa do your
clients call you oppa yes usually even
though they are older than me they still
call me oppa how does it feel when they
are called upon well usually I think
they like to be called as an oppa how do
I say you just say like that they go oh
you mean a new voice yes yeah the voice
changes it's better when you add some
movement
don't just say oppa sale ask them like
why do Korean girls do this I don't know
they think is very thank you they think
they're cute while they're doing this
chicken it looks like a ticket yeah yeah
you guys don't do it in like your
country
not all yeah I think that's tested the
friends between like Korean and Weston
like foreigners do girls ever take
advantage if they try to keep a cute yep
yep yep like let's say if you want to
get a Chanel bag you can just go and and
just point at it to the bag and and yeah
doesn't work when I do to you
let's see okay that was one thousand one
I want
do you think it's actually getting quite
cold should we move on to the next
location
yeah can you warm up my hands I my hands
are usually my hands on you should warm
[Music]
we are at the convenience store and
there is like Korean style ramen that we
can eat yeah let's try these two and so
this is a Romulan cooking machine okay
and put the noodle inside here and take
out the flavor and then you put the
plate here you just crack the egg and
put it inside oh that's all right
[Music]
alright pull it down a little bit
okay so usually you like this
in Korea
you need to make sound while you're
eating just suck it hard as you can I
don't think Korean guys are so popular
overseas because of the mostly kdrama
and kpop how are Korean guys portrayed
in Korean drama every time when you see
the drama you can find a perfect looking
they are very told everything is like
perfect you know how are Korean guys
really I've been told that I'm you can
find the perfect Korean guys and one of
the most famous club in Gangnam it's
really hard to find like these people
that acting in the drama but do you
dislike most about this job when people
first hear about the service some people
think is quite weird yeah yeah something
like that but it's not true yeah this is
completely not true why cut off message
would you like to tell foreigners who
are planning on visiting Korea if it's
their first time visiting Korea I think
it's a good idea to book use our service
because our hope is already to I bring
you guys around and like give you guys
nice tips Korea is a nice place and I'm
sure there are a lot of cool stuffs that
you can experience for first time so
yeah please do visit Korea okay thank
you so much out of me for today I had a
little problem you taught me a lot yeah
was really good I'm glad that you
enjoyed you said you are not allowed to
exchange contact details that's true
well I think we broke many rules to them
okay it's okay to break them out the
rule
number Wow okay I see okay okay we have
a chance yeah okay okay take care okay
[Music]