you know forward Tex really revived
almost any dead number well watch and
find out because it's so annoying when
you meet a girl that you really really
like and it seems super on your texting
back and forth and then WHAM out of the
blue she doesn't text you back
you probably start over analyzing your
last text and second-guessing yourself
and try not to freak out and hopefully
you don't send a lame text like did I
say something wrong
further sealing your fate of being
forever ghosted watch to the very end
and I'll give you my simple 3-step
system to get her to reply back and the
forward text that I send to revive even
the most dead number my name is Matt
artisan from the attractive man and this
is what to text a girl when she doesn't
text you back
[Music]
to be assertive a woman
we've done all the testing you know what
works
Berkeley psychologist found that
receiving a text message makes people
feel more connected and elevates their
mood no shock there but this might
surprise you that the open rate of SMS
messages is 99% yet the reply back rate
is only 45 percent which is why I'm
first gonna give you three crucial tips
that you need to start implementing
right now any time you don't get a reply
back tip number one is don't stress out
about it so many guys freak out because
they have one itis they're putting so
much importance on this one girl that
they're texting and that if she doesn't
reply back then they're really affected
by that so instead I recommend have at
least five if not even ten girls that
you're texting that might seem like a
lot but remember it doesn't mean you're
dating all of these girls these are just
girls that you're interested in and that
you're trying to get a date with you
might only get dates with like three or
four of them but the point is if one
doesn't reply back you still have a few
other options and not only that but make
sure you have an interesting lifestyle a
cool lifestyle at least have a job and
other things that you're focusing on so
that getting a date with this one girl
or any of these girls that you're
texting isn't the most important thing
in your life make sure to have other
things that are more important than
girls now it's one thing if she's your
wife or a long-term relationship but I'm
talking about girls that you've just met
that maybe you haven't even gone on a
real date with and just the fact that
you're worrying so much about it makes
you needy even if she doesn't see that
you're pacing around your apartment
waiting for her to text you back she
doesn't see that needy behavior but
mentally you're still putting her on a
pedestal you're becoming more and more
needy about this particular girl and
when you eventually do either right back
to her you might end up sending a really
needy text or when you finally end up
seeing her you've put so much investment
and mental energy towards her that your
might end up being really needy and push
her away because the fact is she might
just be busy maybe she's on an African
safari and she doesn't have
cell reception or maybe she saw your
text and she had every intention to text
you back but she just didn't feel like
it at that exact moment and then just
forgot about it one time I was hanging
out with my girlfriend and she got a
text from her best female friend and she
had every intention to text her back but
just didn't feel like it at the moment I
forget we were doing something else at
the time and she didn't end up replying
to her best friend for an entire week
and that's her best friend who has a lot
of value and importance in her life so
imagine you the new guy in her life you
don't have that much significance so she
doesn't really have a lot of obligation
to text you back remember women base a
lot of what they do based on how they
feel in that moment so she may not feel
like texting you back
so what try again and maybe next time
she'll feel like texting you back which
brings me to the next point is don't
text back immediately what happens with
most guys is their texting back and
forth maybe every 5 or 10 minutes it's
going great
it seems super on a guy is getting super
excited then girl just starts doing
something else she gets busy or she
doesn't have cell service and the guy
starts freaking out 30 minutes have gone
by an hour has gone by so he texts her
hey are you busy and 30 40 maybe an hour
2 goes by no reply and he texts okay
cool
which obviously means it's not cool and
that he's a little bit affected by it
instead I don't even do a lot of back
and forth texting I just use texting to
set up the date not to get to know each
other and have all this banter back and
forth that just uses a lot of time and
you should have other things going on in
your life like I said before instead of
just texting girls all day long so I
recommend you send the text and you
forget about it you put your phone on
silent and then you check it when you're
free go about your day do other things
beyond your mission and purpose and then
when you're bored and relaxing then you
check your texts and that will really
help you from ever over texting her and
then if you don't get a text back just
wait a day or two and send another text
and I'll talk about those exact texts
that you could send just a second and a
good rule of thumb is if you send a text
and you don't get a reply back then you
wait a day or two to texture again don't
keep texting her and asking her what's
wrong now I understand it fits your
long-term girlfriend that's a little bit
different but again we're talking about
new girls in your life here they should
not be that important and if you catch
yourself stressing about some new girl
in your life do other things occupy your
mind and one of the best things is get
out there and meet more women so you
have more options but just because she
didn't takes you back one time don't
give up and delete her number and
balance is key here just because she
didn't reply back one time doesn't mean
all is lost
remember 45% of the time people don't
reply back so you need to be persistent
but without sending her a bunch of text
and coming off as needy by the way if
you're not subscribed to this channel
make sure to subscribe and tip number
three is to use social media to your
advantage because if you also have her
Facebook Instagram or snapchat then she
can see that you live an interesting
life that you're traveling or that
you're speaking on stage or that you're
hanging out with a group of friends or
she might even see that you're with
other women that you're going on dates
and hanging out with other girls which
can make her more interested and it
doesn't seem like you're just sitting at
home waiting for her to reply back
you're living your life which you should
be plus maybe she started dating
somebody else and she's not really as
interested in you anymore because of her
new relationship but that relationship
might only last a few weeks or even a
few months and if she keeps seeing your
lifestyle she keep seeing your pictures
and your posts then you're on her radar
and she might just randomly text you
back when she's single again I've used
this to my advantage many times when I'm
traveling and I see no point in texting
a girl when I'm not gonna be back in
that city for a year or two but when I
do come back she remembers me and she
asked me all these questions about my
travels because she saw all my pictures
and it keeps me on her mind and on her
radar and it's like it like keeps the
fire still warm it's not a full blazing
fire anymore but you just need to stir
it a little bit and you can easily
reignite it alright now we need to get
her to reply back so here are three
simple steps first remember it doesn't
mean anything just wait a day or two and
then send another text that next text
shouldn't be like what
happen to you or anything like that it
should just be something simple
something short and something random it
could be a fun question like if you had
any superpower what would you have or we
could travel anywhere in the world where
would we go by the way I like the word
we instead of you because it creates a
sense of togetherness or send her a
random picture because remember pictures
speak a thousand words it can be a meme
that somebody sent you it can be a cute
animal that you saw or found off the
internet because women love cute animals
it could be maybe you're walking down
the street and you saw a bum with a
funny sign you can send her a picture of
that or anything else that's interesting
funny or exciting that has happened to
you that day or maybe that week or you
can try a funny role play text like hey
I'm bored let's go rob a bank I've used
that many times and it definitely gets a
reply just anything kind of fun not too
serious that just gets the conversation
going again
so that you can go for a date and meet
up with her and I have even better
examples than this in my free texting
cheat sheet if you don't have it yet
grab a copy there's a link down in the
description now let's say she doesn't
reply back now you still might not be in
damage control yet maybe she's super
busy maybe she's out camping and she
doesn't have a good cell service maybe
she lost her phone maybe maybe maybe but
there's also of course a chance that
she's just not that interested and
there's only one way to really find out
and that's step number two is wait two
to four days so that you don't seem too
needy or eager and then send a bate text
a bate text is just a text that baits
her to reply back something like I think
you have a confession to make
dot dot dot now she's probably gonna
want to know what that confession is so
she'll probably write back and ask what
is it and one option is to say I think
you love me and if she definitely
doesn't love you or even like you then
she'll probably let you know and at
least now you can move on or you can go
more the role-playing route and say I
think I saw you last night peering
through my bedroom window trying to
sneak a peek you're so bad it's kind of
funny kind of gamy but if she laughs if
she's into it that's great you're back
on track or if she says definitely not
then maybe she's not so interested and
you might want to cut your loss another
example of a bait text is I just
realized what animal you remind me of
and
she asked what animal then send her a
picture of a really cute animal now if
that doesn't work then you're definitely
in damage control meaning you know
there's obviously a good chance she's
just not interested at all but it
doesn't really hurt to send one more
text now if she still doesn't reply back
then you can still do a last-ditch
effort if you so wish which is step
number three wait four to six or seven
days and send her these four words are
you still alive question mark
no emoji just are you still alive
question mark you'll be surprised at how
often you will get a reply back
oftentimes it's just a reply like yep
which means to delete that number don't
text her back anymore and of course if
she doesn't reply back then just delete
the number but if she answers with oh my
god I've been so busy or I lost my phone
who is this then there's still a chance
don't over text her but send her some
more fun playful text because that will
boost the attraction she'll see that
you're a fun guy which means she's more
likely to meet up with you because she
knows you'll be fun in person and if you
need more playful text to boost the
attraction along with challenging text
and make her chase you a little bit and
even texts that turn her on then make
sure to get a free copy of the free
texting cheat sheet there's a link down
in the description and to the right of
the screen make sure to subscribe to
this channel if you're not already
subscribed and hit that Bell
notification icon and we also have live
boot camps all around the world so if
you want to know how to meet women in
person on the street or any situation
then check out our boot camp schedule my
name is matt artisan from the attractive
man I'll see you in the next