what's up guys matt artisan here from
the attractive man i'm coming at you
from the philippines manila
so don't be surprised if you see a
ladyboy or two they're quite common so
here's the deal i wanted to talk to you
about texting in particular what to do
if she doesn't text you back this is a
big issue i mean it kind of sucks right
if you meet a girl maybe it was a short
interaction but maybe it's a long
interaction and it just seemed really
really on everything was great he spent
a few hours with her maybe at the bar or
the club or maybe even a date and all of
a sudden she stops texting you back the
next day maybe you sent her the first
text and you get no reply
maybe she's texting you back and forth
and she's replying all the time and then
all of a sudden she just goes cold what
do you do I'm gonna give you some
specifics in just a second but first
your mindset is what's key here stop
worrying about it
who cares who cares if she's not texting
back you are a man you should be on your
purpose you should know what that
purpose is you should have a mission for
your life something other than meeting
and dating women something that's bigger
than that maybe it's your career maybe
something else maybe it's a hobby maybe
you're trying to start a business maybe
trying to move up the corporate ladder
whatever it might be that should come
number one if you start making women
your number one then number one you're
going to start stressing all about it
especially when they're not texting you
back number two
no women no woman wants to be your
number one and your purpose really
doesn't she might say she does women do
say they do that they want to be your
number one they want to be your purpose
they want to be the most important thing
in your life but really deep down a
woman wants to find a man who has this
greater purpose maybe again starting a
business or has some kind of cause that
he's fighting for and she wants to be
there supporting him lifting him up and
helping him achieve that
you start making women the most
important thing not good you're not
going to be able to find that woman of
your dreams instead follow your dreams
and the women will come so that will
really help you not care so much if a
woman doesn't text you back because who
cares it's not the most important thing
in your life at the same time on the
flip side date a few women or at least
be talking to a few women at a time now
I'm not saying you should have a few
girlfriends at the same time unless they
all know about each other and they're
all cool with that once you have a
girlfriend somebody who's exclusive with
you stop talking to all the other girls
but before that happens when you're just
in the dating process or you're just
talking to girls date a few girls talk
to a few girls
I recommend five to seven even ten if
you have time because here's the thing
if you're only talking to one girl you
have one girl's number in your phone
that you're texting then it's very easy
to get stressed out if she stops texting
you back it's you're gonna come off as
needy because you need her she's your
only option but if you got five girls
that you're talking to that you're
texting then who cares one of them
doesn't text you back who cares you've
got four other girls that you're talking
to that you're maybe going on dates with
you send out maybe even a mass text to
all of them you copy and paste it it's
all five of them see what they're up to
this week maybe only three of them get
back to you so what you set up dates
with those three for the week and then
maybe the other two get back to you
later and you set dates with them for
next week
the key is date a few women at the same
time if a couple of those women fall off
the radar and they completely stop
texting you back then go out and meet
more women they're everywhere everywhere
in your day to day life
there are women so meet them and you'll
have tons of options right now I have
more options than I can handle I have
too many girls in my phone it's almost
becoming a headache I mean that's a good
problem to have but anybody can have so
you get get to that level where you're
texting 10 or even 15 girls at a time
it's not that hard you can get a girl's
phone number like that literally 30 40
seconds any girl walking around the
street
eat grocery store wherever you are start
approaching those women and you'll have
more options next be very careful what
you tell yourself your self-talk when
you text a woman and she doesn't text
back you start getting all bent up out
of shape you start thinking about what
she might be doing and you start asking
yourself questions like you know why
isn't she texting me back what is she
doing who is she with things like that
maybe I'm not good enough maybe I didn't
do a good enough job texting or maybe I
didn't do a good enough job in the last
in the initial interaction to attract
her enough instead tell yourself
something different say oh that's so
cute how she's playing hard to get
that's adorable she must really like me
I know that sounds like you might be
lying to yourself so what lie to
yourself you'll feel much better and the
last thing is send her the next text
when you feel like it whenever you feel
like it don't give up right away just
because the girl doesn't send you one
text that doesn't mean anything maybe
she was busy maybe she's dating somebody
else - so what who cares
you're not exclusive with her yet so she
shouldn't be exclusive with you yet if
it's a girl that you just met right so
send her another text maybe it wait a
day maybe wait two days three days it's
really up to you there's no rule send
her another text something that's
compelling not like hey what's up or you
know what are you up to what are you
doing that's yeah you could do that once
in a while but it's kind of boring
instead something more compelling like
hey I have a super fun idea dot dot dot
or I just remembered or I just realized
what animal you remind me of and then
send her a picture of like a super cute
dog or super cute cat you can find one
on the internet it's pretty easy and if
she still doesn't reply then wait even
longer wait a week
so what be a busy got half things going
on in your life date other women and
then just reply to her send her another
text when she and when it pops into your
mind wait a week can say something like
you're the worst texter back ever or
you're starting to lose cool points or
one of my favorites that I came up with
that works pretty well
is if you're falling desperately in love
with me don't reply back to this tech
you'll be surprised how often you'll get
a reply back so check this out
I got this texting app that I came up
with to help guys out with what to text
in different situations first text
openers random text funny text witty
text more text that will get her to
reply back if she's not replying back
text that will get her on a date so that
you can ask her out on a date the right
way and look like a real man
instead of a wuss so go ahead check out
the app there's a link for it down below
go ahead and click the link get the app
it's awesome and make sure to leave a
good review I'd really appreciate that
make sure to subscribe to this channel
got a lot more tips coming up for you
and again my name is Matt artisan with
the attractive man peace