They say there are bad guys and good guys.
Which kind are you?
Why don’t you answer?
I will Kakaotalk you.
Okay.
You are very attractive.
&lt;When a woman who likes lion meets a man who likes tiger&gt;
Hello
[Na Young Kim, 26 Years Old, Actor Trainee]
I am Na Young Kim, 26 years old living in Seoul.
I majored in Drama
so I am in acting career.
Hello
[Won Jun Sung, 32 years old, businessman]
I am Won Jun Sung, 32 years old, living in Yongin.
I am Brand Marketer.
Q. Your type?
My type is one with edgy style
and with active and energetic character.
My type is one with wide shoulder
and with good looks.
I like someone who acts like a grown up and is bright. Also those I could really talk to.
Hello
Q. What is your interest these days?
Uhm
I like drawing.
and calligraphy.
I practice those.
In my case,
I am thinking of doing leather arts
to avoid some boredom from work.
So I am looking around what I should try for.
Oh really?
Yes.
You like to craft?
I really am not having any fun these days.
Q. Do you like movies?
Yes, I love movies.
Q. What genre is your favorite?
Also your favorite actors or actresses?
I do not have a preference on genres.
I really love watching movies.
I used to watch two movies a day
in media rooms of my college library between classes.
Do you have a favorite actor or actress?
My favorite is Natalie Portman.
of Black Swan?
Ah yes.
Q. Do you like animals?
I think they are cute.
Maybe cats and dogs?
Your favorite animal is a dog?
I like tiger too.
I like lions.
Ah~
I love animals.
I love pictures of lion,
and dogs, cats, cows.
You like cows?
Yes
Don’t you mean beef?
Yes. I like them as animals,
because their eyes are very clear.
Hmm
Q. Do you have any celebrity look-alike?
It seems inappropriate to tell you that here.
Is it a person? Or non-person?
He is a person.
Ah
Why not?
I will Kakaotalk you later.
Ah~ yes.
It makes me wonder.
I have been told as a lookalike some times.
Sang Yun Lee? (Korean Actor)
I am sorry.
Me?
So Hyun Kim? Known as child actress?
I have been told her as a lookalike.
Q. Who is your favorite singer?
I like Hip-hop singers.
Ah~
E-sense,
I also like ‘Nucksal’.
You must like ‘Show Me the Money’
The show is quite interesting.
I am also a big fan of it.
I hope they make it two seasons every year.
Q. Do you go to Karaoke?
Ah~ Yes.
Do you rap?
Rapping?
When I am excited?
I only do it when with closest friends.
I wonder how you would rap.
I am bad at it.
I practice at home looking at the lyrics
before I go to Karaoke and rap.
Do you practice at home?
Yes.
She likes Hip-Hop.
So I thought we might listen to the same music and talk about it.
I could imagine her practicing rap at home.
It made me laugh.
Q. They say there are bad guys and good guys.
Which kind are you?
I am a very good guy.
Ah~ You are quite sure about that.
Yes
I think I am a real good guy.
Ah really? What makes you think that?
I am born good.
You must be very good to others then.
Yes.
Being a good guy means
that you do not play a game
Ah~
and you adjust to others’ needs
I am that kind of guy.
He sounds like a good guy.
(My type) is bad guy who is good?
I need to get both.
Bad guy who is good.
Q. What is your blood type?
I am O.
Ah~
What is yours?
Mine?
What do you think?
A
Why?
A is most populated.
Ah~ I am not.
I am AB.
Mhm, AB
So your personality suits to the standard O?
I am very active
and like gathering with friends,
What is AB like?
I’ve heard that AB is very attractive blood type.
You are attractive?
Yes. We are unpredictable.
Unpredictable..
That type of blood type?
You have that kind of character.
Active and bright
Those are attractive styles.
I like to find something not predictable.
I think type O guys fitted me well.
Q. What is your hobby?
Q. For example, do you like to exercise?
or visit some quiet places like forest
and rest?
I like them both.
For my case, I like to go to places I could rest for vacation,
and for the normal weekend, I do outdoor activity.
For example,
I play basketball in the team.
You play basketball?
Yes.
I play basketball
I started surfing at Yangyang
2 years ago.
So you like to exercise?
I love playing sports.
I also like to exercise.
For vacation, I like to rest.
But normally I do acitivies.
Aha~
Q. What is your vacation type?
For me
I do not like scheduled tourism
where you visit 3~4 travel spots.
If I were to travel,
I set up for a long term schedule
so I could feel like I am living there.
I like to see one place for a long time.
I also love to travel in a long term.
If this does not fit well with each other,
it is very hard to accommodate.
So you’ve been to some resort towns?
Last year, I’ve been to Bali for surfing.
Wow
It is a good place for a rest.
I surf at day and rest at night.
Oh~
For my case,
I do not like being sent to one to another very quickly.
This fitted well with her style.
I was surprised that our style for travel fitted well.
Normally people go here and there
when they are travelling.
Producer: Is there any place you would like to visit with your boyfriend?
Bali?
I really wonder
so I would like to turn around and see you.
Me too.
I want to turn around.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
Hello
It is so awkward.
Nice to meet you.
Where do you live?
It’s been a month since I left Busan.
I am from Busan.
Oh really?
I came to Seoul when I was 20 years old.
For real?
But you look like you are from Seoul.
Maybe because How I talk?
Yes
Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?
His voice was good.
He seems like a good guy.
Her voice sounded very young.
I thought it was cute.
We’ve had a lot of things in common.
It was neutral.
Q. How do you feel after checking each other out?
His images I thought of before seeing him
and after seeing him were similar.
He looked like what I’ve imagined of.
He had wide shoulder and looked like a grown-up.
She is pretty.
Wow she is pretty.
I liked it.