Is there anything you would like to do when you date someone?
You are similar to me.
I was quite surprised too.
I would like to turn back and see you.
I would too.
&lt;When a university student man meets a woman of the same age&gt;
[Park, Ji Won, 24 Years Old, College Student]
Hello, I am Ji Won Park, 24 years old,
and junior in Seoul National University of Science and Technology.
[Jun, Hyun Ji, 24 Years Old, College Student]
Hello, I am Hyun Ji Jun, 24 years old,
and junior in Danguk University, majoring in Communication.
Q. Your type?
I would like to meet someone who is puppy-faced
I would like to meet someone who is warm hearted.
and also whom I can talk to.
Hello
So, would you like to ask me a question first?
Q. Who is your favorite female celebrity?
My favorite female celebrity is Kim, You Jung.
Ah…
I like someone who is outgoing.
Uhm, I like Woo Do Hwan.
He is sexy.
He has those sexy eyes.
Q. What is considered most important when blind dating?
For example, out of look, height, personality or etc?
It is important how he looks for first confrontation.
He does not have to be good looking
but the first impression goes long way.
I see.
Uhm…
Q. How do you spend your own spare time?
I tend to have a lot of free time on my own so
I go out for café,
or do shopping in Hongdae or Shinchon.
You do not prefer to stay at home for relaxing.
I prefer to go home just for sleeping.
I also do the same.
You very similar to me.
Q. What is your favorite food? And What food do you not enjoy?
I love eating food.
I do not prefer spicy food.
Oh, I also do not like spic food.
Oh really?
Yes, I actually do enjoy eating food but
spicy food is not my favorite.
I like most kind of the food except spicy ones.
I also have a sweet tooth.
So you eat most kind of the foods.
Yes, I do.
Q. When you get stressed out, what do you do?
I do exercise to release the tension.
I also eat delicious foods but
eating foods makes me exercise more.
I do both exercise and eating.
Q. What is the most important thing to consider when dating someone?
I think her responsive behavior during the conversation,
is important to me.
I moved toward him more because
his responses were very similar to my thinking.
I also think one’s response to my opinion is very important.
So I felt kinship with him.
Q. What is your dating style?
I like it to be comfortable as friends.
I would like it to be passionate and excited also.
But at the same time, when you date someone,
it sometimes becomes closer than friends because you see each other more.
So I prefer more comfortable and intimate dating style.
To be honest,
I’ve been thinking of some romantic relationship
that could be seen on TV show
So it made me wonder how it is like to be in a intimate and comfortable relationship.
Q. Do you tend to lead in the relationship?
Q. or do you tend to give in to another?
I would tend to give in as much as possible
when both has to compromise.
Do you have a specific taste in doing something or going somewhere together?
I don’t really.
I think if together, it would be happy to do
anything or go anywhere.
Even if I did not like it before, it would made me like it.
I was moved my his response.
‘If together, it would be happy to do anything or go anywhere.’
Q. What do you want to do the most if you have a boyfriend?
I would like to travel around with him.
A year before last year?
I’ve been to Osaka with my mother and grandmother
and thought it would’ve been nice to come
back again with my boyfriend.
So I thought of going away together if I have a boyfriend.
I also felt the same.
Most recent trip I’ve went to was
to Jeju island with my family.
I felt very jealous when seeing other couples traveling around.
I know. I’ve went to Jeju Island by myself.
I also felt very jealous of them.
Ah~
Q. After you argue with your girlfriend,
Q. how do you make it up?
You must talk first
to understand each other.
I try to meet her in person and talk to her about it.
I also feel the need of conversation right after the argument.
I know.
Also, I have a similar question to ask.
Do you tend to do what I do after argument?
Or is there anything else?
I am not sure if I have any specific skill to do that.
I really haven’t had any experience of reconciling after a big fight.
So you never had fought with someone?
I really haven’t had anything to fight with.
So no.
Aren’t you surprised?
It was surprising to me.
It is quite hard not to get upset about anything.
Even with friends.
So it makes her a bigger person
if she tends not to get upset on anyone or anything
by stepping out of the situation then communicating calmly.
Q. Do you go and introduce your girlfriend to your friends big and loudly?
Q. Or do you just keep it to yourself?
Up until now, I’ve been only telling it to my parents.
It got me thinking that
if I introduce my girlfriend to my friends
it would make me happy and my girlfriend happy.
I also think about those stuffs a lot.
It is very surprising.
Normally my friends
do not tell their parents about their relationship.
It got me surprised that you do that also.
Then how do you think of your boyfriend introducing yourself big and loudly?
I love it. I would like to see
his friends.
Ah…
Q. Lastly, how do you feel now?
I am very excited to see you.
I would like to turn back and see you.
Me too.
After listening to your responses,
it made me feel that we share a lot of things in similar,
so it was really fun to talk to you.
I also felt the same way.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
Hello
Hello nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
What do I do?
It makes me so shy to talk to you face to face.
It was very fun to talk to you.
You too.
[Q. When you heard her voice for the first time, how was it?]
Her voice tone was a bit high,
and her pronunciation was very clear.
I liked it.
I liked his voice a lot.
Very organized tone?
[Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?]
I thought it was a fix-up.
I felt so much in similarities in that sense.
During the blind date, I kept thinking ‘I know.’ ‘I am the same.’
It was hard for me to keep it down.
It made me want to talk to him more.
I know it is a blind date but we shared so many things in common.
It was like my friend who knows me so well.
But then after seeing her face to face
it made me want to talk to her once again.