What is most important thing to consider when dating?
I think that is more important than the appearance
My voice has been complimented well.
I was about to say.
I am very nervous.
&lt;When a man who has wide shoulder meets a tall lady&gt;
[Sung Won Joon, 32 Years Old, Businessman]
I hope to have something in common
to talk to during the blind date.
And,
It would be great if she is pretty.
Someone who is warm-hearted?
[Lee Ji Young, 27 Years Old, Teacher to-be]
I wouldn’t mind if he is younger than me.
Park Bo Gum?
I would prefer someone with more mature sense rather than young one.
Someone with pale skin tone?
and with wide shoulder
Park Bo Gum!
Uhm…
Hello
I am asking questions right?
Q. I like listening to music.
Is there any album or songs you like in particular
that you’ve listened to lately?
I like ballads.
Yoon Jong Shin just released ‘Yes’ after ‘Like it’.
Yes he released ‘Yes’.
I listen to that song day and night lately.
Have you just broken up with someone?
No I haven’t.
I just listen to the songs I like over and over again.
I loved the song too.
I like hip-hop.
'Yes’
‘Like it’…?
I have sang the songs and I liked it.
♪ Is it okay now
♪ You’ve been low
♪ The end to our
Q. Is there something you wanted to with your girlfriend?
I would love to spend times with her
Q. What about doing something cultural activities together?
I would love to do it together.
I love going to a movie
or seeing musical or drama
Oh really?
Do you like going to exhibition too?
Yes
Whichever contents they are
I like to see them.
I am interested in those.
I would love to go and see those together.
Ah~ I like to hear that.
Q. Do you tend to stay indoor?
than outdoor?
If the weather is good, I tend to go out
for example, going to Hangang,
or to a beach
Q. How many times do you think is appropriate
to meet per week or month when dating?
Twice or thrice in a week?
Okay
You do not put a limit to it.
Yes.
But if the situation does not allow
only once a week? They see each other.
Yes
But if you only get to see each other during weekend, it would be sad
so if the distance allows
trying to see as many as you can is better.
Okay I see.
Q. What is most important thing to consider
when dating?
Warm personality.
I like someone who is caring.
Also someone I can talk to!
Those are more important things to consider than appearance.
Q. I would like to ask a similar question to that
You also have a certain thing to consider
for example type of appearance?
I do not have certain preference.
Someone who acts sweet and cute?
Okay
I do not think I could act cute
So I have not much to say about that.
Q. Are you a quiet person?
or outgoing?
I become more outgoing if I get closer to people.
I have been heard that I am much different from the first impression.
What do they say about your first impression?
Look quiet and cold?
They say that a lot.
Friends often told me ‘You looked so cold at first that it was hard to approach.’
‘It was hard to open a word with you.’
‘But after I get to know you,’
‘You are like my younger sister.’
Total reverse in first impression
Normally those who look cold are not cold
but actually warm hearted,
and those unexpected
make them attractive.
Q. May I ask if you smoke?
and how much you drink?
I do not smoke.
but I drink.
Do you have a lot of gatherings?
I like to gather some closest friends
and drink not heavily.
I rather prefer to talk and drink
than to go and party.
Q. What is your favorite body part of yourself?
Uhm, a balance?
Balance?
I think the features are balanced.
Balance is important.
Mine?
Wide shoulder?
Q. Could you tell me your 3 strengths?
A question that could be asked in the job interview…
I am very optimistic.
My voice has been complimented well.
I was about to say.
I think that is one of my strengths.
I really liked his voice.
His voice was better than the last one.
That part, I really liked.
I was thinking of ‘Should I move forward on the next question?’
So I stopped.
Seems like I’ve moved enough already.
Q. There is a concept of ‘guy’ friend and ‘girl’ friend.
Do you keep them close?
I do not think it is impossible to keep them close.
Also seeing them alone often is not okay.
So you just keep them acquainted.
Yes, just one meal?
Just one meal
No movie together
no drink together
You have those limits in detail.
like one meal
Yes I do.
Q. May I ask about
your dating pattern or style?
I try to think myself as a warm person.
I try to call here frequently
That means the girlfriends
did not ask specifically about you calling back?
Yes. They had not.
Q. Would you consider it seriously
if you date now?
Yes.
Okay.
It is not like I have already planned on it.
I had always been serious in the previous ones.
How about you? Have you?
I have not been taking it seriously
Yet I did not start it if
I could not see the future with him.
I have experienced many people who think
dating and a marriage are separate things.
So I thought it is important to figure this out.
So I have been thinking
this is the most important thing to consider
before start dating.
Q. How do you feel about
long distance relationship?
Long distance relationship means
not only seeing each other that often but also means more devotion to each other.
I do not have a certain limit on those terms.
How far from you become long distance?
Further than Asia?
Asia?
Yes
I live in Yongin.
I have never dated someone who lives nearby.
I moved forward as a citizen of Gyeonggi.
Q. Someone who likes you more vs. Someone whom you like more
Which one would you choose to date?
For me, my intention is very important.
If I do not have a feeling toward him,
I do not date even if he likes me.
So those you’ve dated like you back in equal level?
You did not have a experience of imbalance?
Uhm…
I didn’t.
If I really do not have a feeling toward him, I do not date.
It seems good to me that
she has a principle in dating whom she likes.
I also do so I (moved forward)
I wonder how you look like.
I am nervous.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
Hello
It is awkward.
What should I say?
Did you have a certain image of me?
during conversation?
Your voice is very soft and relaxed.
Someone
with good guy look? I thought of that image.
You look warm.
Thank you.
Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?
His voice was more
warm and caring
than that of Seung Woo.
I had a better image of him than Seung Woo.
Conversation flowed okay.
To be honest
there was not certain attraction to it though.
Q. How do you feel after checking each other out?
Good guy look
Well educated look?
She was tall.
She had pale skin tone.
She was nice looking.
Na Young
was more of my style.
to be honest
I think SW would fit me more.
His character stands out more.
I liked that side of him.