"One bottle of beer?"
/ "Yes"
"I like meat the most."
"It will get better when we get to know each other."
[Min Jung]
"Hello, My name is Kim Min Jung."
"I’m 28 years old"
[Min Jung]
"and currently working at an entertainment agency."
[Hyo Yun]
"Hello. My name is Nam Hyo Yun,
studying business administration
in CHUNG-ANG University."
[Hyo Yun]
"I'm 25 years old."
&lt;Q. Which celebrity do you look like ?&gt;
"A little embarrassing to say it myself."
"But people tell me I look like Song Joong-Ki."
&lt;Q. What's your ideal type ?&gt;
"Someone with heavy tone and low voice.."
"...would be very attractive."
"I’d like someone with pure style shows up."
[Min Jung]
"Hello."
[Hyo Yun]
"Hi."
[Min Jung]
"You have very attractive voice."
[Hyo Yun]
"Thank you."
[Min Jung]
"I’ll ask first."
"(Q)Do you have any type of style in mind?"
[Hyo Yun]
"I like someone who is white.."
"Um.."
[Hyo Yun]
"and I like someone who is pure style."
"(Q)The moment you fall for the opposite gender?"
[Min Jung]
"I fall for little things"
"like the voice I like"
[Hyo Yun]
"You said about voice."
"How’s mine?"
[Min Jung]
"Yes. I like it."
[Hyo Yun]
"Thank you."
I moved because I thought she can be moved
and be thankful for small things.
[Min Jung]
"I’ll ask another question."
"Any personality you prefer ?"
[Hyo Yun]
"Someone who isn’t too extroverted."
"I don’t like it when there are too many guys around."
[Min Jung]
"I’m actually a little extroverted."
"So I thought I should be more careful for my next answers."
[Min Jung]
"(Q)When was your last date?"
[Hyo Yun]
"Umm… I think it’s been about 5 months ago."
[Min Jung]
"Did you frequently had blind dates after your break up?"
[Hyo Yun]
"No, this is my first one."
[Min Jung]
"Ahh...Okay."
"I think it’s not good to meet someone at a blind date who just broke up."
[Min Jung]
"Also I liked his answer that he never had any blind dates afterwards."
[Hyo Yun]
"(Q)What are 3 things I have to know to get close to you."
[Min Jung]
"It’ll be nice if you know what I’m recently interested in."
[Hyo Yun]
"What is that?"
[Min Jung]
"I like to decorate my house"
"and umm…. What else…"
[Min Jung]
"It will get better when we get to know each other."
[Hyo Yun]
"Umm… Okay, thanks."
"I moved not because of a particular answer"
[Hyo Yun]
"but when she said ‘want to get to know each other’ I moved."
"(Q)What’s your favorite food?"
[Min Jung]
"I like most of Korean foods."
[Hyo Yun]
"I like meat the most."
[Min Jung]
"Which kind of meat?"
[Hyo Yun]
"I think pork is the most delicious."
[Min Jung]
"Samgyeopsal? (pork belly)"
[Hyo Yun]
"Yes I like samgyeopsal (pork belly) and also moksal (pork neck)"
[Min Jung]
"How about gopchang (pork small intestine)?"
[Hyo Yun]
"I like it !"
[Min Jung]
"There are a few men who doesn’t eat gopchang."
"So I asked carefully if he likes it and said yes."
[Min Jung]
"I thought we have similar tastes."
[Hyo Yun]
"(Q)How much do you drink?"
[Min Jung]
"Enough not to ruin the atmosphere?"
[Hyo Yun]
"How much is that exactly?"
[Min Jung]
"About one bottle of beer?"
[Hyo Yun]
"One bottle of beer?"
[Min Jung]
"Yes."
[Hyo Yun]
"You don’t drink a lot."
"There was no reason to move forward"
[Hyo Yun]
"because it really doesn’t matter how much you drink if it’s fun while drinking"
"Although it’s not so good if she’s a heavy drinker."
[Min Jung]
"Actually I really like drinking."
&lt;Q. How much do you drink?&gt;
[Min Jung]
"About two bottles of soju?"
"But he said he likes feminine style."
[Hyo Yun]
"(Q)Do you have a hobby you want to share with your boyfriend?"
[Min Jung]
"I hope we can enjoy outdoor activity together."
[Hyo Yun]
"I don’t like to put too much time into something."
"I also thought I wanted to share the same hobby so I moved back."
[Min Jung]
"(Q)Do you like to go on a vacation with your girlfriend?"
[Hyo Yun]
If I have the chance, I’d like to.
[Min Jung]
"(Q)What do you want to do if you go out on a date?"
[Hyo Yun]
"Going to Han river, going to a good restaurant or drinking together,
nothing so special."
[Min Jung]
"He said he likes traveling and dates that aren’t so special."
"After hearing his answers I moved because we have a lot in common
so I thought we could really hit it off "
[Hyo Yun]
"(Q)My last question is, what do you think about friends of opposite gender?"
[Min Jung]
"I could make new friends through my boyfriend"
"so it’ll be nice if you can take me to those meetings."
[Min Jung]
"I don’t really care."
[Hyo Yun]
"I’m a little jealous."
"If I tell you I don’t like meeting with a male friend"
[Hyo Yun]
"What will you do?"
[Min Jung]
"Then I won’t."
"If my boyfriend doesn’t like something I wouldn’t do it."
[Min Jung] : "Hello" /
[Hyo Yun] : "Hello"
[Hyo Yun]
"Pleasure meeting you."
[Min Jung]
"I’m Kim Min Jung."
[Hyo Yun]
"Nam Hyo Yun."
"Nice to meet you."
[Min Jung]
"I never thought someone younger than me would show up."
"I wanted to be more active but"
[Min Jung]
"he said he didn’t like extrovertish person in the beginning."
"So I acted introvert which I regret…."
[Hyo Yun]
"She was much better than what I thought."
[Min Jung]
"Wow he’s handsome."
"A pure young man?"
[Min Jung]
"He was like an idol."
"Even though it was different with what I thought I still liked it."
[Hyo Yun]
"When we faced each other I thought she was very pretty."
"Although she wasn’t 100% my type just by seeing her"
[Hyo Yun]
"but wanted to get to know more about her."