Do you separate between those for dating and those for marrying?
Those having some distinctive feature, so called pretty girls, are not really my type.
I love floristry.
Some sort of unfair governmental regulation?
&lt;When a lawyer with deep voice meets to-be-music teacher&gt;
[Seung Woo Ko, 33 Years Old, Lawyer]
Hello. I am Seung Woo Ko.
I am 33 years old and an attorney at low.
[Ji Young Lee, 27 Years Old, Music Teacher]
Hello. I am 27 years old Ji Young Lee, living in Banpo Dong.
I majored in Viola
and preparing to be a teacher in next year.
Q. Your type?
Personality really doesn’t matter.
Person itself is the most important.
The most important thing is… appearance?
Hahaha
Warm and caring guy
like fatherly figure
I like someone with delicacy.
I am worried and excited at the same time.
-Hello
Q. May I ask what you are doing?
I am an attorney at law.
Aha
Q. May I ask your 3 strengths of yours?
My strength?
Yes
(Firstly) I live my life to the fullest
Secondly, I live well.
(Thirdly) I will live that way.
Those are three strengths I have.
Q. Do you have any cultural interest?
I do not have the preference.
Let say, going to a museum
I do like going to a movie or listening to a music.
But I do not usually go to concerts
or have (specific cultural interest).
I expected someone with some sort of sensibility.
But
He does not seems to have (sensibility).
Q. Do you have any hobby that can be played or displayed proudly to others?
I love floristry,
which would have made me become a florist.
I’ve learned for a long time.
So floristry might fit for that answer.
Floristry…
Well it is just a hobby.
It seems to be a very neutral answer to me.
Q. What stands most important when seeing a woman?
I see when a woman is very distinguished in what she does very important.
Those who work very hard..
Someone who love herself
and her work
I found those women to be powerful
Uhm…
Then do you have a specific type, in appearance wise?
Those having some distinctive feature, so called pretty girls,
do not go well with me usually.
I like someone with cute vibe.
You seem to weigh more on one’s vibe.
Yes.
His first word,
‘I like someone who is distinguished on what she is doing.’
Uhm..
sounds like he weights more on internal things
than external things.
Q. Your parents might have had certain wish toward your job
from the childhood.
If they have, what was it?
They would like me to have a stable job.
for example a teacher
So I am planning on becoming one next year.
Ah~
My father also practices law.
But he really does not want me to do also.
He just shows how it is being done by practicing it by himself to me.
Of course I have been influenced by that.
Q. Have you dated a woman
who was not so your type?
To be honest, your type changes
as you age,
or case by case.
So I do not think that your type only depends
on specific appearance or so.
Hmm
Yes that is me.
Q. When you are dating,
you get to meet his friends or colleagues.
For example, if your boyfriend would start the start-up company,
you might join some gathering of his with his colleagues or friends.
Uhm, yes.
What would you do?
I haven’t really had an experience of gather together when dating.
Ah yes.
So I haven’t had a lot of those gatherings.
I have become friends with them if I had the opportunity.
You do not like those gatherings?
It is not because I do not like it.
But I happened to see just each other.
Yes
Q. May I ask about your dating pattern or style?
I normally do
as women tends to please.
For example, ‘You call me certain times a day.’
‘You see me certain times a week.’
I do as she asks me to.
You adjust yourself to another very well.
I do not think that is an adjustment.
I really do not mind.
Q. Do you prefer meat or raw fish?
I prefer meat.
Do you like lamb meat?
I love them.
Oh really?
Have you had lamb rib, not lamb chop?
I love lamb rib more than lamb chop.
That is awesome.
I love lamb meat.
Lamb meat are indeed excellent.
Women tend to not like lamb meat.
They are usually not fond of that funky smell.
But she said she loves it.
I moved toward her without noticing.
Q. Do you like cat?
A cat?
Yes
I used to have a cat.
Ah really?
I love cat and dog.
Ah I like that.
They are great.
I love cats.
It’s been 7 years I’ve had a cat.
Those who are not pet people,
might not fit me well because I talk about cats all the time.
So I think those who like animals
tend to have a warm heart.
Q. Are you religious?
I am born Christian.
I go to church every Sunday.
Have you ever dated with someone not religious, or with different religion from you?
Most of them I’ve dated were not religious.
Do you preach?
If he is interested, I will.
If he is not, I would not feel the need to do it.
I see.
Q. Do you separate between those for dating and those for marrying?
When I date someone, I also consider a future with her.
Q. Do you appeal actively to someone you like?
I am always very active.
Ah~
Have you seen a woman being active?
Yes I have.
Doesn’t matter if it is a woman or man.
I am active
and those I’ve dated were mostly active.
Q. Is there a certain unfair governmental regulation on the industry you work in?
My major is music
and the market for it, or classic music market in Korea is very small.
I would like to see those markets grow more and become more active.
I believe those who are very focused on the industry that they are working on
and have been in that industry for a long time,
would have those kind of issues.
It is not like they are just doing things because it is given.
Those are the ones who prepare for the future.
So I asked that question.
Q. May I ask if you drink or smoke?
I do not smoke.
but I drink.
I love whisky.
It is not like I drink heavily.
I like whisky itself.
I am very much interested in liqueur kind and its culture.
I like to visit those whisky bards in Hannam.
Ah~
I go there time to time.
You are very similar to me that way.
Do you drink?
I like cocktails.
Each bars has their own signature cocktail.
Yes.
I like to go and drink those.
Have you ever been to bar alone?
I have time to time.
To Bar?
Yes
Ah really?
Oh~
Women tend not to like whisky or cognac.
I enjoy drinking whisky.
I normally do not drink soju or beer that well.
I like that.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
-Hello
Nice to meet you
You’ve done well.
What should I say?
You look much younger than I thought. I heard you are 33.
Ah really?
You are 27?
Yes
What do you play?
Viola
Ah really?
That is great.
Do you know Viola?
Of course.
Ah really?
I do not know that well.
It is okay.
Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?
Her voice trembles at first.
Felt that she was a nice person.
If she does not tremble at all, it might have scared me.
Can I be honest? For real?
His voice was very good.
He talked too well.
He seems to be sly.
She seems to talk and show her quality well through conversation.
It was very neutral.
I like neutral.
I would like to talk to him more?
His questions were a bit serious.
I liked that.
Q. How do you feel after checking each other out?
He seemed very polite.
I had different image in mind when talking to him.
Producer: Is he your type?
His appearance was.
She is pretty.
She seems polite.