Are you into K Pop idols or celebrities?
I am really into dancing so I like BTS, BtoB.
So you like EXO?
&lt;When Yonsei Queen who loves EXO meets Boy Fan of EXO&gt;
[Lee, Hyung Song, 22 Years old, college student]
Conversation from the last date did not go that well.
Q. How do you feel about joining for the second blind date?
But for this time,
I would like to meet someone whom I could really talk to.
Uhm,
I like someone with warm-hearted look.
I would like him to be that one.
For this time,
[Park, Ji Won, 24 Years Old, College Studnet]
I expect it to be excited rather than being comfortable.
Then I would like to have a nice conversation with her.
Hello
How was your trip to here?
It was okay.
I took a bus.
Okay then, I would like to ask you a question first.
Q. What have you been doing lately?
Currently, my semester is on so
I go to school for classes.
What year are you on?
I am junior.
I am also junior.
Ah~
Q. What is your major?
My major is Chemical Engineering
Ah~
What is yours?
Uhm it is named as Biotechnology but
it is simply known as Bioengineering.
Oh, I am also Chemical and Bioengineering.
Oh really?
We have some similarities.
We probably have similar classes.
Q. What do you do when staying at home?
I watch TV a lot
I tend to be relaxed by lying down most of the time.
Then do you go out with your family in the weekend?
My mother likes me to go out with her.
Do you have any sibling?
I have a younger brother who is a year younger than me.
I can picture a happy family.
I am very close to my family,
compared to others.
I am also close to my family
Ah~
So I found that to be similar.
Q. Do you prefer going outside
or staying in?
I prefer going out and being quiet.
Huh?
Maybe going to some quiet places?
Yes, I go to café by myself a lot.
I have also done a lot of activities within college
I tend to attend the mandatory meetings.
At the same time, I spend my spare time
going to café alone or shopping alone
or going to a movie by myself.
This has been more often than going to the meeting with other people.
I also prefer being alone quietly.
So if the boyfriend is active and outgoing,
and wants to go out to crowded places,
that would cause a problem
when actually dating.
I thought that matched my taste.
Q. What is your dating style?
I prefer friend-like dating style.
Uhm
It is hard to put it on a word.
Being comfortable when together style?
Ah..
Q. When was the last time you’ve dated?
It was a year and two months ago.
It has been some time.
Q. How much is adequate for dating costs per month?
I really haven’t thought about the cost.
But I do feel as a burden if a guy
tries to handle all the stuffs by himself
and feels pressure on him.
For example, if a guy pays for the dinner
a girl could buy a desert.
‘You are a guy so handle all by yourself’ is
pressuring me more.
Q. How much do you think is adequate for dating costs per month?
I live in Seoul by myself and handle all the living costs by myself.
I do not spend much on myself,
but I spare a lot for my girlfriend.
Q. What kind of hobby do you like to share with your boyfriend?
It is not much of hobby
but I would like to go around and find delicious food.
Do you have any likes and dislikes?
I do not have any specific for that.
I do eat all kinds of food.
Do you like cilantro?
Cilantro? Ah~
I have been quite shocked after having cilantro.
I also do not prefer cilantro.
Me too.
Q. How do you feel about long distance relationship?
Let’s say it is hard to meet up at Ilsan.
Before living in Seoul,
I thought Gyeongi-Do and Seoul are same thing.
So you don’t mind the distance?
Ilsan is not that far.
If I like, I prefer to go to where she lives.
That answer seems to be telling me
that distance doesn’t matter.
‘Of course I can come to Ilsan.’
I could hear that from his answer.
So I liked his response.
Q. If two people get into a trouble,
what do you think is the good resolution strategy?
If I get upset about something,
it is hard for me to say it right away.
I think about it in my head, not getting upset about it,
then it grew inside and gets me upset,
then I tell him about it.
So you just hold it in then tell it away all at once?
I do not tell him about every single thing that makes me mad.
If it has been 5 times, then I would tell him I got mad 2 times.
or something like that.
Uhm…
I would like her to tell me every time.
If it is not a big thing,
you could just mention it then have a conversation about it.
You could adjust some things to each other.
I would think that it is better than not telling it every time.
Q. If you are dating,
are you the type to adjust
or to make her adjust?
I prefer to adjust myself to her.
Man and Woman are different.
I adjust by thinking of that difference when dating.
Then let’s say, you fought with your girl friend,
and it is clearly her fault,
would you still apologize or get mad at her?
You said it is her fault.
Yes.
Uhm, then how about 80% of it is her fault?
Ah…
I wouldn’t get mad about it right away.
I would meet up with her and have a face to face conversation.
It would make a huge difference.
I would ask her one by one.
I liked that side of him.
Uhm
To be honest, I am not the giving-in type.
So it would cause a lot of fights,
if both are like that.
I am not asking him to adjust everything to me
but if he tends to give in to me
it would cause less fight.
Q. Is there any specific moment or experience
that makes you feel ‘Ah he is the one for me.’?
I tend to like someone
who is good to me.
I don’t like playing game.
I like someone who
continues to be good to me.
My mind grows upon him.
If you like someone, do you go up to him actively?
If I like this guy very much,
I would go for it actively
I do not think that it is awkward for a girl to go up to a guy first.
I have never seen any girl coming up to me first.
Most of time, I’ve went up to them first.
So I felt interested in when she mentioned going up to a guy actively.
then I moved closer to her right away.
Q. Do you like to tell other people when dating?
I am not ‘In a relationship’ status on Facebook type of girl.
I obviously tell my close personal friends
but do not go up to them and say ‘I have a boyfriend’
loud and clear.
Most of my friends would know so
I do not feel the need to tell them.
I have been hiding since.
So if I date this time,
I’ve thought of opening it up widely.
Q. If a boyfriend lives an hour ride away,
saying that he wants to see you a lot,
but you’ve got only an hour, would you let him come?
You are saying if he comes to Ilsan, and ask me to come out,
I would go out or not?
It took him an hour to get there,
see you for an hour
and go back taking an hour.
I would just go out to see him.
I wouldn’t go out if I ought not to
but he came to see me taking an hour ride,
it is not nice for him if I ask him to go back.
Okay I see.
Are you a fan of any idols or celebrity?
Ah to be honest, I like boy groups.
Ah really?
Who do you like?
I like to dance so
I like BTS, BtoB,
and etc.
Ah..
I am not that into girl groups.
I like those who could dance well.
For example EXO or etc.
Ah really?
So then if your girlfriend likes celebrity,
how would you feel?
If she visits their company office,
or she goes to see their performance on stage
Wow you are familiar with the words!
I have been interested in those things
so it is okay for me,
but it would surprise me if she goes frequently.
Let say there is a concert,
if she asks you to buy a ticket together, would you?
Of course I would.
Oh really?
Yes.
I would go to PC café if it needs.
Q. Do you like music festival like UMF?
Uhm, I do not prefer EDM, is it correct?
I don’t like too crowded places.
I prefer to stay at home
because I do not like crowded and loud places.
Ah I see.
But if my boyfriend asks me to go,
I wouldn’t say no to that
but I wouldn’t enjoy myself
going to those festivals
Then you wouldn’t hide your feelings if you go.
Huh? No, not really.
It would be too loud for you.
Ah I do not hate it that much.
It would make you happy if boyfriend asks you to go to EXO concert.
If he obtains a ticket, yes
Okay, I see.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
-Hello
What should I say?
Ah ..you are really
never mind.
What? Why?
Never mind.
Junior?
Yes.
So you are in engineering?
Ah..
Aren’t you in engineering too?
Yes I am.
You must be very famous around school.
Not really.
Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?
I thought she was quiet and calming style.
but she was fluent
telling her stories well.
So I think I could talk to her well.
When I asked him a question
he mentioned more deeply than I’ve expected.
So that made me to talk to him well.
Q. After checking each other, how do you feel?
Appearance is not my priority,
but thought she was very pretty.
To be really honest, when I first met him,
I didn’t have ‘Oh I really like him’ feeling.