What do you do?
I am a lawyer.
Oh~
Do you like to watch zombie movies?
Woah, you are very passionate.
&lt;When man and woman who both likes zombie movies meet each other&gt;
[Ko Seung Woo, 33 Years Old, Attorney at Law]
For this time,
I would like the conversation to flow well.
[Kim Na Young, 26 Years Old, Actress Trainee]
I was so nervous at first time.
I would like to talk to him more
this time since this is the second.
I would like to meet a woman
who likes her job and does her best in it once again.
Uhm, someone with
big personality and big shoulder but cute face?
That kind of style?
-Hello
Q. May I ask how old you are?
I am 26 years old.
Oh, I am 33 years old.
Ah okay Hello again
Yes hello
Q. What do you do?
I am a lawyer.
Ah, I see
This is the first time I have met someone
who works in that industry.
What about you?
I majored in Drama
and working as an actress.
I have just moved to Seoul.
Where is your hometown?
Mine was Busan.
Ah~ Busan it is.
Yes.
Mine too is Busan.
Oh really?
Yes
Oh~
In Dongnae-gu
Yes
Nangmin-dong
I am from Nangmin-dong.
For real?
It is a place where people from Busan is not even that familiar with.
I was born there and lived for a few years then moved to Seoul.
So it is my hometown.
I was surprised to hear of the word ‘Nangmin-dong
Because
Most people from Busan are not familiar with that place.
So I did not expect to hear it from him till then.
I felt close to him.
Q. Do you love what you are doing?
You do enough to continue to do it?
I thought of doing something else after graduating college.
But I made up my mind and moved to Seoul to do this.
So I will put my heart to it.
Even if it would be a hard way.
Whoa, you are very passionate.
I felt that she did not treat her job lightly
when hearing her words
of deciding to move to Seoul from Busan,
where she has spent her life.
It is definitely not a easy decision to make.
She is eager,
focused and passionate,
which has made her to come here.
I think that is very brave of her.
Q. What do you think is most important in a relationship?
To respect the personal time
and personal space,
while to cherish the moments spent together.
It can be very hard on each other when these two collide.
So I think it is important to respect the personal boundaries
while to cherish the moments that are spent together.
So yes that is me.
Yes.
Q. What is your blood type?
Mine is type B.
Ah…
Yes.
I see.
Why blood type?
I do not like Blood type theories that much.
It may be because I am a type B
and most women do not like
men who are type B. I am not sure why.
And secondly,
it seems it is not based on scientific data
but rather for fun
Q. What is your personality like?
I tend to keep silence at home.
It is very important for me to have some quiet time alone,
which may seem that I am an internal person.
But when I go out, I am very outgoing.
Are you a quiet person at home?
I do not talk much at home.
I am also a quiet type at home.
So I would like to meet a person
who talks more at home.
So I moved backwards.
Q. Do you enjoy watching Horror, or Zombie movies?
Oh,
I love watching Zombie movies.
Oh really?
What is your favorite film?
From zombie movies?
My favorite was ‘Dawn of the Dead’.
First time I’ve seen was when I was little.
It was so good that I watched twice.
It is a work of art.
It is a textbook
for how zombie movies should be made.
You love zombie movies too?
In college, I loved watching them,
especially those of George Romero
from the 80s
Dawn of the Dead is like a textbook
for a modern zombie movies.
2004 release, right?
Terrific movie.
You really love watching them.
Yes I do.
Yes, I used to be really into
those horror and zombie movies.
in Senior year in college?
After I finished submitting the thesis and had nothing to do
I binge-watched horror movies.
But the ones I liked
were not women’s favorite of course.
So I thought that side of her was good.
Q. Then the best movie in your life must be Dawn of the Dead?
I love that film but it is not the best movie of my life.
Q. then what is yours?
My favorite is
Constantine, starring Keanue Reeves.
Is it a war film?
No, it is not a war film.
I am interested in those supernatural stuffs,
like spiritual thing, angels and demons.
Ah~
This film is based on comic book series.
Adapted from that series.
Yes
As it was being adapted by a film
the main character’s name ‘Constantine’ was still used
it is a great film. You must watch it.
I have watched it more than 7 times.
He was very excited when explaining it.
He was very adorable.
It was very fun listening to his story.
It seems like he really likes that film
and is very much into it.
I felt attracted to him.
So I loved forward several steps.
Q. What is your like and dislike
for food?
I like lamb ribs.
I like them.
And also grilled large intestines.
Grilled large intestines?
Large intestines, yes.
Q. Do you have hard time deciding what to eat
or do it quickly?
I do it quickly.
Ah~ I see.
Q. Do you prefer to go and visit hot crowded places
or to rest and enjoy the nature?
I do not enjoy that much from being relaxed in the nature.
Ah~
I really do not prefer that.
Ah…
I do not like
those scenery in nature.
It must be metropolitan.
I have been in Marines.
I have spent 6 months in the sea.
Then I got sick of the sea.
Ah I see how you got there.
What about mountains?
I hadn’t liked it once.
Ah…
I hate climbing.
Ah, I really do not like that.
If he had said ‘I like it but it is not my favorite’
I would have stayed there not moving
but he has shown his disgust in it very clearly
Q. Which famous person do you respect,
or like?
For my career wise,
there is a person called ‘Kim Young Moo’.
I respect that kind of person very much.
He is the founding partner of the best law firm in Korea, Kim &amp; Chang.
He is my role model for career.
For celebrity, there are so many.
Uhm,
For a special interest,
I am not sure if you know
‘ChulGu’, famous Afreeca TV BJ (Live Video Streaming Service)
Ah yes.
He has always been the center of issues lately, has been on a news
been doing something very weird but
He was the one of the founding members of live streaming Video service BJ.
I get what you mean by that.
He used to be a pro-gamer (Starcraft).
Yes I know.
He used to BJ the gaming TV.
Gaming TV?
Yes.
She has shown her interest in what I’ve mentioned.
It got me excited.
That sort of feeling?
sort of lamb rib?
Q. What was the average term of relationships you’ve had?
Most of them were long term or short term?
Most of them were not long term.
If it was a long one, it lasted a year.
For short one, less than 6 months.
There have been terms in-between.
Yes…it had been that way.
I see.
I think you must see a person for certain amount of time
to get to know that person, rather than seeing one after one repeatedly.
I do not think it is a good to see one after one repeatedly.
Q. There are a person who leads and another being led.
Which side you tend to be?
I tend to be a person who leads.
Oh really?
I say it straightforward
if I want something to be done.
I did not hide my feeling.
Ah I see.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
Hello
Nice to meet you.
I would like us to have more conversation.
The time is very limited.
Yes I feel the same way.
Nangmin-dong?
Yes. How do you know Nangmin-dong?
My grandmother still lives there.
Wow what a coincidence.
Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?
He led the conversation very well.
So I felt comfortable enough to get along.
I felt the need to have more conversation with her when
I felt that she was nervous
because she is younger than me
Q. How do you feel after checking each other out?
During a blind date, he appealed his opinion strongly
so I expected to see a strong looking man
but he looked very soft
It was absolutely different from what I expected.
She is pretty.
but
not close to my type?
but she is adorable.
I did not know the session would end that quickly
and after I saw my standing position at just where I started.
I felt very…