I really wanted to look back
Among the entertainers l listened to, l resembled Suzy
&lt;When Suzy of job training met an office worker&gt;
Hello
I’m 29 years old, Kwang-Geun hong and I’m an office worker at a company located in Samsung station.
Hello I’m 24 years old , job seeker and I would like to meet someone who looks like a man with a lively personality.
I would like to meet an active person who is not passive.
I'm pretty nervous right now.
I’m really curious so mad.
Hello
So be awkward and I really wanted to look back
Very fluttered
I think his voice was so good that I thought I wanted to see his face once.
What style of appearance do you like?
I like manly man.
I want him to be a positive, leadable, dependable man.
Are you being dragged?
I want someone who can depend on each other rather than being dragged around.
I like men with sexy looks
What do you think of your appearance in a 100-point scale?
And why?
Could I rate it as a 10-point rating?
Yes, please tell me a 10-point rating.
I want to give 7points to me.
Please tell me why.
Because I think my face isn’t bad but my face isn’t popular nowadays, So cut three points.
Are you satisfied with your face?
I’m not dissatisfied.
Who do you look like from entertainers
and What part does it look like?
Among the entertainers l listened to, l resembled Suzy.
I think it’s okay…
wait um..
There is no one who doesn’t like Suzy.
If she resembles Suzy, then I should go back for sure.
What style do you usually wear?
It's different every time.
Do you mean you wear different clothes depending on the situation?
Right
It depends on where to go.
It’s plain
I think he can wear different style of clothes depending on the situation
Who do you live with?
I live with my family,
I have a sister and a younger brother, and I’m second.
I’m raising three Maltese.
Puppies?
yes
I think people who are raising puppies usually have a responsibility
and tend to take care of others.
What about your family members?
No brothers. I’m an only son.
And my parents are abroad now.
I went forward not because his parents are abroad but rather he is only son
The only son would be likely to be lonely
I went forward because I thought there would be a different side from those who had sisters and brothers.
What do you do on a day off?
I like to do pilates on a day off or go to a good restaurant with my friends.
So go to a good restaurant or excercise
Really?
I also like to eat,
and no one will hate a woman who does pilates.
Do you usually exercise in self-management or have a hobby?
I used to play kendo before,
and I’m usually playing soccer with my friends in the neighborhood every weekend.
And doing boxing these days.
Do you have a hobby that you want to be with your lover?
As you said, l like to go to a good restaurant and want to eat a variety of things together.
Do you like to play around?
Yes,
I got a car recently
and like to drive around here and there.
Just before, I said I liked to go to a good restaurant,
so he remember my story and he answered
me also like to do.
l felt l could go with him , so I went back.
And he said he got a car recently and I thought I could drive with him.
Do you have a religion?
I am atheism.
Are there any three things you should keep in your lover relationship?
First, I do no often contact her when I work,
so I hope she understands this point,
Second, I hope she doesn’t drink alcohol often.
Third I wish there was no time limit to go home to her.
Do you want the time she go home to be unrestricted?
Yes, I want.
I think that communication is important in the relationship of lovers
and that’s when the man told me about the contact,
so I got a good feeling.
But He told me he wanted her to have no curfew,
but how could he tell things the first time
I saw him?
Do you actually have curfew?
Nothing.
Do you think there are three things I need to know to get close to you?
At first I feel a lot of strangers,
you may feel it is not funny,
but when you got close to me,
you’ll feel like I’m a fun person.
That’s first.
The second, I have ever lived in a foreign country
so there are occasions when things are not conservative sometimes.
And the third
I love animals very much.
Are there three things I need to know to get close to you?
I like fun things,
I like the cultural life so I could watch movies like that
And I want you to respect the opponent.
The person has own opinion.
Could it be close if you respect the other person’s opinion?
I think it’s really important to respect other opinion.
I liked it because she talked about what I always thought was important,
so I went back.
How many times do you have a message and a phone call a day in a lover relationship?
I do not know well,
it’s been too long since I have not been dating.
Denpending on what the next day it is.
Just as much as I like.
He didn’t tell me specifically,
just he said I often get in touch and depends on the next day
Ah~~even if he contact the person he like, he are concerned about the next day.
In that respect, the good feelings are little gone so I went forward one step.
Blind date end.
They’ve talked so far…
Time to check each other
Hello.
Nice meet you.
So beautiful.
Thank you.
You’re so cool, too.
When I heard the voice, it was okay.
It is bass.  A voice that woman would like
I want to see his face quickly.
At first, her voice is very blunt and pronunciation is also blunt well…
Is she so serious? but
The more I heard the more attractive the husky voice was and
She looks like an entertainer
The eyes were very big and there were dots under my eyes like me
I thought it was a manly appearance, but it was not
And the double eyelids were dark but weren’t
Just it was normal?
He seem to be a normal guy.