When K-Drama ‘Goblin’ came out…
If I’ve got a time, I can go and visit everyday.
&lt;When Song Joong Ki of Chung-Ang University meets a younger lady&gt;
Q. This is your second blind-date. How do you feel?
A. Since this is my first time,
[Suh-hyeon Jung, 24 Years Old, Unemployed Graduate]
I would like to meet someone that could warm my heart through this winter.
[Hyo-yoon Nam, 25 Years Old, Undergraduate]
A. I am a bit nervous.
Q. Who do you expect to meet this time?
A. Because I was too nervous at last time,
I could not concentrate on the partner that much.
But then it means
that I was not that attracted to her. Hmm…
I would like to meet someone,
instead of making me think, ‘What should I say?’
Making me comfortable enough to start the conversation.
Hello
He seems to have a nice voice
It was very deep.
I liked his voice.
First question is
Who is your celebrity look-alike?
If there is one, which part is most alike?
When K-Drama ‘Goblin’ came out,
people told me I and ‘Lee El’ (Korean Actress) look alike.
It was probably because I liked red lipstick.
That lip color makes me look alike with ‘Lee El’ (Korean Actress).
…’Lee El’ look alke?
At first time, I mentioned ‘Suzy’
As a look alike that I used to be hearing.
Because I could not think of anyone else.
But for this second time, I had decided to mention whom I really look alike.
It seems a bit distant from
what I was looking for in style.
What is the most important quality you look for in men
and the reason for that?
I see how I could talk to the guy,
Because if I cannot even talk to the guy, it cannot be happening.
I would like to meet someone whom I could really talk to.
I have mentioned that I do not want to meet someone
making me think, ‘What should I say?’
So in that point, I felt the same with her.
How do your friends and family describe you?
Active? With humor?
My friends often tell me
that I am a good friend
but not a nice person to those who are not close to me.
But I could be with humor if I like this person.
I see.
He does not seem to be nice for everyone.
I feel that it only matters when one is being good for those who are close to him.
I become more attracted to him because I felt the same.
What is your life style pattern?
I do not sleep that much.
12 Hours sleeping? I cannot sleep all day long.
I am having insomnia these days.
so I tend to stay up late and get up early.
I also have insomnia
I do not sleep much also
I also get up early even if I have stayed up late last night
So if he were not an early bird,
I am afraid that I can’t get in touch with him in the morning
Again this made me feel more attracted to him.
Which hobby would you like to try together?
If I were dating someone, I would like to visit
hot restaurants
I also want to take a picture together while visiting those restaurants
Those are the hobbies I would like to try together.
If I were dating someone, I also would like to
go and have good foods together.
That is one of my wishes.
If you were dating someone, which restaurant would you like to go together?
I would like to go to
this roof-top café in Itaewon.
I would like to go there with someone to have a good food in such nice place.
How many times per year would you travel together if you are dating someone?
If there is time,
I would go everyday.
Okay I see.
Do you like to drink?
If you do, do you prefer Soju or Beer?
Please tell me
I prefer Soju over beer.
I can drink up to a bottle.
For beer, 2 glasses of draft beer
are maximum.
That is an opposite of me.
I do not prefer Soju itself
because of its too strong smell.
I prefer So-mac (Soju-beer cocktail) or Beer only.
I honestly do not drink So-mac or beer but only Soju.
He is the opposite of me.
So I stepped out once because I like to drink
meaning that we would have to order not only Soju but also beer
Which kind of outfit do you prefer?
Occasion to occasion,
I prefer to wear what I would like to wear.
I take extra care on how I look because I am into stylish clothing.
But I prefer not to look too out there
and wear too bright colors.
I also prefer dark colored clothing.
He told me that he also does not prefer too bright colors.
I liked that point also.
When do you feel that you fall for someone?
First impression goes a long way.
I also think the way he similes is important.
I feel it when I see the way he smiles.
I feel the same way.
I also think that first impression is important.
So if the first impression is not so good,
it does not make a good person
no matter how many times I see that person again.
I think the same way.
I will ask the next question.
What do you think of girl friends and guy friends?
How far could you go with them?
I have a guy friend.
So I would like to respect him having a girl friend.
I think it is okay for him to have a meal and go for a coffee with her,
but drinking together is absolute No.
I get really jealous.
Of course I won’t be like ‘Do not see him.’
but I would be like ‘I think it would be better if you do not see him.’
What would you do if boyfriend does that?
Uhm..
First I would hear him out.
so we wouldn’t argue.
If she agrees with me just to stop the argument,
this will eventually become bigger argument later on.
I do not think she has thought this through when she mentioned it.
How many times do you prefer to get in touch with each other per day?
As long as it does not disturb one’s life pattern,
I would try as many as I can.
Do you prefer to talk on the phone or
send text messages or Kakaotalk (SNS Messenger) ?
Uhm
I prefer calling over Kakaotalk.
What is your ideal level of attachment to the partner?
My ideal level of attachment is pretty high.
So I like someone whom I can lean on
and I tend to focus more on the partner than friends when dating.
I would mostly spend my time on work and the partner.
If I were dating someone, I mostly spend my time meeting my partner.
I always think of seeing her as top priority in my schedule.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
Hello
What should I say?
You do look like ‘Lee El’
I do?
Yes you do.
Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?
When I only hear his voice,
I felt that he would be mannish, and much older.
But as soon as I saw his face, he looked much younger.
Before I see her face to face, I thought of her as much subtle character.
But she was very dressed up in person.
Q. After checking each other out, how was it?
He was what I have expected.
because I could talk to him.
I could really talk to him.
His mannish voice escalated my expectation.
I liked him when I saw him.
First I thought her dating style
was very similar to mine.
but then her dating style and characters made me feel
more close to her.