If it is a love at first sight, would you be a couple on that day or not?
To pick one from celebrity, maybe ‘Yoon Du Jun’ (Highlight)?
Thank you
&lt;When a mature girl meets hard-working man&gt;
Q. How do you feel to come back for a second date?
In the first time, I was not really serious.
[Hong Kwang Keun, 29 Years old, Businessman]
For this time, I would be more serious and show my real quality.
[Kim Min Jeon, 28 Years old, Businesswoman]
I am also very nervous this time.
I usually do not go on a blind date but I have given an opportunity again.
I am expecting to meet a nice person.
So I came back.
Q. What kind qualification you are looking for this time?
I would like to see someone active.
I also want someone I could talk to.
I look for someone that I can really hit it off.
Someone who likes my real self.
What should I say?
I look for someone who is more active.
Hello
I like your voice.
Thank you
Pretty name.
-Thank you
-Should we start?
Q. What is your ideal type of woman?
My ideal type of woman is someone who knows when to be serious and when to be fun.
Q. Which body part you think is the best of yourself?
My legs.
Is it firm?
-Pardon?
-Never mind.
Why the legs?
My legs are long and straight.
Q. What do you do and are you satisfied your job?
I work for an entertainment company and am highly satisfied with my job.
Then you would see a lot of celebrities?
I see the artists in my company a lot.
You must have a very fine taste in men!
If she works for the entertainment company,
She would probably see a lot of good looking people quite often.
Q. Where do you live and who do you live with?
I live by myself in Sangam-dong.
Really?
If you live alone, aren’t you worried much?
I am used to do all by myself.
The house I live in has also been handled by myself.
I am independent that way.
I moved closer to the word ‘Sangam’
I used to work at Sangam.
I also like someone who is independent.
Q. What would you do when dating someone?
Do you like surfing?
I have never surfed before.
If I have a chance, I would teach you how to.
Thank you.
Q. Who do you picture when you hear my voice?
It can be one of celebrities.
You sound like you are funny.
If I pick one from celebrities,
‘Yoon Du Jun’(Highlight) a like?
Thank you.
Yoon Du Jun. Women like Yoon Du Jun.
How can I ever be like Yoon Du Jun?
It is funny but I once have been told
that I look alike Nicholas Cage.
What is one thing that I must know to get closer to you?
I like to drink when dating.
I prefer that kind of dating.
Do you drink a lot?
I like to drink.
I can drink in food truck (Pojang Macha)
when sharing each other’s difficulties while feeling very close.
I prefer that kind of dating style. Friend-like. I want those to be similar.
Is there any specific place that you would like to take your girlfriend?
Spain.
In what point?
I can guide her through with my Spanish skills.
You can speak Spanish?
Yes
He can speak Spanish so he told me that he could
guide me through any time.
So I thought it would be very good to travel with him.
You might not like it if you really hear it but
If we have a chance to visit Spain together,
I can guide you through the streets
and visit Madrid
Barcelona,
and see soccer games together
Lastly I would like to have a beer together.
Do you like to drink?
Yes I do
I like drinking in food trucks. (Pojang Macha)
Are you a drunk?
I tend to wink a lot when I am drunk.
To people around you?
To people that I am drinking with
I see
I do not know how to wink.
Like this?
Q. What is the worst behavior that a guy does?
When we are in a restaurant,
I frown upon those who are not nice to the workers there
I like people who know how to behave to others.
I always think that I must do also.
I loved her answer.
I also think of being respectful to others as the most important quality.
Q. Between passionate love and intimate love, what do you prefer?
I prefer the passionate one.
I see
It is my preference.
I prefer more intimate and committed style these days.
Friendly relationship?
Q. What is your bucket list?
What is the one that you must try?
Blind date it is.
Pardon?
Never mind. I like to do bungee jumping.
With girlfriend.
What if that girlfriend is afraid of it and does not want do it?
I would jump alone.
I would persuade her to do it together.
but if I can’t…
It is on how much she trusts me.
If it is a love at first sight, would you be a couple on that day or not?
I would
A reason for that is?
Because I fell in love with that person.
Are you being friendly?
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
-Hello
Nice meeting you.
Nice meeting you too.
Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?
I loved it.
I could really talk to her.
I could see him being active and trying to make me comfortable
but I think it was a bit too much.
Q. How do you feel after Blind-Date?
After talking to her, she matched with my ideal type.
She is 120% matched.
I was not that moved
by his characters.