How tall are you?
I am..
I also like to go to Hangang.
I am excited.
Me too..
&lt;When a reasonable man meets a emotional lady&gt;
[Jeon, Hyunji, 24 Years old, College Student]
I am thinking that
Q. This is your second blind date, how do you feel?
I could talk more having more confidence than the first time.
[Kim, Dongwoo, 25 Years Old, College Student]
I am very nervous.
Q. This is your second blind date, how do you feel?
I would like to have more things in common.
I also wish for 165CM height woman?
Hello, I am Dongwoo Kim.
Hello, I am Hyunji Jeon.
Okay
Nice meeting you.
You too.
I would like to ask you a question first.
Q. Between staying in or going outside,
what do you prefer?
I prefer going out.
Oh really?
What do you do?
I do not like staying in.
So I go to café and read or watch a movie.
I absolutely do not.
Q. What is your blood type?
I am A.
Do people tell you that you are a typical A?
No. they have hard time figuring out.
Ah really?
Yes.
You don’t sound like A.
So they have hard time figuring out.
I thought he is A, but he doesn’t sound like one.
I do not have a preference.
Type B guys are not good guys for me.
Q. What is your hobby?
I like to exercise
and go out to find delicious food.
Q. What is your hobby?
I also like to go out for exercise
I also like watching movies.
What kind of movie do you like?
I like thriller,
I like movies that make me think.
Who do you go to movie with?
Most of the time, I go
alone.
There is a movie theatre nearby my house so I go there by myself a lot.
Do you like eating food and going around for delicious food?
I like it very much.
So my friends ask me about good restaurants when they go out
Yes
they tend to ask me.
I love eating.
Q. Do you drink?
Yes I do.
but I like the atmosphere of it rather than drink itself.
Oh really?
Q. Do you like to drink?
and do you have drinking habit?
I like drinking
but I try to keep it down.
I do not have a specific drinking habit
but I get really high
when drinking
I become talkative and so on?
I think that is it.
I am like that too.
If you don’t go to those engagements, you do not get to see friends a lot.
Isn’t that hard for you to not go and meet?
It is not like I absolutely do not go there
but I go there but I leave early.
It is hard for me to leave early when I am in that circle.
You are very well-managed.
I know, that is the hardest part.
She seems to like
staying up till the end of the engagement.
But I do not prefer staying up till the end
every time.
It is no fun.
Q. What do you think is most important when dating?
I think it is important to talk to each other a lot of things
and be supportive for each other.
Ah~
Q. What is considered most important
when seeing a woman?
For the appearance, I am pretty tall so
I like a girl with certain height
For the personality,
I like a girl with active spirit.
Also I would like to talk to her well.
I would love to meet someone who likes small talk.
Do you prefer a specific type for appearance?
I do not have the strict limit for the height.
But I have a preference in height.
Something like that.
Aha
Q. How tall are you, may I ask?
Haha, I am 160CM
Ah you are 160CM.
Yes,
Ah~
My parents are pretty tall
but I am relatively short so my parents were always wondering about my height.
Yes…
Q. Do you consider yourself to be reasonable?
or emotional?
I am very reasonable.
I do not make a decision based on my feeling.
Absolutely not.
I am pretty much reasonable.
Uhm
I tend to get really emotional
So if boyfriend is also emotional
then it would be harder for both to keep it up.
I would like to meet a reasonable person
to keep the balance of the relationship.
Q. How many times per week do you think is appropriate to meet?
I think once a week, I would spare entire day for my boyfriend.
Ah~
Q. What kind of date would you like to have
with your girlfriend?
I would like to spend time doing usual stuffs.
I would go to have some foods,
talk for hours in café,
or go to Hangang and enjoy the view.
I also love going to Hangang.
Oh really?
Q. Do you appeal to someone you like?
It would depend on how we met.
If we met on blind date,
I appeal my feeling to him actively.
If we like each other,
and we do not play the game,
I prefer that much better.
PD: How about you?
If I like that person, I go up to her and appeal my feeling very clearly.
Q. Would you date someone on the first day you’ve met?
If it is a person I really like,
and I think this is the one,
I can date her on the first day.
I haven’t had that experience though.
I like that side of him
I didn’t move further close to him because
the conversation did not flow that well.
PD: How do you feel?
I am excited.
I am also excited.
I don’t think I can speak if I see him in face to face.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
Hello
Nice to meet you.
What do I say?
I am not sure what to say when face to face, are you too?
Yes.
Are you normally not that talkative?
Me?
I need some time to feel comfortable enough to talk to newly acquainted person.
Ah~ you do.
Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?
Our conversation did not flow well.
That was unfortunate.
For this time, I also found a lot of things in common
but the conversation did not flow well.
Q. How do you feel after checking each other out?
I could feel that she is small from her voice.
His first impression?
He is tall.
I expected him to be very serious, older brother like,
but after I see him, it didn’t give me that
much of older brotherly impression.
Um, how do I put it,
I did not find that excitement.
Something like that.
It is like cute little sister.