Do you have any specific skills to calm your girlfriend when she gets upset?
I do not date anyone that comes to me.
&lt;When Yonsei Goddess of EXO-L meets good-looking guy of Dongguk univ.&gt;
[Lee, Hyun Song, 22 Years old, College Student]
Hello I am Hyun Song Lee, junior in Biotechnology
from Yonsei University and 22 years old.
[Kim, Dong Woo, 25 years old, College student]
Hello I am Dong Woo Kim, 25 years old
and majoring in Drama from Dongguk University.
Q. Your type?
My type is nice looking guy.
I would like to meet someone with seriousness but also
some wit to make me smile.
Someone proactive
I like taller girl.
-Hello
Q. How do you spend your spare time?
I prefer to stay at home.
I prefer to stay and relax at home.
I like to watch TV
or lie down lazy.
I see.
I didn’t find any similarity in that.
I cannot stay even a day at home doing nothing.
Q. What is your favorite food?
I have a older man’s taste in food.
I like Goodbab (Korean Soup with Rice)
He had an opposite taste from mine.
I do eat Korean food
but prefer Japanese or Western style food over Korean.
But he does not seem to like those.
Taste of food is very important for each other.
You could ask me the next question.
Q. How many long-term relationships have you had?
About 6 times
Q. When was the last relationship?
-The last one?
-Yes
Um.. the last relationship was
about 6 months ago.
Ah…
I hadn’t had as many long-term relationship experience as he had
So his last relationship which was 6 months ago was
quite near to now for me.
So I paused for silence.
Q. What do think is the most important in the relationship?
Meeting each other’s needs,
making sure if each other feels comfortable when together
I prefer friend-like lovers.
So I would love to share our daily life and get to know each other more
and eventually get really close to feel comfortable when together.
It is very important to me.
People often feel some pressure that it must be something special
when having a relationship.
I think of those pressure as a burden and unnecessary.
So I thought her response matched with my thinking.
Q. When a boyfriend is not easily reachable because he is busy,
Q. do you still ask for his obligation to contact you?
If he is not reachable because he is occupied with something,
it is of course okay.
What I’ve meant about sharing our daily life is
doing it when each other is free enough to share
where she/he goes, what she/he does,
what she/he does with her/his friends, or she/he works on her/his thesis.
Q. How many times per week do you meet your girlfriend when dating?
Meeting everyday would be hard because each has his or her own life.
Two or three times a week would suffice.
I see
Q. Do you have any specific skills to calm your girlfriend when she gets upset?
I just become very kid like.
Do you mean being cute?
I intentionally play around more.
: I am being cute, which is not really expected from a person of my size.
I cannot stand those cold and silence atmosphere.
I try hard to calm her and sooth her.
Q. Are you normally being cute to your girlfriend?
I don’t usually do it.
Only when she is not feeling good?
I do it to make her feel better
I don’t do being cute often.
If she gets upset,
I intentionally touch her by her shoulder.
Keep doing it…
Q. What is your skill to make your boyfriend feel better when he gets upset?
I also do not do being cute often.
My mother also points out that I am not that lovely to her.
However if boyfriend gets upset,
I will become more cute and lovely to make him feel better.
If she is being cute to make me feel better
while she is not usually that kind of a girl,
it can be really lovely if you think about it.
So I thought of it and felt that it would be very cute and made me feel better.
Q. How tall are you?
I am 188CM.
You are too tall.
Do you have a preference in height?
Between 167CM and 170CM?
So you like a tall girl.
If you give me a choice, yes.
How do you like shorter girl?
I think they are cute.
Being shorter makes
them look cute.
Q. What is your height?
I am 162CM.
For me, between 167CM~170CM is very tall for a girl.
I felt a bit surprised.
Q. How do you feel about long distance relationship?
I live in Ilsan.
How do you think of me living in Ilsan?
If your girlfriend lives in Ilsan?
-Ilsan is not that far away.
-You do not know where Ilsan is, right?
I know where it is.
I do not think it is that far away.
Ah really?
Yes.
If I ask you to come Ilsan because I have some things to sort out, would you come?
Of course I would.
Q. Do you do any SNS?
I do Facebook and Instagram.
Do you post a lot?
Using a lot of hashtags
Putting #Followme #Daily in the end.
I just upload pictures and that is it these days.
I don’t put hashtag.
I feel too lazy to do that.
Posting loads of pictures and
hashtagging useless stuffs like #followme #college
are something I really do not like.
Revealing too much of self on internet?
I don’t prefer that so I asked him.
Q. Do you have any favorite idol or celebrity?
I usually do not have any interest in them.
Ah..
I am a big fan of K-POP idols.
Producer: Who is your favorite Idol?
EXO!
Producer: Whom of Exo?
I love Sehun and Baekhyun.
Q. If you like someone, do you appeal to him a lot?
I need to be with someone
I really like.
And this means it is hard to find someone to be with.
It is of course harder for that someone to like me in same sense.
So if I think I like this guy a lot,
I appeal to him actively
by calling him and talking to him.
I like her being active.
Blind-Date Finished
Now it is a time to check each other out!
Hello
I have a hyperhidrosis on my hand.
I also have a sweaty hand.
What is your major?
I major in Bio-Convergence
like Bio-engineering.
Very different from what my major is.
Yes it is.
I thought it was very interesting that you are in Drama.
[Q. (During Blind-Date) How do you feel?]
When I first heard her voice,
I thought of someone very slim.
His voice was very low and deep.
I loved his voice.
She seems to have herself figured out and hold very firm opinion.
I think it is nice to be in that way.
I didn’t find that much of similarity from him.
[Q. After checking each other out, how was it?]
His look was…
His height was nice and tall.
I prefer that good guy look.
but he looked edgy.
It wasn’t all that bad though.
Uhm...
What I thought of first when I met her?
She is pretty.
I would like to see her again.