MISSION - EYE CONTACT FOR FIVE SECONDS
Five seconds?
Yes.
One, two, three!
Wasn't that more than five seconds?
Hello.
My name is Won Jae Hyeong.
I am Kim Cha Ron.
Nice to meet you.
Can you drink well?
I like to drink.
Oh, you like to drink?
Yes.
Do you shake the bottle?
I just open it.
The glass is pretty.
Have you done a lot of blind dates before?
No, not a lot.
This is my first time...
Oh, this is your very first blind date?
Yes this is my very first time.
So I'm a bit nervous.
This is your first time and you applied to be on this series?
Yeah, I was bit drunk when I applied for this.
Same here.
Oh really?
How old are you?
I'm 26 years old.
Oh 26 years old?
I'm 27 years old.
Ah~ you look very young.
I'm not sure if it's because you are nervous,
but you look younger than your age.
Maybe.
BETWEEN A JAPANESE RESTAURANT CHEF OR A CEO OF A ONLINE SHOPPING MALL, JAE HYEONG'S JOB IS _________.
CEO of a online shopping mall?
Yes.
That's correct?
I see.
At first, I thought you were a college student.
Really?
At first I thought you were doing something in the arts.
I get that kind of vibe from you.
Oh really?
I studied traditional Korean dance.
Have you seen a performance before?
No, I've never seen a performance before.
Oh really?
Yes.
That's possible.
I'll invite you next time.
I'll go no matter what.
THE BLOOD TYPE THAT CHA RON AVOIDS IN A MAN IS ____ TYPE.
Blood type-A
Correct~
Am I correct?
You aren't?
Yes. I'm blood type-B.
Oh~
What's your blood type?
I'm blood type-A.
Oh. You're blood type-A,
but you don't like blood type-A...
Blood type-As tend to analyze everything,
think too much, and are sensitive.
And I found that kind of characteristics didn't match with me.
It's because I am the type to act first.
Oh I see.
You don't avoid dating any blood type?
I think it's blood type-B.
How come?
We tend to argue a lot.
I wonder if it's because we're both kind of stubborn
You don't like that type?
I like someone who is strongly opinionated.
Oh, I see.
I like blood type-B.
Oh, really? Thank goodness.
What?
No nothing LOL
CHA RON'S LAST RELATIONSHIP WAS ______ YEARS AGO.
I’m guessing 1 year ago.
Oh, seems like I need to give you a shot.
Then, how long has it been?
It's been a while. 3 years.
Oh really?
What happened?
Hahaha~ What happened?!
Sorry, my bad. Did I make a mistake?
You're very beautiful
so I'm wondering why.
Have you been asked out before?
Oh, I've had.
But I start my schedule very early in the morning
and end very late at night
so it's very hard for them to understand that.
Do you mean practice schedule?
Yes. As time passes and as there's more practice hours, it just didn’t work out.
It's been a year and half for me since my last relationship.
One year and half?
Yes.
That's still quite a bit of time.
Right.
My last relationship was hard for me.
So I didn’t
I mean couldn’t start another relationship
and then after time passed and being single for a while,
I don't know exactly how to please women now.
Mmm...
So you didn't have any flings during that time?
I had
but I was unskilled in a way...
You guys broke up?...
Right...
Ah, are you usually dumped?
Yes, I've been dumped by all.
You are laughing too much
BETWEEN A SCHEDULED DATE AND A SPONTANEOUS IMPROMPTU DATE, CHA RON PREFERS _________.
A scheduled date.
Wrong.
I like more impromptu dates.
Because of your schedule..
My schedule is very fluid,
so when we meet, I say "I want to go and do this" and we go and do that.
Do you plan your dates?
No. It depends on the mood.
For instance,
you're feeling down today,
then where would you go?
Go eat something delicious somewhere?
To brighten your mood?
Yes, to try and make my date feel better.
No, I mean when you are feeling down.
Oh me?
I don't think I've ever felt like that.
Your mood is always great?
I always feel great when I'm with my girlfriend.
That's... That's the right answer.
Ah really?
CHA RON CAN OR CANNOT LET HER BOYFRIEND GO DRINK WITH OTHER WOMEN.
Cannot
*laughs*
I'm right, huh?
You're right.
But if there's a person you like,
isn't it right to be jealous?
I think that's right.
Oh, but do I look like the jealous type?
Yes.
*staff giggles*
Did I make a mistake?
No, you didn't.
Everyone is…
It's not like I cursed.
Well, hmm. How do I say this?
You seem to be passionate about your work
and therefore you seem to be passionate about what's yours so...
That doesn't sound like a very good personality.
No, I like that.
I prefer that kind of personality.
Oh like I am considerate and think of them that much.
Yes, I think I will feel that way.
For instance, people say even if they are in a relationship, they feel lonely.. you know?
Yes.
So you probably want your boyfriend to express a lot..
Do you express a lot?
Usually guys don't text when they're eating.
Do you?
I tend to send pictures.
Like to validate what you're doing?
No, but more like telling her 'I'm eating this'
and just sharing each other's daily life constantly
so we can empathize together and converse with each other therefore we would get more intimate. I think...
I think your girlfriend will like it.
It's been a year and half, so I'm not even sure.
Then would you let your girlfriend go for a drink with other guys?
Usually, I'd say it's okay,
but if I'm answering for you, I wouldn’t allow it.
What kind of answer is that?
You're so attractive,
I just...
I'd probably feel... You know...
But if I had to give you permission...
What's your limit?
Until lunch.
No dinner.
No drinking at all.
Before sun set?
Before sun set.
CHA RON REALLY WANTS TO BE IN THE RELATIONSHIP WHEN ______.
When you drink?
You want to be in a relationship when you're drinking?
When I come home after work and have a beer,
I think it'd be nice to be able to enjoy it with my girlfriend.
How about you?
These days, I want to enjoy my hobbies with my boyfriend.
Everyone around me is currently in a relationship
That's these days?
Yes.
They have times when they fight,
but also time when they're having a great time
and that's when I feel jealous.
JAE HYEONG HAVE TO GO ON _____DATES TO DECIDE IF HE WANTS TO BE IN A RELATIONSHIP?
4 times?
That's very close.
Is it 5 times?
3 times.
Why 3 times?
Well, when you first meet, image is almost everything you see.
Mmmm...
The second time you meet,
you've conversed by this point,
I think you can kind of see their personality.
And the third time,
it's the day I've made my decision.
And the fourth time, you would pop the question?
Yes, but if I can't hold back my feelings, I'll probably ask her out before three times.
Last one.
COMPARED TO THE FIRST MOMENT CHA RON HAS SAME / DIFFERENT FEELINGS TOWARD JAE HYEONG.
I think it's different
Different?
In what context?
Since we were able to have a lot of conversation,
I think it's changed from so-so to...
You think right now I have better feeling about you?
Am I wrong?
No, you're right.
Then can I ask what your first impression of me was?
Mm.. it was very good.
Oh~ really?
The more we talked,
you seemed like a good person so I had good vibes
Oh~~ That's good.
How many more times do you want to see me?
Today is the first time,
so two more times, and I think I can decide.
So, that's exactly 3 times.
Maybe I think I'll know after meeting just one more time.
I'll pour you a shot.
Let's....
toast to getting over singlehood.