I’m curious about if you think that an individual’s voice can make a big impact on the society?
20 people were recruited to be blind date participants
One-sided Blind Date
I chose female participant 7
because I found her radiant smile to be beautiful
What am I going to do? This is so embarrassing
- Hello
I saw your clip and chose you because your radiant smile was pretty
Thank you
Male
Answers the given question
Female
Chooses the option they want
-Inclination-
“Break”
Mountain vs Ocean
I’m done
For me, the ocean
Ocean!
- You must like the ocean?
- Yeah, I do like the ocean
and don’t particularly like the mountain
- Ah, really?
- Yes
I really like playing in the water
Me too
What type of water activities do you like?
Although I can’t swim,
, I like floating in water. It feels really nice.
I usually take my vacations at the beach too
-...Okay
- Okay
“If your partner goes to the club”
You are bothered vs You don’t care
I think it’s okay to go,
but I’m sure it will bother me
Ah, you absolutely don’t care?
Normally when people say they are bothered,
they call often, are very concerned,
- and how do I say it, [the person clubbing] becomes a subject of suspicion
- Yes
- I would like if both parties trusted each other
- Being careless?
and were not caught up on little things
What I mean when I say, “it’s okay to go but I will be bothered,” is that if I can get my lover to fall for me,
then even if they get approached by others at the club, it should be okay.
- You are confident
- Yes, I’m confident
Because they’ve fallen for my charms. Your confidence is very…
Your confidence is very…
No, just saying that it would be good to go with firm trust in each other
Yeah, that’s nicely said
“Spending money and time, just to see a pretty sight”
Spend vs Not spend
I tend to spend
You tend to spend, too?
Things that are not practical at all,
things that have no use but are beautiful..
I’m curious if you are the type to spend money on them
There are a lot of those. I like seeing the sunset.
Things like these are useless in some sense.
They might be considered useless, but I spend time to see these things.
but I spend time to see these things.
- I also like going to boutiques and looking at cute things
- Uhm
Even when eating dinner,
- turning on pretty lights,
- Ah right
- Lighting up candles,
- You are right
- I think are nice
- Right
That’s why I bought an LED candle.
I like stuff like that.
Aren’t most people like this?
- No,
- No?
- There are many people who aren’t like that
- Oh, really?
- There are many people who are more practical
- Really?
- Yeah
- ...
Okay
Mid-inspection
- It’s already the time for mid-inspection?
- Really?
First, she is more beautiful in person than from the video clip.
She is also better at speaking her mind than I thought.
Also I got a glimpse of her positivity,
which makes our tendencies seem similar, too.
Things seem to be better than I was worrying about
He really seems to be a very decent person.
And when he speaks, he has a little bit of a dialect accent,
which I found to be really cute.
And how do I say it, he seems to be really healthy.
His mind seems to be healthy
-Values-
Values...
“When an uncomfortable topic arises in a public place,”
You move on for now vs You talk about it
I choose to move on for now
You would want me to talk about it, right?
- I’d appreciate it if you would
- Ah
Is there a level of sensitivity to the topic?
Doesn’t everyone have the same level which they feel uncomfortable at?
Actually, no, is it different?
If it’s at the level everyone feels uncomfortable in, I would discuss it too
Have you experienced anything like it?
That kind of experience?
I can’t think of anything specific right now,
but when something uncomfortable comes up,
I try to at least address it jokingly by saying things like, “These days you can get arrested for saying that.”
If it’s not that kind of situation
and me saying something would actually bring an awkward atmosphere,
- I’d be more careful to speak up.
- Ah..
And I’d consider each relationships too.
- I’d consider everything
- Ah..
- I am the queen of causing awkward atmospheres.
- Oh really?
Are you upfront about it?
- Yeah, I tend to say things right away.
- You do?
When too many things are passed by and ignored like that,
- You are right, they might never know their faults.
- Yes
Do you have such experiences?
- There are a lot
- Oh really?
Stuff like that happen a lot in small situations
But when you act that way, your image is also impacted.
You might be viewed as someone who is always pointing things out.
You don’t care about that?
People probably avoid speaking up because that’s a something they care about?
- You right. They usually talk around...
- Yes, but....
- But a problem is a problem
- You usually point things out right away
And it can also come back to me as well. Those kind of words?
I see...
- You should point things out too
- Me?
In a public setting?
I may or may not, depending on the circumstances
"More important to me"
Self-development vs Societal change
Hm!
I have to think about it for a bit
I feel like you would’ve chosen societal change.
For me, it’s self-development
- Oh, self-development?
- It’s really nice to know your answer.
- I think it’s best for both of us to go at the same time
- Me too
So I chose self-development.
I say individuals come first, but we should also care for the society as well.
That’s why we should vote.
- Yes
- This question we agreed on;
because of the previous questions, I thought you would’ve chosen societal change
I’m the queen of causing uncomfortable situations
and a “professional discomfort-er” (a slang for people who are easily offended) in that sense,
but I still think that I need to choose good things to fight for
So are you saying that you are selective about things you fight for?
It came out weird. That’s not really what I meant.
For example,
if uncomfortable topics came up at company or family get-togethers,
I would point them out,
but I’m not the type to be fighting about them online in the comments section
because that’s too consuming for me
Then do you speak up because you want to influence those around you?
Because you think they can change?
Not so much that I want to change them my own way,
- but more so because their words are hurtful towards me?
- Ah right
I’m curious about if you think that an individual’s voice can make a big impact on the society?
Umm, I wish we could use new methods
because I wonder if there are more effective ways to handle things.
I think that those are issues within the structure of the society
and can be viewed as mistakes caused by ignorance.
If those people were the type to be changed after being taught,
they would’ve already learned from the news.
So there needs other institutional method
or company training;
I think it’s good for the higher powers to approach them.
- Because if individuals dealt with them, it would cause so many fights.
- Uhm..
That’s that
"Current attitude towards my life"
Content and happy vs Ambitious
- Did you choose?
- Yes
- For me, it’s content and happy.
- Ah
- I love that phrase
- Ah, really?
Do you make efforts to be content?
I think I’ve always lived busily
so I think I want my partner needs to be more relaxed
- Oh so you want your partner to be this way
- Yes
- Is that me? Someone who is content and happy?
- ...
I’m sorry
- You are full of confidence
- No, not really.
Anyway, I try my best to be content.
But also not to fall behind by being too content either,
since we live in a competitive society
- It’s okay to fall behind
- Oh really?
When I say that I like someone who is happy and content,
I mean someone who goes, “I don’t really know (care)!” in a competitive situation
- Oh really?
- I think I like that type of person.
. Ones who make you wonder, “is it okay to live like that?”
Really.. I do think it’s important to have the attitude to make best efforts.
I don’t think it’s good to give up so easily.
Live by working hard, while being content
Because we are always told to achieve things.
- Especially Korea.
- Right
I feel like when one chooses to escape that route, they are considered losers.
But when I see people courageously choosing that, I find it to be respectable
Though it’s not easy, that is a more respectable decision
Final decision
- It’s already time for the final decision?
- It's already?
- But we did talk a lot
- Yeah we did
Interested in dating
Send an O X accordingly
Ah, the fact that we have make a decision so quickly
- Did you send it?
- Yes
I sent mine too
This is so odd.
- Because it’s with someone I don’t know anything about...
- Right
- I don’t even know your name yet.
- ... It's weird
How was it today?
I really came not even knowing your face and spoke to you.
It was nice
because there were variety of questions asked without any stereotypes
and we were able to get to know each other through them.
If I were to be given more information ahead,
a different image would’ve been formed
Because we talked right away without even knowing each other’s names.
It was a fun experience
The light will turn off on the side that sent an X