I predict that you are going to have crush on me
by the end of this blind date.
okay
hello
I'm Min Joon Woo and I'm 20 years old.
I'm Lee Jee and I'm 20 years old.
Lee Jee?
Yes
You have a pretty name
Thanks.
Can we speak casually?
Yeah
Wanna do a shot?
Can I do half a shot?
No, you can’t
I'll start.
Why are you so tense and nervous?
Because you are prettier than I expected
Thanks
Should I pour you a shot?
You know how to say the right words.
JOONWOO’S GREATEST BREAK AWAY of 20-YEAR OLD LIFE IS ______.
Going to the club?
You got it perfectly right.
You look like...
you live at the clubs
Wait, wait.
Oh my god
it just got hot.
Not in a stereotypical way,
I say it like a compliment
No, that's not a compliment
I went clubbing for the first time this past July.
Really?
You don’t know how to party
You should go there on the New Year’s Day with your ID on your forehead
I heard it was packed that day.
You must like clubbing.
Club? Of course.
Hongdae is my turf
Vexx, Maxx?
Yeah, I swept them all.
Do you put your hair over your ear as you walk into the club?
You gotta toss your hair back like this.
Shall we drink?
Sure.
Wait wait wait.
JOON WOO DOES OR DOESN’T ACTIVELY EXPRESS HIS FEELINGS TO THE GIRL HE LIKES.
I think you would.
I would? Final answer?
Yeah
Then how about now?
RIght now...
I think you're interested in me
Judging from what?
The sparkle in your eyes
My eyes? My eyes?
When I like someone,
I can’t hide it.
So I was right.
How about you?
I think you won't tell if you like someone.
No you're wrong.
Then, how do you express it?
I make a crazy effort to see that person.
In anyway?
Yes
if that person is in a different class,
I will go audit that class
and try to sit next to that person by accident.
Then out of 10, do 9 fall for you?
Easy
Whoa.
Your self-esteem is overflowing
I'll pick.
Oh, I was curious about this one.
LEE JEE HAS BEEN IN RELATIONSHIP ____ TIMES.
Won’t you get offended by the answer?
No.
ten…
times…
You really think that way?
wow
Take a shot first because you are wrong.
You dismissed me
I dismissed you?
because I guessed too high or too low?
Because you guessed too low.
It's 20 times.
You count them all?
I cannot. It's confusing but around there
My longest relationship was 200 days
but it's never been over 1 year.
Same. I've never dated longer than a year.
I try to compensate for that other person a lot.
So eventually I get tired of that person
and she gets tired of me too.
I usually take the initiative and hold onto the guy.
So you don’t like to be adored?
Right. So I like to take care of the person.
For example, if he says "I wanna eat that"
and I'll say "really?, let’s grab them later"
and then the next day I'll buy that for him
and be like “Here.”
Wow. So you are like cold outside but warm inside.
That’s quite attractive.
I predict that
you are going to have crush on me by the end of this blind date.
Okay~
Can you pour the rest
No, you drink mine too
I can totally tell about this one
JOON WOO CAN OR CANNOT LET HIS GIRLFRIEND GET DRINKS WITH OTHER GUY FRIENDS
You cannot.....
is what you think I was gonna say right?
Ah, that's a foul.
You can't do that.
You're not lenient huh?
Before, I didn't allow it,
but after becoming 20 years old now
I realized that person has to live her life too
and hang out with her friends and I try to respect that.
I think if that friend is a woman, it's an automatic no.
May be  just a meal.
Like he's mine
Of course.
No one else can meet him?
Yesh. Like I said before,
I take the initiative in the relationship.
Our opinions are different.
JOON WOO CAN PICK UP UPTO ________ YEARS OLD .
You look very confident
so I say 30?
No, you're wrong.
29...?
29!
Can you guess again?
You're not lenient at all!
I poured less than before.
Comparing how much you poured to me, I'm being fair.
Want me to drink with you?
Yes.
I thought my answer was 29
hmm..
Mine is 26, 27?
So anyone under 30, you can lure them?
of course
To have young ambitions!
when do you wanna get married?
I honestly think age doesn’t matter.
Just, if I like that person and I trust that person.
You never know a person's life and future right?
So with that thought,
I want to be very caring and discreet to that person.
Me too.
You too?
But even though you've dated short relationships after short relationships?
Sorry, that was rude.
Watch out. I told you to be lenient, I am warning you.
JOON WOO EVER HAD OR DIDN’T HAVE A MOMENT WHEN HE WANTED TO AGE FASTER.
I think you have.
I have?
Are you sure?
I will give you one more chance.
you have!
I did have moment when I wanted to age faster.
So you can go clubbing
and be better at flirting right?
Stop bringing up clubbing.
I don’t like clubbing that much
Kidding, kidding.
Anyway, not for that reason.
Because as a Korean male
I have to mandatorily serve military service
so… I'm worried of if I met someone I really like.
Oh, my heart aches
So I am jealous of the ones who are already done with the service.
And if I have girlfriend at that time I wish she wouldn’t wait.
Is it burdensome?
Not so much so.
I honestly think age 20, 21 is the prime time for women
And as much as I'll like to do my best for her. That's not something I can guarantee.
But if she can give me one more chance after my service,
I think that'll be enough
Is it okay if she meets other guys during your service?
I don’t think I have right to suppress her choices.
She has her own life and has to live her own life
Wow, you're awesome
What do you mean? How?
Just you are freaking awesome
I don’t think you'll wait anyways
I thought like that too first.
But if I really love him, I think I can
If he's the one?
If someone I really like waited for me,
I will definitely make her happy.
LEE JEE PREFERS TO TALK TO HER BOYFRIEND VIA MESSENGER OR ON THE PHONE.
Phone.
You are right.
I really like talking on the phone.
Like I can put it on a speaker phone
and do something else,
or I can be on the phone while getting ready.
I did want to try talking on the phone all night until you both fall asleep
and in the next morning, you're both still on the phone.
I have unlimited minutes
Can I call you later?
Of course, I am unlimited.
I like casual relationship.
Casual? How?
I show wacky pictures of myself while video calling
and meet up with no make-up and stuff.
I’ve never experienced that.
(I look pretty without make up)
(Okay, I'll call you later. )
What is that meaningful smile?
JOON WOO FEELS THE SAME OR DIFFERENTLY ABOUT LEE JEE NOW COMPARED TO THE FIRST MOMENT
Same!
Different!
Why?
Drink first and then I'll tell you.
Be lenient.
Okay. Lenient.
Initially, you looked quiet and calm,
but you're actually very bright and outgoing and kind of wacky.
You are right.
Is there anything you're curious about?
I am going to ask you straight forward.
Are you going to keep in touch with me?
Yeah, I am
Really?
Should I pour you a shot?
Yeah, I'll pour you one too.
Last shot
It was fun today
Me too,
I think you are a nice person.
Really?
That's all you have to say?
Yes… I mean no.
You are very bright, outgoing, and look like you enjoy clubbing
Let’s disregard the last part
You seem like you love clubbing.
This is my last question.
When are you doing your military service?
If we start a relationship, I'll go much later.
really?
About when?
when I get a guarantee that you will wait for me?