Se-Hui
Ho-Jun
How are you?
Yes
Thinking of going to school make my heart pound
I hate it
Today's Quest
Who will be the one who prepares a gift?
Should I choose first?
You go first
Se-hui will prepare it I think
It may be just me, but man is weak at choosing gifts
not knowing what to buy them
If we think about them choosing clothes last time
He chose
so I think he will prepare
so you think he will?
yes
Their Date bucket list. Han-river date
be careful
They prepare picnic
Shall we eat chicken?
Really feels like being on a picnic
These days people lend those kind of things
Tables and tent
Their first quest is?
Giving each other nicknames
giving nicknames?
It's really hard
What do you want to call your boyfriend if you have one?
What to call him?
I never thought of it
like this
Then...
What do you want to be called?
I never thought of that too
What about you?
My name
Oh you like your name
Can they call each other name?
Let's try it
It maybe cheesy
It's not even easy
We were eating and this happens
You go first? or me?
I'll do it first
Wait... I can't do it
It's hard
can't help smiling
Let's make many good memories
Ho-Jun
She called his name
He can't even look at her eyes
I'm younger than you but take care of me
Se-hui
Did he just say Se-Hui?
Okay
I'm gonna call you "Hun"
Kind of like a dog name?
telling the truth game
rock paper scissor
then...
You go to coed school right?
Have you ever been proposed by someone?
Yes
Have you ever want it to date that person?
If I wanted I would have
then you didn't want to?
Yes I didn't
If he liked me I didn't like him
There are two kinds of people
One needs to love and the other needs to be loved
How about you?
I have to like him first
you?
Me too
Eventhough she likes me, If I don't like her I won't date her
It's a really sad thing to meet without emotion
Rock paper scissors
Then
We did a lot of things
among them tell me one moment you your heart beatted
When we went to the clothes shop
When you wore the same clothes as me
It's touching
Who prepared the gift?
I got something for you
It was Ho-Jun?
Don't look yet
What do you think it is?
I have no idea
If I give you a hint
It's one of the things you wanted to do
What I wanted to do?
Is it a couple item?
It is
Ta-da
Ho-Jun secretly prepare a gift for Se-hui
He learned to tie though he isn't good at it
He chose it for Se-Hui
I finally won!
Why did you prepare it?
It's touching
There's a unique way to tie it
Hold this
He is embarrassed
(He self talked)
Like this like this
Is that correct?
You try it please
Se-Hui waits for embarrassed Ho-Jun
Isn't he cute?
It's his first time so he doesn't know what to do
I don't think it will fit
He finally put it on her wrist
I'll do it for you
Their hands touches a little
It's already getting dark but they don't recognize it
Penalty time
Did it hurt?
It missed
But I think it hit my vain
Sorry
When I received the gift
It was a surprise
It was touching
It was cute that he had a hard time putting it on to me