Why do you glance over?
Ah...
It’s not because a woman is smoking, but...
Yes.
but it,t.... [stuttering]
Can I get a drink of water?
20 people were recruited to be blind date participants
One-sided Blind Date
I chose participant 5
I usually like individuals who are gentle
and she seems to give off that vibe
- Hello
I thought you’d be the type to be calm and gentle
so I chose you
You like that type of person, huh
Male
Answers the given question
Female
Chooses the option they want
-Inclination-
“Cellphone”
iPhone vs Galaxy
I picked iPhone
Why did you choose iPhone?
I’m also currently using an iPhone and personally,
I like the distinct vibe it has
I would like the guy I’m dating to also be using an iPhone
and enjoying taking photos
Since it’s easy to share
Yeah, since I like its vibes
I feel the same way
“Social issues on social media”
Tend to post about them vs Tend not to post about them
I tend not to post about them
Do, do you...[stuttering]
Do you often post about social issues on your social media?
I don’t post about them often,
but I like people who are interested in social issues and voicing their opinions out loud
Because it’s a sign showing that they are not indifferent about these issues
For me...
I think that everyone...
I think that everyone pays attention to social issues
Yes.
But I don’t particularly see the reason...
wh, why they should post about them on social media...[stuttering hard]
ca, causing disputes in the comment section [stuttering again]
and being stressed about it;
Ah..
Because it's one's choice...
- Aha..
- I tend not to post them
I see...
“When seeing women smoking,”
You glance over vs You don’t glance
I said I glance over
Why do you glance at them?
Ah.. look...[stuttering]
um....[stuttering2]
It’s not because a woman is smoking, but....
Yes.
but because s,socially and culturally in Korea, [keep stuttering]
it, it’s an uncommon sight [stuttering well]
But on the other hand, even if I gla…[stuttering worse]
...............[chaos]
if I glance over,
Yeah....
and....
Hold on. I’m sorry, I’m so sorry
I'm really-really sorry
Am I funny?
No, I’m so sorry, omg sorry
Women and men are both humans [peacefully]
so of course women also have urge to smoke
or wish to try it out
to see if it will relieve stress, or something like…
..............[chaos again]
Can I get a drink of water?
My th... my thoughts won’t come out well LOL
To me, cigarette in itself is considered “preference in foods”
and while it is a natural thing for men to smoke it,
when women do, it always grabs attention,
- which I don’t like
- Ah..
So I’d like someone I’m seeing to also not care about it
and not really glance over
I don’t really glance over a lot either,
but when I do, it makes me reflect on myself
- Doing a double-take on yourself?
- Yeah yeah
- So far, it’s still like that
- Yeah, to this day,
Korea still has remains of this kind of attitude
Mid-Inspection
Mid-inspection..
My image of her was on the calmer and gentler side,
but her ideas are clear,
which is slightly unexpected
He seems to be really nice and gentle
But I like a personality that is self-assertive and concrete
In that sense, it’s not a perfect fit but
he seems to be very thoughtful, kind,
and good at listening to others
-Values-
“Partner’s experience living with their previous partner(s)”
You are bothered vs You aren’t bothered
I picked “I’m not bothered”
It doesn’t bother you?
Yes
You don’t care about their past?
Is there anyone who doesn’t have a past?
- I live by this principle
- That's true... Yes
It’s not really good to be bothered by stuff this, you know?
It’s something that I don’t need to be bothered by
and something I shouldn’t be talking about either
I’m not the type to be so hung up on the past
Ah
I don’t think I’ll be bothered too much either
- Since past is something that has already passed
- Right
This person could have dated other women too,
so I said I’m not bothered
“Friend’s ex”
It’s okay to date them vs It’s not okay to date them
I say it’s not okay to date them
Why did you choose that it’s not okay to date them?
Even if it’s someone I’m really attracted to,
if it’s someone who has dated a close friend,
that’s a factor that will bother me
and it can also change the relationship with my friend
I think I’ll always choose my friend, even if it’s someone I really like
I’m the same with you
Some people might consider it as the past, but it deals with someone who’s a part of my life
As you said, I feel similarly about it
Mmm. I see
“Giving up my dreams for my partner”
It’s possible vs It’s not possible
I picked it’s possible
So you can give up your dreams for your girlfriend?
Yes
Oh..
When I’m dating someone,
I’m the type to be very dedicated
If I think that it would be nice to marry this person,
then I think about things I might have to sacrifice.
What’s your reasoning for saying it’s not possible?
- My partner is my partner and my life is my life, you know?
- Right
So the idea of giving up my dreams for my partner is
something I wouldn’t do
My life is more important
and since I am the center of my life
So the person I’m seeing should have pride in their life and our differences
It’s not that I don’t have pride
Yeah haha
- But you know there are different kinds of work
- Yeah
For me, it’s possible to change my dreams accordingly
Ah.... Okay....
“In order to sleep together, you have to be in a relationship”
Yes vs No
“In order to sleep together, you have to be in a relationship” …
I chose yes
- For me, even if I’m not in a relationship,
- Yeah
if it’s someone who is a good match for me and we connect well,
I think we can do it without adhering to the timeline
I think that the sentence “you need to be in a relationship to sleep together,”
also includes one-night stands.
They might have STD’s and
and I think other risks like that are pretty big
I don’t think it’s right to risk those things simply for the pleasure
So in circumstances where both parties like each other but are not in a relationship,
do you still think it’s not okay?
Uhh,
Do you think it’s only possible if they are officially your girlfriend?
If both parties like each other,
wouldn’t we be dating? That’s what I think
It’s possible to go into a relationship after making love
But what if someone you are “seeing” also see other people or,
So basically not in a relationship?
Yes, not in a relationship and both parties are meeting other people
I should be making a decision. It won’t be taken so lightly
and only be done when I have some certainties
I think that’s really possible
Yep, I understand
Final Decision
Interest in Dating
Send an O X accordingly
How was it?
You seemed nervous.
Yeah because there are cameras and lights,
I was kind of in a daze
- It’s still pretty awkward? It’s weird, huh?
- Yeah honestly
You don’t really know what you said, right?
Yeah
LOL
Like the things I thought, I couldn’t really,
Yeah like you couldn’t really organize them into words
- Couldn’t really circulate them
- Ah...
It happens
I’m expecting some hate comments
Why?
Because my perspectives are a little different from others’
Are you the type to care about those hate comments?
I just...
I’ll laugh them off
So you are saying you don’t care
I think it’ll be funny if they get angry at me...
- Really..
- But I don’t think I’ll be offended
Think you’ll laugh it off?
Yeah
Even if it’s really harsh?
They don’t really know me..
You are a pretty chill person
I’m actually just pretending to be
Wh.....
What is this person lol
How would you react if you got hate comments?
- Me?
- Yeah
I’m also not the type to care about others’ opinions about me,
but I’ll probably still read them
I just won’t be hung up on that or be hurt
I think that some people will be critical of me and others will relate with me
The light will be turned off on the side that sent an X