IN A RELATIONSHIP, YASTA THINKS SIZE IS IMPORTANT OR NOT IMPORTANT
I think you will consider it as an important factor.
How much you love is more important.
I'm okay if size matters.
Ha! You're confident.
Of course.
Oh, Hello.
Can you speak Korean?
Yes.
What a surprise.
What is your name?
My name is Yasta
I am Ma Dae Woong.
Ma Dae Woong.
What is your age?
I am 27 years old.
Oh so you are a Nuna?
Oh no~
Let's have a shot~
Okay.
Cheers.
Nice to meet you.
What country do you think I'm from?
Pakistan?
No. I'm from Nepal.
Oh. Nepal! When did you come to Korea?
7 years ago.
Oh, you're very good at speaking Korean. Nuna~
Let's talk casually. Okay?
Talk casually?
Okay. Let's talk casually.
Wow, you're very good at transitioning?
I hope you don't think I'm being rude.
Nah, nah.
It's just a game right?
Right. It is.
What month were you born in 1993?
September
Oh not that much of a difference. Am I wrong?
What month were you born in 1992?
December.
December?
So about a year.
So that’s about 9 month difference.
Guess we're like friends.
Let's be friends.
YASTA'S FAVORITE KOREAN FOOD IS ________.
Kimchi Stew.
Wrong!
Spicy Braised Pork.
Spicy Braised Pork?
Do you like it?
I can't eat spicy food well.
Usually, Koreans eat spicy food well, why can't you?
I think it's because of my body type.
I sweat a lot. I have a high body temperature.
I'm a very hot guy.
So I like sushi, pork cutlet,
and Gae-bul
What is Gae-bul?
*motions*
How would I know from that?
Oh yeah?
In English, English.
Penis Fish.
What?
Korean Penis Fish.
Like a tes******.
Looks like an old dog’s tes******.
Oh, I think I can guess the what it looks litke.
In the tank, they're like....
Yeah, I think I've seen at seafood restaurants.
Right right?
Penis Fish
Why are we talking about this anyways?
I wonder too.
WHEN DAE WOONG HAS MANY RANDOM THOUGHTS, HE DOES ____ ALONE.
Alone?
What can you do alone?
Ah...
You sleep.
With who...?
With who?
No, not with who, not with who.
I like to write.
I like to write like poems and essays.
Ohhhh~
You don't look like you would.
What is your hobby?
I like to hang out with friends, go to places, and take pictures of each other.
For example, going to cafes and taking pictures.
Are you good at SNS?
I'm a pro.
I am also an Instagram Freak
like facebook and instagram
You're like an attention seeker
I'm really not an attention seeker.
Then, you must hear often you are pretty
Mmm, yea. I guess you can say that.
Mmm, okay.
YASTA'S IDEAL CELEBRITY IS ----------.
Song Joong Ki.
Wrong.
Drink, drink, drink.
Why are you lowering the hype?
Shut up and drink.
Yoo Seung Ho.
Ah! Yoo Seung Ho.
He's handsome, indeed.
He doesn't even know you exist.
Of course~ The celebrity you know doesn't know whether you exist or not too.
What the hell are you talking about.
Who do I resemble?
You don't resemble anyone.
I heard this at least once or twice a day.
Oh really?
Song.. Song (hint)
Song Joong Ki.
Wow!
You? Song Joong Ki?
Not even close…
When I don't talk, I heard I kinda look like him.
I don't really know.
Then you must like girl who looks like Song Hye Kyo.
What kind of logic is that?
Just kidding, just kidding.
Oh kidding? Nepalian joke?
yes.
Nepal joke. okay
THE FIRST THING THAT DAE WOONG SEES IN A WOMAN IS _______.
Is it face?
Wrong.
Is it her breasts?
No.
Butt.
Stop there.
Ok
I look at legs.
legs?
So when you first meet her, you stare at her legs?
No~
If you look at the leg first, that's kind of weird.
That's why you are perverted.
I see her face and go immediately down.
Then you look at her face first.
No, but more emphasis.
Not the face.
But I really look at her legs.
Perverted indeed.
I see. Okay.
If you look at the legs, are you perverted?
No, no.
IN A RELATIONSHIP, YASTA THINKS SIZE IS IMPORTANT OR NOT IMPORTANT
Umm…
I think you will consider it as an important factor
Drink.
It's not important?
Oh really?
Drink. Yeah why not?
Oh?
How much you love that person is more important.
But honestly, it's not important?
No.
Why? Are you sma….
I'm okay if size matters.
Ha! You are confident.
Of course.
MA DAE WOONG'S RATIO OF PAYING ON DATES IS --:--
70:30?
Yeah, you're right.
Is the woman 70, or am I?
Of course the guy is 70%
Of course?
No? Alright.
How about you?
What do you think?
I think 9:1
What?
8:2?
No~ it's 60:40
How about in Nepal?
Men in Nepal pay for almost everything.
Oh really?
yes.
So it's hard to date.
So it's a little more conservative than Korea.
Yeah.
so there's this saying that a guy needs a lot of money to date.
I'm hearing this for the first time.
So I wasn’t surprised about Korean dating culture when I first came
I like to Dutch pay,
but there are more situations when the guy pays more in korea.
But I like to Dutch pay because there's less burden.
YASTA WAS IN A RELATIONSHIP FOR ----- TIMES.
Honestly...
20 times?
Well....
*whispers* How many times did I say?
(7 times)
7 times?
(You said seven times during the interview)
Oh I did?
wrong!
I'm right, right? I bet I'm right.
It's 7 times.
Were they all Korean?
Yes.
they were all Korean.
What do you like about Korean men?
They are fashionable.
They treat you well.
They care about you a lot.
So guys being considerate?
Yeah~
How many times have you dated?
They were all short.
It's okay even if they weren't long.
I have probably dated about 20 times.
Were there any foreigners?
There were, huh?
Yeah, there were.
We only went out for 2 days.
Isn't that like a one night stand?
or 2 night stand?
Isn’t this little too much?
It’s ok?
Since you have dated a foreigner before, are you willing to date a foreigner again?
I really don't care about ethnicity and nationality.
But I don’t think foreigners favor my looks.
sagging eyes, hooked nose, and my lips are…
You have nice lips.
I like lips like this.
What'd you say?
Should I go to Nepal?
I think other countries are better than Nepal.
Was that a rejection?
You're okay, for now...
IF YASTA GOES ON A RELATIONSHIP AGAIN, SHE WANTS TO REALLY GO TO ________.
Busan?
Jeju Island.
Mmmmmm.
I haven't been to Jeju Island yet.
I've lived here for 7 years and still haven't been to Jeju Island.
Do you have a fantasy about Jeju Island?
Not a fantasy.
But it's just so pretty.
I like beaches.
So you just look at pictures?
Yeah
Like on Instagram?
Just search Jeju Island
You know, I'm similar too.
If I have a girlfriend, I always wanted to go to Jeju Island.
Oh really?
*laughs*
It's the last card.
COMPARED TO THE FIRST MOMENT DAE WOONG HAS SAME OR DIFFERENT FEELINGS TOWARD YASTA.
I think it's different.
Right.
I thought we wouldn't be able to communicate
because Nepal isn't a country that Koreans are familiar with.
But I think we can converse well..
It's comfortable?
Not exactly comfortable...
It's comfortable to me.
Oh really?
Should I...
take off my shirt?
Is your first impression of me and your current impression of me the same?
Yeah, it's the same.
From the first time, I thought it was good.
It was comfortable. Just from image.
I'm very good at reading people from first impressions.
So it's all positive?...
Yeah, that's right.
Is there any last question you want to ask me?
What are you doing after this?
*thinking*
Sounds like you're not doing anything.
There's nothing at the moment.
Just wondering...
How about you?
I plan to play with friends.
ah~
I'll pour you a final shot as a Nuna.
I'll accept.
Ok
You're welcome.
Cheers.