That’s why I always want to pay
For a pretty picture..
I pay prettily
20 people were recruited to be blind date participants
One-sided Blind Date
Other people were very still
but participant 8 had lots of gestures
and looked active, so I chose him
- Hello
Uh because I’m Korean-American
I can speak Korean a little,
- would it be okay for me to mix English with Korean as I speak?
- Yes, it's okay
Thank you
Female
Answer the given question
Male
Chooses the option they want
Inclination
Tend to laugh even when things aren’t funny
Yes vs No
It is true that I tend to laugh easily
When something’s really not funny, it’s hard to laugh
So at which level do you still laugh at?
I already have a broad sense of humor to begin with,
- Ah because you have a broad sense of humor?
- Yeah so
I am basically laughing at most things
Ah so you make sure to laugh at things
- Yes, yes
- so that it doesn’t get awkward for the other person
That’s a relief
I say a lot of jokes that aren’t funny
so when the other person laughs a lot,
it makes the atmosphere much more comfortable
When really wanting to rest but partner calls over
You go vs You say you want to rest
I...
I would go
Sometimes you would want at least a day off...
but do you still go?
I would usually go
Even if I want to rest, I think it’s possible to rest together
But if my partner wants to rest
Then I wouldn’t insist on calling them over
I’m saying I would go if the decision was on my part
What about you?
- Me?
- Yes
I used to...
I used to go over every time they called me over
but now I tend to rest when I need, as long as it isn’t something urgent or an emergency
If it’s explained...
I wouldn’t not show up without an explanation
- Cause that's bad
- Yeah, if it’s explained, then it would be okay
So I explain
say "I can’t make it"...
Like, it’s important to explain well
When a professor makes an inappropriate comment in class,
You stand up against it vs Let it slide
- This is a fun question
When a professor makes an inappropriate comment in class,
You stand up against it vs Let it slide
- I really wanted it to be one of the questions
I would stand up against it
Nice!
Do you really stand up? Has it ever happened to you?
Yes
In high school I had a similar experience...
You can’t stand injustice?
- Yeah something like that
- Justice... oh you do?
Because I’m like that
I’m also the same
Even recently, I kept getting in so many arguments and fights with my professors
so I received a lot of criticism and a bad reputation...
Right, right
People make excuses and,
and say because he’s from abroad, he doesn’t know
- You are Korean, right?
- Yes
but the fact that you can relate,
proves that um...
yeah it’s the same
I’m the type to really not let these things slide
Really ah... I can never let them slide.
- I also can’t let them slide, but
- Yes
But I think I can’t criticize people who let things do slide either
- Right
- Because I think that they have their reasons
But if it were up to me, I think it’s good to speak up
You are surprisingly a pretty strong person, huh?
- Am I?
- You don’t look like it but
- Ah I don't... I don't look like that?
- Your personality seems strong
- But you don’t look like it
- Ah, that’s a relief
It’s cool. You are really cool
Mid-inspection
Already?
He seems like a really delightful person and
umm...
his personality is how I expected it to be
Lively and active...
Seems like a funny person
She really can’t hear, right
Can you hear?
Okay
Uh...
She seemed like she would be really nice and soft-hearted
but when she said she stands up for injustice, she seemed really cool
and her self-values are set clearly, so
I see her differently from my first impressions of her
She seems really cool
Values
- Values...
Companies need military-styled discipline to a certain degree
Yes vs No
I think there is no need
Nice
In Korea,
the culture has practiced it for a long time, right?
So as a Korean, you still don’t think there is no need for it?
It’s not true that all Koreans believe there is need for military-styled discipline in companies, right?
- Right
- So I don’t think there is a need for it either
Instead of calling each other by ranks and titles
I think we need to say each others’ names
I think humans need to be treated like humans instead of their ranks
This might be a risky thing to say in today’s society
but for Korea...
The next step?
For Korea to move onto its next step would be by getting rid of the military-styled discipline everywhere
It would be a really quick step to move onto to the next level, I feel like
I’m not saying that other countries are better
but one thing in Korea that’s preventing it is this. Really
Mmm..
I think Korea is a country that had to develop a system of order of rank
- Because we have honorific
- Because of language
Yeah, I think the language differences are huge
For a culture, something that reflects it like a mirror is the language
and we can’t change our language now
But just by easing the order of rank system
A step up...
To advance?
By any chance, did you ever live abroad?
A little...
A little? It seems like it
I normally don’t even like having these conversations
because people have this [conservative] nuance
But because you are saying things I agree with
so... it’s really liberating
It’s very, uh, it’s really.. Yeah
If your partner covers most of the date expenses
It’s okay vs it’s not okay
It’s not okay for me
So you like paying for all the dates?
Ah...
It’s not that I like the act of paying for all the expenses
but I always end up wanting to pay for everything every time
I always wanna be the one to pay
It’s partially a expression for my feelings
- For her?
- and...
Yeah, for her
and partially manners, in my perspective
And also...
Manners...
when there is a feeling of taking care of someone, I think more feelings can form from that as well
Women might not like this expression, but...
It's just...
But the picture looks prettier this way?
And I personally like this picture.
It seems more secure
The picture looking prettier...
I pay prettily though...
- You pay prettily?
- Yeah I pay prettily and often...
Where do you think that “pretty picture” came from?
This is...
This is hard to pinpoint
I think...
But the influence is from movies like the Godfather?
I watched it a lot
In this movie,
The lead male
The lead male always has the image to be protecting over not only women, but his siblings as well
Not saying that this is the correct image
but I think I was heavily influenced by it
Ah, is this what real masculinity is?
- This is how the “picture” formed
- Mmm...
- ...Yes
- You seem to disagree
say what’s on your mind
If you have something to say
"Uhh, umm..."[Imitating her]
In that case, that person
that person just has the financial means
but it doesn’t represent... like manly?
Like it doesn’t represent manliness
But I could see why you would’ve seen that and felt the way you do
Even when little girls watch Disney and Cinderella
- They follow that kind of femininity
- "I wanna be like her"
- That definition of femininity stays with them
- Yes
Because things like that exist, so I understand
But to say you pay because it makes a “pretty picture,”
it would be upsetting to hear
I would want an acknowledgement of my competence
and wouldn’t always want to be protected
Being protected is nice, it’s nice but...
But I think it’s the same for men as well
Was I being way too old-school?
Not that old-school, but...
Old fashioned...?
Not to that extent...
In a relationship, fights are necessary
Yes vs no
I think it’s necessary
- It light keeps going off...
- I know right
Why do you think it’s not necessary?
There are people who fight and last long
but I personally am the type to not make any reasons to fight and just be considerate
so when fights happen,
my feelings drift away, in spite of myself
- Right
- Little by little
I can’t argue too much
The reason I think fights are necessary is
because you can see how your partner treats you in that moment
So when your boyfriend makes a mistake or something like that
do you often react to it emotionally?
You have to answer honestly
Just be honest
For me...
My emotions are way too obvious, from my facial expressions
so when I’m angry, I seem angry
You just seemed like you were
When you said "I’m angry", your facial expression was like
Your facail expression showed it
Because I look angry when I’m angry
I don’t think I can hide it, so..
You don’t get angry?
Get angry... uh...
It’s been a while since I was last angry. Like three years ago?
If I’m at a point of anger,
I have lost all my feelings already
- Mmm... I know it
- And...
And probably tired at that point, yeah
But I still think all of that is a process of love because,
Love is...
Yeah, right
Love is done emotionally rather than rationally
- and it’s not something we follow our brain for
- Right
For me, I know that when I get angry that person’s mood might be ruined but...
Because it is an emotional relationship
and not a business relationship...
Final Decision
- Mmm...
Interest in dating
Send an O X accordingly
Did you send it?
How was it today?
Uh... It's like...
Because you are Korean
I was wondering if I needed to be more reserved
and I also needed some time to use English and relax, but because you were so considerate and went along with everything
I was thankful and it was nice
and really fun time
A really good experience for me
You spoke so humorously,
so it was helpful for me as well
I’m usually funnier than this
but because I was nervous so I
- Me too
- Refrained from a lot of things
You know what I’m saying
The light will turn off on the side that sent an X