Where do u think I live?
Mmm... *thinking*
It takes about an hour by airplane.
By any chance, do you live in _______?
Yeah.
Wow.
What do you think about that?
I don't think I can make a comment about that.
You can’t?
Hello.
Well, this is awkward.
What is your name?
My name is Jung Haejin.
Jung Haejin?
I am 28 years old
and my name is Choi Cheolwon.
Cheolwon?
Yes, Cheolwon.
I think...
I think we need to take a shot to loosen up a bit.
Do you happen to have a symptom?
No, I just have a bit of a hand tremor.
I’ll go first.
JUDGING FROM THE FIRST IMPRESSION CHEOLWON’S JOB IS EITHER A HAIR DESIGNER OR AN ADVERTISEMENT PRODUCER
I think you're an advertisement producer.
Yes. Correct.
Oh…
Your reaction is so...
seems like you weren’t even curious.
No, no. You just kind of looked like it.
Really?
What is your age?
I am 23 years old.
Oh, 23 years old?
Yes.
And are you a student right now?
No, I am not a student.
I'm an airline staff.
Airline staff?
what kind of work do you do?
So I don't work on flights, but everything else in the airport.
Oh, you work at the airport?
Then Gimpo Airport?
Wrong!
Do I have to take a shot now?
Let's drink together
okay.
You are shaking again.
BETWEEN BODY VS FACE, WHEN CHEOLWON FIRST LOOKS AT A WOMEN, HE LOOKS AT ________.
Body.
Wrong. The answer is face
Oh, you're shaking less.
Because the bottle is leaning on the shot glass.
I think when I look at someone's face,
I look at their eyes a lot.
Oh...
I like people with pretty eyes.
Me too.
I think the sparkles in someone's eyes are important.
How about mine?
Your eyes?
They look very kind.
Kind and good-hearted.
Thank you.
Let’s have another drink.
I need to get more comfortable.
Oh, what’s your limit?
I'm okay to drink.
I think your alcohol tolerance is higher than mine.
I think so too.
HAEJIN CAN OR CANNOT SHOW HER BARE FACE TO HER BOYFRIEND?
Cannot.
Wrong.
Oh, you can show your bare face?
Before I couldn't.
This story needs more explanation...
but I kept thinking ‘what if he gets disappointed in me.’
So I thought I needed to show my pretty face all the time
and we couldn't go out on dates for a long time.
But now when I think about it,
I am more comfortable now
and I want to spend more time with them.
And you want to meet a boyfriend who adores your bare face?
Yes. Exactly.
You don't like bare faces?
No, no.
I like that kind of relationship too.
Who cares if I see my girlfriend’s bare face?
In my experience, even though I like that person, if we're not totally comfortable with each other,
we become more distant in the end.
I enjoy having a date at home and watching movies.
Dating at home?
Do you live alone?
Yes, I am currently living alone.
So I like dates at home,
and walk around the neighborhood in our flip flops,
go to the movies...
Just those kind of casual dates.
I see.
Do you not use casual speech?
Me?
Casual speech is more comfortable than formal speech.
Do you like speaking casually?
Yes.
Should we talk casually?
Yeah.
HAEJIN'S MOST CONFIDENT BODY PART IS _______.
Wait I gotta think about it…
Eyes?
My eyes?
Yes.
Wrong.
Take a shot.
Why did you say eyes?
Oh, because your eyes are pretty.
Oh, thanks.
Don't you hear that a lot?
That your eyes are pretty?
My mom has a nice nose,
so a lot of people say I got her nose
and say this part is high and pretty.
Oh so your nose prettiest.
Right here.
I shook it to show that its natural.
Yeah, your nose is pretty.
Thank you.
You look like this celebrity.
Who? Who?
Do you know rapper ‘One’?
Oh, oh I see.
You look like One.
I've heard that a lot.
But slightly more masculine version of 'One'.
Oh, slightly more?
Want to drink?
Wow, you're not shaking anymore.
Oh, I am way more comfortable now.
Now that I've had a few,
I'm okay.
What is your alcohol tolerance?
My tolerance?
About 2.5 bottles of soju?
I like to drink.
Oh you do?
Yes, I like to drink and talk.
I think you need to drink to get to know a person.
Oh. Right...
You can have sincere conversation.
You get comfortable and show more of yourself.
So I always drink once or twice when I meet someone.
Once or twice?
Like when dating?
Yes, with someone I'm interested in.
Do you want to take a shot?
I think we need to drink more.
WHEN CHEOLWON MISSES HIS GIRLFRIEND, HE GOES TO SEE HER NO MATTER WHAT OR HE RESTRAINS.
You go no matter what.
Correct.
You have to see her?
What I mean is that when you're in a relationship of course you miss each other
But when I'm having a difficult time and miss her,
I'd be grateful to have her meet me.
What would you do if you have a girlfriend and she's abroad?
She's abroad after we're dating?
From the start.
From the time you met her, she's abroad.
I don't think I can be in a relationship with her.
You can't?
I don't like long distance relationships.
You don't?
I've given myself a limit of 40 minutes distance away.
40 minutes?
Then that means you have to be live within the same province, no matter what.
Yes
because when I miss her, I can go see her.
Right.
You're just agreeing so casually.
*laughs*
Where do you think I live?
Seoul is very big, you know?
I am pretty good at guessing these stuff.
I don’t think you live in Seoul.
Incheon!
Incheon?
You work at an airport,
so I'm thinking like Incheon or Gimpo.
But there are so many airports.
guess where.
Incheon airport, Gimpo airport..
Are you from Busan by any chance?
Yeah.
(Seoul to Busan is about 5 hours car ride)
Wow...
I feel like I’ve just been pranked.
Wow for reals?
What do you think?
I couldn’t even sleep to come up and do this.
I don't think I can even comment about this.
You can’t?
Oh Busan. I see.
Your intensions dropped when you heard Busan huh?
No, it's not that.
Lots of people from the suburbs actually live in Seoul.
I would’ve thought same too if I were you.
It didn't even see that coming.
For reals, I couldn’t even imagined that you were from Busan.
Oh really?
Yeah, I didn’t know.
WHAT IS HAEJIN’S IDEAL WORK TO RELATIONSHIP RATIO?
There's no hint?
No, there isn’t. Guess the answer, right now.
10 to 0?
Here...
What is 10?
Relationship.
I am 5 to 5.
5 to 5?
It's case by case depending on the job and the person.
There's a time when a job is more important and when a person is more important.
So I cannot divide something completely.
For instance, you got promoted for a job in a different location,
but you have to leave your boyfriend who is in Seoul,
would you go?
Oh.
I would stay in Seoul.
because I must be somewhat qualified to be promoted,
so I can probably find a great opportunity in Seoul too.
Even when you are in Seoul?
Yes, because I know that once I break up with my boyfriend,
I won't be able to meet him again.
Fact is person first?
If you said 6 to 4 ratio, you wouldn't had to drink.
HAEJIN CAN OR CANNOT MARRY BEFORE AGE 25.
Cannot.
Drink. Hurry up and drink.
I got it all wrong.
I am getting drunk now.
If I like someone, I can.
I always tell my mom that I want to get married early.
What's the reason?
I want stability and security with my family.
There are times when I am mentally insecure,
but getting married and having a family of my own,
I can depend on my husband.
I couldn’t agree with you more.
Me too.
Right now I've been living alone for about 4 years.
And I work overtime a lot
and when I come home, no one is waiting for me at home.
I'm thinking what am I working for?
Kind of like empty feeling
So can you give your earnings to you wife?
Well, if we live together, it's all the same.
You were stuttering just now
Oh you caught me.
Your point is off when it comes to money.
No, we live together so…
I think we drank the most.
I know right?
Can you pour me a shot?
I'm worried I'm too sober.
It’s the last one.
Last question.
COMPARED TO THE FIRST MOMENT HAEJIN HAS SAME OR DIFFERENT FEELINGS TOWARD CHEOLWON.
I think different.
Do I have to drink?
I am nervous now.
For your sake, I'll say different.
At first, I was so nervous,
I didn't have any thoughts.
I didn't even register your face, your eyes, nothing.
After some conversation,
I realized we just need to talk more.
We are from different areas too and after we talk about a lot of different things,
maybe our opinions will overlap.
Can I ask you too?
Yeah sure.
How do you feel about me?
Whoa, what is this? Out of nowhere.
Because you could have met someone else, but you met me.
The thing I'm worried about is...
I didn't consider about long distance relationship at all.
Right, I would’ve thought the same.
But we were able to have a nice conversation like talking and asking questions.
So gradually...
Oh really?
Is there anything you want to ask me as a last question?
Something I'm curious about?
Have you ever had a long distance relationship?
No.
They were all in Busan?
Yes.
So what do you think about meeting someone from far away?
I don't really care.
If I miss my boyfriend, I think I will go to see him.
Even if I can only see him for 30 minutes I will go.
I can try hard to not make him sad about not being able to meet me.
When is your train back to Busan?
Oh~ It's at 9pm.
Are you down?
Yes, I am down..