YUMI HAS DONE AS FAR AS _______ FOR HER BOYFRIEND.
Cosplay
Am I wrong?
Hello
My name is Kang Seong Goo
I am Yumi.
Have you done any day time drinking before?
No, it's my first time.
Still, alcohol will help us get to know each other.
Where are you from?
I'm from Cheon-an
ah~
I'm from Cheong-ju
Ah, we live close to each other.
If you say Cheon-an
Yawoori…
You’re right.
Dujeong-dong
Do you want another shot?
Yes, please
Do I just draw a card?
FROM THE FIRST IMPRESSION, ________ COUNTRY MATCHES YUMI’S IMAGE.
Vietnam
Wow…
No
because my friends told me women from Vietnam are very pretty.
I've never heard that before
Really? It’s not easy…
We are not clicking
SEONG GOO GLANCES AT _____ PART OF THE BODY FIRST WHEN HE SEES A GIRL
Her leg
Her leg?
It's kinda similar.
I'll give you one more chance.
Ankles on her leg?
You're correct. Her ankles.
Ankles? That sounds perverted.
Why the ankles?
Right when you see a girl, you look straight at the ankles?
No, not in a perverted way.
I really like women who wear jeans
and you can always see their ankles when they wear jeans.
I know you might not understand...
No, I cannot understand.
But there might be people here who are like that..
What do you look for in a man when you’re interested?
His vibe.
His vibe? Let’s be honest.
No really, I don’t only look at his face or his body, but…
So vibe as in everything combined?
Yes yes.
But I do prefer masculine vibe in a guy.
YUMI IS SELF-CONSCIOUS ABOUT _______ PART OF HER BODY.
This question is very...
I know it’s really awkward to answer…
I think it’s…
I am thinking of one.
But I don’t know if I should say this.
Don't say it.
I agree. I don’t think I should say it.
Never mind, please just say it. I'm curious
Maybe it's this.....
My head?!
No, no.
I thought you were referring to my brain.
Your heart area?
Wait, what?
I definitely need to take a shot on this.
Your answer triggers a woman’s self-esteem.
so that wasn't the answer?
It’s not about getting it right or wrong.
How’s my image?
I seem to have all the bad answers.
What's your answer?
Me?
I have a lot of facial hair
so a few months ago,
I got laser hair removal.
Why are you laughing?
I don’t think it’s working for you.
It’s not..?
What do you think of guys with facial hair?
I don’t prefer…
Do you like the clean-shaven look?
Yes I do.
YUMI HAS DONE AS FAR AS _______ FOR HER BOYFRIEND.
I wasn’t expecting any of these questions.
oh, really?
Special events?
Cosplay!
What the heck? I don’t do cosplays
Not something perverted.
Like a doll mask,
I was talking about that kind of events.
Like Pikachu?
Yes, like...
nevermind…
I feel like I got punched in the face for this question.
What's the answer?
Diet.
I lost 10kg.
Really? Wow.
The answer is lamer than cosplay huh?
I would have never thought of that answer.
It’s so hot in here.
Why cosplay, I'm shocked...
YUMI’S LOOKALIKE CELEBRITY IS__________.
I think I can get this right.
When I first saw you,
I thought Son Yeon Jae
Ohhhhh~ Son Yeon Jae
Was that a good answer?
Not bad at all.
Who have you heard for your lookalike?
You can't guess one?
Nothing is ringing my bell…
I don’t think I can tell you before you get the answer right…
Well, I’ve heard from TVXQ
Who?
U-KNOW YUNHO?
No you don’t look like him.
Oops sorry, but you don’t really look like him…
No, I am the one who is sorry.
Please edit this part.
This one is pretty hard.
SEONG GOO WOULD SAVE ______ FIRST IF HIS MOM AND GIRLFRIEND ARE BOTH DROWNING
I think you will save your mom
But
I will save both.
Yeah right?
You really had to put it like that?
Can you swim?
Out of nowhere?
What if I said I can’t.
If you can't,
I can save you.
I was a lifeguard. I’ve been swimming for quite long.
That's why I said, I'd save both.
Your answer is very impressive.
Earlier, you were like "yeah right, how can you?"
Now that I heard that reason,
Can you trust me now?
Yes, I can believe you.
Shall we move on?
MISSION – TALK WITHOUT HONORIFICS
I'm going to talk casually.
Alright
I am going to start now.
OK
Let’s talk casually~
YUMI CAN GO AS FAR AS _____ IN TERMS OF PHYSICAL TOUCH ON THE FIRST DATE
I feel like this question is put because you can go far.
Don't think too much into it.
Just me.
You want me to answer from just from looking at you?
Friendly touch.
Friendly touch?
Like lightly hitting on the arm.
Am I wrong?
Friendly touch…
It just depends on the vibe.
I don’t have any limits.
How about you? How far can you go?
I'm very cautious of physical affection.
So unless I’m certain about my feelings, I don’t...
Oh you don’t?
Yeah I restrain myself.
That's a good thing.
I never go too far to regret it.
SEONG GOO WILL TRAVEL A LONG WAY JUST TO SEE HIS GIRLFRIEND’S FACE FOR 10 MINUTES OR NOT
I think you can.
Why do you think I can?
I just think you'd be very good to your girlfriend.
Devoted.
When you are in a relationship, you miss that person…
Let’s say, if you're in Cheong-ju and I'm in Jejudo,
would you come to see me?
If I go, will I be able to spend time with you?
Of course
Then I think I would go.
Even though it's really difficult?
But as soon as I see her, I can relieve my stress.
YUMI CAN OR CANNOT WAIT FOR HER BOYFRIEND’S STUDY ABROAD
I think you can.
You think I can?
But it really depends on the situation
If you were in a good strong relationship with someone,
I think you can wait for him unconditionally.
That’s just my personal thinking of you.
I've never waited,
but I've had someone wait for me.
So I don’t think I can
because I know how hard it is.
Personally, I want to study more,
maybe in Korea or abroad.
And if I get the opportunity to study abroad
and I am in a relationship with someone,
I would like to go together.
Together?
That's easier said than done.
So you would take your girlfriend all the way..?
Yes, but I'll plan and prepare everything ahead.
You want it all huh?
If I were to ask you,
would you be able to go?
I think I could
if the guy was certain and there's a future together.
If everything is prepared and planned, I'd go.
It's the last question.
It is.
YUMI  FEELS THE SAME OR DIFFERENTLY ABOUT SEONG GOO NOW COMPARED TO THE FIRST MOMENT
How do you feel Oppa?
Whoa… ‘How do you feel oppa…’
Is it same or different?
It's different.
Me too.
Honestly,
in the beginning I wasn't impressed...
No, be honest.
I wasn’t impressed
but as we had more conversation we had a good vibe.
I liked it.
Do you think you're going to regret coming here today?
To be honest, I didn't have any serious expectations.
But I felt something I never even imagined.
Like a new feeling?
What kind of feeling?
And that feeling
will be a secret…
I would like to get to know you more.
The time was so limited.
Don’t you think?
What’s with the fingers
Alrighty then
Ok. Alrighty then