COUPLEMATE (SAE HEE)
High school student
A person who has never been in a romantic relationship
COUPLEMATE (HO JOON)
Boys Middle school, Boys High school student
*awkward*
Nice to meet you
What is your name?
I'm Hwang In Young
Be easygoing and mature,
But cute and funny
I'm Ji Hoon Park
He speaks in a dialect,
He has a warm heart
What did you come for?
How teens and 20s are different
To see what's different from 20s relationship(date)
React about when 20s see teenagers date
Do you want to use honorifics?
No
Okay
Today's quest
Guess who will ask the phone number first
Loser will be penalized
Ho Joon
Ho Joon? Why?
I think boy will ask first...
That is old story... Everyone can ask first
So I choose See Her
At a glance
Couplemate first meet
Ho Joon waiting for Couplemate at the cafe
As time goes by, I get more nervous.
SAE HEE Greet first
What school do you go to?
Gyung Gi Video Science High School
Do you know this school?
They don't ask name each other, even they are meet first time
So cute
Is it coed?
My school is coeducational.
We are boys high school.
Really?
My feelings hurt.
Can't hide my heart
What is your name?
Oops! right!
They talking about school during 10minutes even don't know each other's name
I'm Sae Hee
What is your name?
I'm Ho Joon
Nice to meet you
How old are you?
I'm Senior (last grade of Korea High school)
Senior??
You are Nuna! (older than me)
How old are you?
Sophomore (1st grade in Korea High school)
What? really?
Sae Hee is older than Ho Joon
Oh no, Sae her will ask phone number I guess
I think so too
Nuna...!
I thought we are same age...!
I born in 2001... so our age difference is only 1 year
I'm still older than you wow...
Younger boyfriend is hot topic now
Why? since when?
You don't see the drama "Pretty Oppa bought meal"(wrong)
Oh no not oppa, Nana
hahaha Nuna is correct
Have you ever been on a blind date?
Not blind date... Introduce a friend's friend something like that
We call it like that too
How about you?
No...
I did, because my school weren't coed.
I don't like blind dates.
Me either
Awkward
Right... uncomfortable with agent too
Get more exciting
How many times have you been couple?
None...
A person who has never been in a romantic relationship
May I ask you...?
What? me? (Yes you...)
Let's not ask each other.
It's hurt my mind
Sae Hee has no boyfriend before
Then, I'm possible to win because she might hard to ask phone number
because too shy
Add sugar to them
That is so pretty
cloud smoothie
Cloude smoothie is very sweet like teenager
Couple quest is arrive
Open it?
Open quest letter carefully
write Buttket list for date (If I'm teenager couple)
Buttket list for date?
sigh*
I miss those days
Do you have anything in mind?
No...
Me either
It's not easy.
This can't be happen
I wanted to come home from school with in school uniform.
This can't be happen right?
I need another one.
If I write that, I'll ask girlfriend to wait in front of school
And also I'll wait for her at front of her school
I went boy middle school, high school like Ho Joon
I don't know who's in front of the school, but there's a girl waiting!
then, Everyone panic
If boy friend hold her hand, then boys are shouting!
20s happy with their imagination
Han river?
I like Han river too
Finally their hope were in agreement
I can't go on the rides, but I like the amusement park mood
The night mood
Tell
or not?
The couple ring
My classmates do a lot.
And couple shoes!
Friends do a lot too
What is your ideal type?
A man who turtleneck suits him very well.
turtleneck... then he should have... small head
ummm... I don't care about head size...
just good at turtleneck clothing
Maybe it's because of a celebrity.
Yes, turtleneck is not pretty, celebrities are pretty
And the boy is not always wearing turtleneck how she know about it
You are realistic
How about you
My ideal type is short hair
Short hair?
I'm sorry
laugh or crying?
But that is just ideal type, It's not I hate other hair style
He leave a choice for Sae Hee
If you like blind date partner
Then say ideal type close to blind date partner
change more like partner style
Cute girl?
Kind and thoughtful girl
Kind and thoughtful girl with short hair?
celebrity ideal type?
Red velvet Irene
Irene...?
Irene face and...
I like Boyoung Park too
His ideas are too extreme.
No one!
Same thing with girl, If go to college, we believe only good-looking guys everywhere
Teenager see appearance a lot
20s less care about that
right
20s think about 'are we fit mind together' more than appearance
Have the satisfaction of one's appearance
however If they are not fit about life values and personality, then they fight and part
Secon quest avrrived
Take selfie together
Take selfie together?
What am I supposed to do?
take photo with...
this (selfie app)
Close in with.
I'm not usually take photo so... awkward
I'm not good at taking selfie... sorry
Cute
They shy to do this
What will be the end of the first date?
oh?! wait!
What is your phone number?
Sae Hee said it!
I knew it...!
They take selfie with Sae he's phone so, phone is already on the table
so naturally...
Sae hee ask about it
Penalty time!
Let's get along well with each other.
thank you
Can Se Hee and Ho Jun get closer?
When I saw her first time
Bright and
active
Very kind
When I know she is Nu na to me
I like that she is older than me
I want meet her more and want to learn about her
Because our age is different, I can learn from her
She is good person
First impression is
He is as mild
kind image
When I know he is younger than me,
embarrassed
I can't imagine he is 17...
I think 17 is young, so I surprised!