I don’t want you on social media
Where does that thought process even come from?
We gathered a group of 20 people to participate in a blind date
They each chose one person out of the line-up
Blindest Date
I’ll go with this one right here.
Uh I chose her because
From what I can tell from her looks
She seems like she’d be nice and friendly
Hello
- You’re even better looking in person
- Huh?
- You’re beautiful
- Thank you
Chooser: answers the given questions
Chosen: if the chooser’s answer is not the answer he’s looking for, the lights go off
[Tendencies]
Hm. Tendencies.
[When you consider a potential date material, Nice Face vs. Nice Body]
Uh, face. I think.
Okay
Mhm, this is going well
So you’re pretty content with your face.
LOL it’s not that
And I actually don’t care either way, but
Usually when you talk to someone you look at their eyes
Rather than their body, right?
So I was hoping the answer would be ‘face’
Since I had to choose?
Well we’re off to a great start, that’s for sure
Yeah
[If I had a fit body, I would show it off on Insta #fitspo]
I would
Mm okay
So you’re against showing off your body even if it’s..?
I just,
I don’t like showing off my body in general
and I wish the same for my boyfriend?
You said you’re not the type to show off,
but I like getting attention
So if I have a nice body then of course,
Because I worked out so I can show off
Yeah that’s true
What would you do if you start dating a guy,
and he turns out to be an attention whore?
I’d probably tease him, in the beginning
But if it gets to the point where it’s bothering me or stressing me out,
then I don’t think I could keep dating him
If it makes him happy, then I can’t do anything about that
Respecting boundaries in the relationship
Yep
[You see three teenagers smoking on the street. Pass them without saying anything vs. Intervene]
I would intervene
I guess you sit well with injustice and illegalities?
Injustice lol
Well I think
I feel like
Uh-huh
I don’t necessarily have to step in
How about you? Why would you intervene?
I mean it’s not to bring justice or anything but
I just think that
Doing something not fit for your age
Is rude to other people around you, especially in public
I wouldn’t be against stepping in and talking to them
But it could turn into an argument or a fight
And I don’t like violence
- I’m kind of a pacifist
- I don’t like violence either
Me neither
I don’t want to go out of my way to possibly provoke them into a fight
They would regret it on their own, sometime down the road
- Yeah
- Right
It’s their life
I guess I like to get in other people’s business
Naw, don’t say that
No I think I am pretty nosy like that
[Halfway Check-In]
Halfway check-in
Halfway check-in?
She’s friendly and thoughtful,
Like I imagined from seeing her profile video before meeting
But, our tendencies are almost completely opposite
I like to exert my energy and be social,
but she seems to be the type to keep to herself
So I don’t know, that’s been on my mind
He’s funny
And..
I think we share a lot of similar opinions
And even for the lights that turned off,
those questions weren’t like, ‘this is a complete turn off’
And I liked his reasoning behind his answers so
I think we’re getting along pretty well
[Values]
[Is social media a waste of time?]
Social media is a waste of time
No, I don’t think so
Ah, okay.
Why do you think it’s a waste of time?
Well I actually don’t think it’s a waste of time, personally
But I want my boyfriend to think it’s a waste and not be on social media
Where does that thought process even come from?
I’m on social media
- But
- Okay
Okay, let’s hear you out
I don’t want him to be on social media because,
I don’t think I want other people looking at my BF’s profile
Like guarding your cookie jar, sorta thing?
Yeah I mean,
A lot of people send messages
- Like sliding into the DM?
- Yeah
I’ve personally seen a lot of people send DMs
And that makes me wary
Okay now I understand where you’re coming from
The reason why I am pro-social media is that
I get most of my info and news from social media
and most communication on social media, so I think it’s necessary
[Love is the only prerequisite for marriage]
Yes, I can get married based just on love.
What are some other things you would need for marriage?
Even if I really love someone and want to be with him forever,
if I don’t have money saved up, I don’t think I can afford the marriage
I want to make a differentiation between ideals and reality
Okay, realistically.
I think we were on a similar thought process, but ended up with different conclusions
I’m not talking about unconditional or blind love,
but in order for you to get to feeling ‘love’ towards the other person, most people have check lists in their minds
and that check list might contain finances, personality, whatever.
and the fact that I love that person already means that person proved herself and checked off those boxes
so I think it would be fine to get married
If I were to get married when I’m not financially stable,
it might be fine for me and my partner, but what if we have a child?
I would ask myself, would the child be happy, too?
If a couple is in that situation,
I think it’s better to not get married and just live together
Or date longer, and then get married later.
I understand where you’re coming from
I think I can accept that
[I can give up my career and be a stay-at-home mom/dad]
I can’t
So you’d want me to be..
a stay-at-home dad?
Um.. yes.
I think we’re both thinking the same thing
- I think so, too
- Right?
I love my job and
I don’t want to lose my job just because I got married
I’d rather be the breadwinner and have my husband be the stay-at-home
It’s the same for me,
I don’t mean to be belittle full-time homemakers
But I’m not a homemaker right now,
and I want to achieve and get a sense of fulfillment from my current line of work,
so I don’t think I can be a full-time homemaker
- What if one person absolutely has to stay home,
- Yeah
and both don’t want to?
If I absolutely had to choose,
I think I would have to be the one working
What if the woman earns more than you? Even then?
Well that would be a different situation but
I think I would choose to work, even without considering the finances
Because I love my career
What if your wife loves her career just as much as you do?
Would you consider..?
Then I’d probably give up
I would probably still stand my ground
but if that conflict persists
it might be better if I yield
in the very end.
Ultimately?
Yeah, ultimately
it'd probably be like that
but that ultimately will be after a very very long time
Kinda like Lee Bong-ju style, you know the marathoner?
Like a marathon
Gotton run that marathon
[Final Decision]
You’re like the MC over here
Send O or X…
This is a little uncomfortable
No running away without saying a word after the shoot
How was it for you? I was really nervous because I’ve never done anything like this before
We talked about a lot of things that we wouldn’t in a normal blind date
I enjoyed talking about those topics, as well as listening to your views
Some parts we really vibed well, and some parts not so much,
but all in all, it was a good experience.