1,2,3
Hello
My name is Seo Dong-won
My name is Jeong Yu-rim
Yu-rim?
Yes, Yu-rim
Nice to meet you!
Shall we take a shot?
Sure
Cheers?
Nice to meet you!
Let’s draw the card.
‘Based only on the first impression, in what year did Yu-rim enter the University?’
Year 2014?
Nope
I’m wrong?
You should take a shot.
It’s year 2009.
Wow, you look so young
How old you are..?
28 years old
Oh is this..?
How old do I look?
Twenty-
Twenty-?
Five?
25?
I am pretty good right?
Yeah
You look really young.
Your skin looks so clean.
Even better than mine!
Not at all. Yours looks great.
It’s the make-up
Well your make-up doesn’t look that heavy
Slow-down cowboy.
Alcohol’s hitting me up today
Big time!
Why, what’s the question?
‘Which part does Yu-rim look at first when she sees a man?’
Maybe thighs?
Oh guess I should take a shot then
Please do
I look at guy’s hands a lot
Hands?
Yes, I like men with pretty hands
Mine are pretty
You say it so proudly!
Did the camera get it?
Actually my hands are huge
Aren’t they?
No, to be exact, mine was lower
Come on, if you’re being that technical
Yeah put it up there
Still it’s big
Don’t be ridiculous!
Why am I getting all the difficult ones?
‘What do you do when your girlfriend’s mad at you?’
Maybe you throw special events for her?
Wrong!
Isn’t it normal to do special events?
Is it?
I act cute for her
(Can you show us how?)
Like a role play?
A role play?
Let’s say you’re mad because I was late
How could you be late?
You know I waited
Can you look at my face?
I’m so sorry
I love you!
‘When Yu-rim likes a guy, she does a certain gesture what is it?’
I think you’ll smile a lot in front of that person
I usually look into his eyes a lot
Eye contact?
Yes
ah~
You know we made eye contact with each other
Sure we did
‘Dong-won prefers to date someone younger, same age, or older?’
Someone older?
Wow, you’re psychic!
Psychic?!
Then how about you
Take a guess
I’d wish you’d go for boys younger than you
Normally I prefer someone as my age or older
It’s a pressure for me to date younger guys
because I feel like I have to take care of the
but it can depend on the person
It’s not like a strict rule and if the person is nice, it wouldn’t matter
Well I am a nice person you know.
I wonder what it is.
‘Can Dong-won say “I love you” to his GF in front of his friends or not?’
I think you can!
Yes I can
I knew it.
Is it hard to say I love you?
I can’t do it.
Really?
In front of your friends?
Do you feel embarrassed?
It’s a cringy thing to do.
The thing is
if I don’t express
my feelings to my girlfriend she might see me as careless
And with my friends
I want them to know my GF is the best
I like your way of thinking
To let them know that she’s my top priority?
I want to be good to her
more than to my friends
I want to tell her my feelings often
Oh~~
interesting question.
Does Yu-rim prefer easy relationships like friends or a passionate romance?
The easy one?
I don’t want to be too comfortable.
I want to be special
and precious to that person
I’d like to be reminded that I’m being loved
You like being comfortable huh?
Do you fart or burp in front of your girlfriend?
I want her to do it right away, comfortably
My parents still don’t fart in front of each other
That was the environment I grew up in
Manners should be kept between loved ones.
I know how to keep them.
I have manners
By accident is fine
What about burping and going like, “Wanna smell it?”
No I hate that
I’m not like that!
Have you ever met a guy through social media? Yes or no?
I think it’s hard not to for you
What do you mean hard not to?
You’re very pretty so..
Are you on Instagram?
Yes
If you’re on it, that’s-
100% chance?
(sigh) I get it
Yes, I have
I see
Have you?
I think you have
I haven’t
Really?
To meet people via social media,
I thought it’d be too casual
If that person DM'd me,
she might have DM'd another guy
I’m a bit uncomfortable about that
I was slightly against it
But...
if that person is really sincere
I could maybe give it a try
Oh this one is the last question
Seo Dong-won feels the same now as when he saw Yu-rim the first time? Or not?
The same
Yes, you’re right
Why is that?
My first impression of you was good because of your bright smile
Because of your smile
I had a feeling that you’re a nice person,
so yes your smile left me a good impression
Then....
Do you happen to have....
plan after this..?
…after this?
Plans?
Umm..
Let me get your number first.
I should have said that first
Ah I was so stupid!
I know! You should know better
What an idiot!
I had a great time today
I did too
After the wrap-up, we’ll see
‘When dong-won likes a girl,
He’ll smile and laugh a lot.”
I usually rub my neck or touch my ears
No wonder your hands were so still
Me?
Really?
We’ll have to see the video later to find that out.