Se-Hui &amp; Ho-Joon
High school student
Se-Hui who has never been in a romantic relationship
Ho-Joon went boy's middle school and boy's high school (school that only have boys)
Couplay start!
Today's Quest
Guess who will tell "Should we talk more comfortably? (not use honorifics)" first?
Loser will purnished...
This time I'm going to choose Ho-Joon
Like, "Nuna I'm gonna not use honorifics anymore"
Se-Hui
Because last time her character was very active
Oh right She asked Ho-June's phone number first
@Hong Dae station
Se-Hui waiting Ho joon
Hi
What should I tell about first?
a word of courage
It's too hot weather isn't it?
Couplemate staring at the bus stop not eachother
Couplemate Quest arrived
First Quest.
Wear Couple look (clothing) that your wanna be style
Oh couple look
They even use Honorific
What can I do?
I think it said "Go to clothing store"
What is your favorite fashion style?
I like t-shirts
and blouse
I wear everything! anything
I like it all
I'm never picky about clothing
Where should we go?
Let's go
What is Ho-Joon's favorite style?
Lakickz
Have you ever been here?
Yes
There are so many pretty clothes here.
yay!
Hello!
(very polite two of couplemate)
Lakickz
Couplemate's pick style is street fashion
Do you think it will go well? because they looks so Mild
I curious about you in normal clothing not school uniform
I curious about that too (both of them)
I think they will so excited
That way it's thier first time seeing eachother without school uniform
They select first couple look first time in life
Umm... there are so much clothing in here
Pick what you want and pick what I want, and selsect together
select and select together right?
Okay I like it
Nuna (Se-hui) This looks like a good fit to Nuna
Ho-Joon choose clothing that suits her very well
And I want wear this!
Which one is good?
Ah? I was going to buy it before.
Bravado?
Bravado~~~ (Ji-Hoon use Dialect)
Isn't it Bravado? (Dialect)
In-Young : I love his Dialect
Have you decided now?
I select yours too
I thought this would look good on you.
They've chosen a different style.
Ho-Joon pick black T-shirts
Se-Hui pick colorful one
Let's try this on
You go first
Okay
I'm so excited to wait like that
Ho-Joon with a bright smile
Ta-ra~
Is it small?
Nah.. It fit well!
Next! Noona!
waiting for the same-clothed couplemate
Se-Hui with a shy smile
You look so pretty.
They looked awkward and strange in lovely way
Second t-shirt choose by Se-Hui
Rose T-shirts
They try on both
Ho-Joon was embarrassed by Se-hui's praise.
They thinking about what to buy.
Seriously thinking about it
I think it's better to buy same one
They are making little concessions.
Choose this one how about it?
Okay I like it
You looks good
I think we're getting along well.
It's not easy even with 20s
could be stubborn.
Right, for example I choose it, but mate could hate it... or bad feeling about my decision
what was the Ho-joon's story that hard to tell Se-Hui first?
Well, Don't use Honorific
Was it uncomfortable?
Okay...
What? I lose again!
Right? Ho-Joon said it first!
He was careful about say something
Let's don't use honorific
Yes, don't use it
I Go OH
They became more closer
Couplemate quest arrived
Second Quest.
Take a photo at the Photo grey booth
with couple look
Oh~ may be that "Life 4 shot"?
ah~~~~~ I got it
Wear this and go to the booth!
Taking photo?
That photo booth is very small
I think they will too nervous about that
Because they in small area together
so excited about being close.
We got the Quest about 4cut cartoon
4cut cartoon?
Ah~~~ 4cut photo!!
What do you what with the pose?
I know, it's hard because it's too sudden Quest
I can't think anything
alright, First concept is cute!
c..Chic...
what? courage?
No Chic!!!
Okay chic
Third, pose that you and I want!
last one is pose like flower!
Let's go
It's too hot in here
How to take this photo?
What was the poses?
Cute, Chic, free, flower
Wh..what is this? so many menu
they look comfortable but actually not... I guess
Heart beating!!!
My heart is itchy!!!
(Panic) Wait.. we...cute...
Ah ohhhhhh what can I dooooo!!!
O..Okay... so...
Ready for this...
Look at this?
this one? that camera?
Shall we?
3,2,1
Cute
What the... I'm incane this(?)
What's next?
What is like Chic?
What is Chic pose?
This is CHIC!
Woaooooooooooooooooooo!!!
I'm crazyyy
three two one
(mental explode) What was last one?
(calm down) Flower!
Done!
Look!
I like this!
Right you look like model in here
You are good in here too
Getting closer and get more moments
Punish time
You are mean!!!
I'm going to hit little stronger and last time
After hit I might flip over couch...
(close eyes strongly)
why you scaring me just hit me!
Okay
(very weak hit... PD hate it...)
Next time you should win
when we wear couplet-shirts
It was first time that I wear same cloting with someone
So I think we getting closer I think
and more friendly
When She wear same clothing with me
she was pretty!
Our couple t-shirts is fit well to her
We also love fashion
So I think because of her, clothing is more shine and awesome