PARK JIN-HO IS ABLE TO PICK UP A GIRL THAT HE JUST MET
You can.
Why why why?
I know now,
What?
You are a player
I am 100% sure.
How do you do
Hello
My name is Park Jin-ho
I’m Jeong Hyun-jin
You have a pretty name
Would you like some first
No let me
I don’t usually drink during the day
Nice to meet you
What do you do, Hyun-jin?
I’m freshmen in college
Oh right, you’re 21
Yes
College student
Yeah
I’m 25
I’ve done my military service
I’m a manager of a bar
And I run the place too.
Then I’ll pick one
PARK JIN-HO’s ideal type woman is ________.
Judging from your bright and outgoing personality
I think you would prefer humorous and funny type of girls.
You are on the right path.
Was I?
Among Cute, Sexy, Sweet categories
I prefer sweet and innocent type.
Ahh sweet and innocent.
Short haired, long haired doesn’t matter
If it fits the person.
You have quite lovely hair yourself.
I am flattered.
How about you Hyun-jin, what is your ideal type?
I prefer monolids.
Monolids?
Mine totally.
They are perfect monolids.
And when a guys has a cute smile, that turns me on.
Let me draw a card out
By the way
sorry to bother you,
but I think it’s because I’m using honorific that I can’t talk freely
Then you can talk down to me
Great, why don’t you do so too
No, I’m very shy
Maybe not talking down,
but I could call you “oppa”
As you wish then
Here we go!
PARK JIN-HO PREFERS TO SET HIS MESSNENGER PROFILE PIC AS A COUPLE PIC OR NOT.
You prefer.
I prefer?
Here take a shot.
Why not?
There is a profile pic and a cover.
I am ok with the cover.
I can allow cover.
But I cannot allow profile picture.
Do you like to show that you are taken or not
Well..
I am not too desperate to show that I am taken.
I love to let everyone know that I have a boyfriend.
Everywhere? Like a newspaper?
Yes.
Alright.
It’s my turn, right?
Yes
JEONG HYUN-JIN’S LONGEST RELATIONSHIP LASTED FOR ___ YEARS
About 4 to 5 years?
4-5 years? For real?
Was it months or years? Just give me that
Months
Oh it’s even months, okay
3 months?
One month
One month? That’s the longest?
Yes
I’m just forever alone
So almost forever alone?
Right
Time to drink
Okay okay
I’ll have it too
one month....
How should I put it
How come only one month?
It was never with someone I liked
Oh I see it was someone who liked you
Seriously I want to try a long term relationship
I also don’t have that much experience with someone that I liked.
So what’s the longest for you?
Two years.
Hmmm.
I am jealous.
You are jealous?
I have only dated once when I was 20.
And since then
Nothing?
Nothing at all.
Nothing at all?
You could’ve asked the person you liked out
I got rejected.
Oh really? You got rejected alot?
I am wounded
I see… So that’s why it only lasted a month…
I understand…
That’s fine,
it happens you’re still just 21
If it was just once when you were 20
that’s just last year
That’s totally possible
This is a good question
It looks promising out of all questions today
BETWEEN AN EXPERT IN LOVE OR A NEWBIE JUNG HYUN-JIN PREFERS WHICH ONE?
Not my final answer but, newbie?
Don’t say yes or no
just look me in the eyes, newbie?
Expert?
A Newbie
You’re right
Thought so
How about you?
Newbie versus an expert..
Each has their pros and cons
So which one?
So answer first?
Sure
Wait a second
I like someone who knows things
A player to some degree
To meet a less experienced person I feel like I have to be the teacher
Ahh
But even if she’s player
I wouldn’t want her to be on another level
I guess you’re a player then?
No, I’m such a newbie
What I mean is that,
it’s better to know things to a certain level than being totally naive
I finally know now.
You’re a player
I am 100% sure.
I can tell
Positive
Not at all
I don’t know anything See my hands shaking?
My turn.
WHEN IS THE AGE THAT PARK JIN-HO HAD HIS FIRST KISS?
When you were fifteen?
You’re wrong
I’ll drink then
10th Grade
How about you? Around when?
In my case,
When you were 20?
Yes, correct
I suddenly feel shallow.
Oh wait. It’s not that year
Ok ok ok
It was one year prior
1 year? Then you were 19?
Maybe you should think about it hard once more
No that’s right
Senior year of high school can be tough
So you released stress by kissing, on your senior year?
ok
You are making it sound all weird now
Why? It’s possible.
I release my stress by eating.
So you ate the lips?
And you liked it
Shall we toast?
Have some, you
I still have it
No my glass
Oh you want it
Cheers
Sure
PARK JIN-HO CAN GO AS FAR AS ____ IN TERMS OF PHYSICAL TOUCH ON THE FIRST DATE
I see you as a free-minded person
So, a hug?
Or a homerun?
No way!
Not at all
But you know
I can do hugging
but an awkward one where you slightly put your arms around with your back hunched instead of a tight hug
You know what I mean
Aren’t you asking someone out if you hug that person?
What?
I tend to think that once you hold hands you are in a relationship with that person
Okay, okay okay.
JEONG HYUN-JIN THINKS THE EXPERIATION DATE FOR LOVE IS _____ YEARS
You seem like a person who believes in pure love.
10 years?
Your glass is empty
I think there isn’t one
No expiration date?
Actually my father is very romantic
so he’s my ideal type
Really? What is he like?
Til this day my mom never carries her own bag
And he always opens the car door for her
So when I see someone being that romantic
Am I being suddenly too serious? Anyway..
Ok, ok that’s fine
So yeah I don’t think there is an expiration date for love.
That’s cool
So I’d like a love like a companionship
I like that
Take the card
Oh, it’s the last one
JEONG HYUN-JIN FEELS THE SAME / DIFFERENTLY ABOUT PARK JIN-HO NOW COMPARED TO THE FIRST MOMENT
Not the same
So not the same
Yep
Based on the conversation we had today,
I think you’re a nice person
How about me?
Do you prefer me at the very first moment or now?
I prefer now
As I’m talking to you, you seem like a bubbly person
I like that you’re lively
Glad to hear that
Do you have anything you’d like to ask one last time?
So you work at night
If so, how often do you usually see each other?
If I have a girlfriend?
Yes
I would usually see her at least twice a week
Twice or 3 times per week
Now you ask me!
So your curiosity’s all solved?
I just wanted to know
You just wanted to know
Let’s say you have a boyfriend
who works night shifts
and he usually gets off work at midnight or 1 am
How would you feel about that?
I would respect his work-life
but I have to sleep early
You sleep early?
What if he has 2 days off a week
So then it’s negotiable?
Yes
I don’t have classes on Friday too
Fridays?
that’s cool
Great
Toast?