2,3
Hello
LONG HAIRED BLIND DATES
What’s your name?
My name is JEONG Seo-woo
Jeong Seo-woo?
What is your name?
My name is Lee Gon,
How about we take a shot first?
Sure
I can’t.. I need a drink
How old are you?
I’m 24.
25, I’m 25.
25?
I need more shots
THE PROFESSION THAT SUITS JEONG SEO-WOO’S FIRST IMPRESSION IS?
umm...
A stewardess?
Stewardess
nope!
If you’re wrong, you have to take a shot.
ah
Why do you think I’d be a stewardess?
It’s just..
Why why do you laugh?
What do you think my job is?
Well, maybe you are a professional dancer?
Are you not?
Did I make a mistake?
Something similar
I’m preparing to become a model,
A model, okay
That’s why I’m growing my hair long.
I wanted to add some character
Character?
Yes, to my identity as a model
It doesn’t look weird?
Not at all
Some girls don’t like long haired guys
Your hair is pretty
I’m relieved
THE MOST FREQUENT QUESTION THAT LEE GON GETS ASKED ON BLIND DATES IS ____
How exactly long is your hair?
I haven’t measured it
Oh really?
Do ladies usually measure their hair?
No we don’t but..
“What kind of hair treatments do you use?”
I’d get that question a lot
Seriously, which one do you use?
Currently I use Kera***
Kera***?
I applied some hair oil too you know
Maybe my hair is too long?
You have that French vibe
French or kind of like a hippie
But yeah that’s what I’m going for, why I kept it long
Oh really?
Yeah there’s a bit of that
JEONG SEO-WOO GLANCES AT WHICH PART OF BODY FIRST WHEN SHE SEES A MAN
His face?
Wrong!
Don’t judge me weird
I see a man’s booty first
Firstly?
Yes it’s that I like men who work out
Oh but isn’t it a bit weird to check out butts first?
Well I don’t stare at it
So just a glance ?
That’s something new
I haven’t seen anyone like that
Oh really?
I’ve never heard of someone checking out butts first
LEE-GON HATES THE FOOD _____
What’s your guess?
Oyster
Oyster?
The answer..
Am I wrong?
Yes
I wrote that I hated Jajangmyeon (black bean sauce noodles)
Do you like them?
No I don’t like it either
Oh really?
That’s a relief
What about your favorite food?
The classic food?
Shaved Ice with Red-beans, red beans,
Are those classics?
Cold bean-soup noodles and those kinds  I enjoy them
I am into classic movies too
So you really like ‘classics’
Yes that gives me a little edge to my image
So you like things with good vibes
No not things with good vibes
But things that make me look like I have good vibes
So you’re pretentious,
oops I’m sorry
So your image is important to you
So it’s just a showy thing
You know things people call “HIP”,
like a hippie
LEE GON RECENTLY MOVED BECAUSE OF ______
Bugs?
You’re wrong
You didn’t have to be too harsh
It was because the clubs
You go to clubs?
Yes
Really?
Yeah
What time do you go and come home?
I’d go there 11 pm get out by 6-7 in the morning?
6 or 7? You have great stamina
But there are others who go more intense than I do
I thought I am not intense enough
Which one do you usually go to?
Club ARE**
Club ARE**?
Then to where..?
I used to live in Nonhyun, but
I moved to Sin-sa
So you moved already?
Yes
I think...
I saw you before…
Me?
For real?
Where?
At the club Are**
Seriously?
My looks stand out that’s why
Shall we move on?
JEONG SEO WOO’S LONGEST RELATIONSHIP LASTED FOR ____
2 years?
Wrong
It was almost 3 years
That’s pretty long
Yes
But you looked like that type
Why?
Don’t know but from the start
I sensed that you’re kind of conservative
How about you?
How long do you think I went out with someone?
About 1..
100 days?
Correct
Really?
That’s right 100 days
It’s written all over your face
I get it
LEE GON NEEDS TO DATE AT LEAST__ TIMES BEFORE DECIDING ON A RELATIONSHIP
3 times?
I got it wrong again
You got 100 days right
I think 1 time is enough to decide on a relationship
Oh really?
Then approximately how many dates do you need to decide?
Well in my case at least I should see 10 times
10 times?
I think I need to at least spend a one season with the person to decide
I tend to be discreet
I’m not saying I am indiscreet
Yes of course
But what if you have like crazy crush on this person
Then I’d see him like 3 times a week?
Oh okay that’s how you’d do it
So 10 dates is like a check-list for you to be in a relationship?
No no, it’s not like that.
But you know you can go on a relationship and break up quickly
Sure
I’m saying that’s not a bad thing
I tent to think ‘We were meant to break up soon or later’
You said you’d meet 10 times before deciding right?
To me that is also part of a relationship, more like dating
LEE GON CAN GO OUT WITH HIS BUDDY’S EX-GIRLFRIEND OR NOT
You can
Yes I think I can
Really?
Yes
Let’s say she goes out with me and we get married
and have a happy life,
You were destined?
That’s right
we were destined to be together
That’s how I feel. So the past of dating my friend is out of...
But what if it’s your best friend’s ex-girlfriend?
Best friend?
Can you still… ?
Wouldn’t he understand because he is my friend?
I don’t think I’ll even get to have feelings for the person
If you really really have crush on that person?
I don’t think I’ll see him as one of datable guys,
like “He is not a man”
That’s how you feel
Okay okay
JEONG SEO-WOO CAN GO ON A TRIP WITH HER BOYFRIEND AFTER ___ DAYS
1 year?
Wrong
Honestly,
if it’s someone that I want as a boyfriend,
I can go without starting a relationship
So 0 days?
But then that’d be our 1st day of relationship
Hmm that’s good
I get it
You had that kind of conservative impression on me
So I expected you’d need a longer time
This is hard
IN A RELATIONSHIP, LEE GON’S DEAL-BREAKER IS _____
Can you give me some hints?
It was brought up a lot today
All I remember is clubs
Only clubs?
That’s not it
Am I wrong?
What is it then?
My hair
Your hair?
Someone telling me to cut my hair short
But honestly isn’t it something you can respect if you love that person?
I want that person to not care about my hair
It’s same me with short or long hair.
Doesn’t it hurt your feelings frankly?
Yes a little bit
Disappointed?
When I get a haircut, I was actually planning to donate my hair
I think I can cut my hair short anytime
but if I’m being told to do so
I’d be disappointed
Can you give up on clubbing, if not your hair?
When I’m dating someone I usually don’t go clubbing
Oh you don’t?
I usually go there to hang out with friends so
I tend to think I’m a good person,
You are
How do you know?
Well anyway
Me clubbing and my long hair makes me look like a shallow person
But actually inside I’m not that hip you know?
So I think I’ll stop going (clubbing) when I have a girlfriend
Because I prefer spending time with her
JEONG SEO-WOO’S MOST IDEAL RATIO OF CAREER AND LOVE IS:
4 to 6?
4 is career?
Yes
Wrong
it was close.
Career is 6 and love is 4 in my ratio
For now?
It’s not like I have a specific job so
But if I get to settle down,
I think the love part will grow
In my case it’s something like 3: 7
Career is 3?
Yes
Or 4 to 7? 4 to 6 I mean
4 to 7 gosh
Then can you give up your career for love?
Not giving up
but even if I’m not doing what I love as a job,
if I love my family I am ok with that job
So I consider happiness at home as bigger happiness
So it’s like seeking out a bigger happiness
I think I agree with you
COMPARED TO THE FIRST IMPRESSION
JEONG SEO-WOO HAS SAME / DIFFERENT FEELINGS TOWARDS LEE GON
Mine are different
Different?
Yes
Is that so?
At first I thought you’d be over sensitive, to be honest?
But I think you’re gentle, as I speak with you more
And you seem very honest
I think we share similar values
Similar but the different answers come from different situations but in the same lines
Yes
it’s like we have similar styles
Yeah I agree
Would you like to keep in touch ?
Umm
I think so, yes