hello guys orga stay with you and today
we want to talk about five things which
Ukrainians are not used to do I hope
this video will be helpful and
interesting for a lot of guys okay so
let's start of a list the first drink
very cold water very often I see people
from different countries from Asian from
States from Middle East they really like
to drink water with eyes and as more
eyes as bad as this is really cool and
you create people not used to use eyes
at all so most of the water even if you
ask blink me please cold water it will
not be cold enough we drink actually
something very close to warm water but
it's not one but it's the you know like
we call it room temperature so it will
not be very very cold and like you will
ask for that the second thing which
Ukrainians are not used to do this is
smile to people you know like you know
this American tradition where everybody
smile to each other when he just see you
he want to talk to you or he just saw in
the street and say people in restaurants
miles you people in the shop smile to
you this is not a common to to Ukraine
and actually yes in our service field
like restaurants and shops people try to
adopt try to adopt it and they start to
adopt it but still it's not the same
smile as they can meet in USA for
example and it doesn't mean that
Ukrainians are very cold or something
like that no if they really happy to see
you they will smile really but
Ukrainians used to have more natural
emotions so if you really happy your
smiles so if your is smile to you it
means that she's really happy to see you
you know as if person smiling to you if
person is just normal
it doesn't mean that he's angry all he
is going to kill you it means just that
this is normal thing for Ukrainians the
next thing this is talking directly
about some things this is what I also
noticed that you cranium stay a little
bit you know they have some topics which
they are not to like to discuss with
anybody
Sampson related to have something
related to your problems and actually
this
even in Ukraine considered like not
polite if you start to talk to other
people you know I have this problem with
house and this is what I'm trying to do
but I don't know but this is considered
not polite if you start to load people
with your problems but if somebody ask
you you know I notice you have something
wrong is your scheme this is considered
like something really crazy no this is
not what is normal for Ukrainians at all
and if you consider this is like
extremely rude how it all you dare to
say something I know that I have
something bad about my scheme like a lot
of people tell me you have braces you
know so do you have something wrong for
Ukraine this is extremely rude this is
not the topic which we are discussing at
all in public and you can discuss this
with close friends if you want if I want
to discuss it but if some just foreign
people tell me about that
this is extremely rude but I'm not
offended to you guys because I
understand this is cultural difference
but this is what we have the next thing
which is actually coming from this
thought this is largely from a lots of
things and this is what you can notice
if you will watch in YouTube a lot of
fails so someone is going and he fell
down
so most of foreign guys what I notice
again this isn't just mine like things
know what is but I noticed the biggest
just love how this is very funny you
know oh you said something wrong or you
did something wrong or you was going and
fell down this is really funny if you
didn't hurt yourself so much you know so
you just was going and you fell down and
this is yes this is very this is very
funny in Ukraine you don't talk at all
about fails if you see that person fail
even if it's seems that you want to love
you don't need to laugh in front of the
him because it's considered crazy
impolite so yes you can say also I feel
so much sorry for you are you okay if is
everything good you know even if it's
more the France I'm not talking that
this is among the strangers I'm on the
France so if your friend
it was going with him and he fell down
or he hit himself or something like that
we never loved from the sinks you know
we always try to be quiet and the best
actually if you make yourself that you
didn't notice anything so this is
considered the most polite but if you
want to show that you notice it at least
I need to say that I want so much sorry
for you but not laugh haha loser here I
go hold on you hit yourself nothing went
wrong with you this is not what yet
yesterday
and number 5 think which you are not
really doing in Ukraine this is making a
lot of friends this is very common as I
noticed four Americans they make a lot
of a lot of friends everywhere
everywhere everywhere they just move to
different cities I think maybe it's
really because for example Americans
they are not not so much Americans all
their lives
live in Van City where he was born so
they used to move all the time so this
is normal to make new connections new
connections new connections because you
always move in and for surely you cannot
keep connections with old friends in
Ukraine most of people they born leave
and to die in the same city in the same
even apartment so yes we have one or
maybe two friends and that's all others
is out of this circle I know and I don't
need anyone else I have this one I have
this tool with you we can talk but you
will never be close to me and you will
never be my friend but from the same
time in Ukraine friendship means a lot
so this is a person who can support you
hundred percent in any situation not
like you know and I know in some
countries you cannot complain on the
problem to your friends this is you know
this is you but you go to say college is
to go to other people you know you
complain to other people and pay their
money but you will never go to your
friends and Ukraine you are going to
your friends if you need help you're
going to your France if you are building
house and you need to help from someone
you going to your friend and he will
help you for free they never charge
money for that if you need to borrow
some things he will borrow you things if
you need money he will give you money
and again this is because he is friend
he's a hundred percent will support you
always so this is five things to each
Ukrainians are not used
do please I'm waiting for comments if
this is normal or not normal for your
countries which is similar what is
different and if you notice the same as
Ukrainians bye-bye