come on years what is today with you and
today I want to speak with you about
Ukrainian airport because I got a lot of
questions for you my dearest and you
have secured how to exchange currency
how to be in Ukraine if you don't have
Ukrainian currency and you can't
actually exchange it in your country so
today I will give answer on all of your
questions how long's Ukrainian airport
which services they provide and what
will be the most convenient and the most
cheapest for you ok let's start first of
all I decided not to speak a lot about
different things because it's better 1 x
2 C then a lot of times to here so I
just went to Ukrainian Kiev Boryspil
International Airport and I just filming
for you everything how it's inside so
first I propose you to see and then I
will continue my video balloons here so
tell me again you arrived here from that
side website and there is farts from
Ukraine from that's and slides from
abroad but in any case to arrive here
and everyone is waiting ok what else we
have here at the airport now I will show
you sure everything will be fine so this
is a taxi that you can order a piece of
text here is current on different
different current or services so in
cable news car you can bring them here
also here also is current all services
and you also can run them here if you
will be hungry
you can borrow fit here but the food is
very expensive of course then you have
exchange so if you need to change
currency you can exchange it here but
they have more banks there then if you
need a theme card you can buy SIM card
here so this is still this is circles
this is source cell phone operator so
you can buy their SIM card and then
there is the few more banks and police
department so everything will be fine
so I think after this video you already
got a lot of answers on your questions
anyway I just want to remind that if you
need to exchange money you can come with
your currency to Ukrainian oil port and
we have exchange office which are
filming for you and also they have a
little bit further to the carried or
they have to ukrainian deported to
Department of Ukrainian banks where you
also can exchange currency so this is
not problem also you can buy a SIM card
in Ukrainian airport and I also so show
you three different cell phone operators
in the airport and the last one taxi
taxis the more interesting topic because
there are a lot of taxi drivers when you
just came after passport control in this
whole well ever I was filming it's
already a lot of taxi drivers and they
all come taxi taxi taxi do we need taxi
do need tech seem like this but when I
was waiting for my client for half an
hour
I stand not far from them and I heard
how they speak what we speak about and
who are those people in general
and I don't suggest you know those guys
are like really scary drivers could just
works on the own they are money and of
course you can be overpriced
you must be probably overpriced because
there is no more benefit for them and
then yeah so I don't suggest you to you
them so far if you just don't have any
other option then you probably saw that
we have a taxi desk where you can order
a taxi also we have uber in Ukraine and
I just want to remind you and if you
will use uber you will have stable price
it's not important if you have warner or
not also we have services like like uber
it's texif i also we have Kiev service
Oaklawn it's also very good service you
can use them in Kiev so good but a lot
of my followers told me that if you want
to use uber in airport you need to be
ready that you need to wait for driver
for 20 minutes maybe half an hour it
depends because Airport and keep is 16
kilometers from Kiev and it takes some
time to go to the airport so sometimes
you need to wait along for a long for
this sexy dubard driver but anyway you
will not be overpriced
and this also can be very good option
for you and I have another variant for
you and my husband to hear all the time
meet my clients at the airport and he
will be glad to meet any my followers at
the airport to help him in style SIM
card maybe tell something give a lot of
answers on the questions actually he
speaks English hello my name is Eugene
I am husband of Roja resna cava I will
be glad to meet you in Aeroport I will
pick up you from Airport bring you to
your hotel and also instead of like
usual taxi driver I can buy for your SIM
card I can buy you local cell phone if
you of course needed and also I can help
you with all of that I like you can have
the internet you can have the calling
have fun in Ukraine welcome to contact
him his price is $20 per meeting it's
not important if you go in one place of
keep another place of key aggresses $20
for meeting and he will wait you already
in the airport so you don't need to wait
him and he know English you know the
staff according to follow this because I
would remind you that we assist all the
follow of all my clients together all
people who came to Ukraine for tour
we'll see them together so he knows
every since the sale of I know just he
is not running YouTube channel yes guys
so you're welcome to contact him and
this is probably everything what I
wanted to tell you in my video about
airport I think you already got all
answers on the questions and if you
still have some questions you are
welcome to write me in the comments as
always and I will be happy to answer you
to everything what you have ok guys wish
you safe trip to Ukraine don't be scared
of Ukraine the airport everything is
well organized and welcome to Ukraine
bye