hi guys OS here and today I with Natalie
she is also very wise woman and I
decided to make this video together
because we together can give you more
very important tips because I will tell
my students you will tell from her
experience and today my will is about
safety rules in Ukraine I think it's
very important for you guys it's really
buddy if you come for marriage or for
traveling or for looking for relatives
these roots of a business actually this
rules will be crazy useful for you in
Anki and the most popular which i think
is wallet cap oh my god yeah as a rule
someone stupid crazy very famous flim
flam movie is the origin of the scanners
one of my American guys told me that
there was a print one man movie in
America which started to show how this
can work
basically you're walking on the street
you see a bag with money right there you
pick up this bag and you you're an old
guy you're looking for an owner and
there come runs and other thing this is
your money you took some of it show me
whatever money you have and you you just
take anything you just take that bad and
you pull out whatever dollars you have
you looked oh no no this is not my money
it's very skillful while he's counting
your dollars he's sneaking in a little
bit not oh he's not going to take all
your money
he's go if you have like say a thousand
she will take three hundred so you will
only notice later and yeah that's a new
version of this game because before they
used to be greedy they would take like
half or they would take more and you
would complain immediately but then
another person comes and since this is
absolutely my money you're going to do
the real they will fight together and
they will run leaving you puzzled
wondering what it was not thinking to
check your money but just actually
published and completely like blown out
of your way in mind and it's a scam
watch out whenever you see a bag
money just walked away across the street
not even touch it because it's a scan
yes and sometimes I rather like romance
on the previous similar video dead guy
said that I even didn't touch it but
some guys come to me start to stick with
me also I suggest don't speak in general
just run solo run it does you can from
this person I don't think this is baby
run no no no no of course no did you
find another one but try not to speak
with people not to discuss with them
anything and even see police we have
DeFelice remember that we come new
police various garage yeah they're not
crap soldiers come to them and say oh my
god this is Canada once Kenya yeah even
if they don't want to scare you it's
better to be insured with two is it will
be bad you're actually right actually
new police is good friends with people
they are not taking bribes don't offer
them any money they won't take it
they're good guys and you can rely on
their help you can ask for their health
and they will help you they are
interested you make money from lunch yes
but generally when you're visiting
please remember that if the megapolis
big city with this wild rules so be
careful when you are taking out whatever
you have in your pocket when you're
walking on the step in the undergrowth
grow things do not keep any wallet in
your pockets anyway put it somewhere
that is also divide your money to
different parts even even if you stop
someone steal one part of your money you
will have some additional and it also
every country because when I was
visiting Europe every guys told me the
same in Germany in Czech Republic in all
threaded watch your wallet so we're
hoping you clean the engines
say that Ukraine is very bad in stupid
country just because somebody is killed
Ramon you know its own on your own hands
yeah guys we just need to be wise did
you see need to be like stupid to show
in all the money up against what it also
not is component they sometimes take a
big pack of
bridge of death and try to come
something is bless you already wait with
never noodles yes someone will see that
and later they come to you and take all
of this money and not in a very good way
no you look actually you'll never learn
yeah it's not way and you will never
understand who take your money and when
it happens you know a kid is a big city
and all this can happen to foreigners to
Ukrainians to everyone who is unlucky to
be in the wrong place around the wrong
people and now when you're taking subway
be careful with your pockets make sure
you don't have anything valuable there
if you fall in your hands if your wallet
somewhere hidden far behind not carry
lots of money with you it's much safer
to keep it in your apartment and locked
or somewhere nsa's if you have this
option but the main thing is that
generally give is very say I want to
emphasize that it is very safe and we
have a lot of things that do not happen
in tears that do happen everywhere else
for example when I was travelling in
Spain I was told me and my husband were
told keep your suitcases next to you and
hold it if this never happens here when
somebody is like pulling your bed yeah
yes no maybe sometimes it is very rare I
think I never heard of it
yeah and you it never no no it never
happens that if somebody like rudely
pushes you out of your car and steal
something they have to really hunt on
you this is such a slim chance that this
shittier happen the animation because
modern cameras they try to work you know
very quiet so nobody will notice it so
this rule things become money yes
thought to take you somewhere discreet
it's not work because
actually a lot of people do a little
police and this is stupid way of scam
brutality is not happening here yellow
but my smart scary smart scan when
people start to speak with you yeah
sounds like in bad ways and I will
emphasize we the safer than New York
especially when it's nighttime when it's
Indian I felt much safer walking into
your streets rather than I was walking
in New York I really feel very safe here
and of course there are districts were
you're not supposed to go even when
you're ukraine's but they don't even
have too many of those generally when
you are alone on the street and it is
evening time people are not going to
attack you or steal something from you
you really have to be extremely unlucky
for that to happen you know and be
careful when it comes to seeing Jesus
around yeah we're gypsies yeah that's so
but excited intuitive gypsies last time
in Kiev I think right I haven't seen
them recently too but if you see them
just cross the street and walk away
they're kids very smart yes yes and in
any way this is like how with all this
smart cam it comes when guys no guard
the girls know that you have something
something that they can steal from you
so this is also don't show a lot of
money don't show the porn you know or
don't show how you put your phone like
so so brightly like invest careful your
flaccid and when you are on the streets
be careful especially with women they
get normal Ukrainian women are shot they
are when you are having a date and the
NGO is sitting like this rock which is
sitting to show from breast it is not
the option and Angeles rather than
showing that she's closed for you know a
decent Ukrainian woman will not be like
lalala
than getting in Francie and so yeah this
is how I tell that some people think
that we are very cold we are not very
cold but we are very like watered
something with yes yes and of course if
you are going to the fridge and some
girls can't be all hello who are you
yeah yeah you do you already scared
because you know girls will not do that
it's crazy for you quiz not a girl will
sit and wait for your step from your
usual comments hello here you go he can
try to make something life she can smile
she can give some like I'm so fat Asians
here I contact but never come directly
to you to speak with you and usual
prostitutes do that and they are recipe
for failure and to lose your money if
you want and stay away from those
strange people and generally remember
common sense is number one rule when it
comes to travelling so if something
doesn't look right
stay away from it if something doesn't
appear to be like going right go away
and close the door yes I also want to
say that a lot of guys think oh it's
maybe cultural difference but it's not
cultural difference sometimes we have
some cultural difference but not so big
and even if it's cultural difference but
you are not feel comfortable with that
so it's better go away from that because
as I see a lot of women manipulate on
these statements and the thing here you
don't understand but it's okay in you
create so it's not common for Ukraine if
are not normal to clean and you don't
need to say that the biggest cultural
difference is just you can and you need
to know that
do not take girls shopping on the first
day even if you really want to buy her
everything and want to make her your
wife
take your time you know this is
necessary in general with the safety of
as it is there are some smart rules that
you need to remember all the time for
example if you go to some strange places
don't go there alone take Olga take all
our interpreter and go clubbing together
and stay away from those girls that seem
to be too happy to be around you
what's your glass because if you said
you're alone if you can use did you have
money you can risk to these scams by
being drugged you fall asleep and she
rolls with you that happened to some of
the guy yet before haven't heard of this
recently but it happens and you should
be aware of it and also I want to add
that this is not only for foreigner so
it's all the same rules with Ukrainians
in general just you need to keep some
rules of safety and sometimes what you
do not go along of course if you can to
come anywhere if you have some goal to
come somewhere it's ok but sometimes a
guys come to Ukraine and just
desperately going to the streets walking
everywhere and those Commerce they
already see that while these guys
actually don't know what to do and then
start they start to put you all I see
you're tourists here and again it
happens also with Ukrainians
so you just need to be smart and wise
they start to approach you they start to
propose the summit adventure yes some
strange things and then the kids can you
so if you don't have some plans were to
go in acquaintances desperately going to
three so take some friends take some
guys maybe try to find some company for
yourself it doesn't mean that it must be
me for example or Network translator
someone need to be with you just because
sometimes you can find some scammer yes
but Ukrainian people are very helpful
Ukrainian people very kind and if you
approach a Ukrainian who can speak
English this Ukrainian will definitely
give you an idea where to go what to do
how to get out of the certain strange
situations ask
for help you know you might be surprised
you may really get it I'm not a foreign
guy for example on the streets saying
guys normal and it was not the central
part of Kiev he was like way out of the
city and she was lost so even GPS didn't
help so I pointed the guy where to go
and I'm sure anyone would do that
because we do care we may seem to you
cold and strange people that don't smile
because smiling in our countries without
the reason is considered like you might
think yeah it look very good friends
with your brain so people don't smile
for no reason
but even without my link they will give
your hand and they will tell me what to
do they will say yes that's true
so you just need to be careful by
default don't think that assumption is a
cultural difference between big because
not always it is cultural difference and
also speak with strange people to try to
culture you on the street I think it's
the most like main rule of safety in
Ukraine because Ukraine in general Steve
but of course we're a lot of people
especially in case there are a lot of
tourists also from Ukraine so here's a
lot of cameras who want to take your
money it's logically like in any big
city right with be safe and welcome to
Ukraine and enjoy our country but visit
win by exploring by learning something
new it is worth it
yes bye