hi guys it's all good today with you
let's talk today about Ukrainian habits
which is not understandable for a lot of
foreigners I guess this will be
interesting for you let's start the
first month Ukrainians drink a lot of
tea tea for Ukrainians this is that
think number wad which you can use for
multiple purpose to warm yourself to
cool yourself to spend some time to talk
to friends to drink with pills and
medicines and for so many reasons so for
example if you are sitting on with your
colleagues at work and you have nothing
to do let's have a cup of tea so this is
kind of like a time spending all the
foreigners they prefer to have water or
milk juice any kind of other drink but
for Ukrainians that he is number one
if Ukrainian person is going to go out
somewhere for some trip so you need to
have some trip or train plane or car
some long trip you need to see it before
you go so you pack all the things you
already where your closest ok let's see
it one minute so people sit on their
backs and sit in one minute
actually this is good happy to remember
if you forget something but yes you
cannot just gather your things and go no
you need to see it and because this is
for all good things
Ukrainian pragma for most of the people
on retirement when they get retired they
can discover so many things with
themselves finally they don't need to
work so they can devote time for
themselves they can start a new hobby
like a divorce and fight new
relationship they can adjust go travel
somewhere go leave outside every see
what you want but for Ukrainian
grandmother this is becoming the most
responsible time because finally she is
not working so she can devote all your
time to Ukrainian grandkids because
their parents usually is very busy this
work with personal relationship and
other things and kids is without a lot
of attention so Ukrainian grandma this
is the biggest
attention maker or stuff like that so
they care about the grandkids so much
you can leave their their grandkids
always they will never complain while
you're bringing me grandkids why
my old things and I need to sit with
your children why I need to feed them
why I need to do all of that and for
sure you don't need to pay them for this
work it's not like nanny work ourselves
like that for sure you can support your
parents if you want but they do this
totally for free a lot of Ukrainians
they like to keep very big dogs in
apartments so a lot of foreigners also
they don't understand this idea because
most of the people who have dogs they
keep these dogs in the houses outside
especially if this is big dog I'm not
talking about this pocket small so yes
Ukrainians they live in general in small
apartments in two rooms so I mean one
bedroom for example and they can keep
very big dog and if this dog always is
making so many troubles because this
space is not enough and people can even
keep dogs on the balcony which is
totally not understandable for a lot of
foreigners Ukrainian people they like to
wear special chrome shoes at home so yes
a lot of people outside as I already
told you once time about that a lot of
Americans they don't take off their
shoes at all when they're coming from
outside to comb so they can walk with
the same shoes or the parchment on their
house and it is totally fine for them
for Ukrainians it is totally not
acceptable for us not taking off your
shoes and come in with them to you know
to the room it is the same like you go
to sleep on shoes on a jacket and and
all the kind of things you know it bad
it is totally not we don't understand
this at all so Ukrainian people they
usually take of the shoes and they have
some special whole shoes and there can
be different options for Viktor for Sam
or for gas everybody is using special
suits for home to do these things which
is actually not popular for a lot of
countries another why do you think this
is package actually package for a lot of
Ukrainian sinks this is the same as a
guest bath so usually yours and yeah
yours because man don't care about it at
all
yours they can have a small bag and they
pack some things if they see that this
sinks is not fitted on the back they
just
the package a diamond package and it is
fine so they can use it normally and
this is considering the same egg back so
like a lot of foreigners they can just
take the bigger back if you cannot fit
everything but not for Ukraine also
Ukrainians they don't have fun form how
you can talk to people who you don't
know for example like nice missus madam
seer any kind of this works we don't
have analogues in Ukraine be what's
happened in a very very old time but for
sure it's becoming totally very old and
not modern at all then he was having
some things in Soviet Union which also
after Soviet Union people stopped using
and there was nothing instead of that so
usually if you need to talk to the girl
you need just to say if you need to stop
some woman on the street so you can come
to here and say hey girl even if this
woman is 50 plus you still can say to
her hi girl and I want to ask you
something guys so this was habits which
I found can be very weird for foreigners
and if you go to familiar with some of
that in Ukraine if you fight such things
please write me what you was thinking
about it and if you notice some
differences with your countries or
similarities also let me know in the
comments and don't forget to check for
other videos which I have on my channel
maybe it will be interesting for you all
so I don't forget to subscribe to my
channel love you all bye bye