as soon as you've got both feet planted
outside Suvarna boom airport in the land
of perpetual smiles yes I mean Thailand
you will realize that there are two
kinds of people in this country those
that want something from you and those
that don't
sadly as a tourist wandering around
downtown Bangkok you're likely to
encounter the former more often than the
latter there's a pretty easy way to tell
though if the person you're talking to
is after your wallet or not before I
continue remember that this applies to
both Thai and foreign scammers as there
are plenty of Westerners who make your
living tricking people in Thailand as
well I already told you in the previous
installation of this series how your
average tide does not walk around
striking up conversations with
foreigners and how those that do often
peddle overpriced Goods false
information or outright frauds but what
if you're talking to someone who doesn't
immediately offer a service or want to
show you something or somewhere how do
you tell if their intentions are good or
bad here's how people who are up to no
good generally start fishing for the
same type of information within seconds
or at least a minute of meeting you even
if it takes five minutes before you hear
what I'm about to say I'm willing to
wager the person you're talking to
likely has ulterior motives you may find
it perfectly normal that someone you
just met asks you where you are from how
long you're staying when you go home
what your work where are you staying
do you speak Thai or is this your first
time in Thailand pretty innocent
questions right and asking them seems
perfectly legit but let me assure you
that these questions are anything but
innocent when asked by someone in a
market a bar the beach or in a taxi only
scammers ask them genuine Thais say
things like what do you think of
Thailand have you been to Chiang Mai
have you tried Thai food can you eat
spicy so what's wrong with the other
questions they're all geared towards
gauging your net worth susceptibility to
what's being scammed and even what type
of scheme to pull where you stay for
example tells them how much you roughly
paying per night that reveals a lot
about you including most importantly
financial information it's less subtle
than the what your work question but
pretty much reveals the same
similarly simply knowing you're from
Sweden and not Italy not only reveals a
lot about your potential financial
situation but also what trick might work
best on you the scammer can even build
some rapport with you if it throws a
couple of phrases your way in your
native tongue then there's that when you
go home question surely this is as
innocent as it gets
no this reveals the timeframe the
scammer is working with do you speak
Thai reveals your knowledge of local
conditions is this your first time in
Thailand pretty much tells the scammer
everything he needs to know it means
you're on your own don't know any Thais
have zero local connections know nothing
of the lay of the land in other words
you're the perfect sitting duck keep
this in mind the next time some chai
says hello outside Pratunam market or
dave from australia just wants to share
with you this awesome land deal he's got
the inside scoop on down on Kamala Beach