hey everyone we taking you all the way
across the Germany today in a heavily
requested show so with us today
is the head of the German academic
exchange services in Mumbai talking
about all the exciting opportunities
waiting for you to study in Germany so
super - Audrey thank you so much for
being on the show today pleasure is all
mine thank you so much and tell us a
little bit about your wonderful
organization and the work you do okay so
the da-ad well it's the day our day in
German which lots of people in India say
Dada or Dada
oh and it's an acronym for Deutsche
academia sure al cows Dean's which is
the German academic exchange service and
it is a non-for-profit organization
underfunded by the foreign ministry of
germany and by the ministry of education
and research right so it is a
not-for-profit organisation meaning that
we do not charge for any of our services
that we provide to the students and our
head office is in Delhi and we have four
other centers in India one of course
being in Mumbai the other in Pune the
and then the third one in Bangalore and
one in Chennai okay and I also learned
it's one of the largest funding
organizations in the world yes that's
absolutely correct
in 2016 we had more than one lakh
scholarships given to all people ah Ross
the world
Wow and we have more than 75 offices all
over the world so there are a really
large organisation so let's let's talk
about the biggest advantages for a
student watching the show
what are his pros of studying in Germany
most importantly when people look at
Germany it is that the innovation the
level of innovation that comes out of
Germany and innovation does not come out
of thin air
of course there is very clearly a very
specific foundation to innovation which
starts with the schooling system in
Germany so the dual schooling system in
Germany as it is called basically
illiteracy is a learning theory by
putting into practice that theory and
there is a very specific term
to it in German which is called praxis
okay and the student is given the
freedom the businesses are very friendly
to the store room to do their
internships so internships become a very
important part for innovation
internships and putting into practice
what you are learning while given this
option or a world-class education in
Gyeonggi it comes back a fraction of the
cost
yeah very nice one scent of German
universities do not charge a tuition fee
wow this is huge
exactly for two years masters wooda
proxies approximately cost 15 lakh of
rupees which is barely an expensive in
terms of an education and exposure
abroad sure of course and also then
there are a lot of opportunities to stay
back in Germany and work in Germany
Equestria so I mean given all these
points we call it always you know the
five points of why you should study in
Japan they are all fantastic
each one of them beats any other reasons
so so if you're watching you've got all
the reasons to study here and let's ask
her how to make that happen
Shabana you spoke about this dual
cooling system that's prevalent would
you like to take us through the
university system as well yes very much
in fact that is a very important
question that you asked Chitina because
the system in germany is very different
from what we have in india and also
different from the u.s. system what
people are aware about it's rather
different you see so on one side there
are the universities and technical
universities and on the other side there
are universities of Applied Sciences
right which are called far coke cooler
or coke seriously now the difference is
that the universities are like our
universities where they have lots of
subjects yes and technical universities
are again University of the tech focused
on technology like we have IITs right
okay so that is a similarity
also the universities or technical
universities are more research-oriented
right
whereas the far cooler short-form as FX
or HS the hoax ruler they are the
universities of Applied Sciences and
they are more industry or corporate or
the energy okay also another very
important fact is that if you have doing
your masters from afar Hawkes Euler then
you cannot consecutively or immediately
do your PhD from a research oriented
University because the focus is
unresolved you can do it after a late at
a later point of time okay but the
University of Applied Sciences is not
mandated to a word or PhD so that is
something that people should bear in
mind area yes very interesting
another question that a lot of people
want to know you know is which is the
best university to go to this is one
question that I get asked every time in
fact I have a presentation or a webinar
or whatever because we come from we are
exposed to the US system royal March but
you have to understand that the
education system in Germany is very
different it's a lot more egalitarian
than it is in the US as you know Germany
is very disciplined Germany has got a
law for everything yes so there is no
question of fake universities and yes
like that which I have heard a lot of
school in a few ratio in a few nations
that they do but in Germany that is
nothing like that also in Germany there
are about 400 universities although
being it being such a small country Wow
and you are not going to get 400 courses
for the feeling that you are selecting
okay so it is more course drizzle right
it means that you will choose those
universities that are offering you that
course right so if X university is
ranked at the top Mellon does not offer
you the course that you are looking at
the kind thing doesn't make any sense
right of course also for example in the
world rankings people do look at world
rankings also know by then we well in we
are a little skeptical about what
rankings are filled but apart from that
the LMU for example the Brits Maximilian
University which is ranked first in the
universe
in the bowl ranking is not have an
engineering course at all so from a
German standpoint there is really no
deinking for state in terms of one two
three four right but there is something
called a CH a ranking which is more of a
comparison of various universities on
ten parameters so you can choose those
views the names of the university select
the parameters that you are looking at
and then it may give you a companion or
universe okay okay so that is there but
of course it is not one two three four
right of four nine which is the DA ad
dot de okay this is the main German
website okay and of course we have
another India based website is under
www.ada.gov I may be might change in the
coming months to dat India may be
migrated here so this is very
interesting you said that you know every
University doesn't offer you every
course and the students need to look up
individual courses and then choose the
colleges so how do the cobalt is
searched where do they look for these
courses well we have a fantastic web
search engine that is created by the
da-ad for international students and it
is called the as I said international
programs it is again available on the
vab main web search engine and there you
have two in the key world you have to
put in your field right and you choose
which degree were looking at either
bachelors or masters or PhD and then you
click on search and we give you a list
of all the courses for that particular
field available at various University of
lis now and then each item on this list
is a link in itself which will give you
detailed information about that
particular course okay yeah so all the
details regarding the course like the
requirements or you know the course
contained or what are the costs and
funding what are the services provided
by the university everything is
available on this
and this international degree program
read search engine is especially made
for English language courses okay and
some English German language courses
which we call 80/20 courses we're
majorly we are taught in English 80% and
20% injured you mentioned 80/20 so one
of the questions that a lot of people
want to know is how much German do I
need to know prior to even applying C
from an academic standpoint you don't
necessarily need to know German because
the classes will be held in English okay
rather you would be tested you would
need to provide the IELTS or TOEFL
scores okay right but on the other PI
from a social standpoint you obviously
need to know German
right so to start with we recommend that
you do a two levels to begin with before
going to Germany because the moment you
get out of the aircraft everything is
going to be enjoying German and if you
want to stay back and work in Germany
then we would recommend you to have at
least be to lunch or a job okay but it's
good to know that if they have a basic
fluency in spoken German to start with
they can get there at least and then
they can get in you they're learning a
versatile offer on campus courses once
you go over there okay so can you do
those in the evening or whatever and
then come up you can increase your
proficiency as you go along with your
education okay fantastic also we have
seen that you know we ourselves come
from a multicultural my feeling was a
you know very shy and the moment you
find somebody who's speaking your own
mother tongue there is a different
connect towards our sin Omega it is the
same with a job even as well also you
have to understand that for the German
people English as a foreign language
unlike for us here we have been born and
brought up in the language here but not
for them here certainly and if you're
looking to work in German companies
you're looking at engineering based
companies with job flows and I guess
there's nothing where salutely necessary
then because you need to not only know a
spoken German in fact you need to know
business German
of course communication yes and business
communication because that is different
former colloquial German diagnosed right
so she's know which are the fields that
you find people increasingly applying
for when they are applying to Germany
obviously engineering from an Indian
standpoint is very very important but
management is coming up tremendously
because well huge lot of enquiry for
management and Germany offers very very
good management options as well there
are two different options in Germany one
is the MBA trial one is the MS in
management okay okay here so or MSC in
management so MBA is generally a
paid-for course okay yes and they might
mostly they require work experience okay
whereas n MFC is most of the times of
free of cost course and they don't
necessarily ask for work experience okay
so the usual figures difference I mean I
have seen a lot of inquiry for banking
and finance for that matter I have seen
an increasing where in quality for
sports management international
management and there have been on and
off enquiries for law right nology as we
always say that Germany has produced
Nobel laureates in all arrived and there
are more than 3.5 million foreign
students in Germany Wow
so let's talk about the master's program
that is the most popular route that
people choose to when they go so what
sort of eligibility criteria would be
there to apply for a master's program in
German generosity eligibility is that if
you have a four-year bachelor's from
India then you are eligible for a
master's in German okay if you have a
three years Bachelor then you should get
in touch with the course coordinator
clinicals they might ask you to do extra
courses during that time or they might
ask you to complete another year in
India so lots of people do for example
if they're coming from commerce not
right komm
right after three years they get a one
year's income okay
yes that's a
leguminous well but you know it but two
years is a little problematic right -
any other criteria you're looking at any
age limit you're looking at four there
is no age limit absolutely where is you
know there have been people who have
been working for 10 or 12 years and then
they have applied for masters and gotten
- Wow
so for fourth grade which is looking at
twelve plus four there's no age limit
and any marks etc that you require
generally yes the German universities
are a little more weighed down by
academics than we have seen the US
universities because of course they have
to justify finally the payment is coming
from the German citizen you know yes so
they do look at approximately seventy
percent and above but that is not a hard
and fast rule okay
okay it depends on your letter of
motivation on a recommendation letter it
also depends on how many students are
applying for that year ago what is the
direct competition that you are facing
so there are a number of factors that go
into shine early getting an admission
sure hey thanks for watching part one of
this two part series of how to study in
Germany for free now I will do a quick
recap and also tell you what to expect
in part two so in part one we did about
the ad if you talk five reasons to study
in Germany we discussed the university
ranking system and also where you can
find all this information we spoke about
the German language requirement and some
of the most popular course choices that
people are undertaking when they go to
study in Germany we also spoke about the
master's program and the eligibility for
the same now look at the part two which
is really exciting and full of
information because of course we're
going to discuss the two types of PhD
programs and the eligibility for the
same the undergraduate program the
Abitur and if you're from IGCSE Ivy or
Indian Board
what sort of conversions do you need
we're also going to tell you about costs
and tuitions and aware is different
types of scholarships that are available
to you because yes it is indeed for free
we're also going to tell you about
application
process deadlines the kind of documents
you would need the various types of
tests for instance that you would need
to take and we touch upon these ours as
well so student visas vers visas
residence permits you blue card and lots
of more information so tune in to that
one keep watching and if you have any
queries you want to ask questions about
studying in Germany or about just about
anything else put them at the comment
section at the bottom and sugar will
reply to them personally I will reply to
them as best as we can and tell us if
you want to watch any other video or any
other topic you want us to cover right
there at the bottom section of this
video and press that little red button
at the bottom to subscribe to the
channel and happy watching