hey guys after talking about the blocked
accounting in so many videos we finally
have a really good news for you guys
today we have Sammy with us to talk
about the launch of blocked account by
cracker
semi welcome tell us what you're feeling
right now it's it's like a baby being
born again yes the second one in the
last few weeks honey
so we are very excited it coracle and as
you mentioned we have been talking about
this quite some time yeah in everything
maybe the block the court will come up
soon some time but now it's finally
there tell us something about the block
the code okay um so as everyone expects
the coracle account like the other
solution it's it's straightforward so
it's very transferring very simple but
functional it will be the cheapest in
the market at least as of now so it will
cost around so it will cost 19 euros a
year application is like a single page
application the students they don't need
any other documents just a passport
copies sufficient apply and once people
apply they will get the first
confirmation by email without data's
lock on will be opened and then the
contagious will be sent by email okay so
like to open the blocks account you
don't need any kind of an like admission
that or something no no because we
assume people sometimes they don't have
admission letter and then it's fine so
you can apply that's also better like it
it saves you so much hassle of like you
know as soon as you have that mission
data you have to go and like run through
all of these processes at least you can
have your blocked account already ready
because it is something which takes the
most time in all of the other things and
health insurance can also be done in
just five minutes through crackle like
you just have to have your admission
that are there but for block the con you
don't need the admission that and like
you can just transfer the money and if
you transfer the money and you don't
have a ideally shouldn't start applying
for the blocked account once they have
the first at MIT let's say but it is not
mandatory and in the past we have also
seen that it gives the flexibility for
the students to up to transfer the money
any time because
stockholders ready so you basically
decides when you wanted to transfer the
money also like I was talking to Sammy
and it just takes like maximum two days
and like it can be processed within a
few hours so like this is absolutely
crazy I think like this could even be
one of the fastest blocked akan services
on the market right now
so Sammy once the blocked account has
been opened now the confirmation has
been saying what are the next steps
which the students have to take care of
so technically to transfer the money is
the next step but in some consulates
they the students can already apply for
the visa just with opening confirmation
so some consulates accept this but some
consulates expect to have money in it
so basically students needs to transfer
the the necessary amount so beta 8600
euros or whatever and they wanted to
block to this account mmm
so they can use their local banks or
Forex services any other option to
transfer the money so once the money
reaches the account they will get an
immediate notification about the money
arrival of the money and then they will
get the so called the final confirmation
for the visa authorities they will need
in any case to get the visa or even to
apply for the visa and this is like
something that you have to take care of
like okay sometimes many consulates do
accept with just the confirmation but
they tell you to like show the final
confirmation afterwards so it's already
better you know to have some kind of
distance like have some kind of buffer
before you are like going to the visa
interview and like get these things
handled already semi what is like the
final cost for like Oracle like what
what is the how much does it cost to
open the block to comp so we have
resided for like like a kind of a
one-time fee so we do not have any
monthly costs and in 99% of the cases
the block the code is needed for like
one year when they apply for visa 99 is
like a fixed price we do not have any
other additional costs or nothing no
hidden costs and you apply now for one
year from the activation date it's like
99 euros which is fixed insurance will
pay upfront no need to worry about an
any monthly costs and then each month
the blocked amount will be delivered to
the local account so surance needs to
open an account when they are here with
any any bank mmm I don't know Commerce
Bank spark has a fourth bank and then to
share this information
and then the blocked amount will be like
transfer to them without any costs being
reduced from there because they will pay
the maintenance and an opening fee up
front
so like funds you will be sent these 720
euros monthly to your bank account which
you will open so it could be a normal
like a student account but like all of
those fall under the zero font or like
the savings account here in Germany
which are in most of the banks free for
us versions anyway so we decided that
the choice should be led to the students
because in some places Spartacus is love
but in some places like Falls Bank in
some places come other banks so we
decided okay let's just leave it open
those rooms so they can open it this is
free anyway that's also a very good idea
because for example if you like restrict
somebody or like you restrict the people
to like just one bank this that exact
bank can have different policies in like
different regions for example if you
talk about sparkles - podcast is free in
Chemnitz for students to 24 years of age
but in Hamburg it still costs 350 but
for example Fox Bank is free here till
27 years of age but you talk about Fox
Bank in Chemnitz then the students still
have to like pay a fee so it's like all
of these regional things and it's better
that you just see in what kind of place
when you are here in Germany you see
what kind of Bank is better in your
specific city right but like for the
blocked account you have the correct and
every single month you will be getting
the 720 euros transferred into your bank
account exactly and many students might
be thinking what should I do
to access the funds yeah so the one
students come here they've left to take
care of the basic steps like enrolling
at the University and they're
registering themselves and then go to
the the city office to register the
address and then of course opening this
normal bank account like the Giro canto
and we need there are all the three
documents so they can upload it into a
coracles portal once these documents are
verified by our team then
the automatic transfer kicks in okay and
if students transferred a little bit
more than required some in the first
month the excess someone will be
transferred in the first payment okay
yeah so the second month will be 720 and
then in the first month it could be a
little bit more because they might they
will also transfer a bit of a buffer
when they apply when they transfer money
and some sometimes students might feel
like that I would like to have 400 euros
more in my account and all these amounts
are not blocked so by law we are only
expected to block the certain amount
like 720 a month whatever excess we have
whatever the existent account it will be
transferred in one time in the first one
transaction okay so they already have
their money in there
I mean access yeah they can hold onto it
and some in case somebody's Weiser gets
rejected
is it possible to consent the account of
rhodes no no although it wasn't it goes
to no no no of course of course yes of
them you know it's an obvious answer
that the money will be transferred back
but also due to the the money laundering
acts and also to preventing the the
funding of like bad bad things and stuff
like that
we need to have the proof of the
cancellation and visa cancellation and
then the money will be sent back to the
to the to the holder so basically back
to the students account okay shouldn't
be a problem
and we hope no cancellations comes up
but you never know and for for
unforeseen reasons these things happens
and then yeah just let us know and then
the process is also straight forward so
I think in general I just wanted to
summarize all of this it's like
extremely nice coracle is going to be
one of the fastest and the easiest and
the cheapest
block the con service available on the
market and I'm personally really excited
to like support it to promote it and I
see the atmosphere and the group already
in our Facebook group everybody's really
looking forward to it in the next
semester so yes now you will have
everything under one single umbrella
from somebody from the people who you
already know
or realized to these YouTube videos and
stuff so yeah just get excited as soon
as you have your admit you know what
other next steps you have to take you
have your blocked account you have your
health insurance and with that you can
just start your studies in Germany by
the people for the people but yes we are
very happy and the more happy faces and
then more people tell us that the our
solutions really helped them that's what
really drives us and like the other two
products please do share your feedback
because we are building this for you
which means if you feel like some things
can get better or something needs to be
changed some text needs to be changed
please do share in the group please to
share it me or to send it to the email
because we really really are taking
those feedback seriously and then which
helps us to like yeah be here and of
course we will take those things with
open arms and we really think that you
share it for our own improvement this is
very valuable at our company and then
yeah all the best and then looking
forward I think for now we don't have
anything in pipeline but there are some
ideas yeah that we are already
brainstorming then yeah if there are any
needs yeah that's like extremely
extremely nice I remember the day like
when blocked account was being launched
it was the Bremen meter that we were
having and like the whole blocked
accounting was already on the website in
the background where semi was presenting
but semi didn't see that and he was like
all right I will promote the blocked
account in some other time but I was
like Sarah look it's already up there
and it's just like a really proud moment
every time you create a product which
really works and like which is nice it
takes a lot of effort it takes a lot of
time and then afterwards when people
actually use it and they enjoy it which
I hope you both like just extremely nice
feeling if you are able to just like
provide something really nice so do
share your feedback like Sammy said and
if you have any kind of question or
something come to our Facebook group
hunt in Germany and you know tag semi or
something annoy him as much as you want
although I cannot guarantee with a new
baby being born in Sammy's family if it
would have so much time but still try
your luck who knows alright then guys
thanks a lot for watching thanks Sammy
for being here with
you up in some other video origin guys
bye-bye
kiss but yeah that's crazy man German
labs are nice rights I mean that's
that's why you should study in Germany
touching and then understanding yeah
it's not in the paper you know and you
see the gear ratio always this is from
the differential shredder was being a
super nice super nice
[Music]