hey everyone and welcome to Germany
willkommen in Deutschland in today's
video I'm going to give you five top
reasons to study in Germany those five
compelling reasons because of which you
want to make Germany the choice of your
educational destination now before we
begin I'm going to remind you that we've
got two videos already on the channel
which are going to detail everything you
want to know about how to study in
Germany for free including the
application process the costs
scholarships and all of that stuff so go
back and take a look at those two videos
and before we get to those top five
reasons for which you want to study in
Germany press the subscribe button and
the bell icon right next to it now let
me give you three highlights of Germany
before I give you those top five reasons
the first is that Germany is the third
most popular destination amongst
international students to study in after
the US and Canada the reason number two
that interests you
is that 12% of all students enrolled in
German universities are students coming
from abroad and number three is that
Munich and Berlin regularly feature in
the top 10 favorite cities in the world
of international students so let's begin
with the top five benefits to study in
Germany the number one reason you want
to study in Germany is for its
world-class technical institutions
Germany has some of the best technical
institutions in the world including some
medical institutions and management
institutions as well as the German
education system is divided into three
main types of institutions the first
other universities and the technical
universe
city's the second other universities of
Applied Sciences also called the FAC
hochschule II or the hochschule II and
the third are the colleges of music art
and theater etc so Germany is coined a
term called praxis which they use in
their entire education system right from
their schooling to the University which
means practice and they teach their
students to apply everything that they
learn in theory into a practical
application in fact the fog Shula or the
hochschule is our industry or corporate
oriented reason number two that you want
to study in Germany is that it has no
tuition fee the government subsidizes
higher education in Germany and the
public universities charge absolutely no
tuition fee to local students as well as
to international students now let me
give you some statistics there are 400
institutions of higher education in
Germany which have about 2.5 million
students enrolled at this point of time
and 95 percent of these students study
at the public universities where there
is ZERO tuition fee but does that mean
that we don't have to pay anything to
these universities no it doesn't mean
that let me explain your cost structure
once you study in Germany the
universities will charge you
approximately about 400 to 500 euros it
depends from university to university
but just a ballpark number of 400 to 500
euros that they will charge you per
semester which is a period of six months
and this covers their administration fee
there could be a contribution charge it
also includes a free travel card that
you will get to travel on all different
modes of transport within Germany so
that's your primary expense 400 to 500
euros per six months now let's talk
about the living cost the average living
cost in Germany is about 700 euros per
month
it's
ballpark number cities like Munich could
be a little more expensive and cities
like Berlin could be a little cheaper
but on an average if you take a number
like 700 euros per month that number
could be a good average to work with
about 50% of this could be towards your
rent and perhaps you'll take up a shared
student accommodation and about 100 250
euros could go towards your food and
groceries and the balance for all your
other living expenses now this still
makes the living cost in Germany much
cheaper than studying in neighboring
France or in Netherlands the number
three benefit of studying in Germany is
that you need to keep a relatively lower
amount in your blocked account and let
me explain that to you when you go to
study in Germany you need to apply for a
national visa this visa has a number of
different requirements and one of the
requirements is to place a sum of money
in a blocked account to show them that
you have the capability of financing one
years living expenses
now remember because they don't have a
tuition fee this amount is lower because
you only need to show one year of living
expenses before we get to the exact
amount you would need to open this
blocked account as soon as you get your
university acceptance letter and you can
also open this account in your home
country before you go there now looking
at the amount at the rate of euros 720
per month
the amount that you need to place in
this blocked account is for the 12-month
period
so that's euro 8640 approximately and
that works out to about 7 lakh of Indian
rupees at the current exchange rate now
let me tell you if you wanted to go and
study in US or Canada
this amount would be much much higher
you would need to show in your account
at least 15 to 20 lakhs if not more so
this is a huge advantage for you when
you go to study in Germany especially if
funds is a crunch situation
seven lakh of rupees in your block
account and tuition fee for free the
number fourth benefit for you to study
in Germany is the work opportunities
Germany offers a substantial number of
work opportunities for you provided
you're proficient in spoken German let's
look at the regulations under your
student visa you're allowed to work for
120 full days or 240 half days during
the year when the term is on you can do
20 hours a week and during vacations
you're allowed to work full-time you
don't need any specific approval for
this you can automatically work 20 hours
a week the moment you have the national
visa for a student your student
assistantships or research
assistantships are over and above all of
this and there is no upper time limit
for that
however those require the approvals of
the university now let's look at this 20
hours a week most students try to work
on weekends for 10 hours a day and cover
up the 20 hours over the two weekend
days and focus on their academics during
the five days of the week let's look at
where they tend to work most students
tend to work at stores and restaurants
but some of the higher paying jobs for
you as a student and I'm talking about
part-time jobs here preferably weekend
jobs could be maybe as a language tutor
as a call center executive or an office
assistant not office assistants are not
weekend jobs but they could be higher
paying even babysitting jobs sometimes
can be higher paying and also if you are
a field interviewer now you want to
combine some of the higher paying jobs
with the weekend jobs and balance out
your work curriculum and the weekends
and that 20 hours a week let's look at
remuneration the minimum wage in Germany
is 9 euros an hour but you could get up
to 15 to 18 euros an hour if you work as
a feel interview or perhaps you could
get the higher number now looking at 20
hours of
you could earn up to 800 euros a month
and that would sufficiently take care of
your living costs of which we said were
roughly about 700 euros a month however
you must know that if you earn more than
450 euros a month you need to pay taxes
and social security contributions which
are minimal as a student however you
need to pay them but they help in
clocking your years to become a resident
and we're going to talk about that later
but focusing right now on work
opportunities the one thing I must tell
you is that for all these jobs to happen
you must be proficient in spoken German
but don't worry about it once you enroll
in Germany let's say you don't know
German from before but you still want to
enroll in a German university or right
ahead and do it usually they're gonna
ask you for your TOEFL scores because
the course itself is in English but once
you enroll you can take up these
short-term German language courses which
are offered at the universities and at
the end of about three months you could
be reasonably proficient in spoken
German and pick up a few part-time jobs
here and there and slowly work towards
getting that b1 level of language
proficiency that is a bare minimum
before you can look for any permanent
job okay now moving away from part-time
jobs and looking at the permanent jobs
that you're going to be looking at once
you complete your degree Germany as you
know is the fourth largest economy in
the world after USA China and Japan and
it's the largest one within the EU jobs
are a plenty but there are certain
sectors that have more jobs and certain
others and let me talk about which those
sectors are engineering jobs are
available particularly mechanical
engineering automobile engineering
Electrical Engineering and even Chemical
Engineering jobs renewable power sectors
very large and specially if you're
working on the solar power those are the
kind of jobs that you could get in large
numbers
medicine is another area of priority and
statistics show that they are about
short by 5,000 doctors right now
another area where they're growing and
looking for people is the IT area so if
you're a software professional and even
other STEM related areas science fields
mathematics fields etc are areas where
you could get jobs readily outside of
these science and technical and
engineering jobs jobs like in the
education sector and in the training
sector are also highly in demand also
looking at the large corporations where
you could apply the large local
corporations in Germany are like a ddos
Allianz BMW Bosch Deutsche Bank Hugo
Boss Volkswagen Siemens and there are
many others so those are the jobs you
can get with the local corporations
there's also some of the large
multinational companies that have a
significant presence in Germany like
Amazon Google KPMG McKinsey so these are
the companies that would typically
employ in large numbers and you could
keep all of this in mind when you're
applying however German universities
have their own career centers and you
could go to them and they will extend a
lot of help to you in preparing your
resume in applying and interviewing with
these companies and also helping you
choose which company you want to apply
to and benefit number five to study in
Germany is the options available to you
to settle down in that country now
typically after you finish your
university degree your student visa will
expire almost immediately
even if the visa was initially issued
for a period longer than the period of
your degree it expires immediately on
expiration of your degree or on
completion of your degree
now you're eligible to apply for an
18-month work visa post completion of
this degree program now during that 18
months you can continue to work for your
20 hours part-time jobs and you can make
up for that living expenses while you're
looking for that permanent job however
you may lose out on some of your student
benefits like that subsidized health
insurance and the free travel card but
you could still earn upwards of 802 now
hundred euros because by then you have a
lot of work experience as well if you're
doing a master's degree you could have
an eighteen month or 24 month work
experience in Germany you would be more
proficient in the language so you could
be at the upper end of the per hour rate
when you're doing your part-time jobs
and you could be comfortable with your
living cause but the goal for you is to
get that permanent job and as soon as
you get that permanent job you're
eligible to apply for a part-time German
residence permit or you blue card now
the difference between the two really is
as the name suggests the German
residence permit is restricted for jobs
within Germany the EU blue card allows
you to move around between the countries
of EU however it is said that for better
long-term prospects within Germany the
German residence card is preferred so
weigh the pros and cons of the two
before you select one but you could
choose either of the two the moment you
get a permanent job and one caveat is
that the job needs to be related to the
field in which you did your degree
program and needless to say language
proficiency at a b1 level is a minimum
must before you get that permanent job
now two years after you've got that
German permit or the EU permit you could
apply for a permanent residence permit
once again it could be either German or
it could be you depending on what you
chose in the first place and also what
is very exciting is that if you've been
there for eight years as a student as a
taxpayer after that you're eligible to
apply for a citizenship and Germany
gives its own students so if you are a
foreigner having studied in a German
university you get a lot of preference
over any other non EU resident or
citizen so once you go to study in
Germany literally the entire job market
is open to you if you'd know to speak
their language so these were the top
five benefits of studying in Germany but
there are a number
other side benefits as well which I'm
quickly going to list out for you
Germany has a large number of programs
available to you in English language
there are numerous masters and PhD
programs and you'll find them all listed
on the da-ad website which are conducted
in English language also the student
community is extremely helpful and
talking about the ad you could even get
a full scholarship which covers your
entire living expenses also the degree
is granted by the German universities
are internationally recognized because
they are now covered under the Bologna
reforms they also have topped faculty
and great infrastructure on a personal
level as well living in Germany could be
a great experience because Germany is
bang in the middle of Europe and you
could end up travelling to all these
exotic countries on your long weekend
and Germany itself is a beautiful
country to live in with a diverse
population weather-wise it's cold but
it's not as cold as Canada so I'm sure
you could adapt beautifully to this
country so having said that I'm sure
you're opening up the websites today and
filling out forms and figuring out where
you need to go in Germany to study so
thank you for being with us right till
the end press that subscribe button and
the bell icon right next to it
and go back and watch those two videos
where we tell you about how to study in
Germany for free and if you have any
other questions that you'd like to ask
us put everything down in the comment
section and happy watching