[Music]
hey guys welcome everybody this is the
28th ask your questions session my name
is para Chaudhary and in this session we
are going to talk about exactly what
stated in this theme which is going to
be the complete procedure for bachelors
in Germany and I know it's like I
understand it has taken a long time for
me to actually come up with this one
because the Masters
yeah the application procedure was on
and then that's why I had to like put
all that content first and now
afterwards the bachelor one is here but
here's the thing and like remember at
this point very clearly once you have
gone through this video till the end of
the live session this is going to be the
most complete and practical video that
you are going to find about studying
your bachelors in Germany so even if you
have gone through this entire video
afterwards and you still cannot make up
your mind then well it's it's a bit
difficult to take this complete journey
of coming to Germany seriously alright
then
well welcome everybody like I said
already I'm seeing some some chats some
some comments here so um hi Soham of
people from Kerala alright super nice so
if like because we start our live
session all the time like this just let
me know from its cities you're coming
from and then slowly and slowly we'll
start with the session and also I think
one very important thing for somebody
who might not know it yet we are coming
to India and we are having our meetups
that means you have the opportunity now
to actually vote watch your city in the
poll that we have on the Facebook group
the link I'm going to put in the
description but just to give it give you
guys a bit of an overview how it is
going to be or like what kind of results
are already out so Delhi is again the
most popular one with 59
comes then comes Chennai yeah right
chasing future can you explain about ug
MBBS sorry chasing future not much idea
about that right now so I wanted to just
show you that thing in just a second
the polls are coming up and Delhi has I
think the most the most things that he
has so like that's super nice we don't
have to go too far but then afterwards
we have Kolkata at the second place so
really really curious about it okay
Nikki Avila is German bachelor's degree
worth anything in India well it
essentially isn't other than like the
only thing that's worth in India is the
work experience afterwards if you think
you can get some really crazy jobs in
India after you have done your
bachelor's I don't think that's true
like bachelors Germans are more tailored
towards German industry and not the
Indian one so like that would be really
foolish to think that the German
master's degree is going to be worth a
lot or is going to be actually taken
equivalent to some degree from NID or
something no alright then in just a
second yeah
so this poll is going to be available in
the Facebook group from now on and you
can just directly go and you can pick a
city and you can vote there that is
going to be really nice so that we can
actually start preparing which city we
should go to we are going to most
probably take the first five cities and
that's pretty much it because we don't
have too many holidays and then the my
University will start again and Elena's
where Elena's work will start again so
just like make sure that you actually
vote and then you know we can just have
the meetups properly
alright then with all of those things
out of the way let's slowly and slowly
start with our today's agenda which is
the complete procedure for bachelors in
German
now let's go to the screen to the
presentation screen so again we were
going to start in two minutes already
dead there's another announcement and
this especially only for the people who
are already in Germany so like maybe if
you are studying in a student colleague
or if you are just I don't know doing
some language preparation course here in
Germany this is going to be something
very interesting for you which is the
big mentorship program which has been
launched on the first January so you can
just come you can take a look this is
actually focus towards just the
aspirants so like if you're coming for
bachelor's or master's both can benefit
from it if you're looking if you're just
a bachelor or a master student studying
in Germany so it doesn't matter from
which country you're from you could be
from Middle East you could be from
Bangladesh India Pakistan Sri Lanka
doesn't matter which country you're from
that could be something for you and the
professions in any country what exactly
does it talk about so like in this
mentorship program we are like exploring
more topics regarding productivity how
to make the best out of the Germany like
not out of the Germany make the best out
of Germany because that's essentially
what why you are coming here you know
you are coming here to study to build
your career to do more things afterwards
and if during those three years or
during those two years of masters or
bachelors you aren't really making the
making full out of whatever you're
studying and is going to actually hurt
you afterwards because the opportunity
of studying in the university is
something that not everybody enjoys the
resources that you have at your disposal
at the time when you're studying in a
university these are really insane like
you can if you want to go to a
psychologist you can go there if you
want to talk to a professor you can do
that if you want to get an opinion of
something you're building on your you're
building and you want to take the
opinion of some professor or some kind
of colleague you can do that so all of
that is extremely nice so
entrepreneurship stress management
career development personal development
and motivation public speaking and
personal professional networking so
these are the topics which are going to
be picked up every every week and every
two weeks we are going to have live
session and every two weeks I have these
Diaries where I'm actually documenting
all of the like struggles that somebody
can come across in a week and how you
can go about it right so definitely you
can take a look at that too it is in the
description today's topics are going to
be first of all like the different ways
to do bachelors then second is going to
be the process third is going to be the
documents in that lengths of what exact
documents do you need because till the
time of batches there aren't a lot of
documents that you can present anyway so
it doesn't make sense to go too deep
into that but I think the deadlines part
is more important then there would be
some words of caution something you
should like definitely be very off
because many students fall in these
traps they fall in some kind of really
crazy offered that the consultant made
to them and then afterwards they just
realized that that offer isn't really
true and whatever admit somebody gave to
them it is actually completely false
so those things happen so just you know
be a bit careful about it I'm going to
talk about this a bit too and then
afterwards you can ask your questions so
bachelor's in Germany so the main reason
you know there's so much drama about
doing bachelors in Germany is
essentially because in India we study
for 12 years here you have to study for
13 years like the 13 years the abattoir
actually makes up the the University
Entrance Examination on the basis of
which you can start studying your
batches for us it's the air tripley exam
the je exam and so on so this is like
the major difference this is the thing
which really just creates all of this
stress and organizational chaos so but
again you can like go you can take away
around it in three different parts the
first one is like just directly doing a
student colleague the second one is you
have your one year of bachelors in India
and then you clear your je mains and
then you can apply and study here and
the third one is like if you have
already done your tenth and then you
have done the Diploma then how can you
tackle this thing so first of all if you
talk about student college student
colleague is actually I would say like
one of the simplest thing that you can
do because you have a lot of lot of
options left so if you do your one year
of bachelors in India sorry your your
field is already decided that means you
cannot move from mechanical to chemical
chemical to something else that's
something that you can't do if you do
the student colleague and you just get a
bit used to the German engineering
culture and you see what kind of fields
or studies would actually be interesting
for you this is actually fun because it
also gives you one extra year to just
judge to just judge what kind of field
you would like to study afterwards right
so student colleague is nice in one year
of bachelor's in India you already have
you are already fixed you're already
just stuck in the field in which which
you actually opted for in the starting
clearing JD means it's difficult if I
would clear J means I would like rather
even just study in IIT because I think
for me personally it's very important
that you also get the experience of
studying bachelors in India so that
afterwards you can do your masters here
because the thing is like you learn a
lot of things you learn a lot of things
in your bachelor's and most of the times
it's not just purely theory now when
you're studying a bachelor in India most
of the times you're going to learn how
to just be around people how to
communicate with them how to actually
whenever you have you are having any
kind of differences how do you not fight
and actually still come to a conclusion
or you know like hostel sharing and all
of those things so I personally think
living in India actually gives you a lot
of patience and a lot of tolerance
because as
soon as you are out of your 12th grade
and then you are in your bachelors the
first year it's horrible I know for many
of the students it's really hard to
actually fit in but like really that's
that's the purpose of hostels and that's
the purpose of the first year of
university it's just make it's just
supposed to make you feel uncomfortable
it's supposed to throw you completely
out of the comfort zone till now you
were just at home you were I don't know
getting food from your parents you were
being taught some kind of subjects from
your father or something but as soon as
you're in the university all of that
goes away so the process the process for
shooting colleague it is really simple
you come you first of all like one when
you are in your twelfth you can already
start learning German till b2 so once
you have written your b2 exam then you
will apply to the student colleague so
for example student collect Hamburg now
it shows that the application for the
semester which is starting in January it
is from first August till 30th September
now and then for the another semester I
think it's the spring semester I don't
know why the helps is autumn autumn
semester that is going to be from first
February to 31st March now it's going to
begin in August so like all of these
things are already mentioned so once you
have your b2 it's written here so like
you need your b2 and then you can fill
out the PDF document of the student
colleague and then you have some other
documents to three other documents and
all of that combined you can send to the
student colleague then afterwards
they're going to invite you for your off
number Pugh phone no and yeah you write
the off number proofing and then if you
get accepted you can start studying and
children colleague if you don't get
accepted you can apply to some other one
so after covering one year of your
studies once you are accepted in a
student colleague you can then write the
first alums perform faster looms
proofing is more or less fifty person is
more or less what your universe
University Entrance Examination is for
example in India it was the iit for us
it used to the used to
the AI tripley now it's completely
scrapped it's no longer there so for you
it's IIT and FSP is more or less like
the german iit exam now b2 is
recommended temporary student visa or
it's also the student applicant visa for
three months you can come with that here
and this is an important website which
you can just take a look at because it
will give you most of the information
regarding all of the student colleagues
now and the website isn't too fancy it's
really basic but it does give all of the
information that you need you just go to
the student colleagues that it shows you
the complete list of student colleagues
which is really nice you can contact
them in case you have any kind of
questions and you cannot understand
something from their website so that is
always also an option right so just just
be careful about that then again one
year of bachelor's it's again direct
application to university or unisys then
you also don't need a lot of German
because after first year of bachelors in
India more or less you can apply only in
the English taught programmes here and
also there are lesser number of courses
and IELTS is required
all right then you have the third option
and I think this is the most difficult
one by far if you have done diploma it's
really difficult to get accepted in
bachelors like you definitely can get
accepted but you have to just throw a
lot of shots at different universities
and see which ones stick now and also
you should apply for the universities
where the application can be sent
directly to the University and not to
some like not to the unionist because
unionist isn't recognizing diploma then
also you should like I said like their
lesser number of courses available one
of the few universities that you can
definitely apply to or try to apply as
big and often Duisburg and you also need
aisles for that ok so like these are the
important things and this is the Ling I
think it got cut towards the end but at
junior sis you can find the link
regarding student colleague that is
really nice and more or less every
single all of the information which is
important is condensed into one single
page and then the second one which
actually allows you to see if your
university or if your school essentially
is accepted by uni assists or not so
this is more relevant for the people who
are actually already doing their first
year in na University in India now let's
talk about the processes so the first of
all you know everybody
let me just know in the comments first
of all how many of you are in the 11th
grade and how many of you are in the
12th grade now if once we have that then
we can have a more meaningful
conversation and a more meaningful
presentation afterwards and I can also
like you know focused was answering your
questions then so 11th or 12
I'm going to wait for a few seconds and
see alright Ziggy case is twelfth grade
John Prakash is again asking about some
lor so that's really not the question
I'm asking right now 11th 11th 12th 11th
11th twelve twelve twelve eleven twelve
all right
that's really nice now now I understood
what what exactly is the crowd that I'm
talking to so like it is going to be
better for for me to just tell you
and also Mabel I'm going to make me who
the moderator tool so that you know
whatever thinks that may hole is saying
just also keep an eye for it because may
who actually did his student colleague
here and he is now waiting for the fs
piece so anybody who is having questions
when I'm giving the presentation you can
also address it directly to me all right
now let's start going forward with that
thanks a lot for your responses now
let's let's go forward with the
presentation and then we can take up
your questions afterwards so 12th grade
we have b2
now once you're in there 12th grade you
know you already should have a aim of at
least doing b2 because without b2 you
don't even have the chance to applying
to student colleagues to most of them
now I even look at the one in Hamburg it
clearly says that you need a attested
photocopy of the b2 certificate of
German proficiency so if you don't have
that they are not going to take your
application seriously and this is really
important to understand now then
afterwards once you have once you have
your b2 you have applied to the student
colleague they have invited you for and
look even in the student colleagues
website it says they have mentioned
every single thing steps of the
application so you have to apply for the
VPD then you have to how do you have to
apply at uni assist all of that
information is mentioned then how is the
often number proof I'm going to be and
so on they also have the how do I say
they also have sample documents here
so I'm gangs proof on voyage then you
can see the math scores all of the
sample documents so see test and all of
those things they're always mentioned on
the university's website like the
student colleagues website most of the
times so just keep an eye out for that
as long as you are curious as long as
you can use your eyes you are going to
find information regarding that
so once they have invited you first
often I'm a proof um and you have
written the often armed up your phone
then you can start studying and student
colleague then afterwards comes your
first alums preform and on the basis of
the score and your fashion through phone
and fifty percent of the grades that you
had in your bachelors sorry in your in
your twelfth grade then a final score
will be decided on the basis of it which
you will be a lot at different
universities so again the documents and
deadlines first of all the documents
which are required generally are a copy
of passports data page so like it is
going to the first page and the last
page then the b1 and or b2 quite exam
certificate like I showed you the one in
Hamburg it is asking for B to go at exam
certificate then the twelfth class mark
sheet now that's really self
understanding then VPD from uni assist
if necessary so the one in student
colleague Hamburg they are asking for
the VPD so you can't really do anything
there you have to provide the VPD from
the unisys then we peel if you click
here the Unionists i think yeah the
unionist thing is going to open and then
you can just follow the steps which are
provided on the website and just apply
for the VPD and also it is really
important and I would like really
emphasize it that VPD you can use for
the next one year so it's not like you
apply for VPD right now and you can only
use it in the next intake no you can
also use it for the another two up to
three intakes right so the sooner you
apply for a VPD the better it is like
for bachelors that is pretty much the
key the sooner you apply the sooner you
start organizing thing the sooner you
get in contact with different kind of
student coeliac different kind of
language institutes and
is going to be better for you and you're
not going to waste some kind of like
precious one or two years I don't even
know if that's precious or like if
that's like more or less expendable
because I would really like if you if
you don't like the education system till
twelve don't think that the education
system in the university in India is
going to be much different it is going
to be more chilled out you are going to
be doing a lot more useless things but
if you want to learn and stuff I think
like you know Germany is definitely the
right place the only reason I would
prefer India would be if I yeah if I
wouldn't have to study to be honest like
specially for the universities which are
not IITs or even in NID is it's more or
less the same drama so just be sure of
that and then afterwards you also need
the application form the filled out
application form for the shooting
college or university or uni assist this
is pretty much the documents that you
would typically need if there are some
extra documents that the Union sister
student cool egg or any of these require
then it is going to be mentioned on
their websites but generally this is it
no lor no SOP or something like that if
it has mentioned there then of course
you can apply but if it's not mentioned
and it's not necessary then deadlines
for application for student kulig winter
is going to be like for student coeliac
just specifically shouldn't cool ignore
universities nothing the winter semester
generally starts in January for the
shirin colleagues
the application deadline for them is
first August 30th September then
afterwards the summer semester which is
going to start in August for them the
application deadline or like the portal
opening is going to be from 1st February
to 31st March then universities if
you're applying directly to universities
the winter semester opens up from 1st
June to 15 July and the summer semester
opens up the portal for that opens up
from first summer to 15 January and just
make sure that these are for the German
thought ones and also every single
University every single Institute
in Germany has their own deadlines has
their own application portals
application procedures many a time so
just make sure that you just take a look
there because like there is really no
where no way around it you cannot expect
somebody to hold your hand and actually
like take you through the entire process
because that wouldn't really pay you out
in the end because every single time
whenever you rely on somebody to do the
things for you you will actually be
faced like you will actually face this
issue that the people aren't going to be
as serious about your things as you
would be about your own and like that's
also completely understandable like they
are not gaining anything other than just
money for you for them it is just a
means to get your money to do some kind
of mediocre work to maybe throw you into
some kind of university and that set and
this is the reason I really emphasize
every single time that all of these
procedures even though they look
complicated in the starting if you just
sit down and if you just read them if
you just go through the websites it's
really easy and you don't really need
some third party to actually like you
know take your hand and do everything
with do everything for you
so that is extremely important to
understand because this will actually
save you from any kind of horror stories
I've heard a lot of them in my Facebook
group where there was there was where
there was the scale and he applied to
with some consultant to study in Germany
and afterwards he received some fake
admits that the consultant created
himself he used those fake admits to
apply for visa in the consulate and then
he got banned for life for from ever
going to Germany like that's how
horrible this situation can be so just
like do not trust I don't know whatever
kind they could be the fanciest
consultants and I'm telling you the
fanciest consultants are really the
shittiest ones like they would screw you
over and if you try to talk about them
they are going to give a
legal notice to you and it has happened
to a lot of students happen to me once
when I tried to expose some kind of
consultant and yeah you can't really do
anything then afterwards if without
actually going all-out war and having a
lawyer and like you know going to these
court hearings and all of that so really
like do not fall in their trap let them
earn money from selling their services
to people who are going to USA who are
going to Australia who are going to
Canada and all of that but do not fall
in their trap do the things on your own
now to know yeah to end this up now
because like this is pretty much it this
is like all of the information that you
are going to need to start applying to
student college to start studying here
now I'm going to like close the session
slowly now with some word of words of
caution first of all is you know learn
German till b2 that is extremely
important you cannot you absolutely
cannot deny or ignore the importance of
learning German to be - it is extremely
important the sooner you do it the
better it is going to be now then the
second one is start preparing at least 6
to 12 months in advance 12 is again a
very conservative estimate I would
rather go up to 18 months in advance
student applicant visa for often an
approval is something that you have to
apply for and the checklist for the
documents is pretty much the same for
the national visa for the student
if you are coming for three months then
you can you know get the block to come
for three months if you're coming for
six months you can come for six months
and so on so this is just a really basic
you don't need a lot of documents you
didn't you don't need too much drama and
yeah that is going to be your strengths
applicant visa with which you are coming
to Germany and writing the offer number
perform tourist visa isn't accept it's
like if you if you come to write the
often improve homeland tourist visa the
universities might not accept it and
don't fall into the traps of consultants
they are really really like they are the
scum of the earth I'm telling you like
most of them like even if there might be
some good ones who are actually trying
to help but the others have created such
a bad image such a bad reputation of
anybody else who might be even trying to
do something good so I would say in
general you know just try to do things
on your own
exactly conditional admits can also be
received if you apply on your own and
whenever in doubt you can directly
contact a student colleague University
or the German mission then also whenever
you have any kinds of doubt like I said
whenever you have any kind of questions
any kind of queries you directly come to
the Facebook group Facebook group is
pirate in Germany you just come you
search first of all if there is
something already discussed like that
previously and I'm going to put this up
it up so that you can see so like just
in the search option you can put some
terms and you can see what kind of
options you are getting so for example
if I write here student Kolak now if I
write student colleague here you will
see that there are actually a lot of
different posts which are actually
regarding shoot in college and then you
can just start you can just start
reading them you can just start getting
more and more idea about it now so like
again I can also like made this really
nice post about FAQ from University of
peda bond so this is also something that
you can just go and you can just start
reading because this is how you are
actually doing smart work you are
actually not falling into the traps of
anybody and you are just doing
everything on your own and the field
that you're going to get afterwards once
you have done everything on your own it
is going to be very better you are going
to proudly say hey I did everything on
my own everything worked out I didn't
pay any extra money to anybody else and
now again like you know if you aren't
able to figure it out and then in the
end you have to give monies to some kind
of consultants and it is going to cost a
lot more then of course like that sad
like you can't really do anything about
it but you can and you will be able to
do everything on your own just a few you
know just search for information on the
internet and then you're actually able
to contact these different universities
the German Consulate and so on again so
with the same aim of doing it yourself I
actually created my online course so
that you can do everything on your own
but the information that you need all of
that is combined in one single place
that means you are spending more time in
actually doing things and not wasting
time and organizing different kinds of
information for you so you have lifetime
access to it you have personal mentoring
in the sense that every two weeks we are
having live sessions in the Facebook
group of the big Academy so this is the
one that you have for parrot in Germany
but we have another Facebook group which
is for the students who are enrolled in
the courses so there we are having live
sessions every two weeks which is like
super nice and you can also like be a
part of them if you are enrolled in the
course also this is an exclusive
community of more than one hundred plus
members detailed information regarding
application procedure visa procedure and
after arrival in Germany then like I
said we have bi-weekly live sessions and
you are going to be there in a closed
group in a closed Facebook group with me
so that's pretty much it guys
now with that I'm going to let you ask
your questions we have 30 minutes time
thanks a lot for your audience and for
you who want to enroll in the complete
guide to studying in Germany later on
which
an online course and you will be able to
find it on my website also the link is
in the description for this course you
can just take a look you can go through
the curriculum but I would HIGHLY advise
you if you would like to start doing
things on your own and you don't want to
waste too much time on just organizing
things you can just like go through the
curriculum see what kind of information
that you you will be getting access to
and just come in and roll yourself on my
website all of the details are in the
description yeah select for that the
relevant courses with big white e10
coupon code you are going to get 10% off
on this one and if you're living in some
kind of remote city where you don't have
good language schools near you or if you
prefer actually learning things online
and not waste time in commuting to
someplace and wasting ten or fifteen
minutes on the way or sometimes even 40
minutes some students have to waste so
if you don't want to do that you can
also take the online course from Michael
and with the link which is in the
description you will be getting 10% off
on that course too so again this is just
some kind of information that you have
to you know like that there's no that
there is like what I want to say is like
you can you know do everything on your
own
and that's how most of the students do
now but if you want to save time on
organization then you are having these
kind of courses which would be worth
investing and you would still be doing
everything on your own you would still
be making your own decisions which
course to study which university to
study in but you would be having some
kind of community some kind of
hand-holding experience or that you know
your transition from studying in India
right now to Germany is a bit more
smooth so again that's pretty much it
now let's start slowly with questions
for the students who are already here
like I said not this patreon one but my
mentorship program is already up it
actually helps students to just be a
better version of themselves to do more
things to use more opportunities when
they are in Germany and it is more
focused towards bachelor students in
Germany
master students and fresher experienced
professionals in any country so just
teaches you more to utilize all of the
resources that you have already here in
Germany all right then enough of that
let me start with the questions now the
grant Kumar is asking I enrolled in an
engineering college but then I dropped
out is it going to affect my application
the grant it necessarily isn't going to
affect your application in the sense
that you know as long as you have your
twelfth grade it's completely fine you
would still be able to apply but because
you dropped out it isn't going to be
some kind of negative that hey this kid
dropped out and he isn't worthy enough
of studying in our student colleague
that's really not the case all right
huija did bachelors from distant
distance learning make me eligible for
MBA guru general that doesn't happen if
you want to apply for MBA like first
requirement is that you need to have
three years of work experience and then
you need to have a full-time bachelor's
so I don't think it is going to be
possible that with distance learning
bachelors you are able to apply for MBA
yeah maybe in some like really like not
soon on private Institute's but not in
the like more reputed ones
all right oh my girl is asking is
learning German too between India vice
for clearing off nama proofing as
learning German in Germany is very
different than in India and we have a
serious competition for Alf nama
proofing so I don't believe that at all
like I think like there are students who
think that learning German in Germany is
better or like you know anybody who was
in Germany got taught better German but
I think that's like that's more or less
a losers argument because that's really
not true if that would be the case then
I would be complaining that I never went
to any kind of actual or I have never
really went to any kind of language
institute I learned German on my own all
I had was my books and I learned that
during the last semester of my
bachelor's in India so now again I could
also be complaining that hey you know I
wasn't able to clear the exam or
something like that but that's not
really what happened what happened was I
learned everything on my own and I was
still able to clear the exam afterwards
and it worked out and it worked out
there was a lot more efforts and like I
would I would have actually loved to
just do some less efforts but anyways I
did a lot more efforts and I actually
was able to receive the result that I
wanted and when I came here when I
started studying it wasn't like there
German is different than my German know
like if you learn German in India or if
you learn German in Germany it is going
to be the exact same thing the tests the
B to test the c1 test C to test all of
those tests are standardized that means
it doesn't matter in which country
you're taking the tests in the if you
have cleared one test or if you have
cleared one level that means you are
basically at that level there is no
comparison or no difference that hey
this is different this is different
level because he studied in India and
this is a better level because he
studied in Germany that's really not the
case all right
obeyed Khan is asking how to increase
visa days if you fail in Alphen am
approval I think may will can respond to
that
because I don't think you can if you
fail in the off nama proofing and like
you can definitely try like me who had a
lot of experience with that he had been
like bugging the foreigners office more
or less to actually ask like even if you
fail like how it is possible to you know
just get things extended and more or
less you can try you can try doing that
and if it doesn't work out then again
you don't have a choice you have to go
back and you have to apply again so
genius Joyner is asking can I start to
learn German now and complete be one
before often improving tests how long
will it take to complete b1 if I
enrolled in language schools this summer
I am studying in 12th now so genius
owner the the main important or like the
main question that you should be asking
is how much time would it take in the
sense that not months but how many like
ours per day are you going to study to
be able to reach b1 or b2 in specific
months so I would rather say if you want
to aim for b1 for b1 I would say for 3
months if you're studying everything on
your own from 5 to 8 hours every single
day it is going to be sufficient and
when you study like you know more
effectively because it was sufficient
for me yeah it would be sufficient 3
months 5 to 8 hours every single day
that you would be actually having the
level b1 afterwards so I don't know if
really like enrolling yourself in the
language schools would really help
because you are having classes on the
side all the time anyways so I don't
think it would bring too much right so
you can also try some online courses
like I said so I don't think May will
respond to that question yeah I think
mail is away now but most of the times
like when you fail in the off number
form you can always go alright so Meola
is actually written the best thing to do
would be to enroll yourself to language
school for a six month course at least
before you apply for a visa then you can
right off nominal proofing during the
course all right that that's also
interesting you can also try doing that
and also if anybody has any questions
like I said you can just directly come
to the main Facebook group and you can
just yeah just like post your questions
there and this is my page this is the
main one I'll be sure my Indian students
are just in poor condition yeah you
can't really do anything about it right
I mean the government isn't really
thinking about the students at all it
isn't thinking about the youth it isn't
talking about the youth so what is
pretty much the point it's really
absolutely nothing I've been a being
assured of so they've talked we're
saying explain VPD so VPD is more like a
preliminary documentation of your
profile that the Union SS does on the on
behalf of the universities so first of
all you have all of your documents you
give it to uni assess uni assess is
going to make one single paper which is
going to be with the VPD and which will
say that this is the score this is the
equivalent score of this candidate in
the German terms so I like in the German
system right so on the basis of that
like with the VPD and with the other
documents like I actually showed you
here with the other documents just a
second like you have the VPD you have
your passport copy you have the b2
certificate German exam you have another
passport photograph and so on with all
of those things you can just directly
apply now select this is something very
important
VPD if asked by the university or by the
student colleague you don't really have
a alternative here you have to apply for
the VPD and VPD you can apply from uni
assist that's pretty simple even if you
like just go to Google and you're type
junior student colleague you are going
to find a completely detailed web page
risk which is going to tell you every
single thing about
studying student collect caramelizing
FSP from one as children colleague
allows you to get into any university ya
care of that's the situation if you
write the FSB from any student colleague
you can study in any university that's
you don't have to write FSB every single
time for different universities SK 23
can we sit in the off nama proofing
without doing student colleague just
with a German language of p2 so SK 23
you know for for this question it is
better that you actually see what the
labels of the testers right now if you
go to the I I'm Gong spoofing you have
the German and you have maths so it is
actually really important for you to
just study both of them really like
properly and then write the exam and if
you don't have p1 then I don't think
you're going to be able to attempt the
German part anyways because it is it is
a bit advanced it is more of the level
from b1 to b2 and not of the level b1
you know so like just take take care of
that you need you will absolutely need
good maths and you're going to need good
German because that is the slavers of
the off nama perform she vanishing and
how much is required in class 12 prods
both so as to get into you Munich CS
branch so she want that's not the right
question the right question would be
what is the equivalent German grade that
you need to get into the CS branch in
the German universities and that is very
easily like in the abattoir like in the
how do I say in the university entrance
exam you need around 1 comma 7 or above
to get into any good university in good
branches every single time there are
universities which have a numerous
clauses that means they have some kind
of cut off that last time this was the
grade of the last student who was
admitted in
into our program and generally it stays
more or less there like it could be
somewhere there could be some variations
but they are not that much and you can
just check the numerous clauses of
different universities to get
information regarding if your grades are
good enough because your 12th grade is
going to account for 50% of the marks
and your grades in the FSB is going to
account for 50% of the marks to make the
final score with which you can apply to
the universities higher than Germany
bachelors from a LMU yeah I mean sure if
you can if you can get alum you'll
definitely it's it's a really really
nice University you know I wouldn't
complain if I get an admit there Germany
has lots lost its charm okay how I mean
most of the people I see here are doing
completely fine please tell more about
accommodation in Germany when we get
enrolled in student collect yeah you can
get to in cooler student hostel given by
University so junior started most of the
times when when you're like studying
student colleague and if it's a private
student colleague it is possible that
they gave you some kind of accommodation
for the first month or the first few
weeks but then afterwards you have to
search it on your own like there's
really no going around there and and
here's a funny part you know like I
think many people are also like not
really how should I put it
how should I put it like some people
aren't really made to like do these
independent things on their own like
they just aren't made it many people
that come here they think hey things
that things are going to be fun but but
then afterwards when they have to look
for a apartment they have to find a job
they have to actually pay the rent and
stuff
they really lose this yeah almost the
paradise filter that they have for
Germany that everything is perfectly
fine everything is really nice but just
because they lost that filter
mean that the situation's situations
actually changed here now it's still the
same thing it's still the same people
the same environment the same strong
economy and if you can complain about
things here man like you must be having
millions of things to complain about in
India and that is also pretty much why I
promote it so often why I'm like
absolutely pushing for students that
they come to Germany that they study
here because I have been to India I have
been through the process I have studied
my bachelor's here and I have seen what
kind of job situation is afterwards and
it isn't nice trust me it isn't it isn't
nice if after spending four years of
your life in bachelor's and some kind of
government university or in some kind of
private Institute and if some company is
offering just seven thousand rupees 5000
rupees sometimes fifteen thousand rupees
what is it like you cannot even live off
of it no so I just don't like I don't I
just don't understand the people who
think that who still complain when they
have come here for bachelor's because
man trust me things in India are very
worse and I have actually left them I
have actually experienced experienced
them firsthand so I completely know the
difference and this is the reason I
promote Germany so much
siobhan single house the climate change
in Germany I never understood this she
wants what do you exactly mean by that
because like if you're talking about the
change in season and the weather yeah I
mean it is extremely crazy it is just
absolutely insane right now it's it's
5:00 it's already dark in summers it
could be 11 o'clock or 11:30 and it
would still be light outside and just
just for a comparison you know once once
we are having more and more live
sessions like maybe five or six live
sessions afterwards you could already
see the difference
but at least can you pick my question
the Washburn who shall he is asking
please tell me how to apply through hawk
Schuler de I have five courses
distinguished but unable to proceed
please so they were like hawk Schuler
dot de I have I have never really set
myself with this particular thing but
you know I'm just going to read more
about it you can send me an email
regarding this thing if you're like
facing some really particular thing but
most of the times you are able to get an
answer from the people themselves like
from the website where you applying for
this generally like I use dot for short
listing the universities and afterwards
you can use junior sis to apply for them
and that's that's that flame scape
should i do bachelors from Canada or
Germany alright so we have two
interesting questions you're all ready
why you said next year is your last meet
up in India the evil is asking so I
think more or less I'm we are thinking
about about it more from like the
security standpoint like yet the more
people you know the worst it gets like
in terms of what kind of people actually
come to the meetup so like we don't
really want to risk it especially when I
have a Luna with me I've seen people
having police and stuff in the meter and
I also don't want to do that like it's
useless I'm just here to like connect
with you and stuff and right now it's
still fine one hundred thousand but most
of the times out of those hundred
thousand you know a lot of them are
already in Germany they already like
make the transition and then some
students they are still in India you can
all again like go they are the number of
students who are coming to Germany
doesn't change that dramatically but the
number of students who are interested in
studying in Germany is changing really
fast so again I think like that's why
next year is going to be the only time
when we are able to do the Meetup
because of just like financial reasons
and all of that yeah
so that's unfortunately that the case
and we are going to see like once the
voting stops then we are going to see
like what kind of cities we can visit
because last time it was horrible it was
like absolutely unbearable to just go to
so many different cities and you know
every single night
I remember the the first time when I
gave the meetup like when I had when I
gave the presentation in Mumbai I didn't
sleep for the last 72 hours and I was
like still I gave the presentation and
then I was still speaking for the next
four or five hours directly talking to
students then I was completely exhausted
and at the same night we didn't sleep
again because we had to go to Goa
yeah so the flight was at 2 o'clock so
again like Dawn's we didn't sleep the
whole time it was just like really bad
this time hopefully we will make the
planning a bit better maybe we are going
to stay more than one day every single
city and in ever in in each of the
cities but we'll just see we'll just see
how it works
flames Cape is asking should I do
bachelors from Canada or in Germany
flames Cape I'm never going to recommend
Canada my brother is doing his
bachelor's from Canada and I just see
how the situation is like you don't you
don't find a job if you don't have good
references you can forget about the
merit it's like the the next level of
the reservation system that we have in
India
it's absolutely horseshit anyways
whatever we see in India like you a lot
a specific number of seats to some kind
of category that's not the case in
Canada but there if you don't have
references it's hard to find a job which
is like really useless I don't really
like this thing so you know never I
would never recommend Canada even I'm
telling my younger brother to like move
to Germany because of the way his job is
getting paid per hour even him even when
he's working
and an accounting company it's just
useless really not worth it
anyways like the people who are actually
now joining in like some of them are
also talking about doing student
colleague here you know like for the
students who are already here you can
come at patreon and you can like just
check out this mentorship program it is
going to be definitely very interesting
for you you can just see what kind of
things you need help with because a lot
of people never really try to change any
of that
they never really try to I don't know
have their own blogs take the initiative
of just do presentations and stuff and
never really develop their personality
all of those things are going to be
something very useful and something that
we are going to constantly work on in
this particular program so just take a
look at that you can definitely check it
out and the students who are like just
purely entrusted and only studying in
Germany like I said you can take the
take a look at the curriculum here in
the course that I was talking about the
complete guide to studying in Germany or
at the Michael's core so both of these
courses are going to be definitely
really important for you alright then
with that out of the way we have the
last six minutes left for the live
session and Sai Kumar is saying should
we pay eight thousand euros every year
so site that eight thousand euros is the
blocked blocked account amount that you
have to show like there is no going
around it so yeah I mean you will have
to pay eight thousand euros per year but
it really depends on how much money you
are spending so from the blocked account
you get the seven hundred twenty euros
to you but then it's up to you if you
want to burn all of those eight hundred
twenty euros or if you want to save
something if you would be a person like
me you would like definitely like love
to spend your money smartly and not just
waste everything so if I would be in
that scenario I might even like still
save up to like two thousand euros or
two thousand five hundred euros from
that eight thousand euros that I have
to pay in Germany um Agarwal is asking
all right so motive behind 2008 in the
situation of visa was very bad it is
likely to get worse how do we tackle
this as we get our twelfth results in
June and it's already late so if you're
talking about like you know if you get
your twelfth results in June that means
if you if we take the example of the
student colleague of Hamburg now for
Hamburg you look at the baby boom and it
is from first August and 30th September
so you will have time till 30th
September to actually apply to the
student colleague but with the help of
the VPD that means you need also another
extra 19 tell you know twenty-five days
twenty five working days for the VPD
part which will be a process by the
unisys no that means as soon as you get
your results in June and you get your
degree certificate degree and stuff
maybe till July you already apply in
July it will take one month for unions
to give your VPD and once you have the
VPD with all of these other documents
you can together directly apply to the
student colleague in hamburg or whatever
student collegue want to apply to so
till 30th september you will have the
time so like don't worry too much about
this one you can definitely like you
will definitely be able to apply and
once they once you have applied then
they give you the decision when the off
number proofing is happening and then
you can apply for the visa visa
interview but in general you know even
if you want to like take a wild guess of
what date or what kind of month I should
apply for the visa interview then it
should generally be like around I think
October so once you apply for October
the thing is going to start in January
and you have to two months which is
completely fine like one month or
something is perfectly fine Sooni and is
it mandatory to study the German for
time job may Hula's saying and nope
but it's recommended and that's also
true it's not necessary to know German
to do a part-time job there like a lot
of jobs you can still do without knowing
a lot of German but if you are able to
learn German and it's definitely going
to be very better for you because you
are going to get better jobs you are
going to have better chances even in
like just normal feels like gastronomy
and stuff know obey it con how much
percentage in 12th grade is required to
get admission in student college so it's
really different most of the times they
always recommend you to get more than
65% that you're up so that you are able
to apply in the shooting colleague so
that is something you should definitely
aim for and I don't think 65% is too
less so Aditya is asking value of an
Android or iOS developer in Germany my
friend here was getting paid rupees 8000
for working straight and ours as an
Android developer recently he moved to
us working for it 4,800 per month man
this is absolutely crazy like what I
have seen here like for full-stack
developers or like even for app
developers the really general like the
minimum salary that you get is like five
thousand euros per month which is a lot
now like eight thousand euros and you
compare it with five thousand euros per
month in Germany
you already see the huge difference and
like this is the reason you know like
like I said all the time this is the
only reason I want to make the goal of
my life to bring as many students as I
can to actually come to Germany like to
come to Germany and to start studying
here because the situation is just bad
in India like it's just a tragedy it's
just a huge human tragedy the way India
has been handling things and it is
likely most likely not going to change
in the future
so every single body you know like
whoever is coming for bashes whatsoever
is happening
you can definitely come to the Facebook
group at least come to the Facebook
group start connecting with each other
because we also have other Facebook
groups like bachelors in Germany and
blah blah blah but nobody is really
active there and this is the reason I am
saying it is better that you come to the
main one and then you can start
researching you can start posting your
questions and stuff and you can interact
with other people you know the complaint
that I have from the students who are
actually already studying their
bachelors here is nobody really comes
down to interact like their part is done
and then they're never going to touch
they're never going to take care of like
answering other people's questions and
like may whole is at least somebody who
is in the live chat right now and he is
like really trying to yeah and he's
really trying to answer most of these
questions you know and like I have a
just wish I would wish more of these
students more of the students who are
actually studying or who are coming for
bachelors here to like respond like that
so that people are actually you know
their their experience of this
transition from India to Germany is
easier or like it's better because I
understand I I know that most of the
times you completely forget how you used
to feel how desperate you used to feel
to actually come to Germany when you
were in India and as soon as you're here
you just you just completely forget all
of that so that's something that is sad
and I hope more students from bachelors
who are studying bachelors here are
actually coming in the group and like
sharing their experiences this is going
to be then a bit more healthy
environment there but for now again it's
time to end the live session now anybody
who is entrusted in joining us on
patreon well we have some really cool
things coming up this Sunday we are
having this bi-weekly diary where I'm
going to talk about the struggles that
I've faced during this week and what and
how you can do too and what you can do
to overcome that because this is just
something that you have to be in the
right mindset so that you can take
inspiration from other people and
sometimes if you are in the same problem
like I was and you can you
for yourself and then we have these
different kind of life sessions we have
guidance programs and all of that just
take a look at that and for the people
who are just absolutely focused or who
want to just find something for studying
in Germany you have these two courses so
with that out of the way
thanks a lot for joining me in the life
sessions it was a pleasure to talk to
you and I'll catch you up in the next
live session the ask your questions 29
which is going to be more focused
towards the students who are actually
already studying in Germany and just
telling them about how they can make the
most out of their bachelors or their
masters alright then guys thanks a lot
for joining in everybody have a great
night see you again next week the same
time bye-bye