hey what's up guys welcome to video 0 of
my JavaScript series in these series in
this series of videos I'm going to
explain basic JavaScript and complete
some of the algorithm challenges at free
code camp dot-com I think the videos are
going to be a lot better than following
along with me in my presentations at the
meetups on Sundays
the advantage of video is you can pause
it you can rewind and re-watch certain
sections and there's also going to be a
github repository
so you can just watch the video
you know first to get familiar with the
concepts and then you can copy and paste
my code or write it out for yourself
anyway there's just so many advantages
and I hope you liked it so in this very
first video this is a super basic and
beginner that's why I'm calling it video
number 0 I'm going to explain what
functions are and this is the basic
syntax so what I have open right now
I've got my Google Chrome browser and
I'm gonna write everything in the atom
editor I'm gonna have two files I have
my JavaScript file which is where we'll
be doing all of the programming today
and I've got a simple HTML file it's
really basic it has a couple of headers
and on line 11 this is where I embed my
JavaScript files and in I'm just going
to use the same HTML file for all of the
lessons and I'll just change the file
name right here for each lesson and you
can do that too
so if you open this example dot HTML
file in your browser you're going to see
this nothing to see here
open your console in the dev tools so to
open that you go up here ok to view
they'll choose developer and open
javascript console all right and
everything that we work with we're gonna
you know work with it right here in the
JavaScript console okay so let's just
jump right into it a function is written
starting with the function keyword and
then we're going to give it a name so
I'm gonna call it say say greeting
that's the name of her function I'm
gonna give it a pair of parentheses and
then I'm gonna show it some curly braces
and right here is where we write the
code by the way these two slashes this
signifies a comment and the JavaScript
interpreter will not read this it's just
gonna skip over it it's it's only for
humans to to read and not for the
computer so we start our function with
this code and it's not going to do
anything until we tell it to you know
turn on and we call that invoking the
function or calling the function and
basically we just write the name of the
function with parentheses and then end
it with a semicolon if we save that and
go to our web page alright we refresh
the page and nothing's happening because
our function isn't doing anything all
right but let's make it do something now
I'm going to write a message to the
console okay and if you remember the
console is just this window right here
and it's not actually going to appear on
the webpage
so let's write something to the console
we write console log and then I'm gonna
pass in a string hello free code camp
and I'm gonna end that line with the
semicolon now I'll save the file I'll go
back to my browser and refresh and there
we go
we've just written our first function
so just to recap we've written the
function and it only does one thing it
locks out this string this message to
the console and it's not gonna do
anything okay if I comment that out it's
not gonna do anything until I call it so
I've commented that out but here I'm
calling it and if i refresh okay now we
get it
so that is basically what what a
function does and I can also pass it a
number of different arguments so let's
give it an argument
let's call let's say hello okay
and now instead of writing a string I'm
just going to write in this placeholder
so I'm calling this a greeting function
and I'm passing in an argument this
argument is called greeting and when I
called the function here on line five
this string gets passed to this greeting
placeholder and now we're logging out a
greeting so if I save go back and
refresh okay I see that now and and I
can actually do something like this I
can use addition with strings to join
several strings together I save that if
I go back refresh there we go that's
pretty cool and I can call this function
many different times so say greeting
let's use Spanish hola and let's call it
one more time let's use the German hello
all right let's call it one more time
and we'll make it say Korean so on dumb
alright gonna save and go back to my
browser refresh well that's pretty cool
so we have hello free code camp
hola free code cap lo free code camp on
young free code camp all right
so our function is pretty basic it's
only doing one thing it's logging out a
simple message to the console and that's
it it's not returning any values and
when you normally write functions they
normally return a value when you do the
algorithm challenges at free code camp
they have to return values or they won't
work so let's do a completely different
function let's call it function add two
numbers all right I'm gonna give it two
arguments a comma B so if we have
multiple arguments for a function we
just separated with a comma very simple
we need the curly braces alright and I'm
gonna say a plus B comma and two numbers
let's add five and three yeah let's save
this okay and we get nothing right well
let's let's save this in a variable or
some so now we've got the variable it's
equal to the value of this function and
let's log out the variable console dot
log some I'm gonna save that refresh it
wait a second undefined ah we have an
error okay the reason why we're getting
undefined is because we did not include
a return statement in our code okay so
all we have to do is use the return
keyword and now our code should work
oops
let's try this again
okay now we get the number 8 5 plus 3
equals 8 so our function is working just
okay all right so the reason why I got
an undefined okay
undefined is when variables have no
value so I got undefined because I
declared a variable sum and I logged the
value of the variable sum right here but
because my function didn't have a return
statement my variable didn't have any
value and so the console showed
undefined just get out of that stuff
right here okay so if I go back to my
editor and save that do it again all
right I'm gonna get done defined and
most good editors Adam it does it's
gonna give you an error it's gonna say
something like this all right we just
need a return statement so the return
statement it it gives a value right here
and this is a variable assignment so now
sum is equal to a plus B or 5 plus 3 in
this case alright so if we save that go
back to the browser now it works one
more important thing to note everything
after a return statement will not
execute so if I write a console dot log
ok this will run I'm going to do another
one and after the return statement this
will not run
okay so what do you think will happen
when we save this and refresh the
browser what do you think you will see
how many lines will be in our consoles
well let's take a look so I saved the
file I'm gonna go back to the browser
okay I only got two lines I got this
will run and the number eight but wait a
second
why didn't this get printed well
remember what I said just a moment ago
everything after a return statement will
not get run the function immediately
stops and it returns a plus B here and
it gets assigned to some so when the
JavaScript interpreter runs this code it
says okay function function function all
right here's a variable let's make the
variable let's assign it a value the
value will be the function with these
arguments so we call the function we
pass in 5 for a and 3 for B we're gonna
print this to the console and we're
gonna return these values returned a + 3
8 plus B or 5 + 3 and that's 8 so sum is
now equal to 8 and we print the value of
this variable right here so that's why
in our console over here we get this
will run and the number 8 okay so that's
all that I want to show you for this
video it's very basic and all of your
JavaScript functions and algorithms and
free code camp are going to use a return
statement okay there's going to be a
github repository I'll put the link in
the comments for this video so go ahead
you can fork that and then clone it to
your local machine and that's it for the
first video for the next video and video
1 I'm gonna teach you how to
versus stirring using javascript and
that is actually the very first
algorithm algorithm challenge at free
code camp I want you to try it on your
own first before looking at my solution
only after you've tried and you've
gotten stuck so many times or only after
you've successfully completed the some
of the challenge yourself should you
watch my video but but if you're stuck
or if you've already completed it and
you want to see the way I've written it
then by all means please watch the next
video okay hope you enjoyed this and
I'll see you in the next video goodbye
I gotta stop it gotta stop it there we
go