[Music]
good morning today we are doing
something very very exciting very fun
from what we've seen online other people
doing that it looks insane yes very
excited we have nice and early picks up
at 5 o'clock this morning I had a bit of
a nap in the car up all the way here ok
no quarter to 8 it's a bit like that's
fine the Sun's up we need to wake up a
lil bit more just male tour guide are
about to go so we need helmets and we
need a quick fuse
really like rubbish rubbish a ah really
yeah I just say to you I cannot find any
of these she wrote for him nothing I'll
stick with these I think these are the
best they found some actually fits
improvised one row-wise another made out
of genius we put the camera away now
that it's about to get very wet we're
taking the GoPro and we'll see you at
first jump is three meters
highest one is twelve just about made it
down here which is a very very steep
part and kind of abseiling down
backwards
[Music]
the highest one
the trick to getting around to this
place but it's all one of my fun things
I've done my phony wallet
probably one of the most adventurous
outside
if
all right going back crippling tomorrow
okay
[Music]
demonstration are here - anything like
that ever hurt me we cannot go from here
how high is this 18 pain
[Music]
big slice we're out it's like a
Wednesday I don't even dance
yes believer this is kind of like this
is amazing we've got great tour guide as
well
[Music]
Wow
go down right on top my name's Larry
then you come up
that they'll be going into location
all top
[Music]
the ocean
a lot slower like real fast and then
when you want it this way
Neverending a adrenaline yeah rush this
day
[Music]
yeah
that's why it's my phone
ladies
lunch is served I am so ready for this
we need it and got a knife through the
waterfall over there it's no crazier
were like umbrellas and stuff they
really made this into like a tourist
spot but the bits we were utterly
everywhere really secluded didn't there
yeah yeah it's funny you jump off the
last waterfall which by the way if we
spoke about this and I know but you were
filling a shop at the time like I was in
shock as you quite heard the impacts the
croissants in her they Swiss applies
like painful in your head there's so
worth it like yeah I never thought I'd
do that when you look back on this so so
high so we're now on a bamboo raft I've
never been on one of these before
seems pretty sturdy
[Music]
you can have to do
[Applause]
[Music]
what we've made it to the top views are
great even though it's a bit foggy Wow
sitting on this little ledge here it's
the highest point in Cebu which is crazy
it's been a full day of adventures for
us it's cloudy I hope you can see down
there the kind of view Lucy's gonna sit
there we're gonna get an Instagram photo
ah this is a man Wow and this is I
actually prefer it at this fault because
there's like clouds just coming past me
and over me and I'm literally the
highest person in spoo right now which
is crazy we have to thank Highland
adventures for today they've they
arranged the whole day for us they saw
at this hour so thank you if you're
visiting Cebu then definitely definitely
booked at all with them canyoneering was
amazing there's a link in the
description this video you can check out
their website see or else they offer but
this is insane
[Music]
so we're at Haley sticks that are trying
to help us down this hill as it's very
steep and the rocks are very loose and
this guy's in flip-flops I think he's
done it a few times you all have got a
technically stick really call it the
magician go and do it hold it
so she called the wizard the wizard
thank you my friends back
honestly followed us halfway up then
gave up the upset that have you ever
seen the top maybe there's a dog up
there they probably won't want to go up
there yep it's happening joy does one
you could choose here and this is just
slipping all the way down so we've had
to have some special assistance
[Music]
[Applause]