[Music]
good morning guys welcome to another day
eg we construct some laundry off and is
that time there we already again
you're kidding so you can make all tank
now island
sure maybe have a 30-minute Drive
formalities and it and it looked very
nice it's salivate this is nationalist
really
see today we're gonna go to a motorbike
rental place now and I was like so we've
been thinking we've done quite a lot
recently and we've been tinkering on our
own the next few days so we're gonna try
and get up like two maybe three days see
how that goes and
find somewhere called alona beach which
is
bent upon on the eye
[Music]
we also can't quite believe that it's
mid-november and we're walking around
here in 30 degree heat usually by now at
home we'd be in scarves jumpers winter
jackets it's Lucy's birthday in five
days or four days
very soon anyway three days and it's
going to be so cool to spend a birthday
in a hot country celebrate in the Sun
yes you recognize us yeah yeah so this
guy who again the motorcycle has seen
our videos which is crazy he's gonna
sort us out now or get some helmets on
safety first guys and our bike it's just
how they are waiting for us
so we're with Allen Allen Allen
recognized us from our videos he thought
we looked familiar and and here we are
it's gonna sort us out with a motor by
today no problem at all what's our
pleasure thanks for having us this looks
good
[Music]
and thirty minutes later we're here very
nice drivers net night scenery along the
way they look amazing
there's loads and loads of boats and
this is quite busy as notoriously the
most work I've seen in a very long time
that's nice atmosphere like relaxed vibe
some dive shops and restaurants this is
called a Luna Beach Ilona got 100 alona
beach hopefully we won't be loners on
this Beach because there's loads of
people these don't fit in there so it's
melting like leave them on top this
place is lasers and stuff is like tide
staffs Angie's Filipino soft noodles
loads up the main makes me came here
though is the coop it's got a lovely
view
a lot of places have a little bit but
this one you can sit right be and if
you're coming to where are we we've been
to so many places pango island yeah I
know I need to sort my house
oh my god it's long enough to tie here
now that
lassic if you are coming here we were
hundred-percent already we've just got
it today but punch them recommend
getting a motorbike go see our mate Alan
when we were looking at taxis and stuff
and booking tours and things from our
hotel it's quite pricey compared to say
Thailand and even like El Nido and stuff
it was going to be 3,000 pesos for a
guide to take us around kind of the main
stuff which isn't bad a whole day yeah
exactly entry on everywhere is on top
there so for 400 a day which is what our
motorbike costs you can get you can get
around yourself and it's lovely the
drive here was so so nice we're going
quite fast you go along the coastline
really nice wide open roads palm trees
wind in your hair
sunshine is lovely so that's literally
just over five pounds a day and we can
feel cheap there anyway and we've been
discovered explore because we're we're
saying tricycles don't like to go past
that often so we have to like walk into
like the town bear the lakes you better
hop on a bike and just go everyone it's
so much more mind is that banana shakes
and arrived
so good got mango green mango lovely
pile and vibes dispersed amazing loads
of peanuts which we not got prize I know
you ignore the chips that's just the
English people who are here before us
gone for a nice piece of crispy chicken
with some egg fried rice which I'm going
to squeeze some of this and this is the
one hand on the chicken I think it's
like a lemony lion type thing calamansi
[Music]
this managed to take some good Instagram
photos on top of the rock over there as
a little viewpoint I didn't know about
if you've come all the way to the end of
the beach and then got some little steps
it's not secret for you point that we
discovered we're gonna go for a swim in
just a second but we want to find the
best spot all those speeches it's busy
but it's calm isn't it it's quiet it's
not like partyish or anything lovely
really nice stretch basin as long as
well loads of bars and restaurants are
kind of place a little bit like port
barton actually tiny back as loads
people selling stuff on here as well
like home homemade crafty things more so
than the ocean bags and stuff I think
there's only one or two Island tours you
can book from here
I want a coconut
I want a coconut can we get coconuts why
do I want one I don't know I saw someone
with them and now I want one can you get
one for me
[Music]
okay so we just left the beach got on
the moped got about one minute down the
road literally and the heavens opened
the rain came crashing down it was kind
of spitting when we left we were like be
right we can hold off by the time we get
home no one minute in lashed down so we
pulled over the side road we've hopped
in air for a little Coke Zero seems to
be the cheapest ring my dear I think
it's just started to stop so we're going
to hit the road again and get back we'll
see you back with hotel back in the
hotel now guys we've got TV in this
hotel room which is good news because
whilst we work and doing emails stuff we
love having something on in the
background I don't know what it is we
both we both kind of need it it's like I
don't know how do you work do you need
to work in like a silent room or with
music or with the podcast
yeah I'm not distracted I just need it
in the background for some reason a
little movement I hate a room with no
windows doesn't have window but that's
why I'm glad it's got a TV I hate a room
with no windows or like natural light
and I can't work just in silence with
nothing going on anyway we made it back
we've got out the rain you made it back
guy who's lending us a motorbike is a
guy called Alan at what's it called go
man something yes
Gomes motorcycle rentals and the guy in
the blog earlier who recognized us from
YouTube on Suarez Street if you visit in
the area whilst we were out he text us
and he said guys I've got a faster newer
better more modern motorbike for you
guys if you want to come back and swap
it's got a full tank gas and I won't try
to do any extra so we were like yes
we'll get on that yes announcer these
will show you in the morning we've got
it for why we've had it for four days in
total so we've got it for three more
days so it means we're gonna be able to
explore the whole of the bottle
everything we want to do we've been
planning I'm just transferring all the
clips over from today and the photos we
took and stuff this is the kind of admin
side that we don't usually show you in
the blog and also some bad news
yeah some really really bad news Lucy
burned herself basically when we were
swapping over motorbikes when Lucy got
off she brushed her leg and
the exhaust pipe wasn't that I was like
chatting away and I kinda lost balance
this is a bed with a towel on a head by
the way can I live lucky all right
you're gonna have to look at me but
listen to Lucy why I move up I'm sorry
I'm gonna show you the burn in a minute
okay
and I basically let Neal and Alex was
talking and then I took a step back just
as you do like moving around as you talk
yeah and then I set that exhaust yeah
bike which is wheeling Hall it's really
getting hot from like a 35-minute drive
back and I like leant my leg on it and
so I don't know it's kind of didn't
react just kind of got on a bike and
left until I got home and I was like
okay it's still actually throws like
come on it's burning so bad so you had
to like get some I hate your husband I
went up to the bar upstairs and I was
like my government's burnt herself on
really badly on a motorbike can I please
have a cup of ice do you have any ice
and they were like yes we do have ice
but there is a charge was like I mean we
needed it's always he was gonna pay they
could have charged me like 20 quid I
would have had to pay it could we need
their ten pesos nothing's like penny so
we get the ice and we put it on but it
still hasn't really helped does it can
we show the blog yeah it's quite yes
quite red calling off you can't let that
yeah just a bit late sorry it looks like
I've been leaning on Taylor my way
just here yeah it's in the shape of
something that I leant on alright guys
hopefully her burn will heal nicely in
the next couple of days we have we're so
excited to explore more of this island
we've got loads of cool stuff plan okay
can I get a sneak preview of what we
might go and see we've changed up
desktop background to it on our computer
have a look at this hopefully gonna go
and see some of these guys in real life
fingers crossed so keep watching the box
guys were in the Philippines for a lot
longer if you're new to the channel we
upload every single day so please
subscribe for daily videos and we will
see you very very soon roller
outro music if it's not already playing
see see nice
[Music]