[Music]
hey guys welcome to another Tuesday film
now today we are doing something that
has been recommended to us by you guys
we are trying things you might not
really be video the other day it enjoyed
that so this is another kind of I guess
it's like fast food here in the
Philippines but it seems quite different
Lucy's gone to order a load of stuff now
and we're going to try it I have no idea
what to expect
then I've trust her to order again I did
this enjoyment she came back with
spaghetti and hot dogs and we'll see
what we get
[Music]
and I got to run outside but Iranian
snakes and every no hours or days
therefore one of the things has a
ten-minute wait I have to 15 so we have
a break now
honey
it was 3 5 X 18 356 pacer
Wow that's about five pounds in females
females and links with the nose can you
really bring you get loads in size 5 9 6
- out
and the cervix means HSN
that no offense
it was one thing I said oh let's go face
but I think that's my baby
so we're a little bit quite annoyed
because those are in crisis a very big
being very popular
ridic
but inside
like trains with it
about the pages like in Titanic
I think you will believe your hands a
mere electric baby
these people walking past before tonight
why do you see a knife
really good
that's a mess get rid of them oh you
smog over to the paper
let me try some of the school it is a
place to I'd not meet at that
I really like that
big fan of that that's really good right
this looks really nice I'm guessing this
is like soy sauce go for it okay so
these are like dumplings yet
Wow tastes kinda like the sausage grow
that's really good that tastes like
sausage rolls but nicer who goes with
the soy sauce
Wow I could eat about 50 of these
genuinely you need capillaries so
there's a pork right or feet
Ronen looks like beef
Wow
guys really really flavored
fried rice though below
favor
yeah
we talk back
how good
we'll be rich
so the recipe is like different textures
yeah I think so
so next up we have a combo meal I'm
gonna try and guess what this is because
either I didn't order it
obviously rice guessing this is pork
noodles
I should say by reason to my order I'm
really hoping these are kicking balls
are then off
okay that is like a set to me barn or
something
oh it's really shocking maybe I think
there's these little like practice where
there's like a little spat at the ranch
just filling them there may be as much
Louis Mackey cabinet phone
okay get involved
these claimants really be like
average
I get to not having this that you're
coming all this out the admits the
universe company with 10 Paragon
okay I really want to know what this is
Oh
those eyes they scare me to death
like white lips please delicious
focus on that
the inside is
I've no idea what that is it's on the
comment each tell us what it is it's
really sweet take up the doughnut or a
dessert or something
cinamon wrong
you get where they were like
to customers to ring bells I was like
five minutes but I've stopped ringing
the bells now and we ever with our third
one and we now know how to even the bell
ringing stop ringing your bell so we got
the ice cream the jelly this looks like
banana this time that's new for us and I
don't know what this stuff is
and some ice involved we now know that
you need to mix it so
that seems very slow but apparently it
makes it less messy it use two spoons
they get in the way because a free onion
thank you give this guy
that's really nice very cold
if you've got sensitive teeth I would
not recommend one of these strangely
this looks worse than the other ones
we've had the taste wise I think is the
best one the last one we had in the ice
cream in he's had a ton of the turbo ice
cream
ice cream singers close
we'll let you be
greeting a nice way to finish off a meal
I scream
yeah
right
- finally
so the final verdict on Chau King we
liked it it's probably better than
jollibee in our opinion but it still had
that kind of buffet food taste it the
quality wasn't that a lie is still fast
food is the price we're going to explore
more the shopping move this shopping
mall is huge so we're going to come back
here tomorrow so if you're new to the
channel we daily vlog so come back
tomorrow hit the subscribe button mate
or you are subscribe to the channel we
film every single day of our travel so
we will see you in tomorrow's video
[Music]
[Applause]