good morning guys welcome to another day
you geez
[Music]
we have come to the same place as
yesterday for breakfast because it was
that good it was so good and again the
look of this presentation 10 are 10
tastes from it today turnout
how good does that look again it's like
an American breakfast but it was so good
yesterday so we've come back the coffee
is also insane and they've given me a
little happy sunshine on my coffee this
morning yes a litte bit cloudy today we
were thinking of heading to a beach but
the plan might change slightly or we
might go to the beach later but we'll
see what we end up doing hey nobody
figured out full tank with you
we figured out how to open this thing
get another full tank in the bike from
our come our drive yesterday we use
pretty much a full tank is about 2 or 3
hours on the road a full tank here cost
our town a minute 120 hundred and thirty
forty some are going to Adam over to the
Apache point nailin when turning is very
violent 50
they get bored it's quite the one to
instability but we do have some
toothpaste it correct I think I'm going
to put the ground over here there's some
very very busy restaurant was it called
I remember loading guys in the comments
said that we need to try it out fuckers
had breakfast
they speak up
oh yeah something going on some show
we're storing here tonight
the outfits we're going to head to
again which lovely weather day
but alona beach was like really really
busy and very torquey loved it we have
some nice food there and stuff so we're
going to go to Italy a big place where
we are in a point in style
it's one bit more secluded we pass but
it's meant to be a bit
let's begin a story page we're gonna go
into our bill each other so brings
cleaned off the fingers drop the knife
sunny day here we go now God
so this is a place that apparently we've
got a go at some point last no if it's
good
[Music]
this is what I need
that's chunky we also need to pick up
some tiger balm because I lost it and
Lucy's bites very itchy it's really fun
I also feel incredibly tall right
just arrived here at Dom luan Beach and
is a lot busier than we thought it seems
to be like a quite a set up resort we
have to pay 75 to get in 25 each plus 25
to park the bike and I can smell
barbecue of course I can hear karaoke
because we're in the Philippines we need
to try some karaoke with some people at
some point and yeah like it's packed
there's a whole area over here where
people are like eating and stuff so
maybe we can get lunch here get some
barbecue but good atmosphere can't work
out it looks more like locals than
tourists at the moment but could be
Filipino tourists from other parts on
holiday or whatever they come to the
beach let us know do you guys what do
you do if you're filipino do you you go
to different countries or do you go to
your own country because it's so amazing
do you hop over to palawan or let us
know where where you go on vacation and
what time of year you go I'd be
interested to know that but that's cool
we're going to explore so this seems to
be the area where everyone's kind of
eating and stuff which is cool and then
you walk a little bit further and you
literally walk right let's swallow and
you're literally on the beach but Lucy
just made a really good point that it is
Sunday there's bound to be more people
out I think it's cool
friendly vibe Brighton Beach where we
live in at home in England would still
be a lot busier than this on a weekend
[Music]
we just walk down the beach a little bit
further and it's kind of much quieter
sand is so white and the feelin looks
really good I think this nice kind of
smile because if you look here these
people it looks like far out but there's
still only up to like their ankles in it
and there's a Christmas tree on the
table all of that anyways come here for
a quick drink now because your ass gonna
be chosen getting a nice fresh fruit
juice I don't they do it is this fresh
fruit juice I'm guessing it's what fruit
today like same on the disruptions we'll
ask them in a second but that'd be nice
to see drink and if you've been watching
the vlogs for more than maybe two or
three episodes then you'll know that
we're currently obsessed and I mean
obsessed with the fruit shakes okay so
so good probably good for our teeth
every day but it's found a little friend
here as well hey
hello that a kitchen or there's a really
small packet of oh my god how small tiny
and I'm a high to the floor looking at
focus gonna be a blogger yeah yeah don't
be youtuber
this cat does not like Christmas Hey
thank you very much thank you
Cheers good what's happy dashain I think
that does happen again what is your shit
is really good really sweet
this is why I wore this shirt
we actually walked along a little bit
and this is the quiet part of the beach
it is actually silent if you listen you
can just hear the water there's two
people there there's a couple of people
there but it's so much better than that
we're good so we got our swim stuff got
out we can probably pretty much get
changed if it's not around this is gonna
be cool we gonna chill here for a little
bit hopefully the rain I think the
clouds are going that way
you knew how to figure though yeah of
course man two hands full
[Music]
thank you up to the airfield
Oh what should we do you know I'm always
on my mind yeah baby
the other one we're good yeah
[Music]
maybe I
[Applause]
[Music]
little things I should have said
Oh
[Music]
thank you guys let's get to a donation
what I'm happy to give him no problem
thanks so many sing another song please
hope you'll enjoy any simple but humble
presentation thank you
[Music]
no idea with serenades that they you do
the singing in the soul whenever I see a
guitar my boys might try and like see if
I can audition for their band full-time
stay in the Philippines complaining I am
he's gone to Beach yeah
just seen another guy flying a drone
seems like the drone laws here must be I
don't know that are they quite relaxed
last night because we really want to
bring our drone up yeah next time we
come back here which I think we will
want to come back here at some point
soon we would love to bring our drone
which would be super cool anyway we're
looking for some lunch now this is such
a nice chilled day everyone's out on the
beach a little more watch haven't worn a
watch since we left the UK I think it's
quite late we ought we want to get back
before it gets dark and before any more
rain comes but luckily we've actually
been pretty lucky with the weather today
like you can find quite definitely we're
lighting a busy a bit now we're back to
where we parked the bike but this is a
nice beach it's different to alona beach
what would we prefer prefer this yeah
because alona beach it was busy the
whole way along and you couldn't really
yeah you can find your own little space
really but this is cool it's nice
atmosphere chilled we are hungry need
some rice haven't even rice about two
hours
[Music]
classic they've come now to somewhere
could be fun to be farm
it's be fun and it's a restaurant and
it's a resort it's no different means
here and we just typed in restaurants
near well a little restaurants on this
island and it comes up number one so we
thought it'd take it out and we walked
up here the sun's disgusting and we're
on these little stores George is nervous
because we're putting the camera on it
with tape or anything it's gonna four
witnesses no I'll tell you why I'm
nervous because this here this is like
the ridge you get that look it's like
it's literally like that thin nice and
cold
[Music]
these are the cokes that are like really
nice these a different to zero no
calories so do these are caffeine
caffeine free coke doesn't matter okay I
think this has nothing look at the color
of coke light it's like it's see-through
is that what is its water down cake no
no that's not what coke license but the
ice that you had is now now takes you
down for ages okay
booter eisewhere chicken sounds looks
amazing comes with these like crisps has
like some sauce on that looks good and
Lucy's Pizza have to say I am quite so
you want to burn update me
I think the first night when when delish
oh you lost when though though it is
today you did it it was yes it wasn't it
my night was away before I then I'm
raising a kadai basically it's gotten
quite red let me show you oh wow that
looks really dumpy there there you go
yeah that's the size of it for you
there's my finger now because we didn't
put cream on I already know I don't you
should have done well it's a bird's
approach to put burn cream on it we ran
out the cold water but not for like 20
minutes after you did it anyway I think
I'll be alright I think I'll survive and
we're gonna have a bit of a chill now
it's actually my birthday tomorrow and
I'm very excited and I'm it's a pretty
amazing place to be spending actually so
feeling very lucky right now it's not
like hard work the harder you work the
luckier you get
think about that for a second good so
we're gonna have bit the chill out now
and treat ourselves to a film as my
little birthday Eve evening say don't
say I don't treat you right I know it's
amazing
you know you can take your Netflix
account you're sending your mum's like
not our nice true and that's sounds
simple but for us we're both editing now
I've just I've just written the weekly
juice because we have we have like
probably five or six work hours a day I
mean this job that would but then
vlogging technically work hours yeah
like creating the contents of kind of
work so it's like our whole day pretty
much like 6:00 in the morning till about
11:00 or 12:00 midnight is doing stuff
so like watching a film for us taking
two two hours
Oh perfectly ninety minutes I don't know
yeah a true me neither and that's like
rare for us and exciting and that's like
that's fun does that only happens on
birthdays we can have a little look
through now what sort of Shum are you
thinking Oh something light-hearted and
fun - self you're both you always say
that dog is like obsessive like romantic
be a lava chick flick and I'm more like
I want one that makes me go wow how did
that even happen that like you have to
really think about and pay attention to
like I like intelligent films it's
really like easy film this is already
half 11:00 all I can be asleep in the
first 15 master or pick when I'm gonna
watch them because you'll be asleep
anyway we're gonna have a look through
Netflix now but we've told you guys this
before we can actually get on different
versions and Netflix due to a VPN
company that we're working with at the
moment
and again they split to this video
they're called pro EXPN and again as
always we'll link them in the
description of this video so you guys
can check them out but it means we can
get onto like different Netflix's but it
also that there's loads of other
benefits and it's just working really
well for us while travelling like we've
had the account now for probably like a
couple of months maybe and we use it all
the time like it's always a ceremony in
the background it's not hard to use and
when we like out and about using
internet like in other places even like
in hotels and stuff like you can never
be too sure who else is on the network
so it's just like a safety thing so VPNs
of Virtual Private Network and not only
does it allow you to get access things
that you may not be able to without
there and in different countries and
like when you're traveling around and
things but it also like I said it means
that you're kind of protected and you're
much safer so any data online that
you're accessing or working one is
actually encrypted with this VPN so it
means that that your work safer like if
you're in like a cafe and I think the
uses example before but yes say you're
in a cafe and you're working on
something and I don't know your bank
details are on it whatever either
basically people question I'll steal
your money yeah it's always good when
people don't steal your money so it's
just a huge safety thing for us that's
probably the main thing use it for but
then also bonuses like the Netflix thing
and being able to actually get on like
different websites that we may not be
able to without it I'm like it behind
the EP ends are popular now but if you
guys have seen this article 13 thing
coming
which might become a nice scary
especially for youtubers in an out of
Europe to be honest anyone creating
content online I'm a thief VPNs might be
getting a little bit more popular if
they can find a way definitely so with
the link below there's also a 50% off
code so please feel free to go and check
that out it's super cheap as well like
when I first heard about VPN I recycle
that must be quite expensive but it's a
lot cheaper than I thought it'd be and
especially with 50% off is actually half
the price of what you think it might be
oh well done says me who's terrible of
us yeah
did me terrible at mental maths I'm good
at maths with a calculator who isn't
good at math to the Catholic you know
I'm good with numbers in general but I
just can't my brain doesn't seem to be
using a calculator is what you're saying
my brain I don't know my brain content
to wait well there's three types of
matter the calculator or mental math if
you can't do mental math it means you're
good in a calculator
I'm better at calculator but thanks for
watching today guys and we hope you
enjoyed this video we'll see you
tomorrow
we've got a nice fun day that we're
actually gonna go and explore on our
bike again but there's lazy different
your head just period loads of different
fun things we're gonna do so thanks
watching and as always we'll see you
[Music]
[Applause]