our final coffee in Port Barton
[Music]
I've gone for the American pancakes this
morning police has got some scrambled
eggs with onion which is a really nice
touch
so today is another trial day I'm going
back to protest so we hope we have a bus
booked at 9:00 only find in there
absolutely the paper but also wrote our
names down a bit they don't channel see
I don't know how both it was in the same
place we let their last riders to
double-check and I thought I will be
there so don't worry be looking we've
lost our bus ticket
yes for hopefully and we're gonna go
there in sight or grab that but we'll
show you one hands and show you our
passports of ID can you like living like
this go get on because sometimes it's
Teddy laid-back I'll do that but every
time we've got a bus before they have
willing to see the ticket and we need to
get to water princesa today because we
have a flight to catch tomorrow morning
and I made my hotel but to my friend
tonight so that we're there nice and
early for an early flight will they make
it will they won't like well they won't
what exciting viewing
[Music]
we're on the bottom ADA this bit of a
rotten party going on in here
we've arrived and we need to get some
cash outs to you actually get anywhere
let's get 20 we'll drive too much drugs
to a cash point but our bag to defend
now the former trike has just dropped us
it got some stories to tell you in a
minute
all weights were inside we've just come
to join me now we've had a few comments
recently say we have to try this place
it's like I think it's like the
McDonald's equivalent for Philippine
and we had to try it because you know we
like trying different food we go and
it's obvious and like want and make
Filipino food the recording city exactly
it's there it's the food that they go
see when they first be thankful to eat
we're gonna go in the menu I think the
free
okay go
so first impressions here this place
planet looks like the McDonald's of when
I was growing up as a kid when it was
kind of more like playing chairs and
just looks different before McDonald's
had their huge rebrand read fit and it
will became a bit more modern it looks a
bit like that so it's actually bringing
back good memories for me of coming out
with my parents on the weekend having a
personnels as a tree you just don't have
a little look at the menu
we're gonna see whether fancy order
we're going to try and get a few
different bits so we can experience it
properly and have a variation of the
menu
getting popular loads of different types
burger but also some bad date select
sauce on
chips and ice cream this lot and Ivers
come back here tonight report back to
you by Sugano Iowa they saw something
cuisine for meal then you get like
spaghetti fried vanity with my daughter
so random I know I love okay Lucy has
gone to order the food and while she's
doing that I'm gonna explain a bit more
about what happened on the bus so we
thought our bus this morning was nine
o'clock so we've got right half seven
breakfast we'll go out we'll have coffee
have a nice relaxed breakfast and we'll
go we'll go to the bus station for our
8:00 to 8:30
so we're still in room eight we have a
knock on the door and there's a guy from
the bus terminal with the lady going the
place we were staying in saying guys
your bus is waiting for you it's an 8
o'clock bus what time did you think of
us was we like because it was 9
we'd actually lost our ticket as we said
today 4 so we can check the time of the
bus so just when you think you get good
at traveling you lose your ticket and
you forget time your bus lucky though
because of all the confusion
it worked in our favor because the fact
that they were trying to rush us on the
bus and bus waiting for us we were just
shut up to the Bartok they didn't ask to
see our ticket which we had lost so it
all worked out like we paint the bus we
paid for the ticket on the first day we
got here then we're back now we've porta
Princesa we have a flight tomorrow over
here for one night and the food is on
the way off so excitements
nice wow that's amazing
they hit melb saw spring rolls yeah my
chicken it's cool
lovely
okay so we're from the UK if you didn't
know already and to have rice and spring
rolls as part of a fast food menu it's
so different to us that just does not
happen anyway just don't get like
chicken bits chicken mainly burgers
fries chicken with fries or salad or
like a carrot sticks or something but no
really understand and then drink so
there's never like this like a combo
meal thing with four different things in
UK in trips and this chicken they ask me
for one it's spicy or not I said yes
there's a little flag in it it's quite
feel and I didn't ask what it'll be
and I also don't know what flavour
anything else is but it looks really
good Oh is he like cutlery
yeah so to get from the bus terminal to
here we had to first to get some cash
out so we had to get a tricycle to drop
us at an ATM and then dropped us here
kind of in one trip
and the guy so we have been quoted
before like five ten minute journey
we've been paying out fifty 17 maybe a
little bit more pesos ago this guy was
like it feels like a 10 minute journey
total obviously there'll be maybe like
five minutes away since the ATM can
maybe fifteen minutes but it's all down
one road nice and simple journey and
this guy was like yes it's going to be
200 each to get to the ATM to 400 and
then 250 each to get from the ATM to
here which is literally at 30 second
journey he was trying form that would
have been nine hundred pesos we've got
him down to two hundred that please do
bar so if you're here because I don't
know like we said to him we've been in
three weeks almost three weeks now and
you can never paid that much and then he
kind of went okay fair enough and then
went down to it uh probably still too
much I'd say we went down to two hundred
we actually gave him three hundred
because he did wait out the bank for
ages but that was our choice asipi of
that as I say it was just way too much
forget that okay I'm gonna go straight
in with this spaghetti because I've
never had fast-food spaghetti night
I'm sure it so you're wearing
firstly in public secondly on it's
probably helpful yeah hmm that's so nice
I saw loads of people which we
definitely tell that became very popular
that's really basic it's just it's just
forgetting tomato and cheese but as tag
at McDonald's is spaghetti it would be
honor
I'm surely a bit healthier for kids well
that looks like gravy
and there's a second one
maybe this is curry sauce this one
smells a bit like sweet and sour I've
been happy nights with the spring rolls
I think that's a gravy spring rolls are
good there and it is that pork
that's insane so nice I like that baby
it's a little bit like a seek receiving
the rise exist
rice yeah
normal rice most tasty this is a little
flag I still keep our chicken on it was
fighting back and he's rich again or
even a spoon sorry
he's on the baby
let me get in there that's good that's
like KFC yeah it like different like
that for different posting
- chicken touch I wonder do the stories
and stuff I guess so I guess is frozen
but if it's good it's good right okay
well what is checking out how many doing
them all
you have the inside that's really good
is that counting isn't it and the
chicken flow like moist wise fast food
so good for you why so fast food so
tasty they're so bad for you also got on
the way a burger and fries right and
fries and a hot dog okay right fun
sharing a meal good thing we're hungry
so the rest of the food has arrived we
want to get into this hotdog give you a
little box for it okay small fries very
small fries tiny that's smaller than
McDonald's like that's like a kid's
portion of a different idea unless you
order the kids meal they made maybe we
have I don't know what is the sauce
I like that really
pretty good bourbon smell really would I
like that yes you will up this is much
more your popular Street to navigate
yeah it's gonna start with cup of fries
get into the mood you know
ha
fresh crispy fries are good okay I like
the little box this comes in packaging
ten on ten I see what you mean with the
sauce stun someone in the comments
please let us know what this yellow
sauce is on the Johnny beef hot dog bun
feels a little soggy it's not toasted it
tastes feels like it's steamed rather
than toasted okay
I knew you'd like there I like you think
that is unhealthy yeah like again if
McDonald's in hot dogs
okay so so let us know in the comments
if you're Filipino
what's the deal with McDonald's we know
you have McDonald's in the country but
it's totally be more popular
are they rivals or are order people go
to both let us know what the kind of
deal is cuz in the UK
McDonald's pretty much has the monopoly
for fast food there's Kentucky Fried
Chicken there's Subway there's other
play Burger King there's other places
but really in the UK McDonald's has it
covered for fast food so is that the
same with this here last night we're
interested very cheap its how much
everything was the three men three three
three home
a thousand pesos 300 the milk
try 300 for long are you serious - 64
this is the next dish people to try the
Aloha burger and I think it's like that
frame at the moment cuz it was that
appetizer on banners and stuff it feels
like a McDonald's burger imagine
elephant double cheeseburger
yeah there's a bit of weight to that and
leather packaging
the puddle so coming through
Oh interesting bun I think this has got
like pineapple in
yeah that's why it's called a loafer but
look at that steam coming on horrible
weight loss bacon pineapple cheese
and the ones we feed them we're always
good it's very wet though like the
baddest music n is the bun not toasted
that's toasted vanilla that's like it's
been fat inside
I think you're lying I know you really
well on that face there's something
novel right
if I call my cabinet in
don't think better the plant I say that
while sat in here he is nice I think
it'd be rough but like any night there's
something not quite right
okay do not this taste like this tastes
like a school canteen cheeseburger like
really fun of cheap meat basically it's
got space to think that's why I don't
like
I like it changed McDonald's doesn't
taste I'll talk to this is very very
different from the glass
I know we keep comparing to my dollars
but from our experience you have to go
on with fast food like it's fine high
quality but it's not that nice my
favorites still combo baby chickens
amazing my supreme rose and I still get
to eat rice with the right steps and
finally the float okay so was it like
oriental okay hangover cure right there
imagine I've been hungover weight
is more is much like a dessert you
wouldn't either
exactly you don't know how good this
feels
I'm too long with that Wi-Fi isn't it
ready oh my god get ready for many long
ok this is good news because we have I
think it's six videos by the time you're
watching this they're all up you've seen
them all but right now for us we have
six videos that need to go up because we
haven't have Wi-Fi flask of days so we
are very very happy with that situation
I comfy yeah I'm not saying it's in a
relaxed or sleep though we're doing work
we have to bash out these blogs because
with no internet situation we've been
answering email loathing anything
planning booking stuff so this is going
to be like a huge work afternoon into
the evening so I can't imagine it being
very interesting to watch we won't bore
you with that no we're so good actually
let's do a quick one of these but I'm
not moving so your session to move the
camera around and I'm just going to sit
here go on in best window with a nice
new you've got a tram with you TV mirror
George
bottoms or actually quite a big biker
with a decent shower the hot water
hopefully
all right thanks fishing today we hope
you enjoyed this travel day and us
trying out some Filipino fast food and
we'll see you tomorrow but it's probably
going to be actually a bit further than
that because we're not behind on blocks
but you get the idea
thank you for being patient with us
thank you for your messages see if we're
okay as well from the lack of uploads
but no all good just see village my face
down okay now we're back in a big city
with Wi-Fi hey leave a comment if you're
new and hit the subscribe button cc'
[Music]
[Applause]