[Music]
good morning guys welcome to another day
to do trip today
well hey we've fully been taking
advantage of all the types of foods here
we had to file
we've had lots of ice cream Italian
especially lots of Italian here bit lots
of Pete's a lot five great fact today we
are off to find when a
we also find these Filipino food we have
had quite a few comments on some of our
videos at the Philippines of food we
should try so we're going to take them
go find its restaurant look at them and
you and basically pick some of the food
you guys are suggested that we try here
and we'll let you know we think of them
this place has really really good
reviews
okay
okay bad research on my part apologies
that wasn't a Filipino restaurant it was
a seafood restaurant and it would be
like instead of saying the name of the
dishes just kind of like like chicken
weird something
wasn't like the actual name of the dish
we're looking for yeah I'm on
traditional and it's quite touristy here
so we're going to try it and look around
[Applause]
heeey
thank think so
No okay they're closed this isn't going
too well if he knew it'd be hard to find
Filipino food in the Philippines okay
this has gotta be air this one looks
more filling
hopefully it's open yes it's over so
their menu is all over the earth which
makes it easier for us okay so tell me
if I'm pronouncing these right in the
comment this it and the shrimp sinigang
with rice so three defeats three very
different dishes from what they look
like on pictures hopefully
so I'm very hungry
smells good
this is the importance is it I don't
know what this is on top but we'll give
that go we've got the chicken just here
and then the soup has come in a little
mini saucepan and they've got two dots
of rice to have the soup chicken I've
become a price and then we've got little
bowls and spoons of the soup as well so
what once we go forth first I really
want to try that walk yeah okay now this
one isn't pulled on the one that comes
with rice so maybe you don't eat the
price okay so we've got to anyone for
smells absolutely incredible I don't
know a source for that I know I don't
know what it is
outside I
subscribe that
I think it's pretty much crispy fried
pork and crispy pork fat okay but it
tastes
it's very nice taste it's very unhealthy
no it's kind of to be like cracking but
juicier what's the sauce like Janet
Peter Mayo I just know
I suppose I love Batman
nobody does need to be like
oh good that's amazing why don't you
have a silly game on how to make this
150 which is about the chicken is 160
which is like
and then the shrimp is 200
she looks really good it looks really
like soft as well so I'm coming in so
I wanna get some sauce
I don't know if I'm eating its right
yeah I don't know if I'm eating this
right bias you you just have a little
bit with rice because we saw your
comment we saw that when we were saying
that the car last time was too salty
rise to it kind of break it up saying
good nice words eat tasty
I'm really heartless five actually
[Music]
again bracelet II miss lemon is a bit of
sweet sour it's really nice I'm really
fine now I need to try so this killing
me three bits of chicken sauce it looks
really good
almost looks like a gravy okay smells a
bit like gravy okay okay straight
Henderson chicken
that's a sauce
seaway need the rice with it very salty
loads of flavor ton of I know you mean
that sweet sour
me I like a sweet-and-sour gravy that's
the best way I can describe
chickens good goes well with the sauce
the rice is needed so lastly we have the
shrimp sinigang which have resurfaced I
guess we pour it into a bowl you're
going to serve it so you remember it
something to you some ingredients that
you put in for flavor but don't need
that easily
I think we're the same thing here I
assume I saw something in second
together elation eaten
there's onion tomorrow is that cause
yeah I think other looks like one Inori
could be a source
I think it is yeah
yeah how is that a good way or a bad way
I like yes it's probably a bit too
fishing for me if I'm honest like I'd
like bronze but this tastes like to
share the model
it does take that well and not sour like
something soured in a bad way give us a
place like that but it tastes like it
has very strong flavor again quite so
I don't know how it would different
looks like chicken or prawns you have
left but it's pretty good to do to fix
it see someone help me because that's
too hot to be cut this soup inside Viet
Rochelle we have made such a mess of
disable I'm glad we got a big table I'll
be totally honest here because this is
what we're all about honesty or honest
opinions on this stuff this is not
something I would ever use the order
like a fish see it's just so far away
from I would normally have but let's try
it
that's quite nice yeah that's pretty
good like refer the chicken and the pork
perform a I can appreciate them exposed
to uprising with this yeah so it's gonna
say it's pretty salty yeah so have some
rice for that it's good its fishy but
we're at the beach so ya know how you
get into this guy ruled on here and
we're gonna go and treat ourselves to
some desert now over on the beach okay
fine fine you do it
so what's the verdict exposed a
what's the verdict you've got a rape
firm out of 10 and put them in all ready
yep
so the chicken was my favorite overall
okay they're an overall experience the
pork was up up like 9 out of 10 it's
lovely the pork I'm gonna say it was my
guilty pleasure I couldn't eat all of it
I couldn't eat loads of it you just need
a little bit like it's like an Chopra or
sweet or something is delicious you
don't need much of it 7 out of 10 as an
overall meal yeah
currently in water the weight of this
tunnel right up forever and I'll be
honest the soup not for me so I'm not
going to rate it because it's unfair
because I'm not a huge fan I mean like
three are ten but I'm sure it was really
good right I'd say for me oh you're so
right about I feel super something like
I really liked the pork but you couldn't
eat like a whole plate of it yourself or
you could be obviously coats but I
probably would be able to
yeah chicken I loved and loved the
actual bits of chicken and the sauce is
amazing the rice and stuff and again
soup was like it was fine it was nice
but not for me maybe if it was chicken I
would have probably liked it like the
flavor was nice but it was just a bit
too fishy
I do like porn so I don't know maybe
maybe it's got a fishy sauce anyway let
me know in the comments guys cuz I don't
know we don't really know it then we
disorder it off a menu and write it for
the best okay that's pretty much what we
did but with fall in a skirt we're ready
for some dessert we are trying for the
second time and hopefully the right
weight this time hello hello I know it's
not hallo hallo the women calling at
hallo hallo because that's how it's
spelt like for us how you pronounce that
word so we're going to try that now
again again we tried it the first time
we were like eating on a different part
separately and but all the comments are
like guys it literally translates to mix
mix to mix our next time we don't need
your property at all so try again we're
gonna try and do it justice this time
and apparently each place has different
recipes so this one's actually different
to us we had let's try it yeah give it
go any English people watching can see
what you can on sit hallo hallo but now
we know now yeah
mix it up eats it like a Sunday yeah so
here is exactly what's in it purple yam
creme caramel sugar palm fruit coconut
strings jackfruit sweet chickpeas didn't
know that mung beans coconut jelly which
are the little cubes and evaporated milk
[Music]
thank you very much thank you a picture
in here and what the other one that
might look very different but they said
they also did bring forth all different
recipes they shall honors please do
everyone's gonna be like that it's not
how you mix it it must be pretty hard to
mix this looks better than the previous
ones if it's to fullfil
was that enough coconut let's coconut
string that is well good jelly
mungbean oh you're gonna lose it lose it
okay I'm getting into the swing now I'm
getting so good at it
cool gainer that's what it should look
like and I've used two spoons probably
not the way to do it but it works
better places for breath three nice
this mouth fools gonna be a bit red
chilly most eventually okay this is
what's on that menu
where's the sweet chickpea
what should a pun friend is that this
yellow stuff
yeah from ah there's one be not be from
very little jackfruit you can add some
red chilli
so cold
that right - any plans from the other
galley or got chickpea or a mung bean
there sweet chickpea they're not that's
normal sorry tasted a bit a moment's
potato he's done and I oh no it's not
potato was a yam
I'm so confused what this is how much my
throat that I'm having it met it's much
better having it mixed it's still
freezing cold it's a bit of a cold a day
here today it's too cold for my teeth
what fairly sensitive teeth not too bad
but yeah this is much better mixed so
thank you to the hundreds of people who
told us how to eat this thing properly
because now we can enjoy it it's much
better the new vlog is uploading guys
but take a look here this is what we've
been struggling with yeah I think we did
Wi-Fi our hotel I think probably on El
Nido in general isn't the greatest okay
anymore ah there we go
yeah we came back to our hotel after
after a delicious lunch we loved the
Filipino food and is now eight o'clock
and evening we we had a little nap we
didn't mean to we have like this
absolutely how many dozen I do like
5-minute is and then woke up and it was
eight o'clock yeah like I hate that
because we didn't get to do the stuff
wanna do hopeful we can do it we get
that later but I guess needed it we got
time this is the thing Lucy and I both
huge advocates of hard work which you
know if you follow us on Instagram or if
you follow these vlogs you know that but
but we also know that you have to listen
to your body can you sleep in you sleep
if you're tired you're tired if you need
a big pizza / pasta you need a big piece
this truly is a food repair because I
think the last clip we were just eating
our hallo hallo and now we're going out
for food again
so I love a food blog I'm not
complaining that's nothing important to
remember that as much as we say work
hard pursue your goals achieve what you
want to achieve and put in the work do
more than everyone else like we get six
to eight hours of sleep every single
night so we're not saying burn yourself
out we're not saying drive yourself into
the ground if you're working hard on
some of you love you shouldn't even feel
like work
different market which is like a kind of
go to the end of the stretch borrowing
we have a common soccer ball I mean so
night like a dream
both refunding
like my uncie
[Applause]
so no but no like literally is coming up
this Olivia this is the beats that we've
been working a lot in the videos you've
seen the speed we can normally walk
about there the C is coming up and
hitting this wall tonight and the tide
is way here there's apparently a really
bad storm
from the USA we don't think it's going
to hit here
well maybe a bit but not as bad like
palawan seems out of the way and we've
got coke flight each and we've ordered
some chicken guy rush and they let us
have two sauces smoking to decide
between chilli and garlic whoo oh yeah
thank you
it's looks good this looks like an
accountant coming here
and promise
let's see how is it delicious French
chicken we got some garlic sauce with
spicy sauce Wow
can you recognize the seat I can
obviously why aren't you taking about to
this amazing ice cream there is
seriously what we got this time really
yeah
is it good nice on top of the pancake my
god
[Music]
we are off to the shop now to get some
water and then I was livin up earlier
except I was going to try and do a bit
of work but it's actually hostile at
night I can't do anything I think we
probably need to sleep off and just like
tomorrow's a new day
why the charts is it sharp no I do
we nearly had to climb over that gate to
get back into our hotel they've locked
it with I mean if we manage to like put
my hand the game ain't about now thanks
for watching I hope you enjoyed very
food heavy vlog I'm actually dropping
out thanking you help Anne yummy know
that sure let me take this thanks
yep we hope you enjoyed watching today
tomorrow we're doing things fun in the
morning on me I'm looking forward to it
and please do subscribe if you are new
we've had quite a few at me new viewers
from the Philippines on the last few
videos I'm very uh professor sounds like
maybe was subscribed so thanks so much
of your new and welcome to the channel
we do daily videos or by traveling
around but also we document everything
every day and the story post on
Instagram are not roads on Instagram so
make sure you're calling us that off
handle self so go and give your in the
way we run pit in the air
[Music]
[Applause]