[Music]
that was the loudest thunder I have ever
heard
have you heard louder Thunder than that
loose she said no what yeah I know it's
crease that's fine you know perfect it's
fine
good morning welcome to another daily
juice today's vlog is gonna start a bit
story right okay so we are now in the
Philippines we are an important
principle we didn't get hair like that I
wish we did yes we have a nightmare we
did so you last saw us in Hong Kong we
left Richard it was like 6:00 in the
morning when we got in from Macau it had
a great day yes we get back to our hotel
room at nearly 7:00 in the morning the
good thing is our flight wasn't till a
bit later the next day so we wake up
very hungover very like so hungover what
do we do no don't say it
we got we got my daughter's Amy bad we
don't we don't even have it in the UK
Milan over but there's no other like
hangover food when I knew where it was
anyway we then get a taxi to the airport
we get to the airport we wear Pro it's
now we're lining up at the check-in we
haven't printed our confirmation we
thought I'm not fine hockey is the word
yeah don't be cocky like okay the lesson
is about to be learned
so we're there we probably got despair
we've not gone from ourselves that much
time because we're getting good this
whole traveling thing now so queuing up
wait for is it what final keeps checking
is like 20 minutes as an arrow gets the
front thank you hi passport please no
all right here's our passport we are
flying to Manila the capital of the
Philippines yes you don't even either
13:03 isn't it you have been evenly
whatever but we'll get up and get some
cash on we get there we don't
money like we're we're winning there and
straight after that fly we had another
flight to port to Princesa which is
where so at the problem is key I thought
because the guy was talking to us he was
making conversation in like are cool so
where you off to you after the after
Manila and your think we're gonna header
than supposed to professor because we
have a flight booked I named Armco and
we're after that literally thinking
about who's wondering what we're doing
when yes we're after the Philippines ago
and we are honestly like I think we are
noisy actually see how it goes still
planning yes yeah still planning it well
if you don't know where you're going
next and you have no proof on the travel
then I can't check this flight the
check-in gate closed in about 30 minutes
from this point we were like what do we
do we haven't booked and we haven't
booked another flight out we haven't
decided where we want to go Philippine
either we thought that we might be able
to check in before we get to Manila or
before we board to fly it like an hour's
time and find something to do but you
guys I'm gonna know this gates closing
see and I can't check you in until you
can show you me a confirmation of
another flight or way of getting out the
Philippines so we have to leave that
queue join in the back and by the time
we got back to the front of the queue we
needed to decide how long we want to
spend in the Philippines yeah decide
where we're going next you find a cheap
flyer
see if we needed visas in that country
booked it wait for the email
confirmation to come through and show
the guy so he could let us on our first
flight I admitted that we've had to
force a plan up at this point we didn't
even have someone to stay that night so
we were properly winging it we were
going to get there and see what happens
kind of thing so I think realness is
forced us to get our act together and be
less vague we're here now we're leaving
here at some point was not going to tell
you when we're yet if you are sir twelve
the weekly juice and you already know
you all you know the story as well so
anyway we've had a bit of a an odd
morning went with some breakfast little
bit planning and then suddenly you hear
this huge thunderstorm it's lightning
there's heavy rain
it's crazy we wanted to be out by now
but the anyway the weather's clear so
they can get out we're gonna go out and
see something called the bay walk in
port princess satirize some Filipino
food yeah because obviously these vlogs
we like to include all the food we
eating from wherever we go in the world
we've heard from people who've been that
the food in the Philippines isn't
actually great so we're gonna try and
find some nice food we're gonna I mean
we're gonna see what it's like I've
really had my neck that hurt I think I
slept funny like that's fine about yeah
and then if I might go yeah got your be
on rye and don't worry you will get a
duty blog rim talk for this huge huge
hotel room very very soon
[Music]
okay so we're on this crazy took turn
there so different to like in Cambodia
or whatever and the guy just saw someone
new as like wait one second like yeah
and now he's pulled up to see his friend
no idea what's going on but we've been
told to wait we've been told to wait
here
cool so we're here at the bay walk and
it's really quiet I mean it's a huge
place you can see the sea the mountains
in the distance look amazing there's
loads of dogs walking around I don't
really know what those two do here like
if you look here there's nothing
actually we just walk that way and
conally fine yeah it's kind of weird I
saw this sign online call it I love
Princesa
so yeah we'll take a stroll down here
it's hot day let's go this way okay and
we'll try and find some food
this is really cool hair like it's it
feels really choir there's not any
tourists here at all
although it looks like there should be
from like that I love what a possessor
and stuff there's just where the stores
and things food and then oxy always
walks in here these boats and then if
you look over there that he's insane
mountains are like the clouds and mist
and stuff all around them
that's the coolest bit about this place
I think yeah that's amazing I think that
we need to get some cash so you kind of
come down here use most of the small
amount of cash we had - yeah so and the
guy I think I feel like we need to start
getting lower amounts out because it was
like 70 to come down here which to pound
and he was like we gave him 100 do you
have changed no I think he did have
changed but it's a thing I'm guessing
that he pretends he doesn't have changed
so we could have another 30 which is
like another 15 pence oh it's fine for
us but to try and get some smaller
amounts do you think yes if we can even
find an ATM if you can find 19 but right
now it's sitting very quiet so just what
is the town be now
watch Alex good
it's really loud here very hand
sanitizer
we all
we go mosquitos we operate definitely is
working on so if we've been signed by
like local repellent and some of you can
hear of like they feel and stuff like
something is very not really hair
country and blackberry age to us so we
found one
he's like thank you
yesterday for 35 minutes and I got like
10 fights around the next I was crazy
that people have to play quickly
talk about knowing they'd be fine by
tomorrow so line
we together
no other
Toriko it's baking
crazy whoo - have fun at work like me go
get some food this place looks good if
we can get over the river
so about the music but they seem to
having a good time singing along come
into a place
perfect aim where the nose what's doing
I was trying to cover you up the menu
there's a load of like seafood barbecues
and stuff along here including this
place but I do other stuff as well
problem is we're not huge on seafood and
enough clams for the first time the
other night so I know pretty good garlic
soup you watching us thank you
[Music]
we ordered and throw about this music on
if we're gonna copyright pets or not and
we've ordered you get it here so I can
show you this is a Filipino noodle
bihaan with chicken and also a chicken
curry but again the lady said hasn't
Filipino Carrie but we're not sure it's
actually called and we're gonna give
this a go they give you small fork to
use and a plate to share their back with
I wanted one that was so big
so not close the paper really 14 July it
takes a little bit like instant noodles
but not in a bad way like it has a bit
fresh it's a noodle with the flavor of
intimate so you've got these like thin
glass type noodles like c3 ones cabbage
carrot chickens although it doesn't look
that great the chip that's just a bit
bone
yeah and that can sit yeah yeah pretty
good that's great thanks so much cool so
the chicken curry is also right really
good Chinese chicken very strong smell
rice with it as well sci-fi
[Music]
very salty as well
that's tasty
first impressions good
yes when you've been told is bad and you
expected it's bad it's good fantastic
it's like Chinese taking care either
yes kind of spicy to know that spicy bit
very salty loads of flavor and it's all
fresh okay so to finish off we've gone
for this which is called low the low
someone who follows are some Lucy on
Instagram who's from the Philippines
told us we must try this desire and
flare and cool break from careful ice
cream and straw and what looks like
Whitney be you kind of the kind of milky
is very like warm wet and the ice cream
looks good out there try get some ice
cream some corn flake and one of these
little jelly beans
[Music]
okay I need to try each individual
element I think that's nice stop things
the ice cream that's all with that's a
really weird flavor I can't tell what it
is
perfect background music for this
[Music]
that's the verdict ladies gents milking
our cereal okay so the ice cream was
sweet potato which I've never had before
and it's a little bit weird it tastes
like the sweet potato crisps that we had
the other day we've come back now down
to the water and there's so many people
long ago now it's really with us I think
people come down here for the evening
Perry's really nice sunset spot and I
think there's a market opening up behind
us we might stay for a little bit of
that but we do have a hotel swimming
pool which we want to check out let me
have it yet but the waters kind of murky
in it and some of it I'll share you were
awesome in here in the hotel yes
[Music]