I spent three weeks in the Philippines
and only about a week of that was
actually spent on beautiful islands like
all the ones that we see in pictures I
did my research I watched all the
YouTube videos I read all the blogs
about where to go and what to do and yet
we still have so much trouble we even
start questioning ourselves are we doing
something wrong why is it so hard to
find a nice beach in a country made up
of 7,000 islands now don't misunderstand
me
we did still have an amazing time but
all mistakes we made could have been
avoided if there was more information
made available that wasn't just oh my
gosh the Philippines is paradise it is
paradise but you need to know where to
find it and once you do I promise you
you will never want to leave
you
[Music]
so how do we find paradise well that's
easy just avoid these mistakes number
one fly to Manila Cebu or prayer to
Princesa and then immediately leave
unless you're looking for the city life
which can be great as well leave head to
the beach that's why we went to the
Philippines at least was to go to these
beautiful beaches and Islands so leave
tip number two avoid the taxi scams
obvious I think most of us know this
turn the meter on but if you're new to
Asia something you might not know is
that taxi cabs here love to refuse
people if it's not going in their
desired direction or maybe it's too far
or even too close so here's a tip if the
cab is refusing to take you for whatever
reason they have and this happened to
Jordan I with seven taxi cabs late at
night in Cebu refused to take us and so
what we did was when the 8th one came we
just opened the door we got in we sat
down we pulled up her map and said hey
we're going to her friend's house take
us here we know where we're going and
then he went tip number three avoid the
crowded tours everywhere you go the
locals will tell you that to go to this
island or to go snorkeling you need to
take a tour or go on a private boat this
is true however when you take these
tours you're either gonna be offered the
ultimate tour the island hopping tour
all these abundance of tours and likely
there's gonna be probably 40-plus people
on that tour and when you go on this
tour you only stay in the different
spots for snorkeling in Islands for
about 30 minutes maximum and then you're
off to the next destination which is
really frustrating if you don't really
want to be rushed and you don't want to
be crowded by all these people you want
a relaxing experience or you can take
the other route and hire the private
boat but this private boat depending
where you're at especially in Corona El
Nido can be very expensive I'm talking
as much as 7,000 pesos or even heard
15,000 pesos if you got majorly ripped
off which does happen but maybe you're
traveling alone or you're not staying in
a hostel so you can't really gather up a
group of people to split the cost of the
private boat so you have to pay that in
full if you're like us that wasn't
really achievable it's definitely not
budget and it didn't even sound
appealing to us so what we did instead
was we found a place kind of more off
the beaten track an area called San
Vicente and this actually offered all
the same things except no people and
only 3500 pesos for two people to have a
private boat and it was amazing here we
got to do the same things that you would
do in any other tour except that there
were no people we got to take our time
doing whatever it is we want and it was
honestly the best snorkeling of this
entire trip honestly this looks like a
swimming pool it's that clear and you
see the reflection off the water is just
ridiculous
[Music]
number four where do I find a nice white
sand beach as I mentioned earlier you
would think in a country made up of
islands there would be white sand
beaches everywhere you go right they
told us that these would be white sand
beaches they're not unlikely you're
gonna stay in these small towns that is
nowhere near these nice beaches unless
you can afford to stay on the islands
which is pretty pricey even for the
Philippines then you're gonna have to
take a boat where you're gonna have to
do a private boat or you're gonna have
to do a tour island hopping for example
and again you are going to be on a timer
you do not get to decide how long you're
gonna stay on that island before you go
to the next one and the next one and the
next one even if they're pretty
sometimes you just want to relax right
at least for us personally we just
wanted to wake up to a nice beach and
have it essentially entirely to
ourselves but it to look like all the
pictures and we finally found that of
course at the end of our trip and again
in this area called San Vicente we
stayed in an Airbnb where we woke up to
this beautiful beach and on top of this
beautiful beach to ourselves we got to
go to even more beautiful beach when we
took our private tour and found the most
beautiful island I think that we
discovered on our entire trip that was
exactly what we wanted it is so nice out
oh my gosh
[Music]
now I'm not saying that the only place
in the Philippines to avoid these
mistakes is San Vicente no that is just
where Jordan I personally found what we
were looking for and got away from all
these crazy tourists and people so you
know other areas like this exist I mean
the Philippines is made up of islands so
I recommend if you want to find kind of
more relaxation and you know beautiful
answer yourself to look for smaller
areas and places a bit more off the
beaten track maybe close to a big
popular destination but maybe a little
bit out of the ways from it that's what
we did and actually San Vicente is not
too far away from El Nido and parts of
Princesa which is where most people will
go it's just a little bit farther out so
you know you can find other areas like
this the last thing that I want to talk
about that is an obvious one but it's
very important is number five travel in
groups I realized this isn't really
possible especially if you're a solo
traveler and this can be difficult but
the Philippines like any other country
has its dangers and these dangers can be
found off the beaten path and can be
found in the most touristy destinations
of that country unfortunately I fell
victim to one of these dangers when
somebody slipped something into my drink
I wasn't out drinking I wasn't even at a
bar I was at a cafe when this happened
and all of a sudden I was sitting down
we had moved to a restaurant and I could
no longer read the menu I merely lost my
appetite and everything kind of got
strange I felt like all of a sudden the
room was spinning kind of like a fan
would and it just started spinning
faster and faster and faster and faster
and faster until I was just losing my
mind and I knew something was severely
wrong and so I kept telling my friend
Jordan like I'm not okay I'm not okay
like you might need to call an ambulance
like I need to get out of here
thankfully because I was there with my
good friend Jordan I had somebody who
could take care of me and I had somebody
who could put me into
tricycle and take me back to the Airbnb
where I would be safe if she wasn't
there obviously I don't know where I
would be today now as I said before
these things happen everywhere but the
Philippines is still fairly new to lots
of tourism it might be a bit of a higher
risk that doesn't mean that the
Philippines is unsafe it is still safe
to travel it just means that you should
be a bit more cautious and I recommend
if you're traveling there to try to
travel in groups or at least use the
buddy system especially when you're out
at night now I don't want to leave this
vlog on a sad note so let's talk about
one of the best things one of the
highlights of this entire trip and that
was at this Airbnb in San Vicente this
Airbnb was just exactly what we wanted
it was on the beach and the people there
were so generous and they provided us
food they just they treated us like
family
so apparently our Airbnb is throwing
Jordan at a welcoming party for our
first night
let's go check it out
is
[Music]
but that's not it they even taught us
how to fire dance fire dancing is an art
work it is industry to be the food
because the more you love the fire the
more beautiful the pattern she can make
[Music]
of course that's just practicing and
then the real thing no papi it's okay
you're even better at this than me open
open up yeah you just have to not be
scared of it love these PA but I didn't
do a practice round like Jordan oh my
god there's no futon yeah no no it's
poppy it's okay it's okay if it touches
your hands no just do something you're
comfortable with I'll be pulling that if
you do something do with that yeah I'll
be taking it if here if you did
something wrong
don't worry you know you did that do
this you can do that I promise
play it just think of it as the practice
once you can do that
ah the fish guy
oh my god hello don't panic
[Music]
no need
and
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
this truly was the best way to end our
trip to the Philippines and why I'm
still in such high spirits about it
of course there was things had gone
differently but I am still very grateful
for all the wonderful experiences we
shared and all the people we met along
the way and I hope this video still
encourages you to visit this amazing
country but at least that you're more
prepared than I was on that I will end
this video and I guess I'll see you next
time Philippines if you guys have any
other tips any other mistakes that I
didn't mention which there are a lot of
them please leave a comment so that
other people can see it and other people
can have a great time in the Philippines
some of them are really important I'll
definitely pin them to the top but
please just so we can help other people
really maximize their stay in the
Philippines if you plan on visiting
other thing a lot of you guys asked me
about the gear I use specifically the
Philippines video of is everyone saying
what camera do you use what for audio
all these things I put everything in the
description of my videos and I put links
to them as well so anything you want to
know about you know song choice where I
stay everything I put in the description
of my video so definitely check that out
ok the blogs over bye