good morning guys welcome to another
daily juice ignore this for now we have
breakfast in well minus three minutes
the hotel here cook us breakfast so we
need to go and get that
[Music]
so the Sun he recognized us which is
cool and they've just like our time
laughter they watching our videos and
stuff it's first time we've been
recognized in a difficulty by the people
from that country as well not just like
a traveller you get it done you we need
to go the big bags are on oh that's so
heavy when we've got all these on let's
go get the bags off photo shoot yeah
yeah cool you want to be on the vlog
you're on the vlog okay
thank you very much thanks so much thank
you
[Music]
just Osmond upgrade and we've got one do
it for that
they would explain that a little bit
better so George when I'm gonna want to
an upgrade
and you do that exact thing turns out
everything is all coming in at any
transfer not great you know what he had
especially summer
available with loads of leg room which
you know that we need because although I
look quite sure next to George I've got
quite long legs and join us very toys
like picks up two or three on you yeah
we put an athlete there lots of leg room
which is perfect they don't make that so
we just get up the wrong flight which
nearly went to Cebu turn off the toilet
anything to be walking back with the
there's a chocolate waffle no way
serious noise for you maybe I could have
like half or something they offer you
our umbrellas here for the Sun nice
touch
[Music]
[Applause]
I'd say three four one four vodka
just gonna stroll in it
that's an easy easy I'm saying like
where it normally comes up to and then
there's another spare tomatoes thank you
very much Philippines Airlines
[Music]
bullabbai
we get sky trees
and
it's my favorite bit about airports the
stance that everyone gets into when I
see their bags
ken-san
are usually pretty lucky heroes and
usually our backs crafts you distinct
there in the fights we've done so far
with the sauce electical and the past
bizarre
five outweigh this feels kind of weird
because they've just left me the right
it's picked up our bags and then we're
like looking for summits departures so
we're we're doing all of that work all
over again there's a Wendy's over that
Ursula TP tonight I'm 16 a 100 ml dose
drinking a mathematical go check in game
the fuck you guys I'm also what got me
to do you have a channel what's your
channel thank you just rustle this up
for you oh wow noodles with some sesame
seeds black beans
I would've thought here on these and
almost is eating it's normal this is
what this is what an airport day looks
like that was very funny
the guy briefly and I saw some YouTube
and that's probably got an upgrade on
this flight today is going well
[Music]
that's what second flight would
seriously where priority boarding has
burns on the bottom of this upgrade is
totally already bad
come with me I'm not really asking
away to a place where we eat
the world in action while we can be live
with no distractions
this is what we waited for
[Music]