good morning guys welcome back to
another day you do another daily vlog
another juicy lot learning on a call
these videos welcome this morning's a
bit of a work morning for us we found a
really cool little cafe spot here in
Cebu and it's almost like we're back in
Brighton it's a very there's a place we
go to a home we'll kick some green and
home if you're from the area you'll know
it and it's kind of very similar just
finished off a flat why you don't see
many menus here with flat white so had
to try that very nice we've got several
videos to edit we've got lots of emails
to send we've got some client work to do
so they're busy we've got a laptop beat
out like cracking out and work this
morning
[Music]
fight for your comments without so many
that it's crazy how many you guys have
went over the earth now and it's so
interesting like hearing your views on
everything we do as metals of never
being strapped I can see someone that
never been to England before is making
videos if you go into your Facebook and
it's great that here in your thighs
point of views and please do keep
commenting on our video
many comments it's getting harder
because there's so many yeah
[Music]
okay so for lunch today if you've been
watching our videos you will see that we
have tried a lot of different Filipino
food so we've tried all sorts of
traditional stuff we've tried the fast
food we've tried jolly moves tried Tower
King but we've seen the comments and
there's one thing we haven't tried
there's one thing you guys been telling
us to try I mean something that is
famous
so everyone's been saying
you must try the stitch and that's we're
doing today for lunch and we're very
excited because we walk past the
Minnesota yesterday and it smells so
it does it smells amazing so today we're
going to try some electron we read it
for the electron restaurant here's our
guy
they're going to help us out look have a
look at this this is what we're going to
be eating so we're going to be trying
this out today for the very first time
we have never ever tried this we're
going to see if they got a table - it
looks pretty good I mean the restaurants
empty but we got there early so we can
get it fresh fingers crossed we're gonna
enjoy it because we have no idea hi I've
got a table - please thank you very much
in size and anyone famous or the
original I think we're going to original
because that's what we should do I think
the more
maybe shake a leg
and only one we'd ever tried we don't
know
this is like
hopefully I thank you can we just get
the original small to people thank you
and that's it for now
I've got a good partner furniture yeah
it's usually like the lemon and lime
thing yes like tablets are nice yes
right
thank you
you mix it all together okay cool and
then eat it with okay great okay cool
thank you very much so they give you
this stuff which is nice onion it's like
a lemony like thing and then you use the
vinegar olive oil
mixing together how much should be
making yeah thanks so that how much you
might to use yeah and then you make a
dip you're gonna see if they'll let us
film
they pretty much get home I feel happy
that we're trying it in like the place
it's well known in like the most famous
place apparently our speeding and
electrons actually a Spanish
this guy doesn't do it right in front of
a window in the shopping mall second
lesson looking for teamwork
Oh
this is saying when the fresh that can
arrive 10 a.m. and 5 p.m.
thank you very much guys
I know everyone's looking ass it's not
because family ass
the future thank you Tamia
my name is drink is like a shake I don't
know
yes the shake of the head by an instant
frozen apparently it's really good to
have lunch
calamansi
alabanza there's a very nice taste like
[Music]
like a shake with ice I guess
freezing cold oh yeah that's not be
liable at Apple skin that's nice
whoever made this dip yeah dude actually
always iffy for that spot so I asked
I'll ask aunt Hallie make things can you
help us make the bit yeah
that's great
this company is dishonest agreements
yeah we have tomato and onion chili and
11c no lactose by your
[Music]
yes passport iku nagae
yep
[Music]
maybe outside sassy okay
vinegar little spicy yes yeah
great thank you my mom you're just going
to make sense please Stefan I'm MC for
death sauce okay cool thank you thank
you very much
so it mix all this together
[Music]
yeah suck it and then squeeze this in
Oh with all the seeds basket okay cool
alright that's fine thank you
we are being very well at after
I guess doing all of the same time quite
they get better skin and the bit of
banana better it's not the meat
let's get a little bit of
it smells amazing bye Mike let's have a
close up a bit back the smelling yeah
the smell is incredible
I'm gonna get a bit of crispy star
[Music]
okay did this
therefore you look at us like
don't even see that
that is really good that's so tasty that
is really crispy / he doesn't have the
teeth whenever I have practical I don't
have fracking line because it has 42
much this christmukkah is easy to eat
the meats really good what does it taste
like is there like flavor in it it's got
the person's fight with you spider
okay you know when you have to come down
yet but it's quite dry
yeah this is like a really really moist
yeah down there really yeah wow I love
that nice we've got everything we got
the phones this is literally straight
off the game
that means slightly pink the sauce is
really good very flavorful
missiles is really good
me so knows what means
shake it shake
devezin I thought it'd be quite
comfortable yeah it's soft but still
crispy at the same time you don't have
an audience for your first reaction you
need a little bit more I think I'm gonna
be without the sorts of again
okay
how good
yeah
maybe like that so anything it's much
softer but if you don't kind of quickly
with the night
and this fools
yeah yeah try both but I really like it
with the sauce it's so different it's
not too spicy it's an entirely different
issue
and I don't know what the kind of
standard price is best
the training guide pops
[Music]
but it was 295 days
- people pleasers - sweetie
the way people were saying with
people saying you must try this it
sounded there's no license on Charlie to
try it it's like I think they just
really wanted us to taste it because it
was so good do you like it
yes yes every day
[Music]
to make me happy really nice very good
to eat your favorite here in Cebu
yeah very much excellent thanks so much
thank you
what I like about it is that even though
you order one dish and it's one thing
that comes actually because of the
company you get all different types of
meat if that makes sense so you get if
you prefer it a bit fatty in a bit juicy
and unhealthy then you get that there's
many really soft stuff and then
underneath there's some dark meat which
is actually tougher more like gammon
real steaky chunky stuff as well so you
get both
yeah and the fleet that's it that if the
flavors different throughout a cut of
meat
maybe it's the herbs but all right sorry
about it's just delicious thank you
thank you very much
take grandma's is great thanks so much
thank you thank you that's great yeah
that's great yeah
[Music]
I was a really good experience actually
the food is amazing out all the staff
really friendly really really nice
serve at all
I mean I mean only one I've tried but
it's very good for a first one well no
it was really good
recommended we now need some breakfast
for tomorrow we're getting up really
early tomorrow we're off to do something
really really fun yes we can't have our
breakfast at Mae's LaRue which we've got
right thing to do our thing and Mae's
house so we need because it was really
it at 5:00 a.m.
no morning so we need to find things
really early start yeah you want to keep
it healthy so we're thinking of picking
up some fruit or some other because I
don't know we keep kind of eating pretty
unhealthy and we want to mangoes dried
mangoes that could work
sure
thank you very much
they weigh your fruit volume Jennifer
what they do special treatment or let's
crank this up there's what we need ash
is a little bit noisy to vlog with so
I'll take off but I'm gonna get very hot
we loved that let John we are still so
so full
make sure you're watching tomorrow guys
because we have a very very fun eventful
day planned we cannot wait we're really
really excited we're teamed up with a
very cool tour company that's what I
love about what we do these YouTube
videos I'm not so many opportunities for
us that yes you can look as tourists and
stuff but we've been lucky enough so far
to work some incredible companies
including a company that is sponsoring
the channel at the moment a company
called Pro EXPN they're a VPN server
Virtual Private Network and they've
given us an account which we're using it
basically protects your it basically
protect cos say the word protect it
protects you online so say if you're
going into cafes and public Wi-Fi spots
and stuff you don't know who could be
lurking products being have been
educating us with cyber security online
safety all that kind of stuff and
hackers can literally say ok say so say
your so say your doing your online
banking your transferring money or
whatever and you're all done to a Wi-Fi
network in a public place like a cafe or
restaurant some another if a hacker is
on the same line they can literally read
your stuff and access bank details and
all sorts of other private information
so that's one side of it another side of
it we're using and is really cool that's
the unlock certain websites where
certain websites are blocked so for us
traveling it's been really really handy
we've been out to get on Netflix we be
able to get on the American Netflix
which is causing get some extra stuff
that you can't get in the UK can't get
in other countries so there are so many
benefits to using this service we're
using it with really really enjoying it
and we're happy to promote it to you
guys and they've been great they've
wanted to give you if you're interested
in signing up they want to give you 50%
off a membership so half-price
subscription there's a link in the bio
there's a discount code go ahead and use
that check it out if you want to if you
want to know more information there's
loads of information on their website so
if that interests you check it out we've
got an early start so we need some sleep
now the room is a mess this is what
happens when you're trying to pack two
bags you're trying to edit and export
vlogs and transfer some clips between
hard drives and yeah our bags down there
okay that's enough of that thanks so
much for all your welcomes back to the
Philippines as well that's been so cool
to read thanks for watching today guys
we will see you tomorrow for
blog on Sykes I did seize him by
[Music]
[Applause]