[Music]
good morning guys just arrived at the
beach I would just want the office and
we're doing a tour today with mom and
bang tours but to pay the environmental
fees because we're going to survive
losses that you need to light onto which
normally means they're going to look
pretty amazing we're back to get on the
boat now it's a very hot day today what
comes in at 9:00 in the morning and I
think we're on here until like quite
late Saturday there's loads of different
stops off during the day snorkeling
kayaking that kind of thing
[Music]
on the boat now we just now a tour guide
Chris we are so lucky with the weather
the other day in Portman says that when
we sow it was rainy and stormy the sea
was really really choppy but today is
beautiful blue skies and sealants so car
we're lucky because there's a small
groups they said sometimes hours 24 25
ten of us roughly and there's also some
people from Oxford's down there so
that's cool so don't forget the name of
our boat we are on Invicta really just
all right because sometimes other guests
after they enjoy they are already moving
on the wrong boat reading so I'm gonna
forget Phillip just mode
our first up will be the secret Lagoon
because normally the tile and DC third
stuff into a but I want to make like
first one okay so again after a small
big secret Lagoon Jimmy so in lunch area
our last edge will be the seventh
commando which that's that part of my
last part of Midland behind
[Music]
Oh God
tiny island with a pool
there's not because it looks like a
turtle which is why all over the
approximates funny things like like in
halluf a rat chicken Island thing
because its place where the turtles
actually protected and they breed it's
kind of a conservation area for turtles
which is cool
[Music]
just look at this this okay Thailand I
think it's that way we've got here
before I can see the gasping set got it
so many others so we're getting here so
let's do
[Music]
much colder in here it's mainly like the
shadow starting day one we were at
halong bay
remember when we collapse but it was
nice it is amazing probably the coolest
place we've been in I would say oh yeah
people were stood up and their Thailand
was cool we got a guy the Tyler was cool
I think this top set just slightly I
think I've never been analyzed
[Music]
pulling into the highlight of our need
oh now this is the bit this is the part
you see on all the brochures on the
internet Google Images this part
like this play
it's actually quite funny more boat to
do exactly same thing you will queue up
and get a picture on the front away I
know all the boats around this way
exactly
[Music]
this day is getting better and that
allows and the threat of all common
today I don't think we've ever seen
anything quite like that we're now going
through here we have to take a kayak
because he's been most common gap in the
rock here it's like a one-way system
there's a bit of a traffic jam going on
down this it's better right and now I'm
sorry have a mall that's not in tonight
and are not as we go we seems if I and a
baby that's just Oh Ava love and only in
the dark do we see our sunlight home is
where we were home is where we want to
be and yes we don't have time to say
goodbye and this ain't the last time now
this time before we go raise your hands
raise a toast time is something special
just like hey we're now in this like
tiny little haze it was discussing here
Alicia as I go around more people come
in and it's like a mini Lagoon like
within it you can see here
it's like tiny so cool so what is like
murky still kind of fit but it's not as
clear as out there
[Music]
it doesn't actually feel real like the
water is just the most ridiculous color
it's so clear crazy all these amazing
cliffs around here and here we are on a
kayak flowing through the middle of that
I think the plan now is to head back at
the boat and have some lunch they're
just preparing that or now for us and
they were just going to sit here and
join us and hopefully there's a little
bit of a dip in this movies but I've
never seen water so clear but it's still
blue we've come onto a beach now and
we've got this little Hut to ourselves
so so cool so nice
for that way and we disappear like
amazing such a nice beach this is like
I'm gonna subscribe to one thing we've
got off the bar with like music food
you've got all these mountains above us
with blue sky and then you come below
and there's palm trees and there's these
gorgeous little huts along the seafront
there's people on a swing turning out
having a great time laughing enough man
and something that will sit there the
sand is not white then you've got these
really cool boats lined up because
there's only one survey there's also
like George's swimming around
[Music]
before
these are so good they're massive
absolutely huge cheers well so I was
showing them Tamerlan good choice here
we're gonna end the stock off here on
the beach
taken around el nido today we absolutely
have probably one of the best days I
suppose out all the time I secured that
means having a good time
we are absolutely loving the Philippines
see you tomorrow fun and games good
night
that's a weird ending no one side then
we'll look the instead beautiful beach
good night
[Music]
[Applause]