complimentary 7:00 till 11:00
[Music]
okay how are you yes yes please that'd
be great
hello starting off with some coffee this
morning made a bit more
you want a strong menu thank you very
much that's great thanks so much lovely
now we could say a proper good morning
guys welcome to another daily vlog
another daily juice we thought today
we're in Cebu City we thought today we
would check out some of the biggest
shopping malls apparently we've heard
here the shopping malls are insane
they're huge
we're starting at SM City we're going to
also go to a few more today one of which
is like the sixth biggest in the world
or something which is crazy
so we're going to go there check it out
what's going to get some snacks as well
eat our way around these malls see what
stops I got to see how they compare to
British malls now I'm excited this guy
[Music]
Christmas has started in the Philippines
with welcomed by all these lights a huge
Christmas display and also shout-out to
the security start friendliest in the
world Missy Avila said I was a very
beautiful I'm grateful to the peaceful
country nice a beautiful map right right
Wilson below if you get the reference
[Music]
my favorite today
apparently criticism
like knowing it now ideas and
so it looks like we will kill along like
the bottom level now all the clothes
shops and its brands that you recognize
at home right Uniqlo forever21 hm there
is tons of stuff and then this stuff
that we haven't heard of as well like
what surplus we saw we have a culture a
Filipino look at the look how big it
like we've just come from down there
this isn't even one of the biggest ones
yeah it goes all the way down there and
then I think the Hanalei 90
and then I think there's like four
stories outside massive
okay
we need some goodness start the day in a
good way
you father's finished me
Oh
they're very green
it tastes like what's that every
department got to I hate when you get a
premium a fellow youtuber that I
mistaken sugar for this tastes lychee
that's like what the nurse really
so listen up some reason are really into
logo t-shirts at the moment so like
t-shirts like this one that we bought
the other day in Taiwan it's got a
little DW with we're saying that mean -
don't worry very much something ten
different all be a brand name or
something
we just found a rail here all of these
t-shirts have really cool it slogans I
like that I like that wait wait come
back
I like the little hand on this guy and
then one that says just be nice which
it's so so true and perfect but I just
notice that through there another one
that's not good
the only problem here for me is sizing I
tried on an extra-large t-shirt the
other day and it's it's more like a
medium in the UK so it's quite difficult
because I'm quite tall and quite large I
usually write XL t-shirts in England or
double XL so they're quite baggy and
stuff well I think we're gonna try a few
of these on these babies wow really
that's the other thing
yeah and there's like tons that all of
these have like logos and they're all
different as well sorry I thought that
in the UK shop would be like the rail of
22 the same t-shirt this rail has like
maybe two of the same for two different
sizes based on different stuff it's nice
like this is the FM shot by the way it's
the more that I guess the shop of the
more is those different brands and stuff
and no I don't know what half the brands
are but it seems to have a better
thinner
Simon it was that loads different shops
are like somebody's up there left on it
like blown lots of phone
the Sharps photo printing things just
like everything technology wise but it's
quite handy because I thought any you
came in a mall with always spread out
and you wouldn't have a certain section
for it but here it's like you come here
if you want something electronic you
okay so this is actually a whole floor
of tech stuff which is actually really
cool it goes all the way down there all
the way down there and all the way down
there there's even a place here to keep
your buggies that is cool you don't get
that anything that machine is freaking
out I stopped just come into like a TV
store and they sell low load electronic
stuff as well and we've just seen the e
biggest TV in the world and it's just
turned off as I'll show you
Wow there you go really oh my god no no
that's the TV guys that is how thin it
is that's even bigger that's crazy
75 inch UHD 4k LED TV I want one of
these that's incredible
leaders protect its end I saw a part the
front of this color
he said Lucky's yellow over in your hand
and I swear outside of the next morning
[Music]
[Applause]
y'all assent enough
which is about a 10-minute Drive away
from where we defer and every single
more we go and any entrance has like a
security like go there and one of them
BP things to go through an effort it's
like really really good secure scope you
don't really have that audio and there's
more Christmas decorations look at
this one feels much more like
quiet
let's kind of I've only walked and I
don't know but like the other one heads
and it with stools and stuff for food
it's one things more inside folk song
shops and maybe like all the restaurants
are somewhere
I'm guessing that it feels quite
different to the other one and maybe bit
closer
interesting but the other one looks like
a really fun like Christmas tree ends up
this one seems much more serious
we're hoping to get some food here as
well so we'll see picking up some
coffees quick the cake killers but they
do it they do a mango cheesecake I've
never heard such thing that looks
unbelievable so we're not gonna go for
any further
- espresso macchiato so just come to the
outdoors but now and I didn't expect
this it's like where are the restaurant
sides it's like an immersive like green
area only like two level three level oh
cool there's that paper city outside
Loza types of food by the looks of
things what do you fancy
I really know
I kind of feel like
something healthier yes me too it's good
yeah dono let's see where is its ever
wonder our dealer all this is food
everybody ok this is a bad for people
out there can't make decisions right oh
yes about that actually we could stab a
little over like one course in each yeah
[Music]
coming up there yeah yeah gonna be in
the block
[Applause]
more super friendly people everywhere we
go big rice bowl food arrived looks good
chicken CICIG and for iPhone
very good lunch was good with fueled up
this mall definitely feels Pasha it
feels kind of like more class in a way
is I I know it's just nice by the lights
and I saw the shops at Mercer it's more
expensive brand
I don't know this our gap it's more Fred
Perry less we've seen it's more bit more
designing yes what I'm saying is the
stuffs it way out of our budget so I
think we're hoping another car was over
to the third more we're going to check
out which is f mp5s MC side and this is
the one that is the sick biggest in the
world
[Music]
thank you so much thank you okay thank
you - thank you thank you
the starter SM I think it's a seaside
the troubled sea side so statements like
the bigger version so we're inside it
looks again massive and I think we are
gonna I notice in lunch I think we are
going to get some snacks here there's so
many let our look another place to keep
your trolleys so nice every night wrap
them is telling us that this is mad
like this is crazy to thing to get a
driving license you have to buy it you
have to take a test no exams it's no
speed limit you can drop you on and
there's no like rules right if we just
absolutely back to lane my mind
hüseyin looking like there are accidents
and stuff but
it's mental like in the UK you have to
look theory test and they look at
practice so like there's so many things
you do it wrong you get fired to get to
him he fails and you don't get a life in
here there's none of that because I was
like so who teaches the kids to drive
never like they just they learn on a
scooter first and then they and then
they buy a car then they just teach
themselves that's crazy but we made in
one piece despite that so one thing that
sets this smaller path and the others is
it's on the seaside so you can actually
see the sea and go out here and get a
view of Paris pretty cool so we're going
to check it out now
[Music]
see the question wasn't what did you say
the other doors make a mix for us for
one she's like bigger super bubbles I'm
like because I loved it in Taiwan and
this is hazelnut flavor YUM give it a
try
what are you doing cuz Pierce air
you're gonna have to you're gonna have
to cut it up you know oh my god so
everyone
all the goodness your urine I'm at
[Music]
what was a softer than Taiwan they were
like more firm these are kind of like
this
and how she sounds so good
we could watch a movie I don't if it'd
be in English thing slice trophy I
haven't heard of any of these films
because we've been away for so long no I
don't go on Twitter okay so it's been
really interesting going around these
three different malls today because
they're so different right they're so
different like obviously they're similar
shops and stuff and some of them trying
to record a serious but this one is the
biggest by far but it kind of icon is
kind of lacking a bit of atmosphere in a
way I know it's late in the day now but
it's very very quiet it's not here the
first one I'd really good atmosphere
those families out kids out and then the
second one was similar I think the first
one had the best atmosphere and then
this one like there's hardly anyone
happened he's very quiet
let's go on more remove it's it's bigger
and there's more shopping people are
spread out more
you
so other than shops and restaurants your
beer there's like an ice rink a cinema a
bowling alley again
with that I don't know toilets maybe
there's salon there's dentist illiterate
hand and foot bars there's anything like
you can live here if you had to like in
this because everything is it I love
this Porsche and Audi showrooms in the
middle of a shopping center we saw this
in Bangkok as well that's pretty cool
and Bentley
the Christmas movie we're gonna get home
now - really tired been walking around
malls for eight hours my legs are shot
to pieces that fill a cup front of
Merritt felt like we've done it justice
no it's a blast of cool malls we hope
you've enjoyed following us around come
around with us today
yeah the visiting still comes this one
but the first one we went to is probably
a favor
that's Heidi bit not not by any clips or
anything but we got a few little bits
yes the beard is getting a trim I've
seen the comments don't worry here we're
gonna we're gonna tidy up a bit give it
a little bit shape but for now we're
gonna end this vlog so thanks so much
works and if you need to the videos we
upload every single day daily blogs on
this channel please give it a thumbs up
if you enjoyed it today and if you are
new please hit the subscribe button as
well that really really helps us out as
your arm okay this camera sweet heavy
for me tomorrow oh yeah you've got
something we're trying tomorrow I think
oh yeah okay interesting
we're not say anything I know thank you
for watching I would be
[Music]
[Applause]