[Music]
good morning guys welcome to and NASA oh
wow a lovely day and welcome to another
day juice and welcome to Manila there it
is lovely
is it wrong to wear glass sunglasses
indoors very bright that's better I'm
back right I'm shattered we got into
Manila last night and it was fairly late
last night checked into our hotel and we
tried to go straight to sleep we enter
the vlog and then try to sleep but we
kind of been up throughout the night
because we slept for too long on the
plane so I think we've messed ourselves
up here our body clocks for a bit
screwed now yeah I do also have a little
bit of a cold George
fair enough he's making the bed I won't
complain I might have a bit of a cold I
had one in England and I thought oh just
cause of the cold weather and then I
think being on an airplane for 13 hours
with air conditioning has made me feel a
bit worse but it's all good I'm
definitely ready to go out and get some
coffee and some food because we have any
instance of breakfast aeroplane food in
the afternoon welcome to a delirious
vlog guys we're back welcome to the
delirious juice delirious daily juice
today thank you bye see you breakfast
[Music]
there's one thing we have been told
about Manila and that is the traffic and
we just had a little experience of it
just then but I'll tell you what it is
nice to step out in shorts in a t-shirt
and in sliders and for it just to be
warm the UK was so the noir thing
they've been so sunny that we have to
adjust it Wow yeah actually can't it's
too bright we the UK was so cold whilst
we were back for Christmas
is this our breakfast place these noises
this is all we heard all night was now
literally all night
[Music]
really I found my mum can you give me
breakfast and rice meat we've come to my
call
Jeffrey Dahmer he found the foot up
lights out
I agree just like to do what you got
[Music]
I think I'm gonna pass and what the copy
is
and God please have the bacon cheese and
mustard
and I have some plain rice thank you so
much
so he told me that was their locally
brewed coffee so I was so happy to be
back is amazing hope is obviously a
breakfast you look good
[Music]
fearow go multi brief pause in the
b-roll this is amazing
[Music]
sighs I guess I see good anyway
that breakfast was very good we can
recommend to this place ready thank you
guys see you later thank you all filled
up ask your turf rice for breakfast
again now there's one thing we need to
do today and that is try and buy a drone
charger we've bought our drone back out
with us this time because we didn't have
our drone last summer in the Philippines
and we missed out on some insane drone
shot opportunities we can find them
anywhere we've come to flat battery a
drone and no charger but there is a DJI
store about 20 minute walk away so we're
going to walk it it's not too fine
thanks
it's not too far so we're going to walk
it and it will give us a nice chance to
walk around Manila a little bit and see
what we think of this place I've got
good vibes so far there is a lot of
traffic is busy it's polluted oh we
heard all night was like honking of
horns and police sirens and stuff but
it's a phone call
doesn't everyone looks like it's really
like hectic like when you get in get
straight back out live even matter
people that have said all you're
spending time in Manila who are you sure
like it loads the Filipinos set up well
I don't know what I mean I mean like I
think it's really cool and I've got too
much of it yeah like we've walked out
the breakfast and now we're down the
street but so far I'm thinking Instagram
closer
[Music]
yeah we warned about the configure yeah
they did mention that
[Applause]
[Music]
really windy today Manila and I've just
met a new friend I'm gonna do this guy's
look how cool that is let me find
anywhere all right let's go in the
comments tell us today is by the way
let's try
[Music]
that one okay we got out results very
good and they said it was closed on the
outside and I was like let's go try I
can see some feet in there let's go
always try it later
it's got a bit warm outside since we
left this morning so we've come into
this it's kind of like a food court and
there's all different tiny little food
schools everywhere and we found
calamansi bar so we're going to get a
little calamansi juice now these are the
health benefits are most interested in
weight loss on the Christmas
[Music]
yeah the old lingo right let's try this
bad boy
I'll get my straw out
[Music]
see these are the bits we usually cut
out
well fresh zesty that's good it's
honestly crazy how much far through
there is hair like we've done always
talking my inside jollibee
everything is cut everywhere Domino's
come with either fast food wise it's
crazy like I can't let is I feel like
there's more fast food places and there
are shots that's probably true like a
lot every corner there something and I
love that every time you say Johnny mean
admit that I was right next door and say
funny
[Music]
I make it every day it's couple of hours
until we meet Nellie a point actually
made Mandy but I don't know when with me
from now we're gonna get so a cloud
architect sort themselves out and then
we'll be up sweet we're hungry it's half
one oh we're back to hotel really all
bad and it's emails that kind of stuff
back on the grind that you have a no it
was about to lose my faith we want to
work harder this year what I work smart
of that is being more kind of efficient
with our time and that sort of thing so
we did a dedicated kind of our email
sit-down session now we need some food
what we're thinking of getting is Chow
King there's one around the corner
nothing too unhealthy we want to be
healthier this year as well but we
remember that they did a big rice bowl
thing I think is a chin tea too bad
unless we see something else on the way
that we like the look
[Music]
thank you fell off my chair
there was our favorite child condition
we did on same thing with you
we have had incense they all know it's
really good and I don't think it's that
bad
I know Frank job means I'm good for you
but the right move I had time to go meet
million mark in their hotel lobby
[Music]
just met my kennelly have a little
catch-up as we walk along very very busy
streets of Manila seems to be getting I
don't know felt like a rush hour here
it's nearly four o'clock Mike knows all
the best coffee spots in the city so I
headed to a coffee shop we're gonna get
planning this January trip
[Music]
hi guys Oh
we made it we all met up we're finally
making a juicy on the front of a exact
how excited out can planning session
going well we nearly know where we're
going tomorrow which it but we are
enjoying some very very nice coffee Mike
knows all the best spots
[Music]
planning session complete
I've been put in charge of these so when
the lady comes out and pulls the number
out it's like bingo I've got to be ready
to put my hand up and get our dinner so
it's a lot of paperwork just for a
dinner yeah shipping is Mike's promise
good thing so we've come to a ramen
place which we really enjoyed when we
were in Singapore recently Mike says
this is the best one in Manila so I can
you take can you cross your fingers
without doing it with the other hand
I thought yes you don't yep I can't I
can't do it come on I can't get it round
no quality content
[Music]
we couldn't get a seat next to Mellie
and Mike so they're over there enjoying
their meal hey guys hey guys hey guys
hey guys
[Music]
hey guys okay this looks incredible
I don't actually know what's in it
the nawaz's I'm used to it
delicious we're heading back to the
hotel now we have loved walking around
Manila today we are definitely way more
impressed than we thought we would be
with this city I know were staying in
Makati which is a slightly different
part that we've really enjoyed walking
around today we've had a really good
time planning with these guys and we're
so excited for our trip excited to it's
gonna be awesome you guys will be
following every step of the way so if
you're not subscribed already make sure
you hit the subscribe button
daily blogs in real time loads of behind
the scenes are stories make sure you
follow us give Nelly a mic a follow to
their details will be in the description
and as always we'll see
[Music]
[Applause]