[Music]
good morning guys early start this
morning 7:15 we are off to the airport
with flying back to the Philippines
design into Cebu who are done with the
Philippines we look forward to seeing a
brand new place clearly to the break we
wanted to see Taiwan the flights worked
out really cool city air really good
time we were going to miss the coffee
here because it was very good at we're
sad that we didn't in time to grab one
more cup of roast coffee this morning
personally with it
yeah we're excited
[Music]
always head upstairs lazy all through
security and everything like that all
the boring stuff out the way we've just
spotted for the most we smelt the most
incredible pastries and it's early this
morning it's not very healthy but they
look so good let me show you okay how
good do these look
[Music]
touchdown in Cebu thank you very much
bye thank you I'm so excited to be there
but we had loads of you guys in the
comments today are you leaving the
Philippines I thought that you should go
through you must try out our I'm from
there what's do this do that absolutely
all right I'll book a flight and it did
tally up in it kind of made sense to
them to go out to Thailand come back in
and the accommodation means that direct
through you like Gretchen calm as per
usual and but we had like a little
message saying you're not say another
hotel this is like my home it's kind of
like the Airbnb situation but it seems
much more like family or any issues I've
got kids and obviously your rooms you'll
remember like we'll be there if you
wanna come and like have a chat with us
watch TV play play a game with chefs oh
so it's so fun it's I can't wait to meet
them they felt so friendly the juicy
vlog do you think
yeah yeah scenic thirteen twelve
thirteen thousand
thank you in the Philippines the juicy
look Ju I see why Georgia Lucy bits
about differently we love we love it we
love the scenery people in one day maybe
yeah thank you
no hot summer that's why I have to hi
anyway thank you very much so right
here's our room gawky good size of you
don't open that because they they it's
very hot here basically and they've they
closed the cans so the Sun doesn't come
in we've got aircon which is really good
but it's gonna take a few minutes to
cool down it's hotter than where we've
come from it's about 32 today the air
would get so we wanted to watch some
previous video to know we've spoken
loads about the Filipino people and
stuff so for this for this state here we
didn't want to book into life hotel with
hundreds of runs which you can do
there's around a some blue here and
there's loads of other big hotels now
we've only done all kind of I don't know
like real experience yeah yeah almost
like we live with the family and this is
exactly what we look for the best friend
Lee may and her sister who met the kids
the girl princess they're just very very
welcoming very very friendly they said
obviously here to a room but feel free
to come downstairs and sit with us
apparently they've got guitar coming out
snow if you're traveling you have the
opportunity to do something like this I
mean back to 350 calm so it's easy today
easy to find highly recommend oh yeah
decorous you get to know people we've
just having a great time the car on the
way you get to know what it's like for
local people to live in yes very
different to like potent experiences
another Filipino so much kind of in
English people know
Filipinos really no I think no just
black oh yes Magister
yeah cool a little we have a home of the
Beatles oh yeah yes yeah yes there was
2007 yeah it was summer I can and then
thought thousand a nice winter about two
degrees there at the moment
freezing is the vision tips
yes oh yes we missed isn't it we miss it
it would say everyone's yeah every day
that's great it's nice to meet you see
you later
enjoy the fish and chips okay that guy
was great
they've been we usually ask people from
clippings if they've been to England the
majority of them say no I like that
security checks coming in shopping malls
we need an England yeah we usually ask
him from the Philippines if they've ever
been to England the majority say no but
he said yes
the majority say no that he had been to
England he he'd been to Blackpool I know
how much that came out of the you
thought yeah I had fit into it every day
every single day it was great
we're now in a shopping mall with we've
come we're in Robinson shopping where
we've come to get some food
it seems pretty big I don't know where
we go it's gonna have a wander round
I've had a nice warm greeting already so
yes nice to call out of here
they weren't at the scooter lady's
different people are very very welcoming
and try their foods we're gonna hop up
in and out like la me baby can order
those food so expect the point that's
why in this video we're going to put up
will it be tomorrow night baby possibly
yeah everything because I think it's
normally it's the food we want to do it
just incredible like a McDonald's
equivalent and more actually agents are
food so we're going to achieve and we
just finished filming the Chow King
video I'm really cool we're finishing
off they kept ringing they kept ringing
Bowser madrunner filter we're finishing
off with a hallo hallo is it good
hey Jordan sounded Jackie wants to try
on but I don't think it's gonna fit him
check it out
oh no it's too small we just st. loads
of choking a hair out that's cool man I
like the look at that but you know what
also makes me look a little bit like a
tennis player that's the only thing I
think what do you think like likely No
I have a big father work for them yeah
all the way from money that we just came
here from several oh you see it's
amazing we're staying I come from words
dang soon like 20 minutes from her great
immediate let's go
[Music]
thank you very much to me thank you
you said you had a guitar yeah he hasn't
played in a long time oh we've been away
with it
[Music]
thank you sure that's amazing
sorry okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's change up a little bit
[Music]
but my next time it down head