[Music]
morning guys welcome to a very special -
Brendan slit so pour the juice of love
daily juice is Lisa's birthday thank you
very much
we've come to our favorite breakfast
spot here we're saying our last day here
we're moving on there's time for one
more breakfast we've been eyeing up the
cakes every time that we come here is it
good
and we've finally got a slice
good amount of writing that's not dry at
all it's just like so good look at it
people would slap it's my alma card it
how cute are they writing happy
birthdays I know so nice the first stop
of today is something called the bamboo
bridge and we've just pulled up I didn't
know what to expect I didn't expect this
like it's so long amazing it's really
cool looks a bit like a nice wobbly and
rails low life we're both quite tall so
I think the railings only gonna like
come to our waste let me show you that's
not high there we can sweat quite much
we'd be nice to have a bit of a dip in
here no I don't think it would
but yeah I can't freely enjoy it
conjugates that was 35 eat so one pound
for both of our bar is it a bargain I
mean I could make a more sturdy bridge
if they're targeting that work that was
a joke for anyone who doesn't understand
our humor well we're not everybody water
yet with this favor there it's not too
bad this is the solid fit yeah I'm a
female get it move or believe me we're
gonna have to keep stopping because a
lot of people here get in the photo any
Instagram obviously know that don't
worry this is like the I'm a celebrity
bridge there's a program there's a TV
show in the UK and Australia have a
version as well where there's a bridge
where they go into the jungle and
normally there's like a firework when
someone might win be the side yeah we
can pretend that we're winning the show
ourselves some fire with the ho idea how
is that it's so wobbly like we just went
one at a time to this minute around
photos and like George's walking putting
one foot here and one foot heck didn't
want to step in the middle it's slide it
back look at that you sit there and it
thing this is your walk out
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you oh we made it go go back now
there's a little shops out here of
course it's crazy cuz our feet and
actually going through it but you can
see here it's literally just made of
bamboo like they've got something
underneath there it's just these bits
here the sole clever
but also pretty fair Oh
[Music]
conservation sucker bar is basically one
came in well but you haven't really
people why here because heat on us care
them of them they're like tiny by
thought they might like this big is like
a fabulous
[Music]
right maybe this one's like this
we've come right through now to the
light souvenir shop you can buy a little
little versions of the Monkees I wonder
if they know just how much they're being
monetized and merchandise oh my god
and get everything you can even get like
a little chest with a little monkey head
on that's cut all my okay look at Lucy
join a few birthday present
yeah these are quite cute let's see oh
yeah if my little sister was still young
I'd get one of these be pretty sure it's
a fatty I know you lost your hairline a
little while ago I did how about we get
you this as a replacement ha ha ha
imagine any item in the world they've
got it here with a little toys they
literally do that Solaris now we never
normally do this but today we bought
ourselves a little souvenir just a
little something to remind us of this
lovely birthday of mine these little
bracelets one a simple black and white
we didn't go for the traditional
touristy ones we went simple yeah this
is mine and that's Lucy's right can you
put it on me I've no idea how you put
them on it was a pan no
there are 50 page Wow yah Padonia garlic
rice we've just ordered a ton of it well
not yet we're about to order a ton of
food
we've been eyeing up this place we've
driven past in most days yes Filipino
restaurant which is amazing and it comes
with and included in the price one of
the best views that we've probably had
for lunch we've got a nice fire table
thank you very much
[Music]
thank you that's great thank you
how excited are you
[Music]
look at this is so much rice yes
reflector
gah oh you think of it okay sorry you've
got spring rolls I comment what these
are oh yeah sure it's a pork belly a ton
of rice and I comment all that is as
well where's the prize in there all
right
Oh No oh yeah
lovely
very garlicky and this mouth though that
office as Travis interested kept firing
extra sizzling gamma
[Music]
yes maybe
chili in Tabasco sauce lovely
that looks amazing dipping your source
[Music]
amazing oh that's my favorite semi to be
in that pork spring roll thing
really nice wow it's all good Oh top
review now these things hold them up to
the camera they look like a pair of haha
they look really good
[Music]
Wow amazing turnout and lunch review
this day is full of changes off plans
we're no longer dropping the bike back
instagrams throw yourself bit sideways
that's what she watching you die haha
yeah
Alan's retakes Alan Anna with a bike
we're having we're not having to we've
decided to extend it for one day because
the ferry our hotel episode is
definitely Council for tomorrow so we
packed a bit another night of them bit
annoying cause literally five minutes
before that we've booked a hotel for one
night in Cebu but it's fine it cost like
five pounds so go for it but the only
problem now is that hopefully the next
day they'd be back up and running that's
the same day as we've got a flight and
the reason we didn't want that to happen
was because we wanted to have a day like
buffer zone almost do K's enemy a quick
I mean this is why we're just using the
buffer zone that we purposely go in one
more night here
and not use a buffer so now I'm glad I
listened to you wow I don't have you've
ever said that before so what else can
you do when your plan fails and it's
Lucy's birthday come out for a little
late night beer and say oh well thanks
for watching today guys
we'll see tomorrow and I'll be 22 why
would ya
[Music]
[Applause]