we go well the morning routine has begun
good morning guys welcome to another
stage juice we're starting off with some
fresh black coffee today as we have done
for most mornings here in Port Barton
I think today because it's a nice day
we're going to try and get a motorbike
again and it's gonna be take two of
trying to see this waterfall
[Music]
but first this is what we need this is
the good stuff and there's a little
cheese in play today isn't a morning
morning
there is we're celebrating today because
today marks Lucy and I been together for
five years
I mean it usually cheers with beer but
this morning right with a coffee I drink
coffee so a very instagram-worthy
breakfast this morning that looks so
good we're now you know with yogurt
it's a freelance YUM I've gone again for
the oats bowl third time now right at
that time yeah this is how they climb
trees in the Philippines
they literally have bare feet and they
were just climbing up the tree very
impressive
looks like it's a school day if your
father wasn't my favorite Austria stop
so 1% out the front I'd like one more
like got warm just written outside
temperature and shears that would you
like apologize for the fruits of the
whole year great thinking she brings
that one and she was like the second one
do you wanna you know I've been getting
you another one for this one's like
frozen if it's like a block of ice
it's perfect one of them is freezing to
drink now and then later the other one
would have melted so that we can drink
really cold will trigger
and our deal for our road trip out to
the waterfall this morning we're going
to pick up our motorbike now try and get
to this waterfall for our life thank you
you won't believe what's happened it
started raining it was so hot and funny
ain't no power and it started tipping it
down because at the same time is our Sun
that's where they can we get to the
waterfall what you have to try it on
it's got a nice finish or
they can see from the color of the
phiiiy nurse of George's t-shirt that
it's a sign rainy again and we had to
find shelter in these trees on exactly
the same Road so we don't know if we're
gonna be able to get out there take two
might be a fail yeah it's very wet on
the road snow although the sun's out
there's big like and holes in the road
and stuff there's a pig over there as
well which is pretty random
we'll give it a go though we will give
it a go bit worried but we'll see
village you're going through like
buildings like right now fools
this is Griff yellow yeah tree I think
they're actually building a road here
ironic
nothing actually building a road show
okay guess what happens it's raining
again we just got through this peak
slushy there and then we've had to find
shelter in these trees because the
cameras in the bag
sorry about these clips being not as
good quality but it better be good I
know it's not even the biggest one of
the two I don't think good off to fuck
thanks and Christmas we bought snacks we
did this guy I know another great part
great historic is in his slider I can't
be on the motorbike because he's too
slippy to push it up so he's on the bike
and I'm pushing it up the hill because
my shoes are much grippier and like I'm
using all of my strength
uphill firstly to push and secondly run
at the same time at the speed that the
bikes going cuz I don't want to hope
slow it down cuz of me being slow
because if it's going quick we need to
take advantage of that and go quickly
kind of this hill
I'm sorry I broke this bloody water feel
better
[Applause]
let's gone up that bet
no we're not we in a basic minute to
level out one we're a bit higher up then
it's okay but if they start there's no
chance again I think this is where we
leave this and then walk but this is
stream to walk through this is what we
need we need one of them
[Applause]
[Music]
you can finally wash off all the magic
competitors and stuff it's really warm
okay we made it to the start of the
water ball
yes rain sunny for this camera way we've
literally just got out of the bags so
annoying
it's another five minute walk here we're
the donation of fifty pesos each other
gates to keep that little hot and things
running and they sell little coconut
stuff so we might go to the water school
check it out and then come back refresh
with a coconut before the treacherous
strike back
[Music]
this is steep oh wow Oh George why are
your own sliders yeah
but about you toys very bad cheaper at
least if you fall I put it on camera oh
thanks and we're walking upstream it's
me we should be getting closer we've
been over taken they've done this a few
times I think there seems to be like
other stream feeding into this one going
down there that it's getting noisier I
think we're getting closer
then expect to see a changing room here
I can hear it
[Music]
babe
we study with
there's room for a quick dip it's very
cold water I bet it's hot today and it's
nice to like fall off of that again
there's no tourists there so like if
you're looking for someone to come away
no fool some foot bath and could be
slightly bizarre and then people having
a nice out of the water
just got some photos right Instagram as
well make sure you're following us this
is a photo I got and this is George this
one and there are names there as well
like film for guys that we do like
regular updates throughout the day on
stories and ok you ready for this drive
back ok that was funny that was probably
the biggest audience we've ever had for
one of our photoshoots
I think Filipino people's like here no
one was really wearing bikinis and stuff
and we and we go swimming in our like
shorts with our t-shirts off Malusi wore
one of them more covered up bikinis like
comes up to your waist dish doesn't yeah
soon as we start again chains loose as
soon as you took your dress off so there
was two hots either side of the
waterfall and this is funny as soon as
Lucy start getting all the guys were
like kind of looking at each other and
within minutes about five guys from that
part came to this heart to watch us
taking photos and apparentiy we're
losers taking photos of me they were
trying to talk to her like this what's
your name what's your name I think we
had a few fans there well not me
ain't Lucy had a few fans there which
was quite funny we didn't want to film
them but you can kind of see in the
background of one of those clips they're
more kind of looking at us and stuff and
their reaction to something they
probably don't see every day
imagine if I was wearing the bikini yeah
oh my can't be more let going down
coming up okay but we need a bad bike
really we need a bike with bad tires
yeah this is not great like a blue
careful scooter powers okay cuz you
can't use much power on the hill and on
this slippy mud but just
awful yeah more losses friends
there are more loose friends
[Music]
[Applause]
okay these are our feet clean we've just
cleaned them
you can see how muddy we got but we made
it back I don't know how we made it back
like that was so hard and it was like
there was more rain or waterfall in her
mind was like this thick and fluffy and
I can't leave my show these have got
straps and velcro I can't lose my shoes
I was like trying to chase the bike and
I just need some food now that's all I'm
thinking about
let's get food no I'll do that again
this our this is tasty this is like a
double chicken burger bun in the middle
we were so hungry sauce just like I need
this
Elise is gone for some Filipino food but
you can carry the chicken curry here is
amazing and I might get it later for
dinner we've come down to the beach now
after filling up with enough food I am
so so full me too and the sun's I think
let's do like oh hang on save me and
then do that look at the color of the
sky let's just face doesn't that good on
coming
it does it does we've actually just
filmed a Q&amp;A video which will be coming
very soon on the channel answering a ton
of questions you guys want to answer no
I'm gonna zoom in a little bit get a bit
more personal okay but one question we
purposely left out of that because we
want to mention it in this video is a
question a few of you guys of art have
we had our teeth whitened and the answer
is yes we have before we left the UK for
our traveling we collaborated with a
company called enlightened smiles and we
got our teeth whitened with the help
from a love teeth dental in Sutton and I
guess enlightened treated us to this
teeth whitening and we had what I had
bonding as well I didn't I so yeah I had
some stuff built into my teammate with
strange sound has been filed and stuff
and you just had the whitening right a
little bit a little bit they kinda
straightened out any ridges and stuff on
your teeth so the process was about a
month wasn't it's about four weeks
yes there two weeks two weeks few weeks
yeah so we have to use a D sensitive
thing
what's worth a D sensitive desensitizing
toothpaste for two weeks
then we did the whitening process with
the trays at home with the gels and and
yeah then you go back into the surgery
you have the in surgery bit which is
like where they do like and stronger
whitening after that they give you
toothpaste to take away Evo white
toothpaste and that's what we've been
using the way it's a really annoying and
annoys you three busts and that's what
we've been using since then and it's
probably kind of taking it round
traveling with us it's so it's like a
normal tool to fight it keeps your teeth
look white yes it's really really good
and you can't get results just by using
the toothpaste it's obvious better to
get the full treatment but if you just
want a bit of a whitening topic then to
place is really good so in light smiles
have given you guys 30% off the
toothpaste on Amazon it's my one yo yeah
if you buy to get better or more you get
45% that's actually quite a lot off and
genuinely like I know there's a lot of
teeth whitening products out there but
when we were chatting to the people at
night and like they've explained to us
scientifically how there's actually make
sense and a lot of the others may not
make them we tried some other ones
before we tried a lot of defining stuff
these are the only ones really that
we've actually seen results genuine if
you go back if you go back on the
channel look at the vlogs where we got
it done we've loved the whole thing we
put in our before and after face my
before and afters like crazy because my
teeth change shape as well as kind of a
look here this is my before and after
light is really really really good stuff
so if you fancy that there's a link in
the description go get yourself a deal
and now we are going to go for a swim
the Sun is setting here and are just
look at this it's our last day in port
barton we don't wanna leave here really
I don't want to need ok swim
yes our last night in port barton so
we've gone for a beer each the Red Horse
beer which is so so good come to
Philippines gets up one of these and we
have ordered a burger the other night
they've run out of burgers and we're
really sad about I saw in the video so
now we're all in America can I say
burger as in one sink in the burger
because we've got our cash so we've
pretty much got our bus tomorrow it's
fine and we've got pretty much enough
cash for tonight's dinner but it's only
and breakfast we can skip breakfast
tomorrow and get a burger each we love
the breakfast we love a morning coffee
or so who sacrificed on the burger but
I've just in another table camera levers
are absolutely huge and they're covered
chips and we had a big lunch earlier so
I think we're gonna be all right sharing
it suddenly turned into a club night
here
the music will and look how busy is the
dance rose packed
okay what this looks no give it what how
does this look so Goods no that's not
fair that beats big are you kidding me
that's so much bigger I'm guessing is
good there
but you can she thought it was really
young
[Music]
[Applause]