good morning today is a work day
[Music]
so every now and then we need to take
like a day to plan where we're going to
book flights to book buses to catch up
on work stuff we've got some client work
to do today to do emails all this kind
of stuff so we thought in today's video
we would bring you a little bit behind
the scenes on how we do that and also
give you guys some tips on how you can
book some cheap flights because we've
got about four or five flights that we
actually need to book and finding the
best way to get from place to place and
the cheapest more importantly is
something we've started to get all right
at so we're gonna bring you in on some
of the behind the scenes today what one
of our planning days kind of looks like
and hopefully give you some value as
well listen I need to book some flights
ourselves this morning so we thought
what better way and time to give you
guys a bit of an insight on how we do
this one of our favorite parts of being
out here and traveling whilst working is
that I like office space is somewhere
like this we always seem to find some
pretty good edit spots there's a pool
behind us a loop we're gonna take a dip
in that moment it's 30 degree heat with
the outside patio area it's great so we
can still like be productive if anything
more productive acts it motivates us to
keep working hard and but we're not like
confined to being on one space we're
gonna book some stuff now and we're
gonna show you guys how we've backed
some pretty cheap flights before like we
thought we've done really well in the
past example of bad planning and a bad
flight booking is when we came to the
Philippines and we had to pick on an
exploit really quickly at the airport if
you've been watching the videos and the
past couple of days you'll know that
story and know that we had a nightmare
we couldn't get into Philippines about
an onward flight the airport we have to
really quickly work one so that's not
the way to do it
you want a little bit of advance warning
do you want to get like a bit of an
advanced booking in like I wouldn't say
I mean it want to see very so much so
checking polite before you book
somewhere but I'd say like the idea
would be like we're talking like for in
six weeks before you're going for
example a Bangkok flight was like was it
250 pounds I want to say which is
through particular distance you're
traveling from London to Bangkok is back
again versus can't that's obsessed with
us hair so skinny
no don't feed it anyway say it one would
definitely be so I have a bit of an
advance warning if you're working it
with the day before then it's probably a
bit too like notice then if it if it's
like months before then you're probably
going to end up like spending more and
these tips by the way aren't just if
you're in Asia like us if you're
traveling around this could be if you
want a cheap life in London really sorry
about this could be if you want a cheap
flight from London if you're looking to
go somewhere if you're back in the UK
anywhere really these are general tips
so the next one and this is a really key
one is date so I mean this in two ways
firstly the date you're actually booking
the flight the date you go on your
laptop and press book can make a huge
difference airlines are changing their
prices all the time and a little thing
we've discovered is that flights midweek
are the cheapest they bump up their
prices on Fridays because everyone's
going away for the weekend Saturday
Sunday flights are more expensive people
have to get back to work so they pay the
premium so if you can book your flights
so the moment you actually sit down on
your laptop and book the flight makes
four that's earlier on in the week just
generally generally airlines increase
their prices as the week's go on even if
you're flying on a Friday or Saturday
look here on the Monday or Tuesday
generally it will be cheaper you can
test this out yourself if you can't be
flexible there's still like ways to get
cheaper flights so a lot of people think
I'm gonna go on a comparison website so
when you're like searching like
comparison websites don't think this is
a right comparison website that's the
whole point Harrison and that's we need
to be looking for there's loads of
different flight comparison websites of
different flights on them so it might be
that one flight comparison website this
flight a is really cheap on this day but
actually and if you look on another
website is actually like say 100 pounds
and then another flight comparison
website might say that flight is
actually 50 pounds on that day and then
vice versa with like be lever so they
can really vary so don't just think
because you've been on a conveyor
that's the only comparison you're going
to get because they vary as well as the
actual Airlines and some of the changes
we've seen have been crazy flights we've
been getting some some really cheap
flights at the moment so some have been
40 pounds which is great then you look
on a different websites can be 27 pounds
or something like that like some places
that will have a deal for I don't know
trying to Thailand fisted I wasn't there
and the other place might not have that
so make sure you're shopping around a
lot you do need to put a bit of time
into it like you could just go on there
and that's fine if you can afford that
but if you're wanting to like us like
save a bit of money and try and get the
best deal possible then definitely shop
around and the other thing if you ask
yourself what can I be flexible with so
dates we've covered the other thing if
you can be flexible with airports you
can save so much money we did this one
when we flew out to Asia for the first
time so we were going from London we
live back in the UK about 40 minutes
away from Gatwick Airport flights from
Gatwick to Bangkok were about six to
seven hundred pounds so instead we
looked at flights from Stansted Airport
which was much further away and the
flights ended up being four to five
hundred pounds for two people so it's
all about being flexible it's all about
finding the right ways so if there's
three or four airports nearest to where
you live or all your destination as well
do different combinations different
origins to different destinations see
what cheapest flight is then one works
that we easily Skyscanner they've not
sponsored this video so another example
of this might be when we were flying and
when we have to get from Cambodia
Vietnam we were looking at the best way
possible and we thought because we're we
were in Cambodia was quite close to the
Ho Chi Minh but that'd be the cheapest
option look at the distance actually if
you look at the map Ho Chi Minh's here
Hanoi is here and we were in Cambodia
here we thought this would be cheaper
because it's closer and always further
away but it actually works actually but
if you look here him putting Cambodia to
Vietnam and for any and citizen taking a
specific Airport and it's insane Hanoi
is it's only small differences here at
43 and Ho Chi Minh's 57 but it is a
difference and it is a saving because
you're being flexible and it might be
then that you work from Hanoi down to Ho
Chi Minh instead of bibble around that
we don't say and again with that if you
can like George said change your origin
so it'd be flexible with London say I
can fly anywhere from London and maybe
get like a bus or a train that's a bit
further it might still work out cheaper
so that work out all different angles
and this is where we absolutely love
Skyscanner is one of our favourite
websites is probably most viewed website
on our commutes right
there are other flight comparison
websites but we love their feature where
you can put anywhere and it will just
give you the cheapest prices as an
example like not where we are and put
London to start any again yes if you're
looking for a little weekend break away
and if you put everywhere so flexible
search everywhere pick a month you'll
want to go for a Christmas break let's
pick December and then you can go to
France for ten pounds Germany for ten
pounds Ireland Italy all ten pound
flights and then you go into it and it
tells you where about Frankfurt that has
the nice Christmas markets it's not so
Hamburg and things like there are
cologne Berlin 23 pounds Iraq this is
great because you can then go down these
are also cheap actually I'm surprised
how cheap they are so then if you think
oh maybe next April you want to go away
somewhere for a bit see it's more
expensive because it's a bit further
away then we were different before but
say when I go to Spain next April
Barcelona at 25 pound erect a nice
little Easter break like it's so cheap
and this is the exact method that we use
to decide generally where to go next
unless we've got like a set plan which
we rarely do so in the Philippines it's
early on out everywhere and then put the
date so we'll be leaving here probably
in November and then it gives us all
these options of places near us but we
could go to today we all.we fancy
Malaysia
working at Kuala Lumpur we can go there
for 39 or maybe we fancy Singapore
Singapore I'll be cool 31 or maybe even
fancy going back to Vietnam ho Chi Minh
40 banter you can see how it works here
okay our next hip and probably the most
important one of this video and the one
that you need to remember if you're
watching this use Google Chrome
incognito mode to search for your
flights and I will explain why so if you
would see in a normal web browser
looking for flights and you search for
flight a couple of times a day and then
you leave it and then you come back
another day and then you leave it again
and you come back the next day your web
browser starts to remember that you're
looking for flights regularly okay and
it saves all this information in its
cachet and it knows you're close to
booking a flight so the web sites
actually increase their prices just
slightly maybe two three four or five
pounds so if you keep searching for
flights they get more expensive
marginally now I got told this ages ago
and I don't I wasn't sure if I actually
believed it so I did my own test so an
example of this was when we were looking
at for our flight out of Hong Kong we
were flying from Hong Kong to
Manila I looked on our usual Google
Chrome and it was something like 42
pounds I've ended an incognito tab and
it was 36 pounds exactly same dates
exactly the same flight it was crazy to
actually see the difference just because
we gone incognito and they didn't have
any information to track us on the tool
and a tip leading on from this which I
only discovered the other day and I've
never heard anyone else say this at all
try different versions of Skyscanner so
what I mean by that yeah you don't even
know is I didn't tell you this what I
mean by that is choose your location so
I was looking on the Hong Kong version
of the website so all the prices were
coming up in Hong Kong dollars which was
fine cuz I know how to translate it so I
noticed this and I thought I let's flip
it on to the UK so I put location UK
currency GBP to make it easier for
myself and it was more expensive it was
like 10 pound more expensive per flight
and you might not think that sounds like
much but when your flights are only 30
40 pounds in the first place that's a
lot of money and that's pretty much what
you'd spend on baggage anyway it's not
like no way I so I flicked it back to
Hong Kong put it back in Hong Kong
dollars paid for it in Hong Kong dollars
and saved ourselves some cash so a
perfect example of what George said I
put in capital somebody here to
everywhere in November this year and on
this page exactly the same this one I
put for that we're in England
English language and great British
pounds and then this one I've still won
it in pounds and I'm still English but
I've simply in the Philippines so if we
look just here Singapore 59 pounds and
then here Singapore is 46 pounds it
works
high-five I think that's my own tip I've
discovered I've never read that anywhere
online before I'm actually really happy
with that
I can tell oh one final tip and as
annoying as it is getting marketing
emails from companies and stuff sign up
to airline newsletters because sometimes
they do these like flash sales and stuff
and you'll have like I know six hours a
day whatever it is to book a really
really cheap flight and you'll be the
first to hear about any of their deals
and we were thinking about doing another
separate video about cheap accommodation
because we've been finally some really
good deals on that as well just enough
to thought here Lucy was saying about
our air B&amp;B
link that you guys can use so literally
all you have to do we'll put a little I
think you'll be a link below and you get
25 pounds off any
don't get you don't have to look in a
thing yet so 25 pounds goes onto your
account when you sign up to it and then
when you decide to go for a little break
somewhere I think you have to spend like
40 pounds and you get 25 pounds of the
booking so you could space stay
somewhere for 15 pounds that's worth 40
pounds so it's pretty good you don't
have to like do anything for it if you
if you just sign up you're like email
address and password or something it's
not that much if you want that wallet
giveaway and we don't work with Airbnb
in any way whatsoever we're not trying
to plug them or do anything like that we
do get a credit onto our own account if
you guys use the link to sign up that's
the only benefit we get it literally as
25-pound if you sign up using this link
that they gave us so we thought we'd
share that so the most important thing
that we have to get done every day
regardless if we're staying in one place
for most of the day getting stuff done
or swimming with sharks and exploring a
new city a new town whatever it is we
have to get the vlog edit it to kind of
take it in terms to edit and we're lucky
that we kind of have a similar kind of
skill set so hopefully when you watch
the vlogs you shouldn't be able to tell
who's edited which because Lucy and I
both have a very similar style and we
don't really have a set routine for who
edits which vlog so it's not like we do
one each and take it and turn sometimes
Lucy might edit ten in a row then I'll
edit six and she'll add it to and I'll
edit five it just depends so if she's
tucked away in there editing I am
writing a new blog post blog post or
something blog post or something we
definitely need to get done on a day
like today I'm currently putting
together a post about our Lightroom
presets so if you missed the video a few
weeks ago where we announced these one
of the questions Lucy and I always get
asked is how do we edit our Instagram
photos which is a great compliment
because it means you guys are liking
what we're doing on Instagram
we both love taking photos we love
editing and rather than replying to
every kind of DM with some advice and
stuff which we were doing we thought why
don't we put together a set of presets
that lets you edit your photos in our
kind of mosquitoes everywhere that lets
you edit your photos in our kind of
start all with just one click so we put
together five presets we named them
awkward desert iced Villa and nomads and
they're all kind of suited for different
style of photos depending on color
lighting what kind of mood you're going
for that kind of thing there's a link in
the description of this video if you
want to check them out if you want to
make your normal standard photos pop a
little bear you don't make your holiday
photos come to life a bit more with
colors and things like that you
before-and-afters here and we're selling
these for just 10
we could have made them more expensive
but we didn't want to ten pounds you get
five presets so we haven't done any
merch or anything on this channel yet
but it's a way for you to get something
from us but also get real value from it
a load of you guys have bought these
already and you've been sending us your
photos and the befores and afters and
stuff so that's really really cool to
see it's also really cool way for you
guys to support the channel if you're
enjoying the daily travel videos which I
know so many of you are which I know so
many of you are from the comments that
we get every single day which is
incredible morning so far into the shark
vlog which was fun to watch back like
that footage
crazy still company happened have a
great day yesterday so I hope you
enjoyed that video and we have edited up
some Instagram sorted out some brand
work I've been working on for a little
while George's written to your blog post
you film another sit-down video we tweet
these days like work hours so it's half
one and it's time for us to go and get
some lunch although we sorta like to do
and we want to kind of enjoy the
sunshine a little bit and this hotel
we're staying and instead of staying in
the room so we're gonna take the laptop
to lunch with us now and get a bit more
work than that but it's cool it's nice a
wall around that a tax oh yeah there's
always time for a swim we just saw them
it was like black covering on my hand
I've ordered some pass down like chicken
pasta with parmesan and what have you
got for noodles yeah philippine aren't
they
but we got another glimpse of this
burger if you saw yesterday's video
you'd have seen us talking about it we
didn't get a shot about them someone's
all past with someone who's willing
service of this burger
it's like 1.5 pounds I can't actually
get we're gonna have it tonight we're
gonna try it tonight so make sure you
keep watching this video to see if we
can handle it
it's the biggest burger I've seen ever
in my life and they don't even offer
other burgers like that's the burger
they do which is massive creamy I must
have spent hours on Skyscanner
earlier this morning it's kind of time
consuming planning traveling turns out
for our next journey we're off to el
nido turns out it's cheaper to cook a
bus through our hotel here rather than
get a flight so that is what we've done
it cost us 10 pounds to get to Orlando
and you don't have to pay the baggage
completers very about all that so we are
very very excited to go though we
haven't yet got accommodations so that's
what we need to look at this afternoon
we need to go on booking comm that's
normally the cheapest way maybe we'll do
another video about booking
accommodation getting cheap
accommodation because that's very doable
as well we use booking.com quite a lot
so that's our next mission for this
afternoon to get some accommodation but
for tomorrow night which we probably
should have done a bit before because
you often get a cheaper deal if you're
booking in advance but then you can get
lost minute deals viki.com can be a big
thing our thinking about you geniuses
yeah we have genius status on
booking.com because we travel so much
because we've booked so many things
which gives us 10% off every booking and
some other benefits
[Music]
the time has come to go any this burger
I'm excited I'm nervous I'm all kinds of
emotions right now look now they were
root yeah alright we're sharing it right
us gonna get a like is huge you won't
believe me until you see it so here it
is Armageddon burgers 350 pesos which is
5 pounds so it's not bad that's pretty
good price for a burger and 1.2 pound
monster burger served with french fries
and go with that we're gonna get some
onion rings as well
they're just for coming out to the
restaurant we closed the office for the
day it is 8:30 and we just finished up
some client work we working on some cool
stuff actually for a new brand to launch
and we're designing some branding for a
launch fund they've got coming up and
some packaging and stuff on that so
that's really cool yeah good day very
productive day our last job of the day
and actually we can't really call it a
job because it's far this probably thing
we like doing the most we are going
through and replying to all the comments
from you guys on the recent videos and
there are literally hundreds so thank
you so so much we still try reply to
every single comment no matter what so
we'd like to try and keep up as long as
we possibly can and it's getting harder
because there's loads more comments but
we're so so grateful so thank you for
commenting on the videos and if you're
someone who watches and has never
commented that's that's obviously
totally fine but if you do feel like
commenting and saying hello introducing
yourself please feel free because we do
love reading your comments it's a it
makes this thing that we do a kind of
two-way thing rather than just us
talking to you all the time
it's nice to hear what you're liking
about videos you can ask questions we
reply to questions on hair stuff so
comments this place to be thank you
thank you thanks I'm a target right
let's get some comparison here this is
an iPhone what if I got a 7 so okay
right that's the iPhone size hold it
like Nick I feel like it don't know it's
big on his camera and it does it does
look great doesn't it it's ridiculous I
feel like that's a normal burger size
like that it's like double ok I put my
hand on it oh you got began
there you go that's kind of great I go
either nothing and these are
ridiculously looking onion rings I
thought they'd be like frozen ones but
these look proper Oh hurt yourself it's
a key and then okay we're going to cut
it because there's no way we can eat
that oh my god that knife just went okay
first section which is bigger than the
size of a normal burger anyway oh wow
oh my god yeah right on take a bite to
get really we did it
we finished it other than we little bit
of bread that we left which to be honest
was probably the equivalent of a whole
barn or Mille burger we finished it and
we left only to onion rings which is
pretty good we need to sleep this off
guys so we're gonna end the vlog here
thanks so much for watching today give
the video a thumbs up if you enjoyed it
and obviously leave a comment say hello
and we will see you oh if you're not
subscribed because we were looking on
our analytics the other day are still
literally red sunburned we were looking
on our analytics over there something
like 65 to 70% of people who watch the
videos aren't subscribed so I was trying
to do mental maths and I couldn't be
everyone who doesn't have anyone who
isn't logged in and subscribe but
watches these subscribed we'd like we'd
hit 10k like tomorrow so if you're not
subscribed please hit the subscribe and
it helps us out so much amis we continue
making these travel videos for as long
as possible so we appreciate that thanks
guys we'll see tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]