so we just real we just realized that
this video looks very white angel we
didn't really all right welcome back to
a new video today we wanted to talk
about the Philippines and how exactly
you should travel it travel it travel it
travel it and how exactly you should
travel the Philippines hey
[Music]
would you do one day is a light try and
do it live and remember oh my god be
hilarious but I really bossy yeah so
when we actually decided that we went
into this the Philippines
I felt very like daunted by the idea
purely because when you google how to
visit Cambodia Vietnam Thailand most
places in Asia
there's things everywhere online and how
you visit and do the roof because it
kind of normally like in one block of
land or maybe there's a few islands off
of it
the Philippines had over 7,000 islands
so when I first saw that up I was like
okay so how do you see them all I
remember you sending me links and photos
and stuff and we were like wow this
place looks incredible the beaches the
scenery we have to go and then it was
like okay how do you actually plan it
where where do we go how we get around
yeah and I guess like how you pick which
islands you want to visit because you
want to see like the best place don't
you and obviously like you've only got a
certain amount of time getting at one
place you don't want to make the most of
it and you want to think how quickly
don't want to move around how old one
even each place we've just finished just
over a full month of traveling the
Philippines so in this video we're going
to explain exactly the route we took
what we saw how we booked it how
expensive things we'll have cheap things
where we stayed we're gonna give kind of
like a full itinerary I guess and we've
had like probably when it is for me the
best month of traveling so far yes from
our favorite place honestly don't be put
off by how many islands there are that
should make you more excited and it is
easy to travel around and we've learned
that now we actually hadn't planned this
before arriving had we because we but no
plan flight to palawan because we were
told that's where it's a good place to
stop and we didn't book a flight out and
then we got told at the airport before
we got into the Philippines that you had
to have known would fly Lewis do you say
we didn't research enough and then at
the air could be had to book a flight
out oh okay two weeks that might be an
ass book that's like bits of Taiwan it
wasn't until we'd spent that two weeks
there that we thought okay we need to
come back and we need to come back quick
because there's so much more to say so
then after four days in Taiwan we
back for another few weeks so if you're
flexible enough to spend an extended
period of time the Philippines we would
recommend a month we're going to talk
you through exactly what we did in that
month we're basically going to start the
beginning and work our way through our
routes now we're not saying this is the
perfect Philippines route by any means
there's still so many places we want to
go we're actually going back there very
soon but for a first-time first trip we
can hundred percent recommend the route
that we did because we absolutely loved
it and we saw quite a few different
places as well I feel like we didn't
spend too long anywhere we moved around
quick enough to get to know loads of
places very different so we arrived from
the Philippines around October and left
in November I don't know when the
perfect time to go would be I think
April May June is kind of sunny and we
want someone timing right now today I
think we're ending rainy season but
honestly it rains for like one hour a
day
it clears so quickly it's still hot I
didn't mean there's less people yeah oh
yeah that's a huge positive actually
and it didn't hinder our experience at
all so maybe do a bit of research on
what time of year to go but from what we
did it was absolutely fine we started in
Padawans as we said we had absolutely
zero expectations like we didn't know
what to expect we didn't know what the
food was like that people were like how
much things cost really we never quite
cheap as most Asian countries are but we
really didn't know what to expect did we
and we kind of went in very open-minded
and really made our way around as we
went yeah so just before entering the
Philippines we were in Hong Kong the
best flight for us to fly into
Philippines was to go to Manila which is
probably the most popular airport that
people fly into we then had another
flight from Manila to port princess or
in Palawan where we started off
Philippines adventure so we were in
Palawan really excited we were looking
around for things to do the first thing
on our list that we wanted to do there
was swim with whale sharks now you can
swim with whale sharks in the place
called odds lob in Cebu is another major
city but there they feed them they
entice them in there's way more tourists
you you're guaranteed to see them it's
not like an unnatural experience the
clear you know you're gonna see one it's
not there's no excitement but us of
course Princesa
people we told in other place
they were like you saw a workshop in
port-au-prince essa really even even
Philippine have you ever been surprised
yeah because you're not guaranteed to
see well hard trick went out with two
votes our boat saw one yeah the other
boat was over there somewhere they
didn't get see on the whole day so they
were disappointed but I've spoken about
this before it was like the best moment
I've ever had like seeing that jumping
in the water
opening your eyes and there being this
huge whale shark in front of me like a
cool I like thinking about it now I see
tsunami so definitely try and get
yourself an authority yep as shopping
imports princesa which we didn't do much
of the only main activity we did there
was the whale shark swimming so we only
stayed I think it was tonight it stayed
in a hotel called a cassia tree it was
probably 20 25 pound a night really nice
really nice breakfast there was a pool
there a good place to stay just for us
to go and do that trip there's
definitely cheaper place in the spa day
so like I feel like awful-looking
disappearance we buried we stayed in
some places that were like 10 pounds and
I some were like 30 pounds and I feel I
can kind of spend what you want so after
that we got a bus to somewhere called El
Nido and that's got to be a top place in
the Philippines definitely going to el
nido it's just beautiful we got a bus
that was about five hours we booked it
where do we go to our hotel
yeah so basically every hotel you go to
will be able to book you next play the
next place two tours but airport
transfer mat load assassination it was
about a five-hour journey and it costs
five or six pounds each so really cheap
I wasn't actually bargain yeah really
good I'm quite distance we'll put in a
map here from Port witness to El Nido
and you can kind of see the distance we
traveled in El Nido we stayed somewhere
amazing called peak house gardens and
again it was probably about 20 pounds
and I amazingly friendly staff and it
was a really good location because the
main pit and I'll need oh it's like a
little strip of loads and loads of
restaurants it's right next to the beach
and we did different talk yeah but it's
all kind of small so it's really nice it
doesn't feel like a huge touristy resort
or a touristy strip it's kind of only it
probably takes about 15 minutes talk
from one end to the other
yeah and within that you've got the
loads of cool little bars and
restaurants shot yeah and it wasn't that
busy the time we went there wasn't that
many tourists around so we were kind of
coming from Thailand and Vietnam we were
like wow this feels really kind of
almost untouched
we get to some even more
types to place further in this video but
for us El Nino was so so cool we did
some great trips as well while we're
there so actually we spent quite a long
time in our new day I think it was maybe
five or six days in the end it was we
did stuff pretty much every day so we
did a zip line from one little island
across the beach to the next which was
amazing
I highly recommend that we did and two
different day tours so there's there's
ABCD and Zed beds like a party tour
which we didn't do and then a B C and D
take you on a boat in the daytime too do
you like beaches lagoons we did tour a
and C we can highly recommend both of
these tour a was amazing when someone
asked me what's highlight traveling so
far I always say Torre and El Nido
because it absolutely loved it it's like
a definition of paradise there's like
these lagoons you can get a kayak secret
beaches that you have to climb through
rocks to get to wait three thought it
was just such an adventure so I
definitely recommend booking tour a in
our need oh and if you have time tour
see about 15 pounds 4cn about 12 pounds
for a I think so again a whole day on
the boat lunch included it's well worth
they're such a bargain also an El Nido
you have to go to an ice cream shop
called gusto the girls and they are so
friendly we ended up staying there for
like an hour one night eating ice cream
the best ice cream in the world there's
a marina that's because you can go to
and for the days as well so I'd say
about five or six days about right I'd
say that's the place where you'd spend a
bit more time if you definitely it
wasn't that expensive food was maybe a
little bit more expensive than some
other places just because it's a little
bit more tourists yeah I guess yeah the
price is slightly but still we could eat
a meal with a drink for maybe six or
seven pounds yeah
and that was like with like the side
dish and stuff so you could probably eat
for about five of the two of you if you
wanted to yeah the next plan was
actually to go to somewhere called Quran
and we still haven't been yeah I'm still
sad about this me too like we had a
fairy-book got that five the morning it
was canceled due to weather loads of
people have said to go there we still
want to go there so I'd recommend
putting it into your trip because it's
only a ferry away from El Nido but we
can't tell you about what it's like
because we haven't been yeah but keep
watching we'll go exactly we will go now
to you but from what we've seen it looks
amazing it looks like an even quieter el
nido similar kind of thing and actually
Bart and mrs. Porter princesa this is
the El Nido and port Bartons in the
middle so if you can I spend a night or
two in port barton because you get the
bus to el nido go back to port barton
and then fly out from the port of
Princesa again and as it's on the way
like it's a lovely if it's like a little
town if it feels really local there's
some lovely beaches we did a great day
tour of about place as well I'm an
island hopping
cheap cheap accommodation because it's
really touristy at all really cheap food
remember that are really really are you
eating for maybe three pounds for the
whole meal our accommodation I think was
seven or eight pounds of night yeah it
was super cheap there was no choice
about local people on local beaches
doing a really good experience we were
almost glad that our plan was forced to
changed and we went there it was really
nice but then I wouldn't spend like a
week there probably because there's
other things you want to see if anyone
yeah so maybe two nights in port barton
that would be good vibhuti really good
cafe good Wi-Fi you took a van from port
barton back to port princesa and it was
like a like a five or something and then
we flew out of course princesa and we
went to this was when actually our plan
change because we went to Taipei and so
we're going to take that out obviously
we had for four days for us which the
two ends of the Philippines together
yeah so then now that we're flying to
Cebu exactly which you can do from what
to Princesa
so Cebu is much more like a busy city
full of shopping malls he's got some
great food it was really much changed
for us after the Paradise beaches of
Palawan to flick back into that city
life yeah experience some amazing huge
Filipino shopping laws because they know
how to do shopping malls there we ate
some great food we went to a street food
market we did we did some really cool
stuff in Cebu including highlight of the
trip for both of us which was
canyoneering and power sand falls that's
amazing and now you can either we did
saying in Cebu because be a bit short
and time we took a three-hour journey to
and three-hour journey from this place
all can get picked up from that or you
can send well barfi a bit more time i
think there's stuff like the end the
sardine run which is a really cool that
experience underwater with a fish and
there's a few more things to do that i
think but again we didn't go there we
actually found time wise we only wanted
to do the canyoneering
point and timelines it made sense to
have a bit of a longer day you don't get
picked up from somewhere in Cebu City it
was really easy to arrange as well we've
got online it was super easy prices in
Cebu slightly more expensive because
it's more proper restaurants restaurants
and shopping malls or restaurants on the
street
and you can still find street food and
stuff you can find cheaper places the
place we stayed was really cool we
actually did a homestay so we stayed
with a local Filipino family and she
only charged us ten pounds a night we
booked it on booking.com so it wasn't
hard to do and if you're up for a really
kind of cultural local experience we
would definitely recommend state doing
one of these home states the one we used
was called Mae's home away from home and
she picks up the airport
so maybe four nights in Cebu including a
day doing the canyoneering
yeah sounds good I wonder if these days
are gonna add up to a month oh no one
work it out don't work it out rough guy
roughly a month don't worry about it the
promise of food we then took a ferry to
somewhere called Bohol which was another
highlight for us we found it this is
amazing yeah really cool it's so varied
when hire a motorbike Gomez motorcycle
rental go and get a bike off Allen he's
a great guy he recognized us from the
blogs it was hilarious at a very cost
eight pounds I think between eight to
twelve pounds each from Sabine and it's
really easy about two hours book it
online
we actually have problems going back
because of the typhoon so we actually
almost missed a flight the next place
but again be flexible in the Philippines
things can change but I found the story
hey so the thing we loved about the
whole is that we stayed in a city called
Tagbilaran City above the city amazing
forest the chocolate hills you have to
do the tarsier sanctuary we did this
funny ziplining thing on a vibe over a
bigger jungle was the best motorbike it
was the best bike ride that we've done
traveling is about two hour drive
through this huge open roads no traffic
winning our really really cool
experience and then this south of the
city is somewhere called panglao island
which is beautiful beaches like great
snorkeling less restaurants and it's
just so varied like you can stay in the
middle and experience both yeah and I'd
say like
for five days four or five days
definitely if you want to go back and
watch our vlogs from the whole you can
see exactly what we did there but I'd
say definitely rent a motorbike because
tango on tours you can hire a driver for
the day but then you're kind of strictly
it's better to do on your own honestly
we we felt so free we could spend as
long each attraction anyway yeah
tamper coffee yes best breakfast spot
really good so after the whole we had
planned to go to Boracay now we were so
excited about this and we nearly didn't
get to go off every was canceled from a
hole back to Cebu we had a flight booked
from Cebu to Boracay but it was all fine
we went the next night fine a so yes
we've got the two-hour ferry back to
Cebu we got taxi from Cebu to the
airport and we made our flight it was
all good we Boracay has been closed for
six months for restoration rejuvenation
of the beaches clean up this huge
government project that's been ongoing
it's absolutely stunning we've we've we
filmed a whole Boracay video here which
you can go watch see our first reaction
of seeing the place so a few tips what
to expect in Boracay you need to have a
hotel booked before you arrive leaders
before they let you on to the island
they check where you're staying
it's like an approved list of hotels
that are complying to the government's
new regulations yes
hotels are a little bit more expensive
in Boracay because it is a touristy
destination and I think seems to be
opening Nelly and Mike from making it
happen we met up with along with that
and they said that the prices have gone
up 30% Wow and that's food tours hotels
like it's more expensive than half for
sure I need to feel it
compared to UK prices but it's more
expensive than other Filipino places we
stay somewhere called Club 10 beat
charts it called Compton Beach was all
really really nice place serve breakfast
on your balcony every morning it was a
walk to the beach oh yeah two seconds
away from the beach recommend staying
there we did five days in total in
Boracay no don't for four days we do
longer they definitely do longer if you
have it's just so nice best beach we've
ever been on the core of the water
absolutely insane a heightened sense
recommend boracay beach could be that's
been more quieter yeah because it would
drag on the main white beach was very
busy like this is a tourist destination
a hundred percent there's so much
building works still going on the main
road behind the beach it's still a
complete building site so within the
next six months to the I reckon that's
gonna
full of brand-new hotels and resorts of
stuff this really is the touristy place
of the Philippines still a really cool
place is insane Beach still recommend it
I think we've come to the end and that
brings us up to a full month for us in
the Philippines I mean I think there's a
few places we still want to visit right
so I try not to see where we end up
going next year that we are visiting a
few places for sure the Philippines and
if your Philippine I'm watching this
please let us know where you want us to
go if you've got any recommendations and
places we definitely have to see we'd
love you to comment below and let us
know it's a little lift up my phone and
every time you comment something of
where to go I right and it would know
there's so long so basically if love you
comment the same place that's gonna
catch our attention that yeah and we're
gonna definitely want to go that we're
so excited to get back to the
Philippines get traveling and see more
the easiest videos helped you please
give it a big thumbs up we hope we've
kind of covered most of the things you
need to know in terms of money so it
it's cheap
the food's amazing you're gonna love it
basically it's easy to get around and
the people are very friendly and helpful
so if you're thinking or how do I get
from here to here ask a local that's
what the hell if you've got any
questions off the back of what we've
said this video pop them below we have a
chat down there and if you're new to the
channel please subscribe the daily
travel videos so anything you add we of
course as always we'll see you
[Applause]
[Music]