and good morning welcome to another day
juice
[Music]
about for breakfast this morning it's
insane it's like coconut milk porridge
right with this peanut sauce but it's
like it's so much nicer than peanut
butter I don't know why it's different
but it's tasting little is that fresh
fruit it's really good right side of the
day and the coffee here is great we are
both very very excited today because we
get to explore port barton today
properly we arrived yesterday afternoon
fairly late so yes there was kind of
just a travel day just get in here and
gain saw it in our room and stuff but
today we're gonna go and properly
explore see what this cool place has to
offer there are like zero toys to us
where we've seen like a handful maybe
genuinely probably about six other
tourists we can rent a motorbike from
our hotel which is great news and I
think we're off to explore a waterfall
and then another amazing Filipino beach
so excited for today the weather's good
although there's a very very big great
cloud there
everyone and we have to water pool the
other side raining we don't need to go
to the waterfall now no yeah
[Music]
so the plan now is to try and go and
find a motorbike to hire and drive to
the waterfall yeah I've seen loads of
people on bikes feel good about for
tourists I've seen which is probably
about 8/10 of the twists that are here
in port barton so we don't know if it
will be busy it's kind of rainy still
and the roads are pretty much just
rubble and dirt so we're not sure what
the drive is going to be like we're full
of bad ideas where is his face do you
see it
nope I've no idea rose
your local water short just around the
corner from our base is actually the
center the fact we had like vegetables
the water and a basic stuff and I think
that people are in a ver they're asleep
hello we couldn't wake them people up
that was too harsh they're having a nice
little afternoon now if we're going to
finish off instead
check out these eggs
I've never seen eggs that color
found the place simply go bike for us
okay my favorite color that will do
usually we treat you here to a very
cinematic sequence of us riding a
motorbike however every name have opened
yet again so we need to put this camera
way
sadly the GH five becomes the panasonic
GT part that we use is waterproof but
the lens that we use but now we're gonna
fuel it and we're gonna try and get this
waterfall if it stops raining we'll let
you guys know and get you out of all
that but until then you're stand-in
there so the rain stopped but we don't
get the camera out yeah because it bags
like soaking wet so we're gonna just be
on this phone for a little bit but
honestly we just went through like it's
much in this bonus Buy
and it's crazy things we've had our legs
down wheels spinning and then one of the
locals on their bike that's probably
quite similar to this one just went
through quite speed and we were there
like
sorry so yeah you know but ten minute
drive now first 10 minutes seems to be
the topic of hope
but I think that kind of climbing now so
maybe my getcha yes and
after abort mission here we've come this
far up this hill but look at my shoes I
think this is better than it was down
there I was holding on to the back of
this and the back end was kicking out
mud and if I wasn't holding it up right
we're just slid over so many times and a
few people to support past us and went
don't even bother trying but the road
gets even worse up there sure it's fine
we might go to a different location
a gorgeous location it's just not really
a day forever I don't think we're gonna
see a waterfall today but now to be
honest I don't even know if we're gonna
be able to get down this hill so
genuinely like I don't even want to film
it it's like that
I think you've all right gonna turn
around I pull it off like what I'll do
if you lean right back I'll hold the end
and keep it back but Mike I've got this
all right let's give it a go
[Applause]
why are you going in there reverse are
you turning the wheel
[Music]
drive down really really fast
go and really say go
okay guys this is the waterfall we're
seeing today lovely look at that
beautiful waterfall the greatest success
failure is that where's our success here
then okay you can see we mean here
there's a literally a car that's going
down this slowly whoa oh wow
[Music]
No
okay when all else fails you know what
we do on this channel we get food we've
stopped here this is supposed to be like
the cheapest
like the affordable restaurant I think
so some I like affordable restaurant for
locals and tourists in town for both
local and foreign Rodan
so we're gonna see what they've got a
bit darkness another finger film but
we're gonna get some food and then we're
gonna try again not the waterfall though
I'm surprised we survived that we barely
did
so cheap so I've ordered to hurry I
think it might be similar to when we had
better and that's really good
I'm George's only gone for fried noodles
yes the mills were one pound 43 smells
and they look quite big as well so it's
a good like a nice little find I think
it's gonna save us some money here if
you come here any more time noodles and
curry - dropped our bike back off and
now we're at the annual port part and
Battle of the Bands the first bands just
died pretty good we're on the judging
panel of song afternoon so checking it
out we're not sure if this is a school
or proven meant to be in here I think
it's like a village hall that we've
wandered in anyway
no one's told us to gap about start a
second song I don't know like what 12
years old or something they can play on
them you'll be fine and wear ties
Halloween
[Music]
so we've just realized this is a
Halloween party
we're pretty sure this is a soundcheck
for the main show tonight everyone seems
to be get ready galas Halloween's not
ready foam banners off so we might go
watch sunset on the beach and then come
back tonight for the party
[Music]
nathless like reading and
we're flying in this Friday night isn't
it
this feels like so much less touristy
than if it needs to like it
everyone's house that is here and that
is chilling out and with their family
they feels like real genuine local
village
maybe the whole chorus does
[Music]
I think it's like the main beach stretch
and unlike el nido where it was tourists
with the occasional local that's all
though
and up everyone that was possible
I like this what you can see here this
is busy this is like the busiest we've
seen it and let there's like 50 people
maximum
[Music]
after the Halloween party now got my got
my costume on I thought this was scary
enough without any masks or makeup no
I'm not sure I'm not sure if people
dress up actually because we didn't see
anyone dressed up earlier but they were
still getting ready for the party so
we're gonna head down there now see what
this Halloween party is all about yes we
are going for dinner first we are going
you can probably guess already we're
going for burgers and the reason for
that is one I absolutely love burgers if
your review of the channel for at least
three videos you will realize that I
absolutely adore a good burger like has
to be a decent burger Lucy also likes
burgers not quite as much as me and we
got talking to the girl athlete cafe the
other night and she was saying oh my
husband runs a burger restaurant on the
beach you have to go his temps a
discount so we're gonna go and check
that out tonight we've got a discount
card burger Halloween party it rains
they badly earlier we're having to walk
like three mud and we've this massive
puddle and we're not sure how we're
gonna get around oh hey oh really okay
oh yeah it's dry that's right and George
is wearing sliders again here we are the
burger place
know where it is you've got quite a long
wait when it's not the way it's like
five minutes but compared to everything
else smell burgers
so they run our burgers human
generations we got up this fight
we got chicken quesadillas blue sky
chicken burger which is like halfway
there we just made some really really
really nice people from Ireland and they
said they were gonna have like our
videos so if you happen to be watching
this one then it was great to be used
hope you enjoy El Nido was very very
jealous emotions being there
[Music]
okay that was interesting it was nicely
the whole village coming together and
having a bit of a party the band was on
we went with our new Irish friends which
was really cool they introduced us to
their boat captain from the tour they
did he like spotted them he was like oh
yeah like it's like come over come over
and we ended up sitting at the table
with these like my five boat captains
they were just laughing but they were
speaking so quickly like in their
language we didn't know although same
but they kept laughing and like
high-fiving us and stuff like that so
tomorrow we have a tour booked we're
very very excited for that we're gonna
go out in the water yeah imma see input
button and see what's going on see
what's going on underneath the sea as
well so it's not being talked and I
think there's a chance that we might see
Turtles tomorrow which would be very
cool because we didn't see turtles in El
Nido thank you guys so so much for the
recent comments and views and
subscribers and everything like that I
think we're we're like so we're like
this close to here in 10 K it could
happen overnight
which is just absolutely crazy so thank
you guys so much if you are new please
subscribe let's keep this going and give
the V a thumbs up if you enjoyed
watching today if you're brand new we
create day travel videos every single
day we're currently in Southeast Asia
but it's a lot more places to see so so
make sure you are subscribed and see you
tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]