[Music]
London Heathrow we're going back to the
Philippines today's actually a pretty
easy travel day so although it's 13
hours of flying it's one flight which is
super easy they've only just started
doing this fly and it's London Heathrow
and all the way to Manila and it's just
perfect isn't it because there were so
many others that was there with one that
like 60 hours with four changes and they
were like no no we're not doing that
it's time to reverse the Hat back in
travel mode like a way of a hat
backwards more in traveling we've only
flown with the Philippines at Airlines
once before and that was a short flight
in the Philippines so we look forward to
testing out this testing I'm really
hungry you hung like seriously hungry
I'm glad you said it
I'm glad you said it I'm starving as
well
[Music]
so what do you want for dinner I'm
really hungry I'm starving mac already
guys asked moaning about being hungry
all the time didn't take long be there
all day terminal 3
not that good of food choices we've
already looked online before we got
there there's much variety there we'll
find something quick tip if you are
taking this flight we just checked in
online to save ourselves this queue
y'all gonna be healthy in January but it
starts when we get definitely this our
last English meal just look at the
burger oh look at this it's a beautiful
beautiful beautiful thing
the final burger so it's a good idea to
drink the fourth version our fry or is
that the probably not laughs here's to a
Philippines adventure
[Applause]
[Music]
no coffee shop is there but it's way too
late for coffee now we are boarding in
about I should have no idea when are we
boarding thing soonish so if you're
interested in this flight we're gonna
miss our flight so you can play piano
[Music]
okay
okay such a big audience here for you
how nice big crowns in the crown that's
lovely oh no that's okay cuz I could
play for another hour
no no I've got a long walk ahead of if
you're interested in this flight it's
the only direct flight from London to
Manila it cost us about five hundred
pound each which pretty good for the
distance five hundred pounds we also
added on extra legroom for ninety pounds
so it's about twelve hundred pounds for
two of us to fly from London to Manila I
don't know when this flight started we
said we were trying to work it out
earlier but apparently like a newish
flight we've not sure what plane it is
but we'll let you know
we jealous of all the people going in
business class leg room
[Music]
ok let's go we go go fly fly now this is
always good
go to get water and there's nothing
there thirteen hour flight and we land
in Manila I think about 7:00 in the
evening there time we've got the first
hotel booked with their meeting Mike and
Nellie but that's not for another day is
there where we can sit down with them
and plan the rest of January we've
literally Lian Philippines we found
nothing
we've literally planned nothing nothing
boats no fights but no hotels books we
can have a planning session with them in
Manila at some point I'm in a couple of
days that's why but yeah players is all
right let's go
[Music]
we've been excited for this for a long
time so thank you all for your
suggestions in the comments every time
we read every single comment every time
we see it suggests never a place we
should go write it down on a little
notes page on our phone there's only so
much you do this trip is more or less
planned around your suggestion so for
things so much well it will be planned
on for as we found there yes planet
planet shorten everything okay we're
happy with our leg room we've got
actually a lot of leg room
you can stretch fully out okay and we've
got pillows blankets headphones screen
to reunify and the people in front of us
in premium economy don't actually have
as much leg room as we do here so that's
why this is a blanket you get headphones
and oh hello I think we're gonna be all
right lil friend
very impressed with the onboard
entertainment everything for James Bond
still have my little exudates we're
going on like James Bond on
there's hundreds and hundreds of movies
[Music]
and dinner breakfast but eventually but
five o'clock in the evening human at a
time so
I think we're going to be the cities
when we get to our hotel date I think
we're going to still think it's like
morning and I hope you can sleep because
it's like one of those like
the last long flight we did was coming
home from Singapore to England to the
other week and this have to say is a lot
comfier we had extra legroom on this
flight with the extra leg room here is
much better honestly as I've been able
to I'm 6 foot 3 ish and I've pretty much
been able to stretch out the loot
boy Filipino name serves up to Manila
the time is 5 minutes past the hour of
17 DME and the date today is the 7th of
January 2019 Monday I'll take go
temperature is recorded at 27 degrees
Celsius manila airport we have arrived
I'm very confused it's like we left in
darkness we thought here in darkness
it's almost like it was just like it
feels like an hours passed or something
in a weird kind of way
and we're here that's a good thing
hopefully we've known as they've still
got Christmas decorations up here which
makes us quite happy because we were sad
to be leaving Christmas behind in the UK
but we know in the Philippines that it
is celebrated long months
I was worried that I'd be too hot coming
back we've been used to the cold now in
England I mean like a full-on like fix
Jimmy got some SIM cards I'm at the
airport and get some cash out we're
pretty much ready to go now and we just
order to grab got the grabber
oh then one's come in they have a fan of
Strobl it's been ages come on guys
there's nobody well babe look at grab
grab usually as the plane yeah get a
photo yeah
that's good we've literally just moved
off the plane and we've already bumped
into some of you guys so thanks for
coming up say hi if you do ever see us
always say hi it's taken about 20
minutes for us to get a single grab
driver but we finally got one and we're
being picked up now about 20 minute
drive to our hotel
we just got to our hotel and this is the
view this is so good yeah no this is the
thing as I was saying a min ago we
haven't spent any time in Manila at all
when we first came to the Philippines we
flew into Manila and then we went
straight out so we're spending a few
days here at the beginning of our trip
meeting Nelly and Mike tomorrow who are
staying at hos that we can see their
hotel for windows is hilarious and then
we're gonna do a few more days at the
end of our trip in Manila as well to
check out some of the things if we want
to check out I think the biggest
shopping mall in the Philippines is here
okay we showered we freshened up and
it's time to talk 20 19 goals but first
let me this yeah that's not good at all
this hair Scituate alright we're gonna
have a little poll in the comments in
today's video I look like an egg we're
not a little poll in the comments in
today's video haircut or no haircut just
comment below if you usually comment say
whatever you like but make sure we
include in your comment haircut or no
haircut like long hair I'm always in
your could stay just as my life we were
speaking about our 20 19 goals on the
plane over here tonight we're not going
to share them all with you now but one
of them is to just really go hard with
these vlogs we want to make them even
better more cinematic more entertaining
more informative more fun so please let
us know what you like seeing in the
blogs we are we are just so excited to
get going on me we haven't even used on
your GoPro yet we cannot wait let us
know in the comments what your 2019
goals are what you're working on this
year what you want to smash you know our
little phrase do the thing which we have
those are the three words that Lucy and
I live by do the thing do the thing that
you love and I think this year needs to
be the year that people just go for it
they take that leap make that decision
do that thing that's been putting off
but what they really want to do and I
cannot wait to see what this year brings
us and I don't mean us me and Lucy I
mean us all of us all of us together we
are so so grateful for our community on
here we're gonna jump in the comments
and reply to a ton of you so thanks to
everybody says hello in the comments we
will see you in tomorrow's
where we're gonna explore more of Manila
please give this video a thumbs up if
you enjoyed it if you're new to the
channel please subscribe and as always
guys do the thing we will see you
tomorrow
wait wait the music my guess
[Music]
[Applause]