good morning guys today we are doing
tour see here in El Nido and we're very
very excited it's all complete different
stops to what we did the other day so
we're kind of got an explorer paradise
again the hotel this morning I've done
is proud
they've given us some black coffee thank
you very much thank you thanks so much
[Music]
just got to the office again we're doing
this tour again we've got the same talk
our different towards different let's
out with man the bang again because it
was over before we'd come back from off
of it the first mission of the day is to
find some Sun cream because we've run
out and it's absolutely are staring at
one very sunny which I'm not complaining
about that my skin burns like that
quickly so need some great bang ten more
money I've prayed for makes its mind
about right here's not all guys from the
other day
sadly he's not doing today's at all but
we've got another wanted to be fine but
just as good we said who's better
[Music]
I'm not yet sure how today is gonna be
able to top the other day but try our
best
somewhere in Tyler meet people walk
through the scene in our blue bag again
we've made some friends already
[Music]
I know people you
so here I got island and we can even
channel to be go snorkeling it's nice
and kind of choose we want a dress
[Music]
just got off the boat and it's crazy
Lagoon or whatever you call it
unavailable and there's two ways to go
here so we can take the easy way several
teams of doing but the guy the guy said
if you want to go this way it's really
cool but it's more tricky and so what do
you think we're gonna do I'll so you're
gonna try this way if the next clip is
me like on a rock like that sorry mum
will be fight it skin define adventurous
try and anything being brave and
everything and then it's like tiny kids
doing the same thing you can see what I
quoted here to meet you wouldn't know it
was here look she's climbing feel that
it was a cave and then again like the
palm trees huge cliff to me award for
what's and I think I am you for this I'm
used to as well I'm not yeah it's just
everyday
[Music]
this is funny massive fans the juicy dog
here the known is that over Dover at
this combination that combination fact
20 photos yeah with all different people
yeah awesome
[Music]
these locks come in so handy hang in
your bag if you're thinking of coming -
live if you think you're coming to let
the Philippines come to Palatine and
definitely come to el nido 100% El Nido
we're thinking of going to Quran which
is supposed to be similar but just as
amazing some people say it's even more
amazing but I dunno how you taught this
hello Antoine those places you read
different things online because some
people say it's completely untouched
which to us it kind of is because we've
been to Thailand Cambodia those beaches
they're much more built up much more
touristy to us here this is like there's
like a few it feels like there's a few
bars in a few restaurant I think there's
over a hundred and they need oh but to
us this still feels like untouched way
more untouched than other places we've
been
Quran is supposed to be even more like
that so if you're looking for a place
and it just looks in it it just looks
incredible if you're looking for a place
to come and snorkel dive surf whatever
then the Philippines has to be has to be
up
[Music]
thank you very much and I'm so much now
we got good for ever it again is these
lunches on folks got some muscles is the
chicken prawns fruits oh thank you
thanks and a massive fish over there red
snapper fish don't get em Waitrose ah
very good grab some of these guys one
each
yes this water it's like the nicest
color I know we keep saying that and
look how clear it is
did you have a nice lunch George so nice
being a healthy mother sandy faith it's
all about to a part of the beach I
[Music]
stopped here at a shrine in the middle
of the sea sounds random and it is very
random but it's cool look at it this is
like literally we have taken about
further out from where we were at lunch
right just in the rock so we can climb
up to the top apparently and hopefully
get a nice view this is unreal you can
take your mask off now my face the one
we went to leave exactly where the hole
in the wall it was out of the water and
a bit in the water where the feet waited
to climb through it this was like a
trench as all I was around at hand if
there was like jagged rocks either side
I go down into this deep water is very
clear even to the bottom but it's very
very far down comfrey diaper and you're
listening through and there's like caves
around you with feet and that was a good
three or four minutes from the boat
proper swimming through my bags above
like one on to me
so cool and it was a really weird
feeling being going through to get to
somewhere like making beats the call to
seek revenge and but also like looking
down or anything below you as well it's
really weird but really nice imagine is
no we're just we just do that I can't
see them okay this might sound weird and
feel free to grill me in the comments
but there's something about wearing a
snorkel mask oh here he goes I can just
float I don't have to tread water
I just float it's because you're you
know why it's because you're breathing
in and you inflate your body with air
yeah and you float you breathe out a
little bit then you breathe back in it's
all your breathing no I'm still but then
when I take them off if I take this out
at a the masks off on they're like yeah
because you're not you're lying flat to
snorkel and then you put your legs down
and then you're going down if I'm down I
put the mask on I would just stand there
and I'd be a won't Sen promise maybe
it's like a citation thing but then I'll
take off a knife it's horrible is that
your lady doesn't cry got the order then
you go in and it play Peter Pan Am come
to el nido guys honestly watch our so we
got to do you can watch our video from
the other day where we told you how to
put really really cheap flights you then
got to get yourself to the Philippines
you've ain't got to get a bus to el nido
then you've got to come here then you
have to download our free sets they're
all your photos okay and you'll have the
best time ever
don't go to Spain this summer don't go
to France on the hand
we are not sponsored by the Philippines
by which we work can you imagine there's
something about island hopping and going
to really nice beaches though she's so
tired we've come off the boat we swapped
instagrams but with more new friends
which is cool
and now we've come out so that Peter
before heading back tonight then we'll
probably go out again tonight we love
this ice cream place were obsessed with
a place most all the dancing people we
fit out like
in the morning last night and then I'll
announce but I take this morning
I really don't think
I question you tomorrow
but it was like
yeah my Alma's gonna read
[Applause]
thank you very much
insert photo now
[Music]
you see on and you
and sorry that the vlog hits they went
up at a new tonight thank you very much
the reason for that is we we set up my
editing we wanted to get the blog
instead we've set up till 2:00 to get it
ready to get it all edited and uploaded
set of top-load left it running thought
right we can sleep now job done
welcome in the morning was he on no it
wasn't on so woke up about 6:00 a table
loaded inside stayed up late for it
thanks very much if you've watched it
today enjoy two blocks today it doesn't
stay
we'll be like every orphan our target
thank you very much wow that looks
unreal okay guys we're gonna we're gonna
tuck into this yeah just a little bit
this way please thank you that's fine
thank you very much we're going to tuck
into this now guys so thanks so much I
hope you enjoyed the vlog
the bike
[Music]
[Applause]