hi guys today we wanted to film a video
dedicated to answering all your
questions that you've been asking us in
the comments on our Instagram DMS
everywhere you've been asking so many
questions so we wanted to sit down today
and properly answer them we're gonna
find somewhere along with speech we're
trying to find somewhere it's not too
much loud music and a little place to
rest this cat somewhere a bit quiet you
guys down have a real chat about
everything about traveling about us
about all sorts of stuff everything's
gonna be covered in this video so we
hope you enjoy it
[Music]
okay I think that'll do we're gonna get
pretty sandy but it's all good so you
guys have asked us so many questions so
we're going to go through a quiet pace
you've got questions here from like
YouTube Instagram Twitter kind of things
they're low close that if one's from
loads of different people there's a
different types of questions as well so
we didn't ask for like specific travel
ones or ones about where we are now we
just said like ask us anything we've got
loads of different story so are you
ready I'm ready
Michael - Michael T we can answer that
one we got here I sure don't know where
we got three and a half weeks I've been
around a few places the favorite thing
for me is the people we spoke about this
in another video but people are super
friendly super welcoming it's amazing
their way of life and it and the beaches
the lagoons the color of the sea yeah so
so many things rain a grace underscore
and Instagram she got how long did you
guys save for before coming traveling
how long did you save up your money for
before decided to embark on this trip
she's saying her and her boyfriend the
planning on going traveling doing a
similar thing to us yeah definitely do
100% firstly for us we were probably
saving for close to six months only
because that like six months before we
came out with when we said yeah let's do
it for sure so it wasn't like we planned
to save for some amount of time we said
yeah we want to go on that day whatever
money we have is what we're going with
that's pretty much what we did yeah but
we had been saving anyway before we even
knew wanted to come traveling all our
spare money that we didn't spend every
month we'd say this is a good habit yeah
so we did have a bit behind us but then
I guess we don't rely fully on the cash
we save because we do make money as we
go around as you guys know if you've
seen any of our videos we doing like
work and stuff of the days we this so I
think is family and this I think always
week is terrible yeah we have ways to
make money as we travel around which
helps us so we only have to dip into our
savings when we need to and we can earn
as we go which helps
SPX long one is this traveling trip a
one-time thing are you looking to do it
again and we vlog obviously will block
whatever we do ever I say it's not a
traveling trip I'd say this is now kind
of yeah and this was probably our fault
by saying we're going on this trip
planned this for this amount of time but
as we've kind of gone along as long as
we can get ourselves by yeah we'll
continue traveling 100% and it might be
there eventually like the long-term plan
maybe in a few years it might be that we
have a face somewhere and we go and do
trips but I feel like that's why I don't
like saying as long as we can move
around for now that's what we're going
to do obviously this particular trip
will end or we'll have a break Laurel
will change slightly different
destinations yeah it doesn't mean we'll
just stop Lily Jemima on Instagram said
how old are you going to be when you
have children I we're honestly not even
thinking about it like like seeing the
cute kids here it's kind of like yeah I
know pretty cute and you've seen
families traveling with kids we're on a
bus the other day for like six hours and
this family has two kids yeah and they
were young and they were like getting by
and so like we can make it happen at
some point but but we're not know yet
obviously we talked about everything
life got names and stuff we it will
happen eventually but like it's not it's
not the radar right now no yeah maybe a
few years no longer than a few years
Jimmy underscored that understood
that if you could go back to a place you
visited in the past in the past few
weeks what place would you pick still
here we can't pick here or the
Philippines we can pick our need oh I'd
love to go back anyway but it's so
recently I feel like we should pick
someone somewhere that we loved a while
yeah I'm gonna say Haiyan in Vietnam
she's me absolutely loved it oh yeah it
was really nice actually I think I'd
like to go back to like Chiang Mai or
something in Thailand
yeah it was so long it was like forever
ago it's like quite a few months ago a
definite all new Thailand again at some
point
Nordic Helen white said would you ever
release new presets in the future
confusion or spectra yes yeah thought
about pre so if you don't know we sell
Lightroom presets there's a link in the
description this video it helps you edit
your photos in our kind of style with
one click it's super easy to do because
it it would be cool yeah that we've
called the first we've caught the first
lot of presets the travel pack it's kind
of it works really nice we've got
holiday photos we have more presets that
we use ourselves that we haven't
released so if that's something that
interests you guide there possibly could
be another release in the future how
underscore hat
on Instagram in the places you have
visited have you seen many tourists this
is different for every single place
obviously like the huge cities Bangkok
Hanoi those kind of places you see tons
and tons and tons of tourists the
islands in Thailand are quite busy
although we went in low season so is
less than there usually would be but
then you hear there's like Betty na it's
so varied I think that's a hard one to
answer because I feel like it'd be a
different answer in every place you go
mrs. Kati Salisbury said what are your
must pack items for anyone planning on
traveling
I wanted to make a separate video about
what what's in our travel bags and stuff
essential items there's a good one
Powerbank Powerbank via phones sometimes
it is it like for example here you don't
have electricity between 6:00 in the
morning and 10:00 in the morning and so
then for hours I use any plugs Werner
things it's handy having a power back to
plug in your phone charge batteries and
things like that and another one which
is five francs for one suncream bring as
much as you can with you in your bag
because it is so expensive out here we
pay I think close to 16 pounds for a
bottle of Sun cream the other day it's
like five pounds yeah
Kim joy Craig on instagram has asked who
wins who wins most the arguments between
you and Lucy
well me most time because I I'm I'm the
peacekeeper so when we well you why not
when we argue I tried like calm the
situation down Prince go well 1991 said
which is the best country for couples
you've traveled I'd say the best place
would be either : drop rosemary in
Thailand yes they probably Tyler Harris
and Ray in 93 will you be going to
America
yeah hunter some point yeah not on this
leg of this trip but yeah hundreds that
want to do American definitely VX l j HX
and ends there please join my country
because if hashtag more fun in the
Philippines I don't know
we've seen that phrase loads of times
everyone saying and we kind of agree
actually Maxtor rj underscore do you
miss your family yeah of course we do
acoustic that's the only negative about
what we do if we were doing this like 30
years ago we wouldn't have the
connectivity
now that I've got you on a FaceTime them
we get we Texan most days you've got
like group chats stuff so it's like of
course you miss them and not actually
seeing them but they know exactly what
we're doing every day from these videos
and then they tell us what they're doing
so we're very very much in contact
contact yeah Dylan Monteith official
said were commencing hey thank you I've
been here since 1:30 okay so how much is
it roughly costing you every week
does your budget change and if so why
okay let's work out a rough daily budget
then fort we spend daily okay so we will
probably we're not traveling it's hard
because every country is very different
but I'm sure we can come to some sort of
average we probably spend about three or
four pounds each on breakfast do like
seven pounds yeah then we'll probably
need to get some transport somewhere
that could be like 505 pounds so then we
if we're doing an activity or something
would need we need entry in somewhere
we'll need to pay for something no more
maybe maybe six pounds or something
maybe if you actually made up because
she needs that around there there's a
very very rough average there we need
lunch maybe not for pound each and then
no this is twenty six already that's
probably about right no I think witness
I reckon I reckon 25 a day and that was
more Thailand wasn't that was Thailand
is really cheap and then we transport
back and some dinner about four times a
so that's 20 pound each a day so that's
not bad
I reckon 22 me five I reckon thirty to
sixty pound a day we're spending three
now yeah and then we sometimes need to
spend like fifty pound on a bus or a
train or a plane fly yeah like 200 pound
flight or something like that so we
might have a day where we literally or
everything's near us we get a cheap
lunch and we spend ten pounds like it's
a very yeah and we do we don't have a
set budget but we do try and make
sensible decisions and find the stuff
that is the best value so if a fly is 40
pounds more but it's six hours quicker
we'll often decide if we want to save
the money or if we want to save the time
we often save the money
obviously we don't time doesn't matter
really or if it does we've only got a
small time in place we'll go four times
one of the questions we got asked about
probably over 10 to 15 times was is the
Philippines safe to travel because
there's a load stuff online if you
google is the Philippines safe there's a
lot of stuff that suggests a citizen and
yeah in some places there's 7,000
islands 70,000 in some places suggested
or is that you're actually told not to
go there so places further south if you
google it you can find out where those
places are and like it open says like is
that green orange and red is there like
Reds like definitely don't go there
under any circumstance orange is like if
you have to come you can and then greens
like go for it and some places are in
the red zone aren't there yeah for
saying that but when we were reading
that at Hong Kong Airport that's a bit
worrying like we're nervous now if you
take for example my white bag I have
each day I'm like clinging on to it I
just check in the pit bull gets looking
around on your zip top trying a few here
I haven't even thought about it likes
things hanging at my back
and after googled it I think Bangkok's
one of the three famous cities in the
world
yeah and we didn't know that at the time
being now we've been mainly for having
around Palawan and it's it's totally
safe obviously read your own advice we
can't travel we know we don't know if
things changing your top right we have
failsafe so our final question was and
this was asked loads of times as well
where are you guys spending Christmas
and we can announce that we have no idea
genuinely don't know we we kind of the
way we plan is that we look for the
cheapest flights
I'm kind of booked couple of weeks in
advance three four weeks max in advance
at the moment it's looking like we'll
probably still be around this area as in
Southeast Asia so it's a big area but
give us some suggestions where should we
go for Christmas let us know it would be
cool to be it would be cool to have
Christmas Day on a beach on a little
bonus question which we've just
remembered hello do you want to know how
old we are and we've seen people
guessing however they are in the
comments someone said I would look so
young without this beard I agree you are
and a lot of people have said you're
younger than me which is
right so I am aruthor
so I'm 25 born in 93 good year
I don't remember my kid Matt and I 21
and I got called 31 the other day and I
got a call to 35 the other day not happy
about it
anyway we hope you enjoyed this video we
hope we answered enough of your
questions if you've got any more leave
them in the comments the Emma
yep anyway we do daily daily daily stuff
in there as well we will be happy to
film another one of these videos and a
couple of weeks or something if you've
got any more questions to answer now
we're gonna help you to see we're gonna
cool down it's hot today no it's not hot
now it's cooler I still need to rinse
sorry about everything
oh my god what Cece thanks
[Music]