[Music]
good morning I'm very quick breakfast
stay up Massenet later parents will
inquire Charlie - oh yeah it's raining
yesterday we forgot the Lord's
repentance and I must learn it was
raining my calf there's some pits the
police at my house it would be a nice
sunny day hopefully be invisible he's
good but I'm not sure how far we're
heading out
I think we're out for quite a few hours
in the hope to see line because a lot of
the time I think you come out and you
don't so we can't go home too much but
if we do it for me that's ridiculous
[Applause]
got them not in a cage they are wild
they're living on the natural habitat
[Music]
so we've been going about the two hours
and it suddenly retains director and
there was lightning and stuff they
suddenly got very very choppy as you can
see the boats going
[Music]
and I gotta fun sticking out pull the
whale sharks aside for now we just it
all
[Music]
no luck as of yet we've been going
around for maybe two hours stop and
think you might have seen one and then
not you may forget to look for where the
birds are like diving and
it's like that house yeah stopping for
lunch now people are gonna get off after
swims we might do that anyway and then
we're gonna try again off something to
think this crossed
[Music]
[Applause]
we're in the open aunt is here it's a
wild quail sharp
it's not like hey you just got in an
aquarium or something you might say I
don't know can see the metal isn't so
big
and then just opening your eyes and
going on little turn seniors or crazy
dream to swim with sharks I
[Music]
I can't wait for the guy
I enjoyed that
you've been so lucky with the weather
despite starting like very cloudy and
stuff
turned into less
it's been the same all day it's really
hot we're hoping then or somebody didn't
put enough
we actually work for this poor company
today so we will of course let you know
who they are
we'll leave a link in the description of
this video if you can check them out if
you ever come in this way in the
Philippines this is one to do
and you can see a whale shark even
better
[Music]
back in the hotel room now we've been
editing up I'm a little bit sunburned by
the way we've been an editing up the
photos from today with the shark whale
no whale shark and check out this one we
go over Lucy how insane is that we're
super happy with those and we're so
excited we actually got to see one so
juicy lover and tour still to come by
the way it's bit messy at the moment
we've as you can see you know we like to
spread out again because it's a massive
room we're gonna get some dinner now
we're gonna use the hotel restaurant
because it's really nice the staff here
love you
we're staying at a place called it at
cassia free garden and so far we're very
impressed will show you around a little
bit here as well in the next vlog maybe
but it's so nice and I they put all
these little lights on and the pool is
just there and we've got this like whole
hue is a huge room isn't it and outdoors
themed table opposite us has ordered the
burger there's one burger on the menu is
called the Armageddon burger it just
came out and I'm not joking
it's I'm not exaggerating I think I'm
gonna have to order this tomorrow night
let me know if you think has to try it
like I'm not even joking its proper uh
no like yeah it's like a basketball so
coming from the size it's really funny
way to explain that is big so mines come
it's basically a massive bowl of rice of
chicken and vegetables I put those a soy
sauce in it and it cost one pound forty
and it's my favorite in the world and
Georgia's one for pollen a cost two
pounds
I can't believe he spent so much money
[Music]
[Applause]