good morning guys today we are basically
doing our own a motorbike tour of the
island of Bohol we're gonna go and see a
ton of sights here and chocolate hills a
bridge what else oh yeah and ziplining
look like yes that's gonna be cool we've
got a sweet ride here from yesterday we
picked this up last night we didn't
realize it was green it's seven months
old
it's a Yamaha and it looks super nice we
found a place for breakfast and we're
heading there now we need some good food
some coffee and then we'll be good you
ready
[Music]
it's just I training we just happening
there we got in chowder for right
you actually day I face time to my
granddad view today means like George
George you looks shipwrecked if your
beard up a little bit this is one where
in the hacker base for I need to get
another one of my little hair bands
which does that nice this as well I
don't know what's going on right we need
some coffee
it's gone I pad here where you can
actually lift at a whole menu and choose
what you want full sets feeling hungry
for this America and that sounds pretty
good Filipino the edge apparently this
is supposed to be quite good the sausage
here yeah cool they do an English
breakfast that's the first English
breakfast breakfast we've seen her can
we have one English breakfast one
American breakfast I'll have a
cappuccino with mine please one you
spread first we've had cappuccino
regular one American breakfast we've got
lucky we thank you so much thank you
love the look at this place so cool in
there
[Music]
this man you really miss me like a once
these cakes look absolutely amazing
look at our cotton seekers the glare
oh look
[Music]
alright alright so we're here well we're
not here we're we're very nearly here
about three or four minutes away it's
been about an hour and a half of driving
hasn't it probably our longest drive
yeah yeah definitely oh it's been so so
good though through the countryside in
getting three little villages rooms been
going three lazy little villages as well
and all the kids are like way being as
we go par so so nice amazing the scenery
huge open roads it's been one of the
best drives that we've ever done in my
mind I'm definitely on some like old
classic motorbike not like a little
scooter moped thing but we are very
nearly there Oh hot it's very hot maybe
go away
I don't really care
I just wanna love you babe
so we made it to Chocolate Hills
Adventure Park they invite us here today
to do some activities which looks so so
fun some of the stuff we're going to do
I've never done before it looks crazy
and then we're going to go to the view
pointer actually see the hills we just
saw a guy with a drone and it makes us
wish so bad that we had our drone but
you guys know why we can't have a
drawing
[Music]
you whisper to me
oh really
yes okay wow that's nice the um Jim Ryan
huge how that feel yeah the shot for
Instagram really cool black and white
was it heavy really happy okay okay
okay back why delete those Oh see that's
cool okay so you're a reflection at the
glasses oh sorry
I'll come this side this is how we've
been getting our exercising lately a ton
of steps
how many 248 I might do a two extra just
to make it two-fifty Wow so here's the
viewpoint these are the chocolate hills
so cool it's hard to believe that these
are actually natural or not man-made
because of the shape of them they so
cool they go on for miles and miles
talk about the moment such an incredible
view here this is what they tell you to
go and see if you're visiting Bohol
we've also just heard the greatest
showmen soundtrack layering on which we
love which is so cool it was like we
listened to those songs around the time
of deciding to go traveling and like the
lyrics and them songs obviously didn't
make us go like we we were gonna go
anyway but I don't know it was a good
time and that film came out and it was
the message throughout it was just like
do what you want do your own thing and
it cut a nice it's nice to hear that
whilst we're here doing it I've also
seen quite a cool sign here no Wi-Fi
bonding time just despite the fact we're
loggers we can still appreciate that
it's nice too
it's nice to be out in the countryside
with nothing else going on at all I
think now oh my God look we're doing
there we're gonna cycle on this yes
cycle how's your balance your doesn't
great no it's not that
so we won't allowed the big camera on
this one so we flipped on to the little
GoPro ah oh my god is high I mean we
jumped off waterfalls the other day
excited it should be a breeze we've been
told there's no need to balance
ourselves
[Music]
Oh ugly fetus
wow this man
the crazy thing is like I'm going so
high above we freeze and the only thing
holding it on is the tire on this little
bit of wire chocolate Hill is in the
background
[Music]
so the little bit wobbly up here little
bit windy very tongue the lips are not
true this being on a bike in the middle
of the sky
[Music]
I was holding on to the handlebars so
tight I was like vlogging with that oh
my god that's crazy no I was literally
holding on it felt like you had to
balance it was scary when the wind yeah
exactly like you're like this the wind
came in oh yeah and I just kept thinking
like it literally held on by a little
tire yeah like it's not like it clicked
all the way around the edge I couldn't
actually work out how it was fixed well
it had a clip underneath it was on the
rope and then the tire information that
that sits on the Rope like that there's
nothing underneath if you jumped it up
then I reckon the wheels would come off
but then you'd become a still attached
to this thing attached to the bike but
you wouldn't be able to get my car so
sketchy
[Music]
enough of these battle yet these shakes
they're like about how this was about
pounding just so good
- chicken curries here there's something
about Jim Carrey in the Philippines is
so nice attack so good really thin it
but it's amazing because someone
commented and said it wasn't
particularly an authentic dish but they
make it really really good it's so nice
I'm glad we had lunch before because
these steps look pretty hectic our
hearts like the philip i was good we did
it in one go they've got little places
if you're thinking of visiting you're
worried about the steps whatever reason
those little places where you can stop
have a rest is about four of them on the
way up so worth if we just sort of sign
as well they're set before 8:00 in the
morning you're allowed to fly drones
we've become early enough you'll be last
fly a drone over which would be so
insane
[Music]
this country keeps on Impressionist
every single day this is one of them
probably one of the best views that
we've had I would say they're like I've
never seen anything like this these
hills and I've no idea how they were
made
you have to look it up later they're not
man-made oh it's totally natural got a
two-hour ish ride back now I'm guessing
the same way that was one of the best
rides we've ever done so shall we get no
indigo that's a good Lord light in there
when we were breakfast this morning we
got given a tempting discount for this
plate I guess it's like same owners or
something so we've been back to hotel
we've freshened up an hour after dinner
it's called just sizzling I'm so hungry
are you hungry starving so they do a
burger yeah and you will never guess
what it's called
I'll tell them
[Music]
let me find that maybe there's a
separate burger menu of something that's
not on this one there's a burger called
the Miss Juicy Lucy by juicy news about
funny they've got four different
lemonade's here as well depending on the
season so what do you think that means
I've no idea what lemonade okay I was
right eliminated Hornet Street how do
you feel
thank you we're also not getting burgers
yes we're going to be healthy again
fried chicken and chips and wedges and
stuff they basically I didn't realize
the placement breakfast is literally
next door to them yeah that's what I
gave the discount codes so that through
that door oh yeah you can see over there
this behind sorry mate so the burgers
are actually from them and decided able
to go through that as far as we know
what it is so I'm not going to have the
juiciest a load bar in GCSE thank you oh
yeah oh my god yeah Cheers
back in the flat comment below if you're
watching when we were in our flat we
know we've got a load of new viewers we
know a load of your originals still with
us
how good does that smell all the food
here is like sizzling it just came past
us here on a hot plate and we just we
just waiting for ours like I'm trying to
smile politely but they're really we're
like starving
we click from four sources and I've got
the spicy time it's in the sizzling
plate every why it's called just yes you
hear that that looks so good smells
amazing I love food we come up so we're
traveling how what we do because we come
out for dinner every night so it's not
like a special occasion you know but we
still get excited when we're really
hungry and Superman tomato paste
[Music]