okay take two of leaving any day
[Music]
action yes good morning guys I hopefully
we can leave this hotel today hopefully
we can leave our need oh not that we
want to leave but it's time to see a new
place we've got a quick photo shoot
downstairs first we've stated for quite
a few nights we've got to know some of
the people here and they've asked for
some photos with us which is great so we
need to do that we got a bus in 20
minutes let's get going thank you for
staying with that definitely deafening
[Music]
our journey is going okay so far we've
come back to the same stop as we did
from watering that's our amigo and we've
got the same ice creams and we stay in
the same spot full circle he's actually
just arrived at our new accommodations
really really cool it's a little tiny
little place is just on the beach we'll
show you more in a minute
Lucy's just checking in Thank You Mitch
doubly so if you want much better go
yeah exactly
every morning yes yes yeah because if
you take a boat it's 15 20 minutes
living there
more hands-on okay we just checked into
a hotel and we called Jenny and she's so
nice really helpful telling us what to
do and she's saying that if the rooms
are full she'll sleep out here in the
hammock for the husband
it's brilliant yes we're connected to
the Wi-Fi little portable guy plugged in
there and our room is there so hopefully
but can we get some blogs uploaded well
Merry Christmas guys if this vlog goes
up at Christmas I just realized that we
haven't actually told you where we are
so obviously our plan was to write to
Quran and change to the weather so now
we've decided to come to port barton
which is a tiny little tonika village
and we've just arrived it's very quiet I
would find a nice little spot for some
lunch and is the only wine that we found
so far because the place of things that
they had Wi-Fi allow you said it's only
a little abdominal fat vanilla that
motor and if nothing would load nothing
would connect so we're not sure we're
doing about these logs I don't know when
it's going to go live or form I have to
come back here later and sit there for a
few hours to let it upload I don't know
but priority was lunch for kids bathroom
I've got a giant coconut here it's the
biggest not
you could easier and I've ordered a
pesto pasta and Georgie's got a burger
burger shop
[Music]
thank you sir actually a vegetarian cafe
so this is a massive veggie burger
potato wedges and an iced coffee server
a mosquito served in a mug which I've
never had in my life and I've added
mosquito in my breakfast pack
[Music]
the way the huge is such nice warm water
we've just found the dreamiest spot here
along the beach perfect for relaxing
after a six-hour bus journey earlier on
today you can we were looking on
booking.com we nearly stayed at one of
these places along the beach here which
would have been cool but I'm very happy
with where we are we're literally about
two minute walk up the road there this
is so much quieter than El Nido we
thought El Nido was kind of quiet and
untouched but this is this is another
level there's they don't even have roads
so there's like no cement roads at all
there's loads to do there's waterfalls
there's a couple of restaurants there's
a few recommendations that we might
check out soon the list is just
absolutely dreamy and I don't think yet
many tourists come here there's a few
we've seen a couple of nice people we
met on the bus overall just walking
around it's very quiet
apparently there's not much from
nightlife here really but it's a very
very small Tower which is it's just
perfect relaxing
and that is Lucy just there currently
being attacked by waves they come out of
absolutely nowhere that's a big one it's
actually a bit risky me standing here to
be honest well for that reason
[Music]
[Applause]
back in the room now and Paul Barton
when they say the accommodation is basic
they mean it I mean it's it's very nice
but I'll show you our and this is the
first room that we've had since we left
in August for traveling that hasn't got
aircon no more wrong oh yeah
second room where we haven't had aircon
and literally and dripping already we've
got a fan and there's no Wi-Fi
we've got we've got a fan here this is
our cooling system pointed at the bed
the reason we put this one over
otherwise we could upload our videos but
we've come back from the beach and
they've taken the dog looking at the
walls that HD Wi-Fi is actually gone
it's not like the signal
y-yea to Wi-Fi has been picked up and
taken away yes and now it's time for a
very very quick
that's what girlfriends are for
well Lucy's busy and the sand off my
shoes I just quickly show you the road
we're on let's go they're picking up his
dinner this is literally what the roads
look like dirt roads but it feels I
don't know something about it there's
just chilled it's lovely isn't that just
I don't know it's just natural you not
me I'm trying to find this place of
Wi-Fi we do like a full loop we go we
find it finally yes yeah we go that way
all the way down these roads actually
even go I think is this way look to our
left in our hotel next door to it yeah
it's actually there this seems to be the
only place with Wi-Fi in port barton
this is going to probably become our
office guys so get used to this place
we're going to make our second home
thank you we sit upstairs
thank you very much this is the spot and
we've got it to ourselves someone's
already here working power power power
go there update the wife my hair isn't
working and you only get one hour a day
and only a like 500 megabytes which
isn't enough to upload a book on anyway
even if it was working so plan D is that
Georgia is going to try and find
something city college he went to two
different shops they'd run out he's gone
to a third one and they said 450 places
which is under a pound you can get a SIM
card of one gig on and then you talk up
yourself so I think for this next these
next few days here we're going to have
to be uploading vlogs from our phones
and which is going to use a hell of a
lot of data but hopefully it's fairly
easy to top it up and do but I guess
it's a good thing cuz it means then
we've got our phones like if you want to
go and explore we'll have GPS and stuff
on our actual phone instead having to
rely on Wi-Fi so I think if this works
then we're all good but it has gotten
dogs have been here and we have any
other started to projects we've been
trying to sort this but hopefully isn't
gonna work out so I'm back I made it
aren't some SIM cards so this is what
they offered me is like 50 pesos for one
it's really cheap I've no idea if
they're gonna work but we're gonna find
out we're gonna see if we can get these
videos out then it comes with a gig of
pre-loaded data so we're gonna have to
try and buy more and load them on I
don't even know him to do that then if
it's like a pre-loaded thing and then I
said I went to like four different shops
and they're basically don't know where
they walked into a shop or someone's
house because there's no obvious
storefronts I mean like all the products
kind of give it away so you just kinda
have to wander in and I said to one of
the guys do do SIM cards notice well and
then looked away and then ice just
hovered for a bit and then I walked out
and then another guy was like Judas SIM
card seems like yes I was like cool do
you do global SIM cards which is the
name of the carrier here he was like
yeah and I thought cool how much are
they fleece and he was like fifty even
though on here says 40 but I got made
their Cup I understand hello oh please
tell me I phone sighs that's too big
well in fact it's a little wonder if you
we're gonna try and we're gonna try and
do this now
okay that's the first sim in put the
mobile dater on we should have a gig
actually though some instructions
apparently got 3G
[Music]
about text welcome to globe things
happening more appropriate background
music there's no work in but a wonderful
world can't complain okay so the
internet situation is kind of there it's
been a little bit of a nightmare because
we had to connect to their Wi-Fi to
download an app to then garcin cards
topped up it's like it's like living in
2004 it's all good we've managed to do
it we've sort out that people here have
been so so friendly that people have
been so good to us they helped us out
with the sim cards they've helped us out
with some Wi-Fi and they've also given
us a 10% discount card for tomorrow
night's dinner at reef cafe is one of
the owners here her husband runs this
restaurant down the road so we're
currently here at my booty you're
visiting you how to check it out food
great white guys good I'm really nice
chill spot we're upstairs upstairs at
the moment just chillin Lucy's editing
away at the vlog so tomorrow night we're
gonna try out Reef Cafe so we'll let you
guys know exactly what yeah the bet the
burgers are supposed to be insane this
is why it's come to guys camp in outside
the Wi-Fi place 27 minutes left on the
upload we sat in there until they
physically kicked us out we try it's
late but we try our best to get these
videos out for you and we're back guys
we did it the vlog was uploaded we were
in there for I think close to seven
hours waiting for that vlog to upload
which I mean there's a nice spot and
we've got some other stuff done as well
that's how dedicated we are to getting
these daily videos out you get addicted
to uploading daily when your daily vlog
it's like tonigh it's crazy because it's
like it's our passion it's our hobby
it's our job it's our it's everything
all in one it's it's like a lifestyle
thing it's not something that we feel
like we have to do it's something that
we really love doing every single day we
want to do it every day we wait and just
think if the guy was locking up and he
chucked us out but we're still standing
outside the building for about half an
hour after after he finally told us we
had to go and we were like the lights
are gonna go off he's gonna turn the
roof off any minute now on it it was
counting down on YouTube but we got it
up it's all good very quickly before we
end tonight we want to give we want to
give a personal thank you of one of our
very very loyal viewers and subscribers
mr. rock star brewski
he has been watching the vlogs for
couple years now I want to say comment
what is every single video comment
every video we got an email today and he
had to put some money into our PayPal
account which like we don't ask for
donations on this channel we're not set
up on patreon or anything like that but
travelling is expensive flights are
expensive and we obviously need to spend
money to be able to bring you guys these
daily videos every single day and go on
with these adventures that we're going
on so completely unexpected thanks so
much it really really helps us out and
this also leads on from some other
questions we've had we've had loads of
DMS asking if we are on patreon and
stuff all of you guys want to support
the channel one way you can do that is
to buy our presets there's a link in the
descriptions then you get something back
I know you get the videos and the money
from the presets is directly linked to
our PayPal account too so it always to
the same place it all goes all the money
goes back into the channel back into the
videos back into travel expenses etc etc
so our PayPal link is in the description
of this video if that is someone who
wanted to because we've had lots of
messages from you guys asking if you can
support us in that way so so we're not
asking for it but it's totally up to you
the option is there so thank you so much
and thanks to everyone who watches all
these daily vlogs where we love reading
the comments it's our favorite thing to
do we try and reply to every single
comment still and we will do so for as
long as we possibly can but for now we
need to sleep because we need to get up
early in the morning go and sit back at
us place and upload this make sure you
subscribe to channel if you're new guys
and please give this video a thumbs up
if you enjoyed today and we hope to see
you tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]