yes thank you very much thank you yeah
sure yeah sure
Sophie I
quick time for selfie before we leave
today we're gonna miss those guys we
need to catch a ferry now ferry over to
the hole
very over the minimum cigar payment
terminal
basically ten patients that pass drop
you in and then 55 speech language
but it's still really cheap and security
here like this Milan Saric especially
walk into a little carton and go on here
they probably do a sketch as an answer
and something you don't have to take
your bags on with you and get some junk
to the rest of the road and they
actually taste it all you can do
he took a free wealth out there
sponsor a person morning coffee we did
have them actually afford already this
is kind of like the festival
I travel down
morning guys good morning - not my not
my favorite smell is in the morning me
bacon but also coffee and you know and
also much but have you already explained
where we're going
yes have you already made having getting
that yeah cool so we can just drink our
coffee and enjoy good morning guys
welcome to the vlog
[Music]
[Laughter]
scoff the fairy has pretty smooth
actually the back seams have bought of
it where I think they always and I think
our accommodation is about a night
without I know it's a nine minute drive
away from theirs we did find maybe a
taxi that I have grabbed here which
denying ball drawn all day and check out
on me panic okay so we found a taxi he
wanted three hundred pesos for a eight
seven minute drive gone down to 150 is
half price straightaway
[Music]
so many Christmas trees so early in the
year more fun in the Philippines I've
been telling you that I want to see what
Li Shu is just do it by the camera if I
turn this camera round now right we're
in our new room we're here we're gonna
treat you very quick yes a little bit
dark quick funny story for you and got
some food to starving
we vote the City Bureau it's like really
cheap it's like 10 times a night so
we're not like on training it or we kind
of ask you but we yeah we walked in
everywhere like the men are doing that
today like the following my own City you
know so if I was a bit taller you can
see if you buildings rather you can well
you can see it you can see a tree or two
yeah and if you if when you're having a
shower you get the TV so it's win win
win
do you want a room tour as well I'm here
I mean that kind of was a room tour we
can't do that okay chair is my favorite
part of speed where's the kettle and
coffee very rare actually
you can't do that that's hilarious it
goes to bet okay this is really
well-designed what's this yeah I like
includes the juicy flock rim told now I
need some lunch such a nice afternoon
here the sun's coming down what's the
time like three o'clock or something now
our ferry took two hours wasn't too bad
Taiwan was cool and we liked seeing new
places we've seen so many places now in
Southeast Asia but at an OPS
I'm so glad we came back we just loved
the Philippines we feel like we've got
you so now because we've spent longer
here than we ever intended to our
original flight was only for two weeks
we extended that and now we're back we
had right here and then we had the Hong
Kong fingers we had to book it on with
flight we hadn't really done much
research about where to go what to do so
then we said oh okay right quick rush
two and a half weeks out of UK Taiwan
and then having spent the two and a half
weeks we thought hang on there's so much
more to see here and that's all we Brits
a flight back and this still is I think
I think even when we leave this time I
still think there's going to be so much
more we can see you guys have been
amazing commenting places we should
visit so we've actually been like we've
been taking stuff from your comments
we've been taking stuff and making
little lists on our phones of everywhere
we need to visit and the list is long so
it's fine mango peach pie from jolly be
by the way don't do it nice so I have a
feeling I know I've been this isn't
gonna be our last time even this trip
isn't gonna be our last time in the
Philippines I have a feeling we'll want
to come back and see more of it so this
is the street we're staying on a bit
further down and we just buy this little
guy
now I wouldn't touch it you mean you
might not see but I don't really know
you love goat staying here really hey
guys
[Music]
they were coming to this place PI AG pea
kayak hey egg restaurant they do
unlimited rights apparently so hopefully
they're open about it right there oh
yeah here we go
and I think you can either sit inside or
upstairs here fresh air
I can see beach
oh very hot today thank you
it's Philippi on food so the good thing
that we've been traveling around for a
while and eating a lot of food is that
we know what order we know what we like
our drinks have just arrived and this is
the nicest thing I've ever had it's a
watermelon shake thank you very much Wow
thank you very much amen
we've been told in the comments they
need to get billing for dipping
look at this chicken looks amazing
[Music]
that Cystic was much better ten times
better than the one had before in El
Nido thanks for recommendation thanks
for telling us that we need to have it
sizzling it was a lot better
[Music]
what happened there I think you just got
a walk out all right it's like Vietnam
style they made it across the road we're
heading into this little bakery to get
some snacks for later oh my god the
cakes look amazing one of these choco
banana and 30 pesos that's so good
chocolate bun log chocolate all the
healthiest of snacks part we've heard
that bakeries are maybe pretty good in
the Philippines so we need to try we're
just trying it okay what I have never
seen it a whole loaf of bread that's
chocolate
imagine the toast would like Nutella
imagine the toast we have imagined the
toast with nothing how do we resist all
of this
that's called just picking up some
healthy baked goods snacks which we will
enjoy later on yeah and then we asked
them if there was anywhere where we
could actually put a toy and they're
like yeah we can put the talking so you
go to a bakery and you're not booking at
or they're going to like text us we gave
them our number they're going to text us
later we're gonna go and see in the next
couple of days some of the sites that
this place has to offer I don't know
where we go we need to get back to the
hotel and I will get through a load of
people
buffalo buffalo go we're walking less
ice except underneath this little shop
as the rain
but it's still really hot so that's
quite nice we don't they get off
[Music]
we were actually saying for my food
by the main cookie
if you've got any recommendations
like we're not too sure and again we
have planted one here on the laptop
laser and I feel
we've had
aah groaning scoffs when it's like a
travel day like sleep you only got half
of me afternoon we dumped our bag came
out some good memories now I don't know
how it suddenly liked in a time living
that cities and working out looking
hopefully it won't rain this is mad why
is it raining there it's like November
[Music]