[Music]
by George goodnight the media guys
welcome to another day juice we have to
firstly thank you very very much for
10,000 subscribers that's crazy we woke
up with that this morning something
we've been working towards for a very
long time so that all that be brave
little governments it's amazing yeah
pretty good feeling I can't even think
about like a leaven is always that's
fine today we are doing a tour around
port barton we have a boat called Kubik
which we're about to board and we're
really excited to check out what's
around it's like an island hopping shall
we get snowed in and stuff like the ones
money though and we've hoping they were
anything but no it will be the judges
yes exactly we don't like to believe
everything read the mincer
[Music]
[Applause]
mylan
Diana come to me
they made
right
[Music]
when you
after that I've read by the audience
[Music]
we've actually pulled up by this little
bit of sand in the middle of the sea its
land all the way around here in like
ocean and stuff and it's just this
random sand bank in the middle of the
city like it's so cool it's like a
little mini island I don't know if it's
here all the time or when the tides off
it might go but it's awesome it's really
cool and we listen them starfish as well
there's so many of them and they're
massive I've never seen starfish that
look so chunky like I'm used to them in
a seal a center that I really spin and
like flimsy that's like a chunky
starfish really cool
[Music]
I think in the Philippines there's over
7,000 islands or something like that so
we're only ever going to see like a
couple of on three percent of it or
something on a short trip I think if
you'll have us we'll be back next year I
want to say I just spin out there we'd
love to come back without a place called
German island which seems really cool
it's like a little beach bar there's a
place with bean bags people chilling
hammocks you can lie and it's kind of
full of young people people kind of
eighteen to thirty I guess here it seems
quite a young vibe people just chilling
and playing they're playing some sort of
game over there we can't really work out
what it is but we're having lunch here
so they're going to prepare our food now
here it's just another day in heaven you
know blue skies clear waters palawan why
are we leaving here I know we're not
even just yet not even just yet but okay
I think I think we'll be back
[Music]
it's quite funny here like new political
act on a helmet chilly out and stuff and
then we're using this chance opportunity
to do some shoots isn't Brown to working
where at this location so it's pretty
cool then we can say to a brand like
we're doing an island hopping tour
tomorrow so we'll get some pictures on
that island for you it's very different
to at home
[Music]
so we're just heading over to lunch now
has been told it's all been prepped and
ready to go and delayed the fish sticks
for lunch actually brought over from
another boat we're at that sand bank and
it's like a little carrier bag of fish
and that's our life is so funny
thank you that's the kind of food I
don't used to fresh fish rice some
lovely looking fresh through your hair
after lunch was really good I'm very
full now and we just take him somewhere
Instagram / forget really for a bloated
belly a few years ago I'd never would
have just eaten a whole fish on a plate
a year ago I would a few months ago I
wouldn't have done but now it's like
every lunch you have is like here is a
fish and used to get into yourself it's
great Beach it's so nice like compared
to something other Island so it just
like nothing
it's my soccer as well with all these
umbrellas a little bit but the waters
icing clear as a wave like a reef care
to smooth the last bit rocky and today
we don't have the boat shoes oh yeah
aqua shoes we were the same we've done
quite a few like Island tours now sort
of all over Asia and it's funny how very
they are depending on the group of
people you're with so you don't pick
your width and then unless you do a
private tour you're going to with people
which we prefer anyway we like chatting
to people in sir and they're not not
today it's like we're with two other
couples and their move wasn't able to
pick ones ones from Spain I'm not sure
where everyone from they speak a little
bit of English but a minute ago at lunch
I thought are so where are you from
anyways like Spain and then he's at you
and I thought oh England live anyway
they sort of looked away and also in no
conversation although no conversation
it's literally your own couple the
separate and we try and make
conversation
I'm Beth I'm a tall we were on the other
day was us and basically everyone else
was Filipino and they were so much more
friendly much more chatty so just show
ignore that I mean they yeah there's
been no conversation on the boat no
conversation anywhere which is a shame
because like we love mean to people but
but we also thought maybe their English
isn't that good so yeah but they're not
talking to each other other
chosen my spot the next half an hour
[Music]
that tour today was really really good
yes probably the best opening we had a
bit of sketchy situation we were on some
very shallow like Coral when it was like
this close to us and we realize you not
supposed to touch it looking around and
everywhere you looked around this circle
was like this shallow chrome we were
like we can't see a bit actually go out
and eventually come out the back we had
to go into the deep end to get around
the reef it's like really fun we managed
we've been back a few hours now
yesterday's vlog is all up and edited a
question we get asked quite a lot is how
long does it take you to edit your vlogs
and the answer is probably between three
and four hours usually so that's like a
pretty much big chunk of our day like
taking our beds tape we offer some
dinner now and we're coming to that
affordable restaurant again tonight it
was just really good I know it means we
like we can have two meals each
so this place literally does everything
I think I'm gonna go for the chicken
curry I think we're gonna get some
french fries as well and they've got a
menu look at this cheap as well
so 75 pesos is like what serve a pound
okay so that means I could get a chalk
open on a pancake I think these are
pancakes for a pound that looks so good
I'm not being horrible we just wait a
like over an hour for this
I need all of this in half don't pour it
nurse we were so hungry I am so full but
I was tasty
our final job before we go to bed is to
reply to all the comments honestly we
are struggling basically sorry about the
village it's not even like we're staying
the Wi-Fi is down what it is and the
rest of next class it's down the whole
village is Wi-Fi is down but the
Internet's not working so there's
nothing we can do like you saw in the
last video how hard for two videos ago
how hard we try to get the vlogs up but
that's why there's been a delay and
obviously sorry about that but there's
literally nothing we can do because
nothing at all there's no no restaurants
have Wi-Fi we've got the three on our
phones but that barely loads like
Instagram notification you not even
connected to a hotspot nothing at all
right but we have been reading your
comments about whether we want to
quickly answer something that has been
asked to do with the mention from a
while ago and to do with the company
that currently sponsoring some of these
vlogs pro-x p.m. the VPN company
mentioned this in the video last week
it's a VPN it's a Virtual Private
Network pro XP and have given us an
account which is so useful for
travelling it means we can get on
certain websites which are blocked in
certain countries like Netflix and stuff
it's super handy for us and it also
means all your data when you're surfing
the web is all secure all encrypted etc
that's safer and easier faster do stuff
online
yes lot online banking all that kind of
stuff when you're connecting to public
Wi-Fi hotspots which we do a lot for
like it's it's nice name that you're
protected like whatever happened
definitely so they have actually given
us for this video a discount code so if
you're interested we have left the link
to their website in the description of
this video
and also the discount code which gives
you 50% off a membership and if you have
already bought something or like find up
make sure let me find the email yeah so
if you saw us talk about this before and
you went ahead and signed up straight
away and you paid full price
don't worry because Kayla at pro xpn
calm and let her know that you've seen
this video of the previous video and
then your refund is 50
to get 50% back so you get the 50% off
deal if you're new and you want to check
it out you can see all the features of
the products and stuff on the website is
really cool we use it and you can get
50% off so go it's like fairly cheap
anyway anyway isn't it it's not like
it's like hundreds of charges a pound
five six it's like it's like you can get
ones for like five pounds a month
yeah and for the safety aspect if you're
traveling or even if you're just at home
in your cell browsing
yeah 50% off makes that almost nothing
so birthday if you're interested check
that out links in the description we
need to sleep now we have a cool dead
plant or so we hope I mean we hope we
can get these blocks out to be honest
Annette at the moment because the Wi-Fi
situation is but when we're in a really
remote part of the Philippines so to get
that benefit we have to sacrifice some
things and unfortunately that's been
Wi-Fi but it's not only like missing out
on actually filming our we're still
filming every single day it's is that
we're now a little bit behind on the
unknown so that's fine because it's
still gonna be showing you every single
day of our trackers and this isn't us
like moaning about the situation like
we're super happy to be here and it's
still great that we're gonna be able to
open so it's fine you just have to be a
little bit patient with either the next
few days but hopefully we'll see see
otherwise we're just filming videos of
our travels and keeping them ourselves
ourselves watch your back ourselves a
little thing you see me in Georgia if
you're nice the channel please subscribe
and give the video a thumbs up if you
enjoyed it today and we will see you
very very very soon hopefully fingers
crossed
mechanically
[Music]
[Applause]