4:35 a.m. the sun's not even up we're up
this is strange but we've got a six and
fair we've got a cat we're all packed up
we're leaving
you ready sky
[Music]
yeah can we put this one on with one
hand
[Music]
only me here this morning I've seen so
good news
Suns coming up looking like a lovely day
here in El Nido the bad news is that the
fairy's been canceled we just asked if
there's gonna be one tomorrow and he's
like alright depends on the weather
bit annoying but I'd rather they cancel
it if it's a safety thing which our
destiny is I'm guessing it's a weather
thing there's this typhoon storm thing
coming coming around there is a flight
available so we're gonna try get some
Wi-Fi see if we can look up the flight
how much that costs even gets the
airport hop on a plane I said okay 6:30
to bring you guys in on a bit of live
planning here we've got a few options
the we're not going to Quran basically
there's no flight the phrase been
canceled we tried to look for the flight
today it's fully booked so and the
people some people in front of us it
said they've been trying for three days
to get over to Quran that's the third
David it's been cancelled for them you
and we've got a flight in a few days
time so we're not gonna risk it exactly
so I'm not gonna risk that we don't want
to get stuck there and not be able to
get back that would be even worse than
it is now being stuck here what a nice
place to be stuck though to be honest so
we're currently looking at a place
called port barton we can get a bus
there today loose around the room on
booking.com which looks okay I'm reading
some stuff on TripAdvisor
it seems like quite a nice place we
might stay one more night here we don't
know yet good news is here obviously
checkout isn't until twelve o'clock
because we've actually got six hours now
you can use our room we can use the air
conditioning the Wi-Fi and breakfast
included here every day and we were like
oh we're gonna miss it this morning cuz
we left a lot of hard for and they don't
start privacy at 6:00 or anything I mean
we sort of walk back in and they were
like what me like yeah I think and took
away our breakfast please they were like
yeah what do you want on my hip it's
perfect - banana pancakes on the way
thank God under coffee but I don't know
don't know what the plan is really and
we dropped the place we had booked in
Quran when we booked it I remember
seeing it said no refund for the money
if they haven't taken the money yet the
booking.com will take the money if you
don't go if you cancel it and somebody
sent them an email saying please don't
charge us it's been cancelled it's not
off for hopefully
be okay I don't know but at the end of
the day I'd rather ferries canceled if
it's not safe to travel then sort of go
and be out here if we find risk it and
now I just want some pancakes right our
breakfast and we just ask we can extend
it for one more night that is calling me
on an hour see if our room is available
or fingers crossed
because otherwise I've got to find
somewhere else but we love her here so
was he okay so we've come back we've
showered after that traumatic experience
this morning
sorry fault and we've been rechecked
into our room they actually cleaned it
as though we'd left so it's actually
nice having a nice fresh room although
we've already ruined the bed again but
we are not adults I swear we're having
this conversation earlier where that's
where adults would like leave things
neatly
we're not messy people but like like the
pillows we're just happy to move we're
just happy to leave the room with the
pillows and the duvet like this but
maybe maybe we should be more grown up
and actually do you think I swear like
so I was like my mum staying in the
hotel room yeah you're right go out and
just leave it like it's same or like
that's so much better oh I love it
how'd they see we're feeling pretty
uninspired of what to do plan wise
outside of our breakfast food is to
focus on our pancake yes so we've
decided to come out and do our research
somewhere nicer and fresher because
hopefully that gave us some inspiration
of what to do
right
[Music]
finally get into trial this coffee shop
around the corner from our hotel
[Music]
this music here is imperfect - I'm about
to say sadly the coffee shop didn't have
Wi-Fi so we can't go there because we
need to do some emails and work whilst
we're there to try here ye
we're getting pretty hungry now we tried
like seven places
we kind of go to sit down there wasn't
working so maybe they want my stone but
anyway we're too hungry dance with me
and then but we figured we can't really
eat and work at the same time we'll eat
now and then work out the beach I like
how food is first priority's and we saw
some comments the other day we're not
just like millennial kids who can't live
without Wi-Fi and we're just like trying
to get on snapchat and stuff our job our
business relies on internet access so I
mean over in the Philippines we know
it's kind of unreliable so we're not
moaning about the internet situation at
all
we also had someone comment and say that
the situation with the Internet can
probably improve in the next year or
something which could be very cool fast
because I'm sure we will link back to
the Philippines very soon after me but
now I think it's time I mean it's only
it's only right to give you guys I've
ever beats time-lapse
[Music]
about the five night in between my mango
shake that looks really good
that looks so good also smells really
good and then you have someone a plastic
sauces being human
just mango someone all like it's not
like sweets up in there someone also in
the comments told us to eat as many
mangoes as possible while we're here
because apparently they're the best in
the world I'll try some so try to be
healthier so we're both trying to get
some more fruit into our diets so for
like one or two bananas in this for sure
and just a little bit chopped like this
I actually read once a little bit
chocolate can be good fuser
microwave summer this reminds me of
summer as well probably if I call
definitely okay it's like two in there
yeah partly the UK's got some very very
cold weather so if you're one of our UK
viewers let us know the temperature
because we can't imagine it we are here
in shorts and flip-flops and it is
absolutely boiling all day every day
it's kind of weird that it's Halloween
happy Halloween today by the way it's
Halloween it's November tomorrow oh
you've got another
hello
yes
happy Halloween trick or treat but
fighters are Halloweeny ask your
Halloween trick further by now we'd only
be working out the winter coats the
scarf the gloves
making hot chocolate I don't want to
talk about now I'm jealous it's kinda
like we just froze in time in August
when we first came on this trip we've
just been in heat ever since good news
also we were worried this morning like
we said to ourselves doesn't really
matter but like climbing wise we've got
up early we've not we've not wasted or
they existed in paradise like it doesn't
matter about the whole fairy big council
thing we're all okay but what was a bit
annoying was that we've obviously paid
for the ferry and we'd also confirmed
five nights of accommodation in Quran
with his hotel and although they hadn't
taken the money through booking Comet
said
they will take the money if you don't
turn up if you cancel you still get
charged with an amount so I know refund
policy which is totally fair enough I
get why they do it some tall people
maybe mess them around and don't pay
we're going to turn off and and their
rooms gone and it's too late to send
again forget it and we were thinking
that's kind of annoying like obviously
we spent quite a bit yesterday on
flights and stuff and then coming to buy
more accommodation for five nights
somewhere else but we send them in an
email and said this is the obviously
caused by the way there any chance you
can not try to ask they said that you
can request it to not charge you so we
thought well we'll try that and they
said that some SMS saying no worries
it's not me in charge can you let us
know where you're coming from please I
have interested they can see maybe they
don't have other people turned on today
that's why but they probably miss
appreciates us letting them know sort of
early in the morning to hopefully they
can tell the rooms together and putting
it back up sale and also the ferry
company we booked through has also put
the refund back into our PayPal account
so we're fine we're back up to where we
were and we've got another night here
and like honestly yesterday I was a bit
sad that was on Earth Day and I thought
oh I would like one more night here and
good
yummy
this is probably going to be better than
fish chips at home because because the
fish is so good out here so fresh mmm
them chips are so nice tartar sauce
we're at playschool happy B if you're
wondering let's try some of this fish
or a skirt and flake right there that's
heart ah
mmm I saw a good sign us yeah Oh
amazing
blimey everybody starts three
so one of the wages in the toilet she's
afraid of see she is so scared and they
try to scare over them just found a
place where we can book our bus to port
barton tomorrow
Lucy's oh the game club and they go
we've decided
Lucy's filling in all the details 700
per person which is about 10 pounds each
and it's a four or five hour journey so
that's a really really good value
sighting
we never won yes please so if any of you
guys have any tips for us in port barton
do let us know in the comments
okay thank you
see later
thank you
[Music]
we've just taken a try speed down to
last vimana speech just in time for
sunset he's so kind he was stopping all
the way to hell out not to take photos
at least verbs of most viewpoints on the
mountain through knife and the other
sons are setting now very hot I've just
ripped to my phone it's like 31 degrees
and it's like half 5:00 at night crazy
very humid today to be able to heading
down that looks amazing the Caesar I got
the thumbs out it's much clearer than
when we Swedes it flying down here last
night I mean it was kind of fun to
really say it was kind of dark it was a
bit stormy and if I'm hit you to it and
it's gonna be a real nice under bollocks
me
[Music]