so now we're going to review some of the
homework that I'm going to assign and
terminal commands will be like print
working directory and LS LS - LA and CD
dot dot up and and then LS and CD in 209
change directories and I don't know what
other ones
yeah maybe make derp if you want to show
that and and remove recursively force a
directory to delete the directory you
may
so we're recording all this so you can
look back at those but that's it take a
screenshot of it just showed me a couple
of terminal commands and all those
terminal commands are listed in our
course outline if you're finding this
video online just click on my name and
go to my most recent playlist for the go
programming language web development and
you'll be able to get to this outline
but all those terminal commands are
right here and you know here we have
print working directory LS la LS
permissions not going to worry about
that yet CD make your touch clear don't
worry about change mod environment yeah
that's it right so that's that's pretty
much all of them so I'll do the first
first hands-on exercise and then the
next one is installed go take a
screenshot go version you've already
done that easy extra points you've
already created github repo maybe you
added to get ignore file maybe you
didn't but this dot get ignore and you
could just tell it to ignore like you
could look up your own BS code get
ignore golang right and you can look up
a going get ignore file and so here's
one and we'll go look at it you can just
copy that to you bash history vs code
test so I can just hit Raw right
here and then copy all that put that in
a file called dot get ignore and it'll
be a hidden file and it will ignore
things from github for me so upload that
screenshot a hash function now a hash
function we talked about that because it
golang.org when you go to download you
go to download go we have these hash
functions down here sha-256 and and so
for Windows let's go one amd64 MSI
windows AMD 64 MSI so here it is right
and we talked about what that is the
sha-256 checksum hash function so in
your own words just kind of describe
what a hash function is remember they
take the program on their end that
they're going to deliver to me and they
run it through the sha-256 check some
hash thing and to figure out you know
sha-256 mac right we're using eat linux
unix commands mat commands i can look up
that command to see oh how do i run that
it's sha some - a 256 file and then i'll
run it so when when I receive the
program I downloaded then I run it and I
should get this exact same answer which
means that what they they got that
answer on their side when I run it on my
side I need to get that answer otherwise
what they intended and what I received
were two different things pretty cool
so just describe that in your own words
for this assignment and then terminal
commands here are some commands and then
provide an explanation for each of those
commands just because not everybody's
familiar what they do and let me talk
about some of those for a second since
touch will create a file change mod you
can look
- we'll change file permissions so when
I look at like stuff here and if I do LS
- la I get that let me go up a level
okay and now I have permissions and
those permissions are read write execute
read write execute read write execute
okay three times three times read write
execute read write execute read write
execute and when I look at our course
outline I could see that here write the
same thing read write execute redirects
you to rewrite execute and you can see
them right there and its owner group
world so read write execute for the
owner read and execute for the group
read and execute for the world right
well the owner is this person the group
is this person or that group and
everything else is the world so those
are permissions on a file it's beautiful
it's easy it looks a little at first but
just read right XD read write execute
read write execute for the owner the
group the world and then you could
change those you could change them and
by the way here we have addy is a
directory and I don't have any files
let's see if I have any files here I
don't have any files there but if I do
like touch on a no cowboy and then do
this again now I have instead of addy
for directory I just have - and that's a
file so I'm going to remove and if I if
it is a directory I do recursively with
force I'm gonna remove cowboy and now
that should be gone
it's gone so the way change mod works is
you're gonna pass in a number like
change mod 777 temp text or change mod
six six six tip hahaha temp text well
what are those numbers so Reed has a
value of four right has a value of two
executes has a value of one
you could get whatever combination of
some of those up as you want so if I
wanted for for for the owner if I wanted
permissions of only read for the owner
so if I wanted permissions of only read
for the owner I would give for and if I
wanted for the world group to read and
write I would give six because read is
for write is to 4 plus 2 is 6 and if for
the world I wanted to give execute I
would give one so I would do change mod
461 temp text and then it would change
this RW x RW x RW x to match that
appropriately it would be for the owner
it would be it would be read - - for the
world and world we gave it 6ob
read/write - and for no that was the
group and for the world it would be
execute so be read write execute and
that's what would show up right here
from four six one you get it how many
people get it so what would be the
change mod if I wanted to give owner if
I wanted to give owner read write
execute permissions what number do I use
read write and execute what number do I
use what number do I use so read write
and execute scan be four plus two plus
one seven read write and execute for the
owner if I want to give the group read
and execute one number do I use what
number did I use read and execute for
the group 5 because read is 4 execute
one four plus one is five for the world
if I want to give the world write and
execute what number do I use write and
execute for the world
yeah b3 and so I do change mod 753
filename or directoryname and then those
permissions are set simple dude if
you've ever tried to change permissions
on Windows
we need to help but they want to keep
going hmm
so if I want to give the owner so my
command will be changed mod on that one
753 you know file.txt
all right just like down here change mod
7 7 7/10 text so 7 7 7 which would mean
that the owner has read/write/execute
the group has read/write/execute and the
world has read write execute because
read is for world is to execute is 1 and
that's 4 plus 2 plus 1 is 7 what does
this one say what is that 1 what kind of
permissions were given to file dot txt
with that statement go tell us what kind
of permissions yeah then they're kind of
crazy you know all right what kind of
permissions are given with this one
let's take a crack at it how about
yourself
owner can execute group can write the
world can write and execute yeah so if I
wanted the owner to be able to just
write what number did I put down for the
owner to just write is for 4 oh no
you're right - my bad she's like yeah
you're absolutely right right if I just
want the owner to write its - if I want
the group Z if I want the group to be
able to read what number do I put down
for the group Sariah
it's a command we're looking at terminal
command so if I have that touch I don't
know
Aspen LS LA and I can see it's got
readwrite for owner read for group read
for world and if I do change mod and I
want read write execute for the owner
read is for write is to execute as one
read is for write is to execute is one
so I ask myself if I want read write and
execute I add four plus two plus one and
that's seven so for the owner they're
going to get a permission of seven seven
and then for the group which is the next
person in that permission chain owner
group world
here's read write execute we have owner
group and then world so for the group if
I want just read write if I want just
read write for the group I'm going to do
four is read to is right add those
together and for the group I'm going to
put in six because its owner group world
so the group I put in six and then if I
want just read for the world if I want
just read for the world read is four
so I'm going to put in four so seven is
read/write/execute or two plus one is
seven and that's gonna honor read and
write is six and that's gonna be for the
group and the world is just going to be
read which will be four so seven six
four and I'm gonna do Aspen's
change mod seven six for Aspen and then
we're gonna see this go from RW whatever
to RW x RW r RW x RW r all right so the
RW X is 4 to 1 or 7 4 plus 2 plus 1 is 7
that's for the owner for the group RW is
4 plus 2 that was the 6 right here and
for the world it was read which is 4 was
that good better I had to slow down I
was going too fast
yeah cuz you have to look at that and
then look at this and it's too fast
everybody else okay cool you got enough
to understand change mods just how we
set permissions and the reason that's
useful is at some point we might upload
files to a server and need to set the
permission to execute run this right and
then we'll have to go in and look at
what are the permissions and change mod
it set the permission so that's where it
comes in to this class and web
programming I'm gonna remove that file
just remove it and now it should be gone
it's pretty sweet when you get good with
those commands just being able to kind
of create things change permissions move
things it's actually really nice alright
so there's a long video 16 minutes
what are we learn in this video mostly
change mod and terminal commands