we are learning about delaying for
webdev this is an entire playlist here
on YouTube you could find it by clicking
on my username and then just looking for
my most recent playlist on going webdev
and the first video will give you access
to all the code the code resources so
check it out and we're looking at
functions now now if I wanted to I could
play around ba a little bit more I could
have it take in I can have it defined
with multiple parameters okay and so
when I call it now I have to pass in
multiple arguments I define it with
multiple parameters and I call it with
multiple arguments just terminology okay
and I'm returning a simple string
it's sprint when we looked at sprint
hold down command on my keyboard and
click on sprint spaces are at it between
operands when neither is a spring string
so no space should be added so I need to
and he is though because you know at
least one of those is a is a string and
only spaces are added what neither is a
spring strings I need to add my spaces
and I'm gonna return multiple returns
you can have multiple returns so I need
to return a string which is what I'm
returning with funked sprint and I'm
going to return y plus 10 I've been
doing sequel in the mornings with
Roxanne so I want to add semi-colons to
the end lines you don't have to add
semi-colons the compiler will add them
in for you they're there they're just
out of the way to keep things clean Zen
beautiful not cluttered this is not the
house of that one relative what you have
where crap is everywhere this is like
the Guggenheim Museum in New York it's
clean there's space emptiness it's nice
now why do I have this red line up here
I'm returning to values and I'm only
catching one so I either need to throw
away one of the values I could throw
away that one value that's being
returned now the compiler knows that I
know what I'm doing right I'm throwing
away that number that comes back Y plus
ten or I could assign it something and I
could print it if I look print line
spaces are always added between operands
this is an operand this is an operand
this is an operand this is an operator
operating on the operands I don't know
if this is an operator I guess it is if
these are operands print line formats
using default formats for its operands
and rights to standard out just looking
to see if operator was included that's
not this is an expression it evaluates
to some value expressions evaluate to
some value eg y plus 10 is going to
evaluate some value it's an expression a
statement is a line of code to be
executed
buta programming a statement is a
syntactic unit of imperative programming
language that expresses some action to
be carried out a program written in such
a language is formed by a sequence of
one or more statements a statement may
have internal components eg expressions
to evaluates values I'm sharing with you
what all this means because when I
learned about programming it confused me
you know sometimes they talk about
statements and expression like I don't
know what you're talking about right
parameters and argument what are you
talking about all these different words
so I'm teaching you the language with
which the language which we use to talk
about the language or the language we
use to talk about programming how many
people that's helpful for you right so
you could point to something when you
get into a code shop and start working
you can say what's going on with that
expression right there or look at the
statement on line 25 or lying 26 look at
the statement on line 26 and you know
you're not gonna say you'll sound like
you know what you're talking about which
you will know it's talking about you'll
know the difference between statement
and expression between very between
parameter and argument you define a
function with the parameter you call a
function and pass in arguments beautiful
so we've got multiple parameters we have
multiple returns that's kind of cool
and I think that's a good place to end
on this video we've kind of got some
functions here going I think I'll give
you a hands-on exercise in the next
video so you can code