here's the solution to this hands-on
exercise I'm going to create a new
folder 0 3 and then create a new file
thing and this is package main and func
main and then I have to create a new
function so funk foo and and if I had
returned to be there but that's the
basics for function and I want to take
in a string any variable and I also want
to take in an int and so this these are
the parameters when I define my function
I could pass values in so I define my
function with parameters I could pass
values into that so when I pass a value
of type string into this function and
type int into this function I'm gonna
pass in a string in an int I have to
pass them in as this in this order so I
will call this function foo and I have
to pass in a string and I also have to
pass in an int so I defined my function
with parameters it's gonna take a value
of type string and a value of type int
and I call my function with arguments
it's going to take an argument of types
of type string and an argument of type
int in that order when I pass in Tod
here to this string it gets assigned to
a variable X when I pass in 42 here to
this int it gets assigned to a variable
Y the scope of x and y is this function
I could use and reference the variable
X&amp;Y inside that function not anywhere
else so I could come here and I could do
format print line X comma Y and that
should run now the nice thing about
functions this allows us to modularize
our code we take a chunk of code and we
put it into a function and we call that
function something that it does a
calculate grade maybe so if we are you
know working with students we could have
a function calculate grade which will
get all the scores for a student
calculate the grade grade and return a
result we only have to write that
function once and we could call it over
and over so it allows us to not repeat
ourselves in our code do not repeat
yourself DRI is the principal and it
allows us to call a function many times
I don't know who 17 I will do my friend
Cole and now when I run this right each
time it called that function it passed
in arguments of the requested type and
then you sign those two variables and
then it ran the code here so the program
entered here it ran foo I ran foo I ran
foo around food program accident so
that's this solution to this problem
create a func and created a func it
takes two arguments a value of type
string and a value of type int takes two
arguments about you type string about
you've type int the func should print
out two values prints out the two values
from func main call the funky made and
passing your name and age called the
func I made passed in my name and a
number and then call the func in and
pass in the name and age of one of your
friends so I called it again and passed
in the name of age of other people so
some important concepts covered there
this is a function alright so we created
a function functions allow us to
modularize
our code and dry do not don't repeat
yourself all right as opposed to if I
just had you know all of that over and
over and over again up here I am writing
the same code over and over and over
modularize it right and this function
functions bunks are defined with
parameters parameters specify value of a
certain
tight to be passed and when the funk is
called and then when we call a funk we
pass in arguments right anybody have any
questions about that I see some people
struggling a little bit maybe with just
sort of understanding this idea of
putting our code into different places
and then calling it so the mind learns
well through association and what that
means is if you go to like let's say
friend takes you to karate his karate
practice and then afterwards you go get
amazing Mexican food and then next week
he says hey let's go to karate and you
think cool I want to forego an amazing
Mexican food afterwards karate and
Mexican food got associated in your mind
or in my sequel class which roxanne's in
with me I can't remember the students
name until I I told a story about how
you say can in Spanish lotta like a can
and then as soon as like I did that my
mind went back to when that story
occurred a week before and when I
learned his name and his name Jose came
to me so that story lotta and his name
were all associated in my mind so as
soon as I said the lot to store and like
oh yeah his name's Jose came to my head
so the mind learns through association
I'm telling you that because some of you
I could see are struggling a little bit
with this idea that you know we kind of
modularize our code and put it into
functions and then call those functions
and so a good thing is to think about
some
that we can compare that to some sort of
an analogy and an analogy might be like
storage containers in your fridge right
like so you get done with dinner and you
had steak and you get salad and you had
rice well if you threw all that into one
container it's just kind of gonna be a
big mess you know
and you throw that in the fridge you
pull it out now the rice the salad and
the steak all the flavors are messed up
but if you put them each into their own
container and then store them in the
fridge when you're ready to use them
again you pull them back up out and open
up each container and it's like oh cool
you know there's my salad container
there's my my container for steak
there's my container for rice and you
get the container with the stuff in it
that you want in the same way these are
containers and we put into them things
that are related like here's the
function which prints out the name and
the age cool we only want to write that
function once and then we could use it
over and over and over or here's the
function that calculates a student's
great cool we only want to write that
once and then for each student we'll
call it so that's called calling a
function when we call a func
right we passed in arguments does that
how many people are feeling like on a
scale of zero to ten what's your clarity
on this stuff here good 10 10 10 8 9 e 9
huh good good 9 8 good cool all right
great glad you hear it forget it
I want to make sure the pace is right
for the audience that I got so it
doesn't matter how far we go if we go
too fast and you don't understand any
but that's not gonna serve anyone so
we're just doing what we do doing what
we can do