so here's the solution to this one
create a fog multiplies two arguments
which share which are both the type int
and returns a result isn't it print out
the return value so I'm gonna create a
func which takes in two values both of
type int and it's going to return an it
so remember our signature for functions
is func receiver which is optional
optional identifier which in this case
is foo parameters returns return or
returns and then code all right like
that's our signature for function you
should memorize that and so now I come
down here and I'm gonna return x times y
x times y is an expression it will
evaluate to value and then we'll return
that and all of that is our statement
then up here I'm going to call func
sue so food I'm gonna pass in two values
and this will evaluate to a value right
when I run that that's gonna evaluate to
a value it's gonna call foo it's gonna
pass in 40 and assign that to X it's
gonna pass in 45 and assign that to Y
it's gonna multiply 40 times 45 return
that which is an int and now I'm
returning a value if I try to run this
right now it's gonna give me an error
where am i nothing happened right
it ran but it didn't do anything with
the value now I'm going to catch that
value returns the value and assigns it
to Z this is going to be a value it gets
assigned to Z now I'm gonna func dot
print line that value now when I run it
prints out 1800s cool