so we're talking about funks we're
learning the language fundamentals and
then we're gonna get into web dev so
we'll spend a couple of classes on
language fundamentals and now we're
going to create another funk and and so
to create another funk funk foo and then
we just have it print something hey
what's up and then I could call foo and
these parentheses used to kind of be
weird to me like why why do I need the
parentheses to execute you know and
function you always have to when you
call a function so the identifier is foo
and when you call the function you need
to have those parentheses to tell the
program if there are any arguments that
you're passing in and even if there are
no arguments you have to tell it that so
those friends are kind of that's how a
function executes now a function is just
another type and go-go is all about type
if we look at the language specification
we look at the different types my index
will pop up here in a second the
different types here in the language
specification a function is one of the
types and int is one of the types it's
under numeric string is one of the types
so just just like any other type if we
wanted to we could do some cool things
with it like assign it to another
variable so I'm going to run this and
bring up my terminal and navigate to CD
go source github goes to 11
going webbed oh oh oh oh and I'm in
sixth and 300 nine go run me
and who is here program about to exit
that raw string literal and this is the
entry point beginning of the program
okay so that ran that's cool
if I wanted to just to show you a couple
things about funks I'm going to create
another funk
why is it giving me an error that red
underline I'm 18 and 22 I have to
identify errs being declared with the
same it's the same identifier right I
can't do that
so fubar and this one will have will
pass something in to it we're gonna pass
in a string and then we'll use that
string and we'll return the string
sprint line and it's going to return a
string sweet and now we're going to call
that one and I'm going to put all this
about to exit onto one line right within
the raw string literal just clean up a
little bit now we'll call bar and to
call bar we need to pass in a string and
then it's returning a string so I'm
going to return I don't know sign it too
and that's a number usually I'll sign it
too I don't know
a and I'm gonna just clean this up here
because now we could see you know sprint
line and something being returned so I'm
gonna bring that right here and now I
need to use a because if I have a
variable it's not used watch as soon as
I use it
watch that red underline under a
disappeared you can't have a variable
and not use it
go says what are you doing that is code
pollution code must be clean readable no
unused variables rookie programmer like
put it in later leave a comment make a
note but don't have a variable there
that's not used it's only going to
confuse people
there's a nice Xin fierceness to the go
programming language a nice wonderful
German engineering fierceness the right
aspect right here so I can run that
James Bond is he who is here James Bond
is here and take this space out right
there comma includes the space program
about two exits and I have to sprint
lines so I'm just gonna do sprint on
this one and return a string without the
carriage return that's why I have two
spaces between James Bond is here and
about to exit James Bond is here space
tank and put in little adjustments there
we go we could go look at Sprint and see
about that space sprint formats using
the default formats for its operands and
returns the resulting string spaces are
added between operands when neither is a
string when neither as a string spaces
are added and Sprint's line spaces are
always added between operands and a new
line is appended we get to know what
these different functions do
so that we can use them well let me see
where this video is at we are at 6:37 I
like keeping these short we will
continue our exploration of functions in
the next video