so we're learning go programming for web
development here and the first thing
that we're going to do is learn the
language and we've already kind of done
just a little bit of ground work and
getting everybody's dev environment set
up and I'm gonna give you a really good
resource if you're just finding this
video online and that resource is going
to be the course outline this course
outline is amazing and you can take the
entire course with all of the videos
organized sequentially easily accessible
at this URL I got into education to help
people so if the price of this course is
too much for you just message me on
twitter twitter and i will get you
discounted or free access when you
message me just sort of tell me what
your situation is and and then I'll get
you discount free access so this is the
outline if you want to get to this
outline just go to this URL right here
which is right there
course outline they'll bring you here
and and then all the code that we're
using right now we're doing all of our
code on github it is at going web dev
goes to 11 so github going web dev goes
to 11 and the code that you're singing
class will be under attempt and in 63
fall 2018 so that's where all the code
for is class will be and I'm just now
starting to record we had a couple of
classes where we are getting things set
up so now in here instead of just using
print line package main bunk mains the
entry point of my program instead of
using print line to print that statement
I chose you sprint line maybe at some
point we looked at funked the funked
package right and maybe at some point
we'll want to use sprint line just to
get a string and so here's one way I
could do it it returns a string right
here's the func so functions are the
font keyword and when we have a function
a function is always going to follow
this func keyword and optional receiver
so optional I'll do that
I'll do two like that optional receiver
and identifier which will be
the name of the function parameters you
know which will pass arguments in to a
function has been defined with
parameters so that's a really nice way
to say that we will pass arguments in to
a function that has been defined with
parameters right so we have thunk
keyword and then receiver and we'll
learn what receivers are and then
identifiers for the function then
parameter and then returns and there
could be multiple returns and then code
okay so that's the signature the form
that functions take in the go
programming language and so here I went
to look at the func package and you can
see I'm using a function called Sprint
line from the front package so this is
dot notation so we've got dots
print line from package funked use the
function Sprint line that's how you
would read that and say that from
package funked use the function Sprint
line there's all this code pre-written
for you to use we just have to figure
out how to use it a lot of the hard
works been done for us we just have to
find the different pieces like LEGO
building blocks and build things and
bring them together
cool right so func sprint line I could
hold down command I'm in goal and V s
code is the number one choice it's free
it's awesome I never learned it I
learned JetBrains stuff which I get free
as an educator so that's why I'm using :
strongly recommend BS code though and
here we have func from package bump
sprint line and and we could go and just
hold down command this also works in BS
code I don't know what the key is but
you could click on the function it takes
you right to the definition the code
that was written by the people who
created the go programming language the
definition of that function the way it
was written by the developers of the
good programming language
this is really nice because it allows us
to see how they wrote the language and
we see things which are beautiful and
simple
the three principles the three guiding
principles by which this language was
created was efficient execution fast as
lightning go programming language has to
be fastest like lightning
efficient compilation I don't want to
sit around for half a day to see if my
code builds into an executable that
works efficient execution efficient
compilation and ease of programming make
it easy baby like that reads beautiful
right like that's you know not a bunch
of cluttered stuttering doublespeak pump
you know it's just like beautiful
so sprint line takes a very attic
parameter dot dot dot means many just
like in English if somebody said dot dot
dot at the end of a sentence you know
there's a lot more there dot dot dot
here means take put passing as many
arguments as you want it's a very attic
parameter is the term we use very attic
parameter and then it takes a value of
any type which is what the empty
interface says and it returns a string
cool so I got to return a string so I'm
gonna catch my string and then write
it'll give me that and now I have to use
it and so this is kind of not clean
programming because I could have just
done all that put my phrase right here
and not assign it to a variable but just
kind of interesting to show you
something so we're going to talk about
functions and review functions and I
know one showed that this was the entry
point of the program and then down here
will be the exit to our program
so when it leaves funk funk laying the
program is over and we signify strings
with either double quotes or which other
character anybody remember back tick and
that's a raw string literal which means
I could put double quotes inside there
and it can also hold returns when I
print that raw string literal so we'll
just keep this as video one