so we'll look at the solution to this
hands-on exercise and I guess I'll do it
here so that code goes up create a new
folder and we'll call this 0 on 0 and on
and then inside there we'll create a new
folder I'll call it 1 and inside there
will create a new go file call it main
and its package main and func main and
we want to create a program that stores
two in values and two different
variables so X colon equal 40 Y colon
equal to z : equal X plus y and format
print line see I think that's what we're
looking for to multiplies the values and
those variables together and stores
result in third round and prints out the
value of the third variable so we don't
multiplication and then to run that CD
go source github goes to 11
and golang webdev and then 0 0 0 and 63
and 0 1 0 and o 100 or 80 sweet so that
was our first hands-on exercise and get
another one in the next video