now we're gonna see the solution to this
hands-on exercise and I'll go to my
editor and close this file create a new
folder although to and inside there
create a new go file name and then main
and main and we want to create a new
funk so remember a funk funk keyword
receiver identifier parameters returns
and then code okay so the funk we're
going to create will be funk - and
parameters doesn't need anything
returns doesn't need anything and it's
going to call the store your name
and a variable so X call and equal James
Bond stores your agent variable Y
calling equal 32 and print your name and
your age font dot print line XY and call
it and run it
your spawn 32
that's solution show hands how many
people got it
cool reach out
learning a language fundamentals before
we get in to learn the web program