so we're learning going web dev fall
semester whole class there's a playlist
on YouTube somebody just said where is
it you go YouTube Todd
MacLeod and you know I have a couple
channels one is personal that might be
personal one but then learn to code will
have all my coding ones and and then
once you come there you could just go to
playlist and and all you here's learn
sequel and and I'll have a new going web
dev and so it'll be the most recent
going web dev playlist so that's where
I'll be and now we are going through the
course outline and the course outline
for everybody else can be found right
here right there there's the course
outline and and then so we're going
through some homework so this homework
we had change mod nano is you have to be
on UNIX or Linux puts a little text
editor cat just print out the contents
of a file right so we learned all that
stuff about github last week with SSH
totally cool and we're catting out the
public key so we could copy that drop
that into github SSH area and remove is
to remove a file remove recursively with
force sudo is a super user do so if I
ever kind of like try to run a command
and the command doesn't work right so
let's say I try to you know create a
file with touch and it didn't work I can
do sudo touch uh I don't know what's in
our ski resort all right yeah heavenly
but so I could run that as sudo then
it's gonna ask me for my computer
password I'm not going to type it in and
and then yeah it brought me back to my
prompt
I've got like a really long comp
description there so yeah that's a
pseudo Super User do and then copy will
copy from one place to another place so
that's kind of cool
so I could do LS - la and then I could
do touch and heavenly and then LS la and
I could do copy from here and dot is the
current directory here heavenly - like
home and that's home and I'll do it to
my home directory we'll see what happens
and then if I go to my home directory CD
Wham or that's exactly the same as this
alright go to my home directory and LS
la I've got heavenly there you see it so
I copied something I'm gonna remove
heavenly and I'm gonna go back into CD
go source github goes to eleven golang
web web dev and we were in 0 0 0 and
then 0 0 0 temp and i think is 6363
there we go and and it's still there
here because I removed it from where I
copied it to but I didn't remove it from
there so I can move this if I wanted I
could move heavenly and let me just try
this because I'm already in that
directory I can move heavenly and I'm
gonna move it to my route and now if I
look here heavenly is no longer there
but if I change to my route then
heavenly is there so that was move and
copy
and then echo what's that go do right
now you know a few more to look up there
don't worry about echo PS the pipe
symbol grep and then CD definitely do
these are what's that go echo terminal
command echo and computing is command
command and dos us to Microsoft Windows
UNIX I'll brings the outputs the strings
it is being passed as parameters is
command typically used in shell scripts
basketballs outputs - text to screen
yeah think it's just echo
well heavenly has nothing in it I know
heavenly I removed have okay nano new
file and this is new new and then exit
yes and then echo new file so it just
gave me the file name echo echo E&amp;B yeah
I don't know what let's get rid of that
from the homework edit
HECO is gone I'll get rid of crap all
right so those are some terminal
commands