so we're just continuing to kind of go
through these assignments and so
describe the client-server architecture
what analogy was using class what do
clients do and what do servers do so
client-server architecture is a way to
arrange the roles of computers on a
network just like in a restaurant this
is the analogy in a restaurant we have
clients and servers servers serve food
clients ask the service for food the
server's go and get it bring it back the
same analogies kind of what the roles of
computers on the network do their
clients who ask for information and
servers fulfill them servers are just
regular computers running certain
software they're ready to accept
requests and fulfill those requests like
on the web we have web servers regular
computers running certain software and
goes the software we could use to
fulfill those requests to create a
server so that's a client-server
architecture and Linux user permissions
what does this mean who has access what
kind of access to they have is this a
directory or a file - directory we know
that by the D and we have owner group
world the owner has read write execute
the group has read execute and the world
has read and write I think I have too
many things in there we need to edit
this so it's owner group world
so the first three our owner the first
three our owner the next three are group
read and execute for the group
and the last three are the world read
and write for the world and when we see
that like in our course outline you have
that nice diagram let's see that here we
could see the owner we could see the
group and in the world is everyone so
just understanding the terminal the
shell bash okay
so save that and then we have a changing
user commit permissions and Linux what
command will use at the terminal to get
the following users the following
permissions owner read write execute
what would the number be 41 remember for
for read to four right one for execute
so if you want the owner to have read
write execute what number seven
so the owner read/write/execute
I'm sorry to belabor this if you're
watching this video online but we have a
deaf student in class and so we're just
making sure we go slow she's having to
watch the person signing at the same
time and then looked at the screen but
here we have the owner
read/write/execute
read for right to execute 1 4 plus 2
plus 1 7 and the group is read and
execute so that's going to be 4 + 1 5
and then the public is read and that's 4
and I'm just gonna confirm that
read/write/execute 4 2 1 read write
execute and here we had read write
execute just making sure they're in the
right order cuz I'm no genius I know
what I know and I know what I don't know
and it's important to understand both of
those so I'm still learning to you
alright and then we get into variables
we'll do that in the next video this is
finishing up terminal commands