hi i'm vanessa from speak english with
vanessa calm are you ready to expand
your vocabulary let's get started do you
want to improve your vocabulary do you
want to have fun do you want to see my
house if you answered yes yes and yes
then today you are in luck because I
want to help you understand and use over
40 essential household words expressions
and phrasal verbs we're gonna go around
to each of the rooms in my house and I'm
gonna show you what's there and maybe
what's not there but what may be is
typically there in other American
households so that you can use those
words because in a video that I recently
made called how to learn English at home
I mentioned that you can look around you
and ask questions about your
surroundings what's that what's in that
box who is that
well the way that you can do this is if
you have the vocabulary to explain those
things so I hope that today you'll be
able to expand your vocabulary even if
you are an advanced English speaker I'm
sure that you're gonna learn some useful
expressions and you'll realize this is
what native speakers really use in real
life instead of what they use in
textbooks so I challenge you after this
lesson try to go around your house and
name things you can even write down the
label and put it around if your family
members don't mind this is a great way
to expand your vocabulary so pay
attention make some notes and let's get
started welcome to my kitchen I'm gonna
just go around the room and in fact I'm
gonna go around the kitchen the living
room the office the bathroom and the
bedroom and we're gonna go step by step
through the different things that I see
I'm gonna name them if they need any
explanation I'll try to explain them and
I hope that it will be helpful to you as
you expand your vocabulary alright let's
start with the fridge here's the fridge
or you can say refrigerator if you want
to be you know extra intense but we
often just say fridge pretty simple on
the top you have the freezer and my
freezers on top sometimes freezers are
on the bottom or sometimes it split down
the middle and there's a freezer on one
side and a refrigerator or fridge on the
other side mine's just on the bottom you
can see I have a lot of
magnets and pictures on my fridge is
pretty typical I have some magnets that
some YouTube subscribers sent me some
pictures some magnets that we've picked
up as we've traveled but this is pretty
typical that you'll see some kind of
personal mementos on the fridge here we
have our dining room table in the u.s.
typically people will have a dining room
or maybe their kitchen will be a little
bit bigger than mine because we live in
an apartment it's from the 1920s so
actually my apartment at my house is
quite different than what you would
typically see if you visited someone's
house in the US but a lot of the items
are the same so if there's any
differences from typical houses in the
u.s. I'll try to explain that to you as
well
but here we have the table pretty simple
I bet you learned that in your maybe
first class in English class we have
chairs we usually call these kitchen
chairs or if you have a separate dining
room you can call them dining room
chairs because we have a one-year-old
you're gonna see a lot of different
items around our house that are for our
one-year-old so here we have his high
chair his high chair attaches to the
kitchen chair so it's a little bit
different than a standalone high chair
that would be just a separate chair but
we don't have much room in our kitchen
so we have a portable high chair that
attaches to a chair next let's move on
to this table which is where we cut
things and prepare a food here you can
see a fruit tray you might call it
different things to paint on what region
of the US you're from at the moment we
only have two tangerines on the fruit
tray typically we have more but we also
have a coaster this is where you put
your cups or your mugs usually hot or
cold things to keep the table safe we
also have a coffee grinder for grinding
beans and a sippy cup for our baby and
let's move along over here on this side
we have our cheese grater this is with a
tea even though it sounds like a D
grater it's a cheese grater our knives
we have some measuring cups in the US we
use cups and tablespoons and teaspoons
to measure things a lot of people have
these in
sztyc but ours our cute little cat and
here we have some condiments that we
often use when we're cooking so we have
them close by and handy
we just have honey some balsamic some
chopsticks some salt some olive oil and
of course you can see my plants which
are not doing too well I don't have a
green thumb as they say our plants often
die so they don't have a good feature
looking ahead of them this is our oven
where we cook in baked things typically
we call the top the stove top or the
stove and there's four burners on this
stove top and we have some knobs for
turning on the stove inside is the oven
often I'll just say the oven to mean the
full stove or this full device but you
can kind of use them interchangeably
some people are sticklers about that
kind of thing sticklers means picky
picky about those kind of terms but we
often say oven stove for this general
device but technically the top is the
stove and inside is the oven I have some
pots and pans here there's more under
the counter here I have my glass lid
because inside I'm making some butternut
squash for lunch a little bit later and
my cutting board I have a couple other
cutting boards but this one is my
favorite so it stays close by and handy
on this side of the kitchen are the oven
mitts and our spice rack typically
people will say spice rack or spice
cabinet if they're inside a cabinet we
have technically it's a shelf but we
call it the spice rack because all of
the spices are there I also have some
tea and some cookbooks and some
miscellaneous things on that shelf as
well so this is something that's pretty
different from typical houses in the US
we have a sink most places have a sink
with a faucet we have the strainer or
colander usually a strainer for
straining pasta or other things that
we're washing but we didn't have a
dishwasher until about one month ago and
it's because this is an old apartment as
I mentioned it's from the 1920s so
there's not air can
Janene not regular heating no dishwasher
no washer or dryer for clothes but we
decided to buy a you can see here
tabletop dishwasher this is not typical
in houses in the US but it's the same
idea typically they're under the counter
and it's kind of part of the furniture
but you can open the dishwasher and see
the dish rack here we have some clean
dishes and apparently toys they need to
be clean too so we have the dish rack
and you put your dishes in the dish rack
and up here I have a small dish rack
just for more fragile things like these
mugs or these glasses but you can hand
dry things and put them in the rack as
well so that's just depending on what
you have in your house if you have a
dishwasher or if you need to hand wash
things and then put them in the drying
rack or in the rack above the dishwasher
we have a cabinet where we keep our dry
goods so you can see we have some some
spices some popcorn things for baking
there's some pasta some kind of leftover
dry goods that we put in there to keep a
lot of people will have what you call a
pantry and a pantry is kind of like a
closet where you keep dry goods but our
apartment is pretty small it's old we
don't have a pantry so we just have a
cabinet beside the dishwasher we have a
toaster oven and a lot of people will
also have a microwave in fact I'd say
99% of Americans have a microwave we
just don't have it because we don't have
a lot of space this is an old apartment
like I mentioned so there's a couple key
elements there's one more key element
that you will not see in our house that
I'll mention a little bit later but we
have a toaster oven a lot of people have
a regular toaster and it will just have
slots so we call this the toaster
because it's the only one we have but if
you have a toaster with slots and a
toaster oven you probably need to be a
little more specific and just say put it
in the toaster oven or I put it in the
toaster oven just so people know which
one it's in we have a paper towel rack
this is the paper towel rack the middle
Pease and here are some paper towels for
cleaning up things and we also have a
water kettle a hot water kettle for
heating up water so this is kind of like
our little drink station I have tea
things Dan have some coffee things we
have some dishwashing soap this is where
all of those kind of extra kitchen
things happen and finally it's a little
bit awkward for me to show you with the
camera because it's a little bit high up
so I have to hold the camera myself but
here we have our dishes so we have big
plates little plates you might come
across some specific words for different
sizes of plates but in reality way to
say big plates little plates we have
some wine glasses some regular glasses
tall glasses short glasses and bowls a
lot of people have different sizes of
bowls or different functions for
different bowls but we keep it simple
bowls up on top was well we have some
mugs you can see we have a lot of mugs
because to be like choosing the right
mug for that moment is an important part
of drinking a hot drink you have to have
the right mug do I want the the mug with
birds on it do I want the mug with a
rainbow on it it just depends and it
kind of lends the experience of richer
feeling I don't know if you feel the
same way about the mug that you drink
your coffee or your tea out of but I
feel like the mug is important to me
alright let's go to the next room when
you first come into our house we have a
shoe rack where we line up our shoes and
this is typical in some American houses
but in a lot of American houses people
keep their shoes on for us we lived in
Korea for a couple years so we got used
to taking off our shoes and we have a
sign on the door that says please take
off your shoes we will appreciate it but
a lot of our friends have never actually
looked at the sign and we don't tell
them hey take off your shoes we're
pretty relaxed when it comes to guests
but for ourselves
we always take off our shoes if we need
to run in to the house for something
quickly then it's not a big deal but we
have a shoe rack so that we can easily
take off our shoes and put them away
when we come in our
welcome to our living room there is one
thing I want to mention about our living
room maybe a couple things but
specifically the one thing that you're
not gonna see in our living room that's
pretty typical and that's just a TB you
could say television but we often just
say TV why don't we have a TV well it
was a conscious decision to not have a
TV first of all because I'm not a big
fan of different TV shows and it's just
not that enjoyable for me but also I
feel like I don't want to just have it
on and always be watching anyway if we
can talk about that another time but I
wouldn't let you know that it's pretty
typical to see a TV in American
households in their living room or you
could say family room some people say
main room some people say den kind of
like a lion's den this is like a cave
but people say den I don't know if
that's a southern word but some of my
friends in the South say that but we
call this just the living room or the
main room and that's where we spend a
lot of our time on this side of the
living room we have a piano some shelves
for displaying different things you
might hear this called knickknacks and
that means sometimes sentimental things
sometimes just junk
but for us we try to keep only things
that matter to us so we have some
sentimental items on our shelves and on
the piano there's some picture frames
and another coaster you might see as
well that we have a lot of baby gates
everywhere in our living room it blocks
off the full living room and that's
because we have a 1 year old so it keeps
him safe it keeps us sane and maybe for
you if you have a baby you also have
some baby gates I highly doubt that you
have a tent in your living room but if
you have a baby
if you have a kid that likes to play
maybe you have a tent so we just have
this tent with all of our baby's toys
inside and he goes in there and plays
and we play with him in there and it's
just part of our living space now let's
go on to our bookshelf our bookshelf is
one of the main items main pieces of
furniture in our living room we have the
bookshelf the couch and the piano those
are kind of the centerpieces of this
room so on our bookshelf of course we
have books they are somewhat organized
by topic
not so much right now because I just
tried to organize them there myself but
on the bookshelf we have some speakers
we have some other miscellaneous things
up here like our pumpkins that are kind
of rotting and we need to get rid of
them on the bottom we have some toys for
our babies so the first two shelves are
baby things and then these shelves that
you can't reach those are for us so we
can say this is a bookshelf and these
are shelves ah this is where we lounge
this is the couch and we call this a
coffee table even though
we don't typically have coffee on it but
it usually just means that kind of small
ish table that's in the middle of your
living room or close to the couch you
might be surprised that sometimes
Americans put their feet on this I don't
know if you do this but I know in some
cultures it's seen as extremely gross
but you just prop your feet up on the
coffee table and kick back and relax but
beside the coffee table or behind the
coffee table you can see we have a side
table I know this expression is really
simple and it's kind of obvious but if
you want to denote which table you could
just say in the side table or the table
beside the couch and on the side table
there's a lamp that we use to light our
reading in the evening on this side of
our living room we have we call this
just our IKEA chair because it came from
Ikea
but you might see people who have
comfortable chairs like this in their
living room you might see them calling
them an easy chair usually an easy chair
is a little bit bigger than this a
little bit more comfortable or you might
hear them call it a lazy boy they're not
talking about how you're not studying
and you're not working hard I'm sitting
on the lazy boy no it just means that
when you sit on it you feel lazy you're
feel comfortable so a lazy boy has a
foot prop that comes up so you can
completely relax and lay back but for us
we just call this our IKEA chair it kind
of bounces a little bit it's not a
rocking chair it doesn't completely go
back and forth but it has a little bit
of movement we have here our win
SIL the windowsill is the place where we
can put seasonal things or just some
decorations if we want and the window
here we have the inner window it has
some kind of maybe more old-fashioned
1920's style panels here but we also
have inside our window another feature
so let's get a little closer and take a
look most windows in the US have a
screen and that's on the other side of
this main window just to prevent
mosquitoes and bugs coming in in the
summertime but because it's winter we
also have another pane a window pane
that's down it's the storm window so you
hear you're only seeing the regular
window pane but on the other side we
have a second layer that's called a
storm window and you could put it down
in case of a storm but typically it's
used in the wintertime usually for older
houses because older houses have two
layers of window they don't have maybe
some modern technology for the windows
structure so we have a screen a storm
window and just this regular window
inside before we leave this room I just
want to quickly talk about the basics of
a room we have of course the walls and
the ceiling but here we have hardwood
floors we don't have any carpet in our
house and that's mainly because it's an
older apartment so it has wood but also
because we have two cats and a baby so
it's a little bit difficult to clean
carpet but most American houses will
have carpets usually in the bedrooms or
if they have an upstairs area in the
upstairs but some will have it as well
in the main room or in the living room I
think it's kind of becoming a more
modern thing to have hardwood floors
kind of going back to that classic style
so you might see that you might have
that in your house if you live in the US
but carpets and rugs rugs are just
removable small carpets rugs and carpets
are pretty typical but we just have
hardwood floors this is not laminate in
the kitchen
you saw laminate laminates just kind of
like a plastic fluorine it's typically
in kitchens because it's easy to clean
but here we have real wood hardwood
floors welcome to our office drum room
spare bedroom
bit of everything in another dying plant
and oh we have Dan Dan's working on
editing a vocabulary video for the Feliz
fluency Club if you'd like to learn with
us you can learn with us every month but
in this room we have the office desk we
have the desktop computer we have
laptops and whatnot as well but the
desktop is great for editing videos and
having a big screen so he's sitting in
an office chair and he is using some of
the office equipment how's it going
it's going well are you getting some
inspiration from the fish welcome to our
bathroom we have only one bathroom in
our apartment a lot of American houses
have at least two but our apartments a
good size for one bathroom typically in
the US we say bathroom in the UK you're
going to hear people say toilet but in
the u.s. we do not say toilet unless
we're talking about the physical object
the toilet so in the u.s. when you say
toilet you feel a little bit dirty maybe
because you're imagining the throne that
chair that you sit on so it's a little
bit weird in the u.s. if you say I'm
gonna go to the toilet we can imagine
that piece of furniture so it's a little
bit better to say I'm going to the
bathroom
we use the term restroom to talk about a
public place some people might even say
bathroom for a public place so maybe in
a restaurant or maybe in a gas station
or if you're driving and on a road trip
there might be a rest stop and you go to
the restroom inside the rest stop those
are the most typical expressions that
you're going to hear in the US bathroom
and restroom but I would not say this is
the restroom if I said restroom at a
friend's house I'm gonna go to the
restroom it's quite formal and it seems
a little bit weird like I'm trying to be
too formal when really I'm just going to
the bathroom and it's my friend's house
so I recommend using restroom only for
maybe workplace situations or for public
places like restaurants or gas stations
where you're going to the bathroom it's
going to be a little bit tricky to film
in here because the bathrooms long and
narrow
but we're going to make it work so here
we have the shower and we know it's a
shower because we have a shower curtain
but in the u.s. you'll typically find
two shower curtains on the outside
there's one that has usually a nice
pretty color on it and then on the
inside you'll see a shower curtain liner
and this is I'll try to show you here
this is on the inside of the bathtub and
that's to prevent water from spilling
out I know I visited some other
countries that don't have shower
curtains at all and I found it quite
difficult to take a shower without
getting the whole bathroom wet so in the
u.s. it's convenient we've got a shower
curtain and we have a shower curtain rod
up here you can see to hold the shower
curtain inside the shower we have a bath
tub and you can take a bath in here but
most people don't take a bath usually
just kids take a bath it's kind of small
it's not so comfortable and it's not
really part of American culture for
adults to take a bath you might see in
some movies maybe a woman in a bathtub
with a glass of wine and there's some
candles this is not typical at all that
hardly ever happens
and we just don't really soak in the
bath some people find it dirty to sit in
the bath water because maybe we don't
clean the bathtubs as often as countries
who take baths so we have also a shower
rack you can see it's hanging on the
shower head the shower head is where the
water comes out we have the shower head
the shower rack and up here we have our
shampoo and conditioner and soap and
what not but we have the shower rec
moving on in the bathroom we have a
little table here with some toiletries
on the table there's you know some
lotions or contacts or toothpaste these
are things that you use to get ready in
the morning or to get ready for bed
there toiletries we have a soap
dispenser and we have the sink and a
faucet and it's pretty typical that
you'll see an outlet as well in the
bathroom I know some countries don't
have outlets in the bathroom it can be
kind of dangerous to have an outlet in
the bathroom so of course just don't put
your hairdryer in this
think little word of wisdom and it
wouldn't be a bathroom without a toilet
so we have the toilet
we have toilet paper and we have the
handle for flushing the toilet as well
as usually two separate lids on the
toilet I know some countries don't have
to separate lids it's kind of all in one
combo but in the u.s. we have two
separate lids and usually a brush a
toilet brush for cleaning the toilet and
a plunger in case you need it
and don't forget some more dying plants
just to around out your full experience
of our house oh I don't want to forget
as well we have these hand towels this
hand towel is for drying your hands
after you wash your hands and a
washcloth this is for washing your face
oftentimes a hand towel will have a
little ring and it will be inside that
ring but we don't have that so we just
hang it over the shower curtain rod
welcome to my bedroom the lighting is a
little bit different in here because we
have some extreme blackout shades and
blackout curtains so that we can sleep
and so that our baby can sleep
especially when it takes a nap during
the day so you can see here on the
window we have some black shades and
also some black curtains that is
essential and it has helped our life so
much all right let me show you around
of course the main feature of a bedroom
is the bed here's our bed and we have a
quilt on our bed this is something that
Dan's great-grandmother made but you'll
often see simply sheets in the
summertime or maybe a thin blanket but
in the winter you'll see a comforter
this is a thick fuller type of blanket
in Europe a lot of people use a duvet
but in the US I had actually never heard
of a duvet until I went to Europe so
it's not so common in the u.s. maybe I'm
just taking a little isolated bubble of
people who don't have duvet so if you're
in the u.s. let me know if you have a
duvet but typically you'll see a quilt
or a comforter or just some sheets
you'll see over here is my baby's crib a
lot of people in the US who have a child
they have a separate room for their
child
but our apartment is small so we make do
with what we have
and he sleeps here in this crib on this
side there is a night stand I have a
night stand as well over on this side
the night stand is the table that goes
beside your bed and typically there is a
lamp on the nightstand maybe there's a
drawer or a shelf and you can put some
books or something in that nightstand
that you use when you're sleeping this
is our set of drawers you might hear
people say dresser drawers this I feel
like it's a little bit older English
like maybe my parents or my grandparents
might say dresser drawers but for me I
just say a set of drawers or it's in the
drawer this is a difficult word to
pronounce I hope that you can say it
clearly drawers drawers inside our
closet you'll see some clothes that are
hanging up we hang up the clothes in the
closet or you can say they're hanging in
the closet and they're hanging on what
they're hanging on hangers a lot of
words that have to do with hanging is
that have to do with the closet so the
clothes are hanging up in the closet
some people also fold their clothes up
here maybe some winter clothes or some
pants that you don't want to hang up one
quick thing that I'd like to mention
that we don't have but often typical
American houses will especially
standalone houses apartment sometimes
have this sometimes don't but a lot of
houses have a master bath or you can say
master bathroom and that's a bathroom
that's connected to the biggest bedroom
so typically if you have a household of
parents and two children the parents
bedroom is the biggest bedroom and
attached to the parents bedroom is the
master bath in the house that I grew up
in my parents had this Dan's parents had
this as well
but in our apartment we only have the
one bathroom that I showed you so we
don't have a master bath it's just the
bathroom of the house so you might see
this and if you are in someone's house
or if you're describing a house or maybe
you're buying a house or renting one in
the u.s. you might hear that term
mentioned there's a master bath or
there's a master bathroom
both of those terms are the same thing
it's just a shortened version of
bathroom thanks so much for joining me
in this rather long vocabulary video I
hope that it helped to refresh
some words that you've learned in the
past and hope to add to your vocabulary
so that you can go around your house and
name and label some things that you have
in your house that you see every day it
will help to reinforce those words I
want to ask you a question what is
something that I didn't mention in this
video that you have in your house let me
know in the comments what's an item in
your house that I didn't mention in this
video it can help to expand your
vocabulary I recommend reading other
comments so that you can see things from
other people's houses that I didn't
mention here just keep growing your
vocabulary every day thank you so much
for learning English with me and I'll
see you again next Friday for a new
lesson here on my youtube channel bye
the next step is to download my free
ebook five steps to becoming a confident
English speaker you'll learn what you
need to do to speak confidently and
fluently don't forget to subscribe to my
youtube channel for more free lessons
thanks so much
bye