hi i'm vanessa from speak english with
vanessa calm
do you like phrasal verbs do you hate
phrasal verbs today i'm going to give
you two suggestions to help you remember
and use phrasal verbs in your
conversations
let's get started the first thing we
need to talk about is what is a phrasal
verb a phrasal verb is a verb plus a
preposition or we can call it a
participle it's two parts sometimes
three parts put together so this type of
verb is very commonly used and if you
have been studying English for some time
I'm sure you have run across them run
across is an example you have seen
phrasal verbs in English a lot so today
I want to give you two examples to help
you remember and use phrasal verbs in
the future but first I want to give you
one thing that I do not recommend one
way to learn phrasal verbs that is not
very effective it's very frustrating and
maybe you have been doing this or maybe
you know other people who have been
doing this this technique that I don't
recommend is learning phrasal verbs with
the same verb but different prepositions
for example if you learned go out go up
to go around it's very difficult to
remember the different participles the
different prepositions at the end so I
recommend instead the opposite my first
recommendation is to have the same
participle but a different verb so for
example I think it's a good way to learn
phrasal verbs by saying keep up look up
make up this way of learning will help
you remember easily because it's easy to
remember up and the first part is a
little more unique then around up to
it's difficult to remember that part so
keep up make up look up is a much easier
way to remember phrasal verbs so my
second recommendation goes with this it
is think about a
Corie from your personal life where you
could use these phrasal verbs if you are
learning the phrasal verb look up look
up means to research or to search on the
internet or in a book you could say ah I
remember when I was writing an email to
Vanessa I couldn't remember a specific
word and how to spell it so I had to
look it up I had to look up how to spell
it
oh by connecting a story with the
phrasal verb a story from your personal
life it will help you make those
connections and make phrasal verbs much
easier to remember so to use these two
techniques in my next video I'm going to
explain three phrasal verbs look up keep
up make up using this technique of
having the same participle but a
different verb and in this way it will
help you easily remember these phrasal
verbs and also if you think about a
story from your personal life it will be
much easy thanks so much for watching
this video about phrasal verbs and how
to use them and remember them I
encourage you to go over to my website
where I'll be giving some more examples
and ideas for how to use phrasal verbs
and some samples to help you remember
them thanks so much and I'll see you
again next time goodbye