hi i'm vanessa from speak english with
vanessa calm what's up let's talk about
it in today's video lesson i have a new
challenge for you when i was cleaning my
closet the other day i found a box of
papers that i had saved for a long time
and one of those papers was this article
this article comes from a newspaper
actually from a city that i've never
lived in but somehow I saved this
article I think because it's quite
clever so today we're going to talk
about this article and I want to
challenge you this article is called
what's up doc and in this article there
are over 40 uses of up phrasal verbs
there are a lot of phrasal verbs that
exist in English but in this article he
highlights 40 of those and he kind of
explains why it's so confusing or
complicated and why do we use phrasal
verbs like this in English so what I'm
going to do is I'm going to read this
article to you I'm going to show you the
article on the screen so you're not
going to see my face you're just going
to hear my voice I'm going to read this
article and I want you to take a couple
of these up phrasal verbs and write a
sentence in the comments below this
video
using these phrasal verbs this is a
really clever article so if you don't
understand some of the phrasal verbs
it's okay feel free to use Google feel
free to use the Internet to learn what
they mean or feel a little more clear
about them are you ready to hear this
article wine a page with over 40 up
phrasal verbs let's start reading
what's up duck wow what a day
this edition of the Johnson City News &amp;
neighbor is the largest single paper we
have ever published at 28 pages we are
an hour late for our printing deadline
and I am just now doing this column so
please excuse any errors
I found this information on our terribly
difficult English language
how do non-native learn English nuances
there is a two letter word that perhaps
has more meaning than any other two
letter word and that word is up it's
easy to understand up meaning towards
the sky or at the top of a list but when
we awaken in the morning why do we wake
up at a meeting why does a topic come up
why do we speak up and why are the
officers up for election and why is it
up to the secretary to write up a report
we call up our friends and we use it to
brighten up a room polish up the silver
we warm up the leftovers and clean up
the kitchen we lock up the house and
some guys fix up the old car at other
times the little word has real special
meaning people stir up trouble line up
for tickets work up an appetite and
think up excuses to be dressed is one
thing but to be dressed up is special
the drain must be opened up because it
is stopped up we open up a store in the
morning but we close it up at night we
seem to be pretty mixed up about up to
be knowledgeable about the proper uses
of up look the word up in the dictionary
in a desk size dictionary it takes up
almost 1/4 of the page and can add up to
about 30 definitions if you are up to it
you might try building up a list of the
many ways
help is used it will take up a lot of
your time but if you don't give up you
may wind up with a hundred or more when
it threatens to rain we say it's
clouding up when the Sun comes out we
say it's clearing up
when it rains it wets up the earth when
it doesn't rain for a while things dry
up a guy at work was all stressed out
said he was fed up a Texas rancher
looked at his horse and said giddyup one
guy thought I was too loud he told me to
shut up I went to a casino and the
dealer told me to up my ante
then his boss came over and said ante up
I almost told him to put up or shut up
I'll wrap it up my time is up no more to
put here so I'll give up thanks so much
for learning with me today and focusing
on all of these up phrasal verbs now as
I said in the beginning of this lesson I
recommend in the comments below for you
my challenge is to write a couple
sentences using some of these phrasal
verbs they have a small context in the
article but if you want to research them
or do something else with them so that
you can understand them more fully I
recommend writing a comment trying to
use it and good luck to you see you the
next time bye the next step is to
download my free ebook 5 steps to
becoming a confident English speaker I
want to help you master English and
speak fluently feel free to subscribe so
that you don't miss new English lessons
thanks so much for learning with me bye