hello hello welcome to today's live
English lesson here on the speak English
with Vanessa
YouTube channel I'm so glad that you're
here to improve your English learn an
important phrasal verb today and enjoy
using English that is the goal you want
to learn but most importantly you want
to use what you're learning so I hope
today if you're joining me live you can
write a lot of comments I'll try to give
you some feedback if you are watching
the replay no problem you are welcome to
write comments you're welcome to
participate as much as you can I
recommend repeating some of the
sentences that I say using our key
expression repeat them out loud try to
write them down try to use this kind of
dictation practice and really improve as
we go today thank you everyone who is
here live with me I appreciate it you
guys are awesome
if you would like to join me live we
have live lessons every Tuesday and
Thursday at 9:00 a.m. Eastern Time this
is the New York Times own except today
is Wednesday because if you receive my
emails I announced that we're gonna have
just a temporary time change this week
and next week because I'm travelling to
New York so tomorrow I'm going to be
flying to New York to visit my sister
and there's no live lesson on Thursday
instead it's today and next week there's
no live lesson on Tuesday instead it's
on Wednesday so if you would like
reminders of these time changes it
doesn't happen often but it's important
to be able to plan and not be
disappointed if there's not a live
lesson if you would like these reminders
you can receive my emails that's the
best way quick clear you'll see receive
a little notification about any
Changez and some topics so that you can
prepare and think about them if you want
to get these emails all you have to do
is become part of my email group and the
way that you can do that is to download
my free ebook five steps to becoming a
confident English speaker I hope this
will be a win-win situation for you you
can get the free ebook you can read
those tips and steps and you'll also get
notifications about live lessons so I
hope that for you that will be important
and useful and before we get started I'm
gonna take a look here and make sure
that our a lesson our lesson is
correctly live for some reason I I
changed a little something this morning
so I want to make sure that it's going
well today we're going to be talking
about a phrasal verb which is look
forward to look forward to I'm looking
forward to going to New York and I hope
that for you you can look forward to
something even to something simple
that's really important look forward to
something let's take a look here at our
page to make sure that it's going well
all right I want to change something
really quick make sure that we are live
great all right I think it was a hidden
before so today we're going to be
talking about looking forward to an
event looking forward to something hmm
so for you I want to know what are you
looking forward to are you looking
forward to a special event coming up
soon like me I'm looking forward to
going to New York or for you are you
looking forward to something something
more simple like in daily life I'm
looking forward to seeing my family
everyday what is something that you are
looking forward to and if you are just
joining me right now welcome I'm glad
that you're here
Oh Gabrielle is here hello Francesca
glad you're here today we're talking
about an important phrasal verb which is
look forward to you're looking forward
to something so as we talked about this
phrasal verb I'm gonna write a quick
sentence here and I want to ask you what
is something that you are looking
forward to doing what is something
you're looking forward to doing we're
gonna use a verb after this and I'll
show you my sentence that I just said
I'm looking forward to to going to New
York I'm looking forward to going to New
York tomorrow early in the morning we
have to wake up and get ready so we can
use this phrasal verb plus here we have
important ing looking forward to going
Gabriela says I'm looking forward to
eating my lunch
beautiful Francesca says I'm looking
forward to going to a spa next week oh
how cool nice and relaxing I hope you
can enjoy yourself what are you looking
forward to doing I like to quickly give
you another example if you don't want to
use a verb it's possible that you don't
want to add a verb directly afterwards
so let's say
I'm looking forward to the trip oh I'm
looking forward to like Federica said I
look forward to the summer beautiful so
you are using like we have here a lovely
noun directly afterwards beautiful so
you've got two choices and make sure
that we use an ING verb if you're gonna
use a verb I'm looking forward to going
to New York I'm looking forward to the
trip the trip to New York Joe stell says
I'm looking forward to getting approved
for university best wishes I hope it
works out for you now just as I'm
looking forward to a new job great way
to use this here I have a question for
you as you're making these sentences I
want to know what do you think is the
difference between I'll write this here
how about in orange what is the
difference between these two I look
forward to and I'm looking forward to
what do you think is the difference
between these two variations both of
these are the present tense I look
forward to I'm looking forward to so
what's the difference between these hmm
I will give you a second to think about
it what do you think I'll read some of
your other amazing sentences using this
we could say a lot of waste Oh Lacey
Wong says I'm looking forward to passing
my TOEFL test yes you can do it
Vivian says I'm looking forward to
hearing from you
oh and this is a beautiful sentence that
we often use especially in an email
maybe you are applying for a job or
you're applying for college for a study
abroad internship we could use this at
the end of the email kind of like a
little hint like mmm don't forget to
send me an email don't forget to reply
I'm looking forward to hearing from you
and that simply means you need to reply
because I'm waiting so it's a polite way
to end an email and let them know I
expect a reply I expect you to reply to
me but in a polite way
Gyan says maybe maybe one is a present
in future
God says maybe these two the difference
is just ing hmm as Zoey says one has a
verb and the other has a subject after
forward to all right we've got some
great suggestions here hmm
I'm looking forward to hearing from you
I look forward to hearing from you Oh
so let's first talk about the the
meaning it before we talk about how to
grammatically finish these sentences
these two meanings are really the same
so we need to finish the sentence a
little bit differently but the meaning
is the same for me
I use the second one as you can see here
I use the second one much more often and
it feels a little more conversational
I'm looking forward to getting a reply
from you I'm looking forward to eating
breakfast I'm looking forward to
something hmm so we could say this one
is a little more conversational and the
first one the first one is slightly more
common when you're writing in
email both of these are perfectly fine
really polite if you're writing an email
to your boss to anyone you can use both
of these but the first one it feels a
little bit more a little bit more formal
in you can use this in daily
conversation no problem but it's
slightly a little more structured so
let's talk about how we can finish these
sentences we talked about the first one
or the second one here we have one we
talked about the second one both of
these are examples here about how to
finish it and the second one I look
forward to I look forward to seeing you
maybe I should have left myself some
more room I look forward to seeing you
or I look forward to your your reply
we've got two choices does it look
familiar I look forward to seeing you
I'm looking forward to seeing you I look
forward to your reply I'm looking
forward to your reply oh so really the
only difference between these two ik -
phrasal verb variations is that the
second one is slightly more
conversational but personally I wouldn't
stress about it too much you can use
this in you can write to the President
of the United States the president of
your country and you can say this and
it's totally fine it's not rude it's not
too casual so both of these are are
great we've got a couple more wonderful
sentences here we said Julian says oh I
get it I'm looking forward to is much
more often is much often used yes
looking forward to great John Jack says
I'm looking forward to seeing you oh I'm
looking forward
someday to seeing you I'm looking
forward to tasting your wonderful
cooking and to seeing you AHA human has
a question and human asks what about
these to hearing from you and to hear
from you I'm looking forward to hearing
from you I'm looking forward to hear
from you
so we need to include ing the ing is
essential when we have a verb after this
phrasal verb so after this phrasal verb
we need ing really important so don't
forget it
I'm looking forward to hearing from you
so I want to ask you what is something
that everyday you are looking forward to
every day it's not a big event because
it happens every day maybe for you in
the morning when I wake up every day
because we're talking about every day we
can use that first variation I everyday
I look forward to drinking a cup of
coffee every day I look forward to
taking a walk every day I look forward
to taking a nap because I'm so tired
when I wake up what are you looking
forward to every day what do you look
forward to the food Jan says I look
forward to food yes oh if it one says I
look forward to my breakfast oh knob
shot has a great deep idea here every
day I look forward to meeting my
expectations whoo beautiful idea you set
expectations for yourself and you look
forward to meeting those expectations
Lindsey says I look forward to eating
food every day ah guerilla says I'm
looking forward to watching Beauty and
the Beast
oh I haven't seen it yet
maybe in a couple months but you are
looking forward to seeing it something
that's gonna happen soon Tadeo says I'm
look I look forward to sleeping I'm
looking forward to sleeping oh it's
pretty late for you probably so you are
excited ready to sleep I look forward to
achieving my goal
Oh beautiful oh you look forward to
achieving your goals I look forward to
reaching my goals oh this is beautiful
even if your goal is I wanna eat healthy
today and you successfully eat healthy
that's a great goal or your goal is to
participate in this YouTube lesson this
English lesson great you reached one of
your goals so congratulations you looked
forward in the past you looked forward
to reaching your goal and you did it
beautiful so I want to make sure that we
know even in the past tense even with a
sentence I'll make another quick little
notes even with a sentence like this I
looked forward to lunch when I was in
school a lot of school kids maybe aren't
so excited about going to class so you
could say I looked forward we're using
the past because I'm not in school right
now I'm not in high school certainly not
I looked forward to lunch or I looked
forward to eating lunch so even though
it's in the past we can still use this
we can add here
eating lunch or I looked forward to
lunch great we can use this in the past
because you want to talk about things
that you used to look forward to in the
past beautiful way to use this oh we've
got some other wonderful sentences I'm
going to read a couple more and then
we're going to say a sentence all
together let's see what we have to say
better because I'm looking forward to
seeing the Sun I love the Sun oh you
know what me too
when it's sunny outside it's so much
easier to wake up so much easier to
start your day on the right foot this
expression on the right foot means just
in a good way
I look forward to seeing the Sun every
day oh you mrs. I am looking forward to
seeing you back on Wednesday April 5th
good reminder yes
so our next live lesson will be exactly
one week from today Wednesday April 5th
because usually we have live lessons on
Tuesday but I'm gonna be flying my
flight is pretty early in the morning
coming back from New York so
unfortunately I can't have a live lesson
on the airplane it'd be pretty cool if I
could but this is better better
environment so our next live lesson is
Wednesday you have to wait one week but
there's plenty of materials to review
and go over you can do it so let's say a
sentence together let's say a beautiful
sentence to help you use this phrasal
verb and to help you use some
pronunciation muscles and to help kind
of a mindset growth as you are learning
English it's important to also be
growing your confidence growing your
ability to believe in yourself and we're
not talking about like fairies and
unicorns and rainbows some kind of
unrealistic expectation but a realistic
belief that I can do it I can try my
best and I can do things outside my
comfort zone so let's say this sentence
all together using today's phrasal verb
what should we say how about oh I'm
looking forward to speaking English
simple sentence but the next time that
you have an opportunity to actually
speak English you will have already
repeated this in your head oh I'm
looking forward to speaking English I'm
looking forward to speaking English if
you have a chance write this in the chat
box use this short sentence dictation
practice to write it correctly and let's
say it together I want you to grow that
positive mindset that when you have the
chance to speak English the next time
you're excited about it you are looking
forward to doing that I'm looking
forward to speaking English I'm looking
forward to speaking English beautiful
thank you so much for writing these
sentences it's a good way to practice so
let's say it slowly and then we'll say
it loudly are you ready let's say it
slowly so that you can see my
pronunciation I'm looking forward to
speaking English I'm looking forward to
speaking English are you ready to say it
loudly now that you've got some
pronunciation practice already 3 2 what
I'm looking forward to speaking English
yes I hope that you can say that clearly
and I did Lee and I hope that it's true
for you the more you say it the more
true it will become that you are looking
forward to using this expression and to
using the skills that you're working
hard to create so thank you so much for
joining me today I appreciate it
I'll see you again on Wednesday next
week and if you feel like one week is
too long Vanessa
don't go it's one week well I have some
good news of other English lessons on my
YouTube channel other live lessons other
prepared lessons lots of material you
can learn plenty of phrasal verbs and
idioms mindset tips ideas conversations
I hope that this will be useful for you
over the next week really prepare use
English and if you want to get any
notifications about time changes for
live lessons like today I recommend
reading my free ebook five steps to
becoming a confident English speaker in
this ebook I talk about my personal
journey learning language failing to
learn some languages succeeding with
other languages what has worked for me
and also five ways that you can apply
that to your own life because it's good
to hear someone else's story but you
want to know how does this affect me how
can I use this in my own life so I
provide you with a page of resources
lots of tips and ideas for preparing to
speak English because that's what we're
here for looking forward to speaking
English you can do it thanks so much for
learning with me and have a beautiful
week I'll see you again next week have a
beautiful day everyone I'll see you
later
bye