hello hello hello welcome to today's
live English lesson here on the speak
English
with Vanessa YouTube channel I'm so glad
that you're here to learn English with
me to improve your phrasal verb
knowledge that's what we're going to
talk about today phrasal verbs so if
you're new here to these live lessons we
have live English lessons every Tuesday
and Thursday at 9 a.m. est that's New
York Standard Time and if there are any
time changes I will let you know through
email so if you want to get those email
updates along with email lessons each
week and valuable information about
improving your English all you need to
do is download my free ebook 5 steps to
becoming a confident English speaker
there is a link in the description below
this video and this free ebook will be
delivered to your email and then if
there are any time changes for these
live lessons you will definitely know
when you check your email thanks so much
again for joining me we've got members
here from all over the world we have Joe
Jack hello hello Saleem in Turkey
ekatarina glad you're here glad you're
here thanks for joining me from India
Wow Morocco friends all around the world
Estella hello hello thanks for joining
me and today is our first Thursday live
lesson so I'm glad that you're here on
YouTube the right platform the right
time right place we're going to be
talking about a phrasal verb look into
look into something so I want to ask you
first what do you think this phrasal
verb means what's your heart say about
this phrasal verb I'm going to give you
a sample sentence and maybe that will
give you a little hint as to what this
means my simple sentence is
this is not true by the way just a
sentence my car broke down yesterday so
I need to look into a good mechanic my
car broke down yesterday so I need to
look into a good mechanic or I need to
look into finding a good mechanic what
do you think
what does look into look into mean are
we actually looking into physically
looking into something hmm not exactly
we've got some good suggestions from our
friends live who are here live Muhammad
says find one says to look for search
for something searching for something
searching lots of people say searching
or finding you got it it is searching
and also maybe researching a bit you
need to find some more information about
a good mechanic because your car is
pretty valuable so you want to find
someone who will treat your car kindly
and nicely you wanna search and research
for a good mechanic
so today we're going to practice look
into something together we're going to
look into this phrasal verb and I hope
that you'll be able to use it
comfortably and confidently by the end
of our lesson today let's take a look at
my wonderful clipboard I want to write
the beginning of a sentence and I want
to see if you can finish this sentence
using look into look into let's let's
talk about some if sentences potential
sentences if
you want to learn English this is some
advice you could give your friend if you
want to learn English you need to what
could we say you need to look into hmm
let's practice organ that this is
practicing the sentence structure
because I want to give you some hints
about how you could finish this kind of
sentence maybe your friend says to you
ah Claudia I want to learn English so
Claudio can you give me some advice
about how I can learn English you could
use this sentence well if you want to
learn English you need to and of course
we'll use today's phrasal verb look into
but how can we finish this how can we
finish the rest of this sentence you
need to look into we've got two options
you need to look into we've got practice
more all right we have some suggestions
practice more looking in the dictionary
focusing check out Vanessa's lessons oh
you're so nice
I'll look into a good teacher a good
teacher all Vanessa's lessons again
you're so nice all right so let's use
your suggestions to finish this sentence
in two ways the first way is simply
using a noun so some of you said you
need to look into maybe I'll use a
different color because it's fun if you
want to learn English you need to look
into a good teacher great this is just a
noun directly after this you need to
look into a good dictionary you need to
look into a good teacher you need to
look into a method that will work for
you
a good program look into YouTube lessons
this is a noun directly after here we've
got a lot of great examples here you
need to look into a good book beautiful
well we have another example here some
people used a verb a verb instead of a
noun so let's try to do this instead if
you want to learn English you need to
look into finding a good teacher so here
instead of this noun this noun directly
afterwards we have an ING verb and if we
want to talk about grammar technically
this verb is changing into a noun but
don't stress about that too much let's
make sure that our verb has I n G ing
this is really important so if you want
to learn English you need to look into a
good teacher you need to look into
finding a good teacher both options are
beautiful grammar great sentence
structure so you've got two options and
if you want to make your own sentences
with this maybe there are other options
that you want to try I'll gladly give
you some feedback so we have some
beautiful examples here Esther hello
Esther she says if you want to learn
English you need to look into listening
to some of the neces listening great
beautiful use of ing here look into
listening eggs says you need to look
into finding an English app on your
phone beautiful advice a lot of good
material out there Ariela says you need
to look into reading books thank you for
using ING I think sometimes in this is a
complex sentence in complex
sentences the second verb can be kind of
complicated what should I use ing know
ing edy what should I use so this is
going to be a clear sentence structure
to help you really use this as much as
possible we have a question from Erie
who says can I say in you cutting out
the T so here look in to look into
should we say look in new and recently I
made a video about words like
interesting or winter that use NT but in
this situation you have found a good
exception because this word is short
it's most common to say the T so let's
make sure that we can say look into a
good teacher look into finding a good
book look into finding something so
let's make sure our pronunciation is
clear with this let's practice a couple
other examples and I want to ask you to
use this on your own try to make an if
sentence using look into researching
searching for something with passion and
motivation let me give you another
example and then if you have any of your
own feel free to share you can finish
the sentence if you want to be healthy
you should we could say should or need
here look into hmmm what should we look
into if you want to be healthy you
should look into maybe some you should
look into some healthy recipe books you
should look into a diet plan you should
look into
we can also say look into your heart you
should look into yourself and this is
reflecting on yourself why do I want to
be healthy what are some problems in my
life is it mental health is it physical
health you should look into your heart
so this is a little more maybe
metaphysical but you can also say I
looked into my heart and I realized that
I didn't really have a good motivation
for finding another job so I'm gonna
stay with this job I looked into my
heart this is another way to use this
expression we have some great finish up
final parts to this sentence bye hi dear
says you should look into checking your
weight great way to use ing beautiful
Marco says if you want to be healthy you
should look into eating or exercising
great eating healthy food now bill says
you should look into eating healthy food
good idea Eliza has another sentence if
you want to be a good singer you should
look into a good singing instructor
beautiful and we have one from from
nicely' hello who says if you want to be
healthy you should look into eating more
fruits and vegetables beautiful here
we're using the verb look into heating
you got it if you want to be healthy you
should look into your brain and your
heart
yeah shinta I agree I think some people
say I want to lose weight I want to be
healthy I want to be healthy but we need
to reflect we need to look into our own
hearts and decide why what's stopping me
from being healthy right now Giovanna
says if you want to pass the test you
should look into studying more oh great
you should look
to effective study methods beautiful
this is going to help you in a lot of
situations to use complex grammar
beautiful sentence structure and phrasal
verbs at the same time this lesson is
everything all together let's read a
couple more sentences so that we can
conclude this and then we'll read it out
loud together jean-jacques says if you
want to be happy you should look into
eating more sweet food yes anyone who
gives me advice and says you should eat
more sweet food I will agree with we
have another sentence that says Oh
Augusto you're so nice he says if you
want to learn English you should look
into speak English with Vanessa
so here Augusto is using the first
version where he uses a noun
directly after the expression if you
want to learn English you need to look
into speak English with Vanessa we could
say you need to look into learning with
speak English with Vanessa that's fine
both of these we use exactly the same in
the same situations they're both used
equally so don't worry about which one
is more natural which one's used more
often both of these are great so you've
got two options and I hope that today's
lesson could help you to really focus on
this Senate structure instead of
memorizing look into something else how
can I use this what's a Senate structure
we're using it together so if you would
like now to repeat out loud with me
I hope that this will help you to
remember it use some speaking muscles
and feel confident with this phrasal
verb so are you ready to repeat out loud
with me and use it together we're gonna
have friends all over the world in
Brazil in Canada in Vietnam in Morocco
we're gonna have friends all over the
world repeating together so feel
confident
feel that you are part of this bigger
movement of people around the world who
are interested who are looking into
learning English naturally yes so let's
say the sentence together let's say if I
want to improve my speaking if I want to
improve my speaking because I imagine
that you do if I want to improve my
speaking I need to look into having
confidence important if I want to
improve my speaking I need to look into
let's add a little word I need to look
into how to have confidence if I want to
improve my speaking I need to look into
how to have confidence it's a pretty
long sentence actually maybe longer than
our usual repeated sentences at the end
so I'm gonna write it down hopefully it
will help if I say you or I all right
here you if you want to let's say I if I
want to improve my speaking I need to
look into how to have confidence Oh our
lovely friend confidence okay so I
changed it at the beginning if I want to
speak improve my speaking I need to look
into I need to look into how to have
confidence
I want to improve my speaking I need to
look into how to have confidence and you
know what you're doing it right now when
you're repeating with me you're using
this great sentence structure something
that we've practiced for the last 15-20
minutes or so so I hope that for you you
can have confidence especially
confidence using this new phrasal verb
using this Senate structure go back
review this lesson write some notes for
yourself and use it use it as much as
possible when you write a comment use it
when you speak with a friend use it try
to improve by using English as much as
you can thank you everyone for repeating
with me I agree that this will help you
have confidence so have a beautiful day
have a beautiful weekend enjoy your
Thursday and I'll see you again on
Tuesday 9 a.m. est have a wonderful day
see you again the next time everyone bye