hello hello welcome to today's live
English lesson here on the speak English
with Vanessa
YouTube channel I'm so glad that you're
here today to learn English to enjoy
English and also to participate because
this is a live lesson if you are here
with me live feel free to write comments
in the chat box I'll try to give you
some feedback I'm gonna be reading a lot
of your sentences during this lesson and
if you're not watching live if you're
watching the replay no problem you can
also enjoy this lesson you can write a
comment in the comment box below and
I'll try my best as well to take a look
at your comments and give you some
feedback as well today we're gonna be
talking about an interesting phrasal
verb warm up warm up we're going to be
talking about the basic way to use this
and then we're going to be talking about
the advanced way to use this so get
ready
prepare your mind we're gonna be using
this phrasal verb and I hope that by the
end of today's lesson you'll be able to
use this and understand it when other
people use it as well so if you're here
with me live I want to say thank you
thanks for joining me Gabrielle and El
Salvador thank you for coming thanks for
coming from Russia
Donna Peck in Thailand hello Federica in
italy hello glad that you're here
gizelle in Brazil I'm at an Egypt Wow
international group you guys are awesome
if you are new here let me quickly
introduce myself hi I'm Vanessa and I
teach English here on the internet on
YouTube on Tuesday and Thursday at 9
a.m. est that's the New York Times own
so if you would like to come to the next
live lesson it will be Tuesday or
Thursday at
9 a.m. in the morning if you would like
a notification or a notice about any
time changes for the live lessons the
best way to do that is to just get my
emails I send a notification through
email if there's a time change last week
there were a couple times because I was
traveling so if you would like to get
those emails and also free email lessons
the one step you have to do is just to
read my free ebook five steps to
becoming a confident English speaker I
hope that this free ebook will help you
and also the free email lessons all of
this together is hopefully a win-win
situation you can enjoy both of these
and you can join the live lessons or you
can subscribe to the channel and come at
the same time each week so today we're
going to be talking about the phrasal
verb warm-up I have a question for you
first of all what do you think this
means and I'm gonna ask you a more a
deeper question about it let's finish
this sentence I'm gonna write a sentence
and I want to see if you can finish it
are you ready here is here's my sentence
for the day I'll write it on this
notebook it is in because it's spring
right now in the u.s. in the spring the
weather hmm how can we finish this
sentence how can we finish this sentence
in the spring the weather hmm
what's the most natural clear way in the
winter the weather's cold snowy
depending on where you're from of course
but in the spring now now it's actually
raining but this is still true because
in the spring oh Cardos
it yes in the spring the weather warms
up flew lovely lovely yes in the spring
the weather warms up and for me I feel
like almost like a new person when
spring comes because in the winter
you've been cold you your muscles feel
kind of tight and then in the spring ah
you can relax and take it easy so here
we have the first use of our phrasal
verb beautiful use of it a lot of you
are writing the correct answer great
work
yes in the spring the weather warms up
hmm so let's use this phrasal verb warms
up in a couple different ways how can
you use warm up when when the weather
warms up what do you do what do you do
so you could say when the weather warms
up I like to go for a walk when the
weather warms up I like to uh open the
windows
when the weather warms up I like to wear
short sleeves instead of a big coat what
do you like to do when the weather warms
up so I challenge you to make a full
sentence using this expression if you
write just the answer it's useful but
you need to repeat the phrasal verb as
much as possible
great yes a lot of you are seeing this
unisys when the weather warms up I like
to take a cold shower Oh
interesting interesting
what is it says in the winter the
weather doesn't warm up very true um it
says when the weather warms up I feel
more comfortable
great ah Gabriela says when the weather
warms up I like to eat ice cream great
idea when the weather warms up I'll take
a walk in the forest
great idea calming relaxing great for
warm weather a lot of you are talking
about going outside I'd like to spend
more time in the garden go to the
swimming pool when the weather warms up
I'd like to do some outdoor activities
me too
I think I feel more motivated to go
outside because it's warm now it's
raining but in the US maybe other parts
of the world we have a proverb and the
proverb says april showers bring May
flowers right now it's April and the
shower is rain april showers bring May
flowers so in May there will be
beautiful flowers because it's raining
now
so it's a good way to feel more
comfortable with the rain so this is our
first use of warm up talking about the
weather are you ready to take this to
the next level we're going to use this
in an advanced way so let's imagine this
concept the weather is warming up you're
feeling more comfortable feeling more at
ease
a lot of you wrote this that when the
weather warms up I feel more comfortable
so what is something that's a little
more figurative that we can feel
comfortable with let me write another
sentence here and I want to see if you
can guess what this means let's say my
[Music]
oldest cat is starting to warm up to my
youngest
cats alright so we have a sit-ins here
about my cats I have three cats I have
an old cat he's almost 17 years old and
I have two younger cats who are about 2
or 3 years old here we have our phrasal
verb and we're going to add just a
little bit here
my oldest cat is starting to warm up to
my youngest cat what do you think that
this means we're using the same phrasal
verb imagine this same idea the weather
warms up I want to go outside when the
weather warms up ah I can open the
windows so what about what about with
cats or we can use this also with people
with ideas in a lot of different ways
hmm what do you think that this means we
have some great ideas to play together
to get used to each other oh I like that
one
yes so here be friendly whoo that's a
good way to do it my oldest cat is
starting to warm up to my youngest cat
yes this means he's starting to get
comfortable or get friendly so we can
imagine it's a similar idea when the
weather warms up you get more
comfortable you feel more comfortable so
we can use this in this more figurative
sense that my cat is warming up to my
other cat we can use this for people as
well let's say that you go on a date and
maybe let's say that you go on a date
with a guy and the guys okay but it's
not love at first sight you could say
maybe I will warm up to him later
meaning at the moment you don't feel so
comfortable but maybe later you will get
used to spending time with him maybe
later when you learn more about him it
will become better so you will warm up
to someone so I want to see if you can
use this in this figurative sense
getting more comfortable with it I see
here wonderful sentences someone says at
least as my wife is starting to warm up
to my family we have a lot of verbs here
so let's make sure that we're using all
of these verbs I'll use how about I'll
use another color make sure we use all
these verbs in the correct way so we
have is starting with ing to to warm up
to who so this is a fixed part of our
sentence let's make sure it stays
together when Ali says my wife is
starting to warm up to my family at the
beginning she wasn't so comfortable with
my family but now she's starting to feel
more comfortable starting to feel like
they're part of her family as well I'll
we have a grace in his day by day I'm
warming up to Vanessa so you're starting
to feel more and more comfortable
excellent I hope so Oh
Akihiro has a great sentence I'm
starting to warm up to the new work
environment great so we can substitute
I'm starting to get used to my new work
environment both of those mean the same
thing but if you want to use today's
phrasal verb expand your vocabulary we
can use warm-up I'm starting to warm up
to my new work environment I'm starting
to warm up to my new job I'm starting to
warm up to my new friend
oh great sentence I'm starting to warm
up to my new neighbors so maybe at the
beginning you didn't really know about
that
you didn't really care about them but
now you're starting to warm up to your
neighbors excellent
Gabriela says I'm starting to warm up to
college life this is a great way to use
it we're talking about a figurative
sense here we're not talking about the
weather
physically getting warmer you're talking
about your mind becoming more
comfortable so at the beginning college
life was not so comfortable for you but
you're starting to warm up to college
life beautiful I love it I love it let's
see if there are any final sentences
here we can talk about oh we have a
great one
I hope someone can warm up my cold heart
so in this situation it means that you
feel worried about making friends or
finding someone to love and you hope
that someone will break that barrier and
warm up your heart it's not physically
cold but figuratively figuratively one
says I'm starting to warm up to my
coworkers great great so I think we use
this a little bit previously in this way
but we can also use this to talk about
an idea so let's say for example your
your wife says hey for summer vacation I
really want to go to the mountains and
you were thinking oh I'd really like to
go to the beach and you have a different
opinion so she tries to convince you to
go to the mountains she tells you about
beautiful sunsets and fresh air in the
trees and seeing some wild animals and
you say oh I'm starting to warm up to
that idea to that idea we often say that
idea following this expression I'm going
to write this final sentence I'm
starting
I am starting to warm up to that idea
I'm starting to warm up to that idea so
here we have our phrasal verb + - I'm
starting to warm up to that idea hmm
it's a good idea it's maybe not my
favorite so far but I'm feeling more and
more comfortable with it I'm starting to
warm up to it now we have a great
question Padma asks what's the meaning
of warm up before starting an exercise
so today we've talked about the weather
warming up kind of mentally or
figuratively warming up to someone or to
an idea and with exercise here we're
talking about your muscles becoming
comfortable I need to warm up before I
start running hurt myself so we're
talking about getting your muscles ready
to exercise this is connected to the
other minions but I think today our main
meanings for warm up are more closely
related so you could say I need to warm
up before I exercise I need to warm up
before I play basketball otherwise I
might hurt my shoulder I need to warm up
or we could say I'm warming up to the
idea that I need to warm up before I
play basketball you're getting
comfortable more and more comfortable
with this idea so are you ready to say a
full sentence all together using warm-up
I've seen a lot of amazing sentences so
far in today's live lesson so I know you
guys can listen carefully to the
sentence this is a little dictation
practice can you write the sentence
exactly the way I say it I'm not gonna
write it down I want to see if you can
write it in the chat box we're going to
repeat it all together if you're in
danisha Brazil Egypt Thailand Russia
doesn't matter we're gonna say it all
together all around the world are you
ready we're going to use the sentence
with warm up warm up mmm okay I'm
warming up to the idea of speaking
English I'm warming up to the idea of
speaking English I'm warming up to the
idea of speaking English so can you
write this sentence in the chat box and
say it out loud we're going to say it
slowly so that you can pronounce each
sound I want you to imitate my mouth
exercise those speaking muscles and
we're going to say it together slowly
first I'm warming up to the idea of
speaking English make sure that your
lips are together when mine are together
they're out when mine are out there up
when mine are up let's imitate this
together I'm warming up to the idea of
speaking English loudly and warming up
to the idea of speaking English yes it's
becoming more comfortable to you and I
hope that you can say this sentence out
loud and use it and hopefully with
repetition you'll be able to use this
phrasal verb correctly and also the idea
of feeling comfortable about speaking
English you're warming up to the idea of
speaking English everyone for writing
the sentence for saying it out loud I
hope that you got some beautiful
practice today with English and if you
are thinking Vanessa
it can't be the end of our lesson
already what well I have good news I
will be back on Tuesday on Tuesday at 9
a.m. est that's the New York Times own
will have another live lesson
you have any suggestions for things that
you would like to talk about expressions
or ideas feel free to write them in the
comments I always take a look at
suggestions because I want to do
something that's useful for you
something that would really be helpful
for the people you who are participating
so feel free to give any suggestions in
the comments and I'll see you again on
Tuesday at 9 a.m. Eastern Time
over the weekend Thursday Friday
Saturday Sunday Monday for the next 5
days how can you study English what can
you do to warm up to the idea of
speaking English well you can follow
five steps for becoming a confident
English speaker these five steps I've
this means I've put them together in an
e-book that you can download you can
print it out put it on the wall put it
in your kitchen put it under your pillow
and dream about English this free ebook
is my gift to you to help you know
what's the next step I've included a lot
of links a lot of resources my personal
story about learning language
successfully and also not so
successfully different situations and I
think for you you'll be able to follow
those same ideas and know what's the
next best step for you so the best way
to get this to read this ebook to get
the free information and also my emails
is to download it with the link below
this video or on the screen at the end
it's my pleasure to help you with
English keep up the good work I hope
you're warming up to the idea of
speaking English and I'll see you again
on Tuesday bye everyone
see you later