hello welcome to today's live English
lesson here on the speak English with
Vanessa YouTube channel if you're new
here welcome we have live English
lessons every Tuesday and Thursday at 9
a.m. est that's the New York Times own
in the next two weeks there's going to
be a couple time changes because I'm
going to be traveling to New York so if
you would like to get updates about the
time changes so that you can join me
exactly at the right time feel free to
join my email group if you are already
receiving my emails you'll get a
notification about the time change but
if you don't yet receive those emails
and you want to make sure that you can
join the live lesson on time don't worry
the best way to do it is to read and
download my free ebook five steps to
becoming a confident English speaker
when you get that free ebook you will
also receive free email lessons and the
best English tips and materials that I
want to share with you we have another
little friend today
my cat Pippin is curious about what
we're gonna talk about today and we're
going to be talking about two important
phrasal verbs that often get confused
and even when I was thinking about them
I was trying to think about what the
exact difference is between figure out
and find out so today I want to give you
a fixed sentence structure that you can
use with each phrasal verb and we're
going to practice it here together so I
hope if you're here live with me you're
ready to write some sentences give some
feedback and really use this as best as
you can we have friends from all over
the world who are here hello hello from
South Korea right now glad you're here
Federica Marcio Maxime hello welcome
from all over the world are you ready to
find out how to use this word well let's
start with one of these phrasal verbs
and then if you have any questions about
how to compare them feel free to do that
oh we're gonna talk first of all about
figure out figure out I want to ask you
before we get started how would you use
this can you make a sentence with figure
out before I even give any tips any
hints about it I think it's good to try
first and see where you're starting
maybe you already are using it correctly
great I want to make sure that you're on
the right path and we'll do the same
thing with the other phrasal verb so let
me know what is a good sentence that you
can make with figure out figure out and
then it'll give you as many tips and
hints as possible to help you use it
correctly
we have our first sentence with figure
out Maxime says I can't figure out how
it is to live in Japan oh maybe a
complicated life union says I will
figure out how good this class will be
alright I will figure out your voice
I'll figure out how to use a new coffee
machine we have a lot of similar Senate
structures here it's difficult to figure
out how to use phrasal verbs ooh let's
take all of these sentences and find
three words that are similar we've got
our phrasal verb plus one extra word did
you notice what that extra word is I
will figure out how to get my computer
to work I will figure out how to use
this phrasal verb I'll figure out how
how
is often used with figure out because
figure out implies there's some kind of
process now just to let you know we
don't need to use how with figure out
it's not necessary it's not required
100% of the time but if this phrasal
verb plus fig find out are complicated
to you I recommend using this Senate
structure how figure out how so let's
write a sentence I'm going to write one
here on my trusty clipboard and we've
got some great sentences in the comments
maybe I'll use one of yours as well a de
a de says I I will I love I love the use
of will here because will shows that
you're serious I'm not thinking about
doing it I will do it I will figure out
how to learn more English every day Oh
beautiful sentence this is actually a
really great statement too because it's
positive it's showing I'm gonna do it
I'm not questioning can I do it is it
possible you're saying I will I love
that really powerful statement so let's
say I will figure out plus how I'll
figure out how to learn more English
every day I'll figure out how to help my
little cousin read better I'll figure
out how to do something of course if you
have other sentences with figure out
that do not include how feel free to
write them in the comments and I'll try
my best to give you some feedback
because this word how
all howl is gonna talk about let's use a
light blue color figure out is some kind
of some kind of process some kind of
process so because we're using figure
out we need to imply that it's not an
item we're going to talk about an item a
thing with find out
but with figure out we can imagine in
your head there's a motor maybe an
engine and some gears are turning and
this is a process you're trying to
figure out how to solve a problem you're
not trying to find out the solution
you're trying to figure out how to solve
the problem so let's write one more
sentence using figure out and then I'm
gonna read some of your lovely sentences
I'm gonna figure out how to solve the
problem so here we have our favorite
three words all together figure out how
figure out how and this is talking about
the process figure out how to solve the
problem maybe your if your problem is
that in the morning you have to get to
the airport really early but your car
isn't working you have to figure out how
to solve to solve solving is talking
about this thought process how to solve
this problem maybe you would think oh I
should try to call it taxi or maybe I'll
call my friend
maybe I'll just walk
maybe I'll try to find a bus I need to
figure out how to solve this problem
let's take a look at some of the
sentences from those of you who are here
live
you've got great sentences I love this
interaction and feedback that's the
wonderful thing about live lessons I'll
try my best to give you some feedback so
Ana Paula says I'll figure out how to
improve my English vocabulary with
Vanessa's life lessons oh I hope so I
hope you can use these phrasal verbs add
to your vocabulary
let's see Oh Gail says my son doesn't
sleep at all but I will figure out how
to make him sleep the whole night I
think this is a parent's constant
struggle I will figure out how to make
him sleep the whole night
this is gonna be a process there's not
one clear solution if there were a clear
solution you would have already found it
so you're gonna try to work through the
problem and figure out the problem
beautiful sentence Oh Ahmed says he has
a little dialogue here he says do you
know how this machine works no but I
will figure it out beautiful you're
talking about the process I'm gonna
learn the different techniques to get it
to work I'm gonna figure out and we
often use this together so I'm glad that
you brought this up figure it out I will
figure it out I can't figure it out
yesterday I was helping to babysit one
of my friends daughters and she's three
years old and we were eating some
pistachios together pistachios are a
kind of nut and you have a shell and you
have to break open the shell and eat the
nut from the inside and her fingers are
small her patience is kind of limited so
she tried one of them and she said
I can't figure it out I can't do it and
I said let's look for a pistachio shell
that's open really wide and this would
make it easier for her little fingers to
open it up and she found a pistachio
with an open shell there's a lot with
open shells and she opened it up and she
said I figured it out I did it this
means she learned that process and now
hopefully when she eats pistachios with
her parents she won't ask them all the
time open this open this open his
hopefully she can continue to figure it
out herself
by using that kind of mental process
it's a process so let's go to the second
phrasal verb and we'll compare these two
together the second one is find out find
out hmm what do you think is the
difference between figure out and find
out how can we use find out so far we
had three words figure out how but what
could we use with find out there's one
word similar word we don't have to use
it but we can use it if we want to be
extra clear about using the phrasal verb
correctly let me give you a sample
sentence and see if you can guess which
word it is I need to find out what the
weather's gonna be like tomorrow because
I'm packing to go on a trip so I have to
pack the right clothes I need to oh I
need to find out what my sister wants
for her birthday so I'm gonna ask her
and that's the clearest way I need to
ask her I need to find out what she
wants for her birthday hmm Louise you
got it hey Louise says what what and
there are a couple different words you
can use after find out
no problem but the word what is not
implying a process like how how implies
a process so let's write a sentence
using what I'm going to figure out how
to solve the problem let's write a
similar sentence but using find out I'm
going to find out what the solution is
Oh lovely said it's I need to find out I
need to find out what the solution is so
here we have a specific a specific thing
maybe the solution is a physical thing
maybe it's a mental thing but we have
one item here the solution I need to
find out what the solution is I need to
find out what my sister wants for her
birthday
there's an item maybe she wants tickets
to go to a concert great that's a
physical thing I need to find out you're
looking for some information so that's
going to be our key here is something
that you are possibly seeing maybe an
item or it could be something something
more physical something more physical so
of course let's talk about the
difference between them in just a moment
but first of all let's practice some
sentences with this because there are
some situations when you can use both of
them so before we get to that part let's
talk about some
clear sentences with find out find out
Oh
ayah says I want to find out why I
forgot my lesson oh great
maybe you didn't set your alarm or there
was a time change in the US so if you
thought that this live lesson was at a
different time
well maybe your country hasn't had a
time change yet or maybe your country
doesn't have a time change so you need
to find out why did I miss it
what happened what was the problem let's
see what else we have some other great
sample sentences whew I want to find out
when I can go to the US ah huh so here
this is a beautiful sentence I need to
find out when I can go to the u.s.
Misaki great sentence the reason why we
can use find out here is because you're
gonna be looking on your calendar for a
specific date you're looking for a
specific piece of information hmm I need
to find out when so as I said this word
could change you can use this it'll be
clear but you can also change it
Takahiro says before I eat this I need
to find out what this food is good idea
usually we like to find out what we're
eating before we eat it in fact today
this afternoon in a couple minutes I'm
gonna be driving with my husband to
visit a friend who lives three hours
away and she lives in an area that is
full of Korean restaurants so as you can
imagine I'm pretty excited I plan to eat
a lot of Korean food over the next two
days
so I wanted yesterday I wanted to find
out what is the best Korean restaurant
in that area or what restaurant I wanted
to go to so Dan and I looked on the
computer we tried to figure out
how we could get to the restaurant on
time because the restaurant that we want
to go to has a lunch special until 2:30
so after this live lesson we need to go
there and get there before the lunch
special finishes I really want to eat
some amazing gamjatang
so last night we needed to find out what
were the best restaurants in that area
we were looking for a specific piece of
information in item some physical
information let's read some other sample
sentences here let's see um how about oh
let Lindsey says I'm gonna I'm gonna
find out which kind of food he likes
beautiful you're looking for an item
some information specific piece of
information I'm gonna find out what kind
of food he likes I'm gonna find out
where my pen got lost
aha so you could use either phrasal verb
but it has a little different meaning
you could say I'm going to find out
where my pen got lost you're looking for
a specific piece of information but if
we want to use figure out I'm gonna
figure out why my pen got lost you're
gonna try to learn what was the process
that happened did I leave it on the
counter and then I was thinking about
something else and I forgot about it
you're gonna figure out that process so
if you want to use either phrasal verb
there's a slightly different nuance and
in a lot of these situations we can use
either phrasal verb but it means
something slightly different that
process compared to information cook Co
mathy says I'm going to find out what is
best way to improve English great you're
looking for that information I'm gonna
find out what is the best way to improve
my English hopefully it will be a way
that's enjoyable to you and useful and
you fish it efficiency is important
don't waste your time ah Lee has a
question Lee says I'm originally from
Korea what kind of food are you gonna
eat oh I want to eat all Korean food
right now there's 30 or 40 Korean
restaurants near Atlanta in the US and
my friend lives near Atlanta so we're
gonna try to figure out which restaurant
everyone can agree on and thankfully my
friend doesn't know that much about
Korean food or Korean restaurants so
that means we get to pick so we're going
to be able to have a lot of the foods
that remind us of those great memories
can't wait um Lucas has a good question
ah
he says Vanessa can I say that Columbus
found out America he wasn't expecting it
he found out ah huh so if we use one of
these phrasal verbs we need to add
something something afterwards so if
we're gonna add something afterwards
let's change this and it's a little bit
Columbus the European who supposedly was
one of the first people to come to the
u.s. from Europe Columbus found out
Columbus found out this is the
past-tense found out where America is so
we're adding another word he found out
he got an answer he found out where
America is Columbus was trying to figure
out where America is and
he found out he found out so he was
trying the process to figure it out and
he successfully found out beautiful way
to use both of these so I hope that for
you if you're uncertain about which
phrasal verb you should use I recommend
remembering this figure out how to do
something and find out what to do
finding out what to do and figuring out
how to do it if you have any questions
about these two phrasal verbs feel free
to write them in the comments I'll try
my best to give you some feedback
usually in these live lessons we only
talked about one phrasal verb so today
we're kind of pushing two together and
it seems like we could take a lot of
time three hours and talk about it give
sample sentences and really go over
these phrasal verbs
so I recommend reviewing what we talked
about today and if you have any
questions write them in the comments
that's why I'm here I'll try my best to
give you some positive useful feedback
and help you use it correctly that's the
goal I want to help you figure out how
to use these phrasal verbs correctly and
when you find out how to use them you're
going to be super excited so let's say
one sentence together a wonderful
sentence about English using both of
these phrasal verbs let's see mmm let's
talk about a process I'm gonna actually
I think I'm going to write this down
because it might be a little long we're
gonna try to say the sentence all
together you got it let's say
I was trying to figure out how to
improve my English hmm and I found out
so we're using this in the past tense I
found out that a good solution oh if I
can write correctly early in the morning
solution is with Vanessa I hope so I
hope it's useful for you all right so
let's let's practice both of these
phrasal verbs in this sentence and it's
kind of long so I'm going to write it
out here that and you can you can take a
look at it and read it okay you can
change this as much as you want to say a
sentence that's true for you let's say
this all together
let's practice reading this out loud if
you can if you're in a quiet or private
place I was trying to figure out how to
improve my English and I found out that
a good solution is with Vanessa I hope
that this is true I hope that these
lessons are useful for you I found out a
solution specific piece of information I
was trying to figure out how to improve
my English and I found out that a good
solution is with Vanessa I hope you can
say this out loud repeat it clearly and
use both of these in the same sentence
Amal is repeating this great Lee thank
you for repeating
this excellent I was trying to figure
out how to improve my English and I
found out that a good solution is with
Vanessa so it's not the only solution
there are plenty of ways you can improve
your English but one solution I hope
that's useful for you is these live
lessons so if you are thinking ova Nessa
I would love to learn a lot more because
this is just the beginning just two
phrasal verbs if you would like to
continue to learn English with me I have
some good news first of all there are
plenty of other videos on my youtube
channel that will help you with phrasal
verbs like today expressions learning
tips and this is really going to help
you fill in the places where you have
some questions and if you would like to
join like I mentioned before my email
group where all send you free email
lessons you can download my free ebook
five steps to becoming a confident
English speaker this is going to help
you learn five steps and each one will
have some resources each one will give
you an idea about what you can do to
feel more comfortable feel more natural
and be on the right path for learning
English because there are I'm sure you
know a lot of options for improving your
English so I want to help you figure out
how to improve your English and I want
to help you find out what is the best
method so feel free to enjoy the other
videos on this channel and also read and
download print it out put it on the wall
put it under your pillow download my
free ebook and the link is in the
description below this video or on the
screen at the end of this lesson thanks
so much everyone thanks for learning
with me I hope that this lesson helped
you to start to figure out how to use
these phrasal verbs if you have any
questions or sample sentences write them
in the comments and I'll see you the
next time bye everyone
how
a wonderful day see you later