hello hello hello welcome to today's
live English lesson here on the speak
English
with Vanessa YouTube channel I'm so glad
that you're joining me to improve your
English learn some important vocabulary
words today an important phrasal verb
and to enjoy this community it's great
to write comments participate join live
if you want to join me live there are
live lessons every Tuesday and Thursday
at 9 a.m. est this is the New York Times
own but I have a quick announcement
because I'm gonna be traveling this week
on Thursday I'm gonna be going to New
York to visit my sister so on Tuesday
and Thursday we have to change the live
lesson schedule but don't worry I will
make sure that you get an notification
through email so if you would like to
get a notification about the new lesson
time all you have to do is receive my
emails because I want to make sure you
can stay up to date so to download and
to get my free email lessons and updates
I recommend getting my free ebook 5
steps to becoming a competent English
speaker the link is in the description
below and when you join and get these
email lessons anytime there is a live
lesson time change I will let you know
in advance so that you can participate
and enjoy it because we have a live
lesson today and we have a live lesson
tomorrow instead of Thursday so I hope
that you can join me and today we've got
a really fun phrasal verb to talk about
thank you everyone who is here live one
Clinton hello X I'm glad you're here
nevermind and Egypt Jason from
Afghanistan Alex in Brazil Gabriela
hello evaldo in Brazil
glad you are joining me today Norman in
Quebec beautiful Wow we've got
international friends here today um
Maxime asks how are you doing it great
I'm feeling good trying to stay healthy
and energetic and drinking lots of water
so I hope that you are having a
wonderful morning afternoon evening
whatever time it is for you are you
ready to kick off today's lesson hmm
that's what we're going to talk about
today the phrasal verb kick off kick off
I want to see if any of you can make a
sentence with this without me explaining
anything it's your little test try to
make a sentence using kick off without
any explanations and then of course I'll
give you some explanation some sample
sentences and I'll ask you some
questions so that you can use this
phrasal verb in the most clear and
natural way possible because there's a
lot of things starting recently so we
can use this in our daily lives oh we've
got lots of great friends joining us
thank you Dominican Republic Ukraine
Thailand hello hello Paulo glad you're
here oh we have a couple sports
sentences so Maxime hello Maxime says
the players are about to kick off
alright and Alf but X says Lilian will
be the one to kick off at the meeting I
kicked off the meeting on time what time
will this livelesson kick off ooh
so can you guess from these sentences
what does the phrasal verb kick off kick
off me usually kick is with your leg and
you are kicking a soccer ball kicking
hopefully not someone
else you are kicking with your leg but
in this phrasal verb usually when we use
this in the most situations we're not
talking about kicking we've got some
great guesses yes now that you are
correct it is to begin something to
begin and typically its beginning
something with a little not a
celebration but there is a specific
event that starts something else so we
had some good sentences about meetings
kick off the meeting today Luis will
kick off the meeting
it means he's the one who will begin the
meeting he's the one who's going to give
the first presentation some introduction
Luis will kick off the meeting so I have
a question for you because let's use
this in a broad context here in the u.s.
it is the end of March almost the
beginning of April and it is springtime
it is becoming spring the weather's
beautiful it's warm there's a lot of
flowers blooming so I want to ask you a
question and maybe there isn't spring in
your country so feel free to change the
sentence if you need to you can change
it to summer to winter anything else
you'd like my question is what is a good
way to kick off spring how do you kick
off spring I'm going to write a sentence
here
that explains an important moment in
American culture
we can say
spring cleaning kicks off spring spring
cleaning kicks off spring so here we
have I'll use this one kicks off here we
have an event an event in the US it's
pretty typical there's not a specific
date or time but it's pretty typical in
the spring especially the beginning of
spring when it's getting warmer everyone
cleans kind of a deep cleaning of their
house they open the windows go through
all of the closets clean out your
clothes clean out the kitchen clean the
floors we we do some spring cleaning
so spring cleaning kicks off spring it
means spring has started all P vines is
the same thing I'm kicking off spring
with cleaning my apartment
great you can start this new season with
a clean place some fresh air that would
be great
almec seems is dealing with the garden
kicks off spring oh I see so for you
because you want to have some beautiful
flowers or maybe some good vegetables or
fruits you have to work in the garden
you have to till up the soil and make
sure that it's a good quality so working
in the garden kicks off spring to you
beautiful Oh
I mean why says a new semester kicks off
spring a new semester so for you when
you start school again you know it's
spring this is the new season this is
what I'm gonna be doing it kicks off
spring beautiful beautiful ahh
Takahiro says cherry blossoms kick off
spring cherry blossoms
what a beautiful thing so for you you
can see those wonderful trees for just a
couple weeks I think they only last a
couple weeks you can see the cherry
blossoms and it kind of feels like a
pages turning winter is closing spring
is beginning and a new season is coming
so let's talk about this in a little
different way so this the meaning is the
same but I want to help you split this
phrasal verb hmm we can split the
phrasal verb we can put something in the
middle hmm so let's talk about let's
talk about a way that we can oh now it
has a great sentence about the morning
what do you do to kick-off the morning
hmm he says I kick off every morning
with coffee so let's make this into a
split phrasal verb I kick morning off
with coffee well it's not exactly true
for me because I'm not a big fan of
coffee but I'm sure a lot of you are and
we can always change this to fit your
situation so here
the phrasal verb is split I kick morning
off or we could say I kick the morning
no problem morning is a flexible word I
kick morning off with coffee I kick
morning off with a big stretch
stretching high or I kick morning off by
pushing my snooze button and sleeping
later what about for you what do you do
in the morning to start your day it
helps you to kind of mentally know that
a new day is coming
we squad you're here Estella says I kick
morning off with Ma Tei great sorrow
says I kick morning off with milk hmm
just milk or do you add do you add milk
to your coffee just a glass of milk
maybe nice and fresh God says I kick
learning English off with Vanessa Oh
beautiful I love it Clayton that says I
kick morning off by opening my eyes oh
it's a good place to start quite
necessary in fact among Aman Nina I hope
I said your name correctly says I kick
my morning off with some biscuits
oh I kick my morning off by taking a
shower
I keep morning off by brushing my teeth
I kick morning off with a meeting oh
great way to start the morning so just a
little note I want to make sure that
we're using a verb
afterwards correctly so let's let's
change this sentence just a little bit
let's say I kick my morning off by
drinking coffee so do you notice this
set in structure here we need we have
our phrasal verb kickoff
but we also need here by drinking by I
kick my morning off by stretching I kick
my morning off by going to the gym good
for you I kick my morning off by turning
my alarm clock off great class set I
love it I kick my morning off by
stretching my body Louise grates it
feels good
usually
I kick my morning off with meditation
beautiful so we've got two different
prepositions I know how much we love
prepositions so this is a good way to
naturally learn full sentences that way
you can remember prepositions a little
easier so here we have I kick my morning
off with plus a noun so we have with
coffee and then here we have a verb by
drinking by stretching by cleaning by
feeding my cats because the moment that
I get out of bed they're waiting all
three of them are waiting beside my bed
looking at me and the moment I put my
foot down they run into the kitchen
because they're hungry of course they
have food but they want more food so I
kick my morning off by feeding my cats
Collette has a beautiful sentence I kick
my morning off with great with a smile
and listening to soft music these are
really great suggestions for how to
start our morning kick my morning off so
I want to know for you what about
learning English when you say I'm gonna
spend 30 minutes today studying English
how do you kick off that learning time
what do you do do you need to close the
door keep yourself in a kind of a quiet
area do you need to turn off your cell
phone I kick off my study time by
closing the door keeping a quiet area
what do you do
maybe you kick off your morning with
Vanessa's video great what is something
that you do when you are thinking about
starting to study English for the day
maybe you're enjoying live lessons so
you you need to kick off I'll write a
sentence here maybe a sample one let's
see I'll use this color again I kick off
my study time by how about um making
making a list making a list of what I
want to learn for the day maybe you want
to learn some vocabulary words so you
make a list I'm gonna listen to the
video I'm gonna make my own sentences
I'm gonna read them out loud these three
things this is what I'm gonna do so
maybe you kick off your study time by
making a list and of course we can add
this part here if we want I kick my
study time off by making a list both of
these are great what do you do at the
beginning of your study time on Yujin
says I kick off my study time by
disconnecting the internet
whoo not easy is it so you need to shut
out all other distractions and you
disconnect the internet hmm okay it has
a beautiful sentence I kick
english-learning off by cutting my fears
out ooh you're using two phrasal verbs
last lessons and today's beautiful
you're the winner I kick
english-learning
off by cutting my fears out putting your
fears outside getting rid of them and
deciding I can do this I am gonna learn
this and I'm gonna do well great mindset
Wanda says I kick off my study time by
watching your video
Oh excellent a good way to get your mind
started to learn English I think that's
pretty true for myself that when I wanna
for example go to a French meetup group
I need to get my mind thinking about
French in my mind switching from English
to French so for me I like to kick off
my French study time by listening to
music I think listening to French music
if I'm gonna be speaking French
it helps my mind to think about those
vocabulary words think about the
sentence structure just kind of be
immersed in that language so for you you
might say I kick off my study time by
listening to English music great
oh I'm an emic I trying to say this name
in the morning all right
ah Mon inna amanina uh Medina says I
kick off my study time by cleaning some
mess on my table whoo that's really nice
clearing some space trying to make sure
that you have a clean area to fill your
mind Oh Sarah says I kick off my study
time by watching movies Julio hi Julio
says I kick off my study time by
listening to mp3 mp3 lessons in my car
ooh so you're filling your mind with
English listening to English really
trying to immerse yourself beautiful
idea are you ready to say a full
sentence all together repeat it all
together this is also good dictation or
listening practice because I'm going to
say the sentence and I would like if you
can to write this sentence
in the chat box and that way we can
repeat it all together all around the
world wherever you are if you're in the
Philippines in Brazil in the Ukraine
doesn't matter we're going to say this
sentence all together because we're
going to pronounce it and also it's good
for your mind
to have some powerful statements to say
out loud so are you ready our sentence
using today's a phrasal verb that we're
going to say out loud
is I'm going to use actually one of the
sentences that were you was used before
are you ready I kick off my English
study time by forgetting fear how
beautiful I kick off my English study
time by forgetting fear a really
important concept so my challenge for
you can you write this sentence let's
repeat it together let's repeat it
slowly first so that you can use correct
pronunciation I kick off my English
study time by fir getting fear do you
notice how the word forgetting kind of
sounds like Ser forgetting just natural
pronunciation by forgetting fear I kick
off my English study time by forgetting
fear and realizing I can do it so I hope
for you you can repeat the sentence out
loud let's say this really loud all
together
are you ready before we go we're gonna
say this loud and clear
if you're somewhere private great if
you're somewhere public well they can
probably learn about it too let's say I
kick off my English study time by
forgetting fear oh I hope you said this
loud and clear and you can repeat this
to yourself I kick off my morning by
telling myself forget fear forget
fearless of speaking English I'm gonna
just do it so I hope for you you can
kick off your English study time by
forgetting fear and enjoying it if
you're not really enjoying it and having
a nice time
it's not going to continue because
learning language is a lifelong process
really you're always gonna be learning
something new and that's really cool
because your mind is always gonna be
working and staying young forever so I
hope for you you can forget fear and
enjoy today's phrasal verb so thank you
everyone for joining me if you would
like to join our other live lessons
quick announcement
there will be no live lesson on Thursday
instead we are moving it only this week
to Wednesday tomorrow so I hope that you
can join me again tomorrow 9 a.m. est
I'm gonna be traveling on Thursday so
there will not be internet in my car or
on the airplane so I will see you again
tomorrow for another live lesson where
you can learn about English and learn
about forgetting here
let's keep learning together if you want
to get any updates about live lesson
time changes or if you want to read my
free ebook 5 steps to becoming a
confident English speaker this is my
gift to you I hope it will be useful to
help you really know the next step to
becoming confident enjoying English and
having a good time and realizing for
yourself what is your goal what's the
next step for you if you're a beginner
if you're intermediate if you are
advanced if you are already a native
speaker it will help you know what's the
next step for you and I hope that it
will help you forget fear like we talked
about today you can download it in the
link below or up here I'll put a little
a little button at the end of the video
thanks to everyone for kicking off my
day it's morning for me thank you for
kicking off my day in a positive way and
learning about this phrasal verb
together thanks so much and I'll see you
again tomorrow same time same place to
learn about another important expression
see you later everyone bye