hello hello good morning or afternoon or
evening welcome to today's live lesson
here on the speak English with Vanessa
YouTube channel I am here in a new
location I am visiting my in-laws for
Christmas so you might notice a new
background it's just temporary but I
wanted to welcome you to their house and
welcome you to the end of 2016 I can't
believe it it's amazing it's come so
fast a lot of you have been learning
English with me throughout all of 2016 a
lot of you are new here so if you are a
regular student if you are new welcome
I'm glad you're here we have live
lessons here on YouTube every Tuesday at
9 a.m. est which is New York Standard
Time New York Standard Time so you can
just if you subscribe to the speak
English with Vanessa YouTube page you'll
get a notification whenever there is a
live lesson I hope that you will enjoy
it today we're gonna talk about a
phrasal verb that is really useful and
we're just gonna use it in our
conversation so I recommend for you
participate this is a live lesson even
if you're watching the replay
participate write a comment write some
notes speak out loud imitate the
sentences that I'm using this is a great
time to use English not just here
Vanessa's speak English this is your
time to learn English so I challenge you
to participate and enjoy it if you have
not yet downloaded my free
end-of-the-year gift it is a top three
tips guide it is about top three tips
that I have written about on YouTube so
on
you tube over the month of December I
made about seven videos top three tips
to learn vocabulary top three tips to
become fluent top three tips to improve
your pronunciation there are seven
categories I organized them added some
resources added some details and made a
PDF guide so that you can download them
and remember them print it out put it in
your office put it on your wall put it
under your pillow just remind yourself
of all of these tips so that in 2017 you
can continue to be successful thank you
everyone for joining me here alive
we've got people from all over the world
if you would like to download the free
end of the year top three tips guide
there is a link in the description of
this video so that you can download it
have it in less than five minutes
welcome from Argentina
Leandro I'm glad you're here Paulo my
Christmas was wonderful thank you for
asking
it was just relaxing and we ate lots of
good food I think Christmas in my family
is a really special family time
that's usually what we focus on is just
spending time together playing games
eating food listening to music it's been
really relaxing Thank You Oliver from
Brazil welcome Gracia from Italy glad
you're here now jet from India you are a
loyal English Learner I know
welcome welcome Marcela crystal
excellent thank you for joining me
Ecuador Oh Paolo from Ecuador welcome
welcome
so today we're gonna talk about next
year which is going to start in today's
the 27th 28th 29th thirty 31st less
one week in less than one week the new
year is starting so I have a quick
question for you do you feel like 2016
was slow or fast what do you think do
you think that it passed by we can use
this phrasal verb 2016 passed by slowly
for me 2016 passed by quickly for me and
that's true for me
2016 passed by pas sed passed by quickly
for me I think it seems like it was just
four months not 12 months 2016 passed by
so fast for me and that's great that
means there was a lot of fun activities
a lot of stuff happened and it was a
good year then our jailson says I think
this year passed by very fast mm-hmm I
agree I agree
so a welcome from Vietnam I'm glad
you're here Oh Edgar said it passed by
quickly you took us and quickly all
we've got one slowly Barack says it was
fast and furious Oh so really quickly Oh
quickly quickly quickly quickly Wow for
most people it passed by really fast I
agree it passed by really fast and
there's nothing wrong with that but
sometimes we want to slow down time or
appreciate it but when things pass by
fast it usually means that you're busy
you're doing a lot there's lots of
activities hopefully good activities so
for everyone who said it passed by fast
for me time flew for me that means you
had a full year you did a lot so let's
think about next year
2017 2017 already I feel like I remember
the year 2000 starting yesterday but it
was 17 years ago unbelievable
17 years ago Wow
so the question for today's lesson is
what are you looking forward to in 2017
and this is not a new year's resolution
may be it's connected to a new year's
resolution but it could be an activity
like my son is getting married in June
I'm looking forward to his wedding or I
am looking forward to winter being over
already because it's already too cold
except here even though I'm visiting my
in-laws in the north it's warm it's
maybe 1015 degrees it's amazing it
doesn't feel like winter yet but I'm
curious for you what are you looking
forward to maybe you're looking forward
to improving your English I'm looking
forward to training my pronunciation I'm
looking forward to something else oh now
it says I'm looking forward to starting
to starting my own business now I want
to talk really quick about the grammar
of this kind of sentence because usually
when we have to we keep the simple verb
to start to go to run we don't use to
starting to running to going it feels a
little strange but in this situation the
two is not connected with start the two
goes with looking forward to so looking
forward to is the phrase so because look
forward to is the phrase we can use ing
afterwards I'm looking forward to
starting my own business Mart Masari o
says in two thousand six seventeen I
hope to get a better job and be more
fluent in English I'm looking forward to
getting a better job and having new
experiences great how arson says I'm
looking forward to independence oh it
will be wonderful I hope for you son
Phil I'm glad you're here live
excellence JAMA says I'm looking forward
to improving improving my English
oh man cake says I'm looking forward to
becoming a strong english learner with
your channel oh that's wonderful I hope
so
I will try my best to help you have the
tools and some interesting materials
welcome Francisco from Guatemala I'm
glad you're here Oh Jay hark says I'm
looking forward to going abroad
especially to the States in 2017 oh
where are you gonna go in the US that's
great and your sentence structure is
beautiful I'm I am I am looking forward
to going to the u.s. I'm looking forward
to going abroad you says I'm looking
forward to getting a car oh that will be
excellent do you have any plans what
kind of car do you want or is it gonna
be a long search for you
feels like a big process there's so many
choices I'll stop Southwood says I'm
looking forward to a promotion hmm I
have hope it works out for you that
would be excellent daniel says i'm
looking forward to playing the guitar to
learning to play the guitar
wonderful Oh Richard says I'm looking
forward to the upcoming spring vacation
of the new year this is a great way to
use this this sentence looking forward
to in a little different way because you
said I'm looking forward to
the new year I'm looking forward to the
wedding I'm looking forward to the next
step in my job you didn't use a verb
directly after this phrasal verb I'm
looking forward to celebrating the new
year that would be a verb you used this
noun directly afterwards I'm looking
forward to the new year I'm looking
forward to my birthday I'm looking
forward to the summer great so we have
several different choices you don't need
to always use a verb directly after this
phrasal verb I'm glad we've got lots of
choices here
oh she says I'm looking forward to
getting a bigger present from Santa
Claus than the one I got a couple days
ago oh I hope you're not disappointed I
hope you get something great brno says
I'm looking forward to speaking out loud
great idea
speaking out loud I hope that all of you
are trying to speak out loud during this
live lesson too because when you speak
out loud you're training those muscles
and there's something that helps your
confidence as well because you hear your
own voice using English you don't just
hear a native speakers voice you hear
your own voice so I challenge you when I
read a sentence read it with me repeat
it after me
keep it up use those muscles
Takada says I'm looking forward to
improving my English in 2017 yes I'm
looking forward to improving my English
I'll Sergio has a great idea I'm looking
forward to spending time with my family
in 2017 I'm looking forward to spending
time with my family that's a great goal
and a wonderful thing to look forward to
maybe on vacation or maybe just in daily
life eating dinner together after you
come home from work spending some time
just
having that good relationship that's
really valuable how Antonio says I'm
looking forward to finding someone to
speak English with yes finding an
english-speaking partner or just a
friend who's interested in learning
English is important I'm looking forward
to speaking English finding English
Gabriel says I'm looking forward to
being the first man on the moon if you
are the first man on the moon Sergio
congratulations are on Mars on Mars I
think you said Mars if you're the first
men on Mars congratulations that is a
huge deal oh yeah I mean says I'm
looking forward to giving up smoking
beautiful sentence and you can do it a
lot of people have given up smoking in
their lives I'm sure it's not a simple
thing but a lot of people have done it
successfully you got it yeah Oh Louie
says I'm looking forward to traveling
make sure we add this ing I'm looking
forward to traveling on my bike
excellent
you're gonna go bike riding that sounds
really healthy and when you're riding a
bike it's in for me I feel like I can
see more than when I'm running or even
just walking because unless it's really
physically difficult you're going up a
hill you can observe what's going on
around you and you have a different
perspective you're going fast
riding a bike is fun something so simple
but it's really enjoyable although he
says I'm looking forward to having many
more lessons with Vanessa oh the best
English teacher ever wow what a
compliment well I hope that for you are
all of our English lessons in 2017 will
be useful for you so I'm glad you're
looking forward to it so I wanted to
give you a quick other
idea so we talked about adding an ING
verb I'm looking forward to getting
better at English I'm looking forward to
going abroad or using a noun
I'm looking forward to the summer I'm
looking forward to the wedding but if
someone says something that you agree
with
maybe maybe someone else here said I'm
looking forward to learning English in
2017 and you agree with it yeah I'm
2017 you can just add the word it I'm or
that I'm looking forward to that too
you're telling them that thing that you
said I'm looking forward to summer oh
I'm looking forward to that too you
don't need to repeat back I'm looking
forward to summer too you could but we
usually try to use it that those kinds
of words to make our sentences a little
more clear and not repetitive so this is
a great tool to use when someone says a
sentence like this I'm looking forward
to the new year I'm looking forward to
January 1st because I'm gonna have a big
dinner to celebrate the new years and
maybe your your family member says hey
I'm looking forward to that too great
I'm looking forward to that too I'm
looking forward to that too
I'm looking forward to it too it we
could use a variety of words but you're
just agreeing with them so I have a
final sentence that I want to say
together all together I'm gonna say it
out loud and I want you to say it out
loud too
this is using the word looking forward
to that we talked about today using it
and I'm gonna say it slowly I want you
to imitate my pronunciation and then
we're gonna say it a little faster so if
you are somewhere quiet you have no
excuse
say it out loud with me if you're
somewhere public and you don't feel
comfortable speaking out loud right now
do it later when you get home when you
get into your office if it's quiet great
let's say this sentence out loud and
practice pronouncing you heard me say
this sentence in this expression a lot
but let's say it slowly and I want you
to say it out loud
we're gonna use a sentence similar to
what Honda said and Fabio said we are
gonna say I'm looking forward to
improving my English in 2017 so the full
sentence is I'm looking forward to
improving my English in 2017 I'm looking
forward to improving my English in 2017
make sure that each of these sounds are
comfortable for you
the L the vowels the intonation so let's
say it slowly I'm I'm looking forward to
improving my English in 2017 I'm looking
forward to improving my English in 2017
I hope that you're saying this with me
wonderful tutu says I'm looking forward
to improving my English in 2017
jailson says I'm looking forward to
improving my English in 2017 excellent
Richard Nava chu-young
on Apollo we have friends all around the
world in Europe in South America in Asia
in Europe in the u.s. in Africa in the
Middle East you are everywhere around
the world saying this we are unifying
ourselves because of something
connecting like language like English so
I will say it one more time and then
we'll say goodbye for today I'm looking
forward to improving my English in 2017
and for me as Vanessa as your teacher
I'm looking forward to helping you
improve your English in 2017 I will
continue to make lessons and prepare to
help you improve your English in 2017 so
thank you everyone for joining this live
lesson I really appreciate it
there's been so many people who have
participated I think there's 245 people
viewing live excellent this means that
there's 245 people around the world who
are connecting with each other we have
different native languages different
backgrounds different countries
different native food it doesn't matter
we are connecting because of English so
thank you for learning with me over 2016
let's continue I'm looking forward to
helping you improve your English next
year in 2017 make sure before the end of
the year make sure that you download my
top three tips guide you can download it
at the link in the description or maybe
I'll put something here on the screen
download the top three tips guide so
that you can continue to learn English
with me and get as many tips as possible
thanks so much everyone I appreciate you
being here from Brazil from Colombia
from Vietnam
from Egypt excellent welcome for thank
you for joining me
welcome to the new year soon 2017 see
you later everyone bye
[Music]