hello hello welcome to today's live
English lesson here on the speak English
with Vanessa YouTube channel I'm so glad
that you're here to learn English with
me improve your skills become more
confident and learn an exciting phrasal
verb today we're going to be talking
about an important three word phrasal
verb hang on to today hopefully you'll
be able to use a lot of examples if
you're here live this morning you can
get some feedback from me if you have
questions about it feel free to write a
comment and if there are other phrasal
verbs or other expressions or other
things that you want to see a live video
live lesson about let me know what do
you want future lessons to be about
these are flexible they're live so it's
made for you made to help you if you
would like to join me live but you don't
know how the best way is to come to my
youtube channel Tuesday and Thursday at
9 a.m. est that's the New York time 9
a.m. we just had a time change in the US
so I hope that it's not too confusing
it's always confusing even here but I
hope that for you you can join me live
and if you're here live right now thanks
so much
caleb is here Juma is here cuddlin hello
Andre good morning Alan I should glad
you're here Raul from India Tsuyoshi
good evening I hope that for all of you
you're having a beautiful Thursday and
ready to learn some English so I want to
ask you a question before we get started
today because we're going to talk about
hang on to hang on to what is something
a
physical item that you don't want to
throw away something that's maybe it's
important or maybe it's not so important
that you don't want to throw away I'll
give you a quick example and then from
your from your answers let's create a
beautiful sentence using the phrasal
verb hang on to I have a visual aid
today so this this thing is a cat toy
and usually this hangs on the door but
yesterday I took it off the door and I
put it on the ground within 10 minutes
my oldest cat the one who's 16 years old
16 and a half years old he ripped the
head off of it and as you can see he
destroyed it he loves eating and
destroying stuffed animals in the middle
of the night you can hear he loves it
and now it looks pretty gross it's not
so nice and when you see this on my
floor if you were my guest you might
think Vanessa you need to clean your
house why is there this disgusting
ripped toy thing on your on your floor
but I don't want to throw it away yet I
don't want to throw it away yet because
my cat loves it he loves to bite this I
think maybe this side is too big he
decided he already beheaded it so it's
already dead I guess to him but this we
can use we can use this to talk about
today's phrasal verb I'm going to write
a sentence about this toy and I want to
see if you can make
a similar sentence about something that
you don't want to throw away something
that's important to you or maybe
important to your cat we could say I'm
hanging on to I'll call this just a
mouse the mouse head wow I never thought
I'd write a sentence like this hanging
none - the mouse head I'm hanging on to
that's our phrasal verb today I'm
hanging on to the mouse head and this
just means not throwing it away
I'm keeping it I'm not throwing it away
this is not expensive it's not a million
dollars so I'm not keeping it because
it's expensive and I'm worried about
losing money it has sentimental value to
my cat so I want to know for you
what is something that you are hanging
on to something that you don't want to
throw away maybe it's something
expensive you're hanging on to it or
it's something that is like this kind of
silly but your friends or your cats or
your kids or you love it so you don't
want to throw it away
Julian says I'm hanging onto the piano
that I used to play when I was little
beautiful that is an excellent sentence
with this I'm hanging on to the piano so
this this phrasal verb has a little
nuance a little implication and it means
that it's not so useful now you don't
use it every day it's not something that
it is is really gonna change your life
so we we don't use this maybe if you
play the piano if you play the piano
every day and that piano is something
that you use a lot then probably we
shouldn't use this verb but if you don't
really play the piano that much but
you're holding on to it that's the exact
same thing holding on to it hanging on
to it because it's something that has
sentimental value perfect that's a great
way to use this you're hanging on to it
oh we've got a great sentence I'm
hanging on to my old cellphone I'm
hanging on to my old cellphone this is
the perfect example of what I just said
that it's not so valuable maybe there
are better things but for you you want
to hang on to it because it's it's
something that's comfortable to you
Muhammad says I'm hanging on to my old
laptop I'm hanging on to old clothes so
maybe there's a shirt my husband Dan is
like this when when he wants to buy a
new shirt I usually say take a look at
the shirts that you already have so that
you know what you want or maybe what you
need to get so that you're not
duplicating things but when he looks in
his closet each shirt for him has a
special memory this is the shirt that I
wore when I went here this is the shirt
that I wore when I went there there's a
sentimental value so he is hanging on to
his old clothes he wears them
occasionally but he's hanging on to them
for sentimental reasons we have a great
sentence here our mom says I'm hanging
on to my memories and that is going to
take us to the next step because so far
a lot of you have mentioned physical
items because that was my question I'm
hanging on to my old bike I'm hanging on
to my motorcycle but we can use this for
things that are not physical memories
ideas I'm hanging on to my past dreams
beautiful sentence here so we can hang
on to a memory this is going to be a
little more complex to think about so I
want to write a sample sentence here
let's think about something special
maybe a vacation that you went on maybe
a special time that you had dinner with
your grandma and now your grandma lives
far away or maybe she passed away and
you want to hang on to the memories of
the time that you spent together that's
something that's really valuable to you
you don't want to throw it away you
don't want to get rid of it so to talk
about something that's not so physical
let's make a sentence I'm hanging on to
the memories of my trip to Italy for
example so you are hanging on to the
memories of my trip to Italy I don't
want to forget them I'm not gonna push
them away I'm hanging up them they are
valuable they're valuable so this is a
little different than the first one
because the first one kind of means that
you don't use that item a lot it's just
something that's sentimental or maybe
it's something useful but you don't use
it all the time but for the second one
for memories those are special memories
something precious you never want to
forget them so for you what is something
that
you what is a memory that you want to
hang on to Oh a lot of people said I'm
hanging on to memories of my youth
beautiful sentence Maxime I'm hanging on
to memories of my youth
I'm hanging on to my dreams I'm hanging
on to the memories of my childhood
Gabriela great great you're not
forgetting those those are special
they're close to your heart those are
really important well I'm going to make
another line here and let's take this to
the next level let's take this phrasal
verb and use it in the past because
sometimes sometimes we hang on to things
or on to memories that can be kind of
negative so let's take an example let's
take the a simple example of these
papers I have another visual aid here
in this packet I have some papers from
the bank and I found these in my desk
over here and when I was cleaning the
desk I realized these are not important
why do I still have them I should throw
them away they are not important so I
want to throw these away and I want to
use today's phrasal verb to explain to
explain this idea so let's use it in the
past
does anyone know what is hang in the
past I'm hanging on to my memories I'm
hanging on to the mouse head but what
about in the past because this is right
now this is the present how can we say
this
I hung Oh wonderful Eduardo Young's you
got it hung I hung on to
those papers for too long they're
they're not valuable they're not
sentimental there's no reason to hold on
to them so let's use this in the past
and I want to see if you can make a
sentence using hang on to in the past so
this is something that you threw away
you got rid of because it's not
important to you anymore or maybe it
wasn't healthy for you to hang on to
your relationship so you needed to
forget about it leave it in the past I
hung on to those papers for too long
it wasn't important I hung on to those
papers I hung so this is something
that's in the past and is not happening
anymore it means you don't have that
item it's gone or you don't have those
memories they're gone uh-oh we have some
great sentences Julian says I hung on to
those old shoes for too long maybe they
fit perfectly they were great for your
feet and in the end they just started
breaking but you couldn't get rid of
them I hung onto them for too long
eduarda says I hung on to my first
girlfriend huh so in the sentence I hung
on to my first girlfriend it could mean
that you physically were holding her but
if you want to talk about her memory
that you broke up and you couldn't
forget her you had a difficult time
moving on we could say I hung on to the
memory of my first girlfriend or I hung
on to my relationship with my first
girlfriend after we broke up so if you
want to talk about after
broke up maybe we can add a few more
details that's a great thing that is
difficult to let go of and forget about
you want to hang on to those memories
you and says I hung on to those bad
ideas for a long time I hung on to those
bad ideas so now it means that you're
not holding on to them anymore and I
want to give I'm not sure if orange is
quite a different color here but a
couple times I have said I'm holding on
to so today you get two phrasal verbs
for the price of one it's all free it's
on YouTube but I'm hanging on to and I'm
holding on to is the same thing these
mean exactly the same thing so in all of
these sentences we can use hold on to we
can use it for physical items I'm
holding on to this Mouse head I'm
holding on to the memories of my trip
both of these are great but because in
the comments of one of my videos one of
you asked Vanessa how can I use hang on
to so I wanted to focus on this one but
you can also use hold onto as well um
before we go I want to give you a quick
physical image because we didn't really
talk about the literal meaning hold on
to it hang on to the word hang what does
this mean what kind of image is in your
mind when you think about hang for me I
imagine a child who's on the playground
and their hands are high above their
head and they are swinging or hanging on
a bar they're hanging they're holding
really tight they don't want to let go
that's the image that this phrasal verb
is using hanging on don't let go you
don't want to fall
it's this urgent feeling that I need to
keep it keep my memory keep this object
I'm not gonna let it go so I hope for
you you can use this phrasal verb in a
lot of situations we have beautiful
sentences hanging on holding on to the
past wonderful I was holding on to the
Past for too long but now I decided to
move on and live in the present in the
future so before we go let's say a
sentence altogether let's use our
speaking muscles I want you to speak out
loud with me use what we've learned
today use hang on to our lovely phrasal
verb and how about what is a good
sentence we can use with hang on to oh
I've got it let's make it negative
because we haven't used any negative
sentences yet I'm not hanging on to Old
English methods maybe for you you're
learning on the internet now you're here
on YouTube you're opening your mind to
different ways to learn maybe you are
talking with a speaking group in your
city maybe you're talking out loud
you're using some kind of cards taped in
your house you're using different styles
so let's use this sentence I'm not
hanging on to old English methods I'm
letting in new methods I'm not hanging
on to I need to write this down sometime
so that I can remember it out loud for
you I'm not hanging on to old old
English methods I'm not hanging on to
old English methods are you saying this
out loud with me let's say it all
together let's say it no matter where
you live we've got pee
in all countries Brazil Vietnam Morocco
Korea let's say it out loud all around
the world and focus on a multitude of
other ways to learn English are you
ready let's say the sentence all
together clearly beautifully we got this
I'm not hanging on to Old English
methods I'm not hanging on to Old
English methods I'm not hanging on to
old English methods I'm not hanging on
to old English methods you are doing new
things such as joining me here on
YouTube great work thank you so much for
your participation today we had a lot of
Awesome awesome comments I'm sorry I
couldn't read everyone's feedback but I
recommend if you want to suggest a
phrasal verb an expression an idea for
another live lesson write a comment ask
a question let me know what you would
like to learn more about and I'll try my
best to create an interesting
interactive lesson like this and if you
want to join me again I recommend it
come back if you enjoyed this lesson
come back to the speak English with
Vanessa YouTube channel on Tuesday and
Thursday today's Thursday but there will
be another lesson next week - Tuesday
and Thursday at 9 a.m. est New York time
9 a.m. I hope you can be here to learn
and focus and expand your vocabulary and
not hang on to Old English methods so if
you're thinking no Vanessa I don't want
today's lesson to end don't stop I have
a lot of suggestions watch other live
lessons and other videos on my youtube
channel there are a lot a lot of options
you can spend plenty of time learning
new things you can join my email group
so I send free email lessons every week
they include expressions like today some
tips so
stories to help you understand different
concepts and remember new idioms if you
want to get these free email lessons you
can download my free ebook 5 steps to
becoming a confident English speaker you
get a free ebook and free email lessons
great deal I hope that it you enjoy it
there is a link in the description below
this video so that you can download the
free ebook and at the end of the video
I'll put it here on the screen it's my
gift to help you take your English to
the next level and thank you everyone
for your feedback because really that is
what motivates me helps me to wake up in
the morning and make and create live
lessons for you thanks so much I'm so
glad that you join me and I'll see you
the next time next week have a beautiful
week a beautiful weekend see you later
see you next week bye