hello hello welcome to today's live
YouTube lesson I'm Vanessa and welcome
to the speak English
with Vanessa YouTube page I'm so glad
that you're taking time out of your busy
day to learn English with me and with
our community this is excellent
today we're going to be talking about
some phrasal verbs but we're not going
to talk about just a list of phrasal
verbs we're going to use them to talk
about the past because it's the end of
the year it's the end of 2016 we have 11
more days until the new year so it's a
good time to reflect and think about the
past so let me help you today with some
phrasal verbs that we would naturally
use to talk about the past if you are
new here welcome I'm glad you're here
have you downloaded my free
end-of-the-year gift today we're
celebrating the end of the year so I
hope that you have a chance to download
my free guide it's called
top three tips because in all of
December I have been making videos about
top 3 tips for grammar top 3 tips for
learning vocabulary top 3 tips for your
fluency and in the free end of the year
guide I have written all of those ideas
and added some resources so that you can
really remember them and use them put
them on your wall put them under your
pillow use them and keep it in mind
throughout the read the next year so if
you are joining me live welcome let me
know where
you're from we've got people from Maggie
from Argentina excellence lastly from
Indonesia Betty from Taiwan welcome
welcome
oh I didn't tell you how you can
download the free guide I'm sorry it's
the morning for me I have morning brain
so you can download the top three tips
guide in the description of this video
there is a link speak English with
Vanessa calm / top three the number
three and you can download this guide
it's in the description of this video
I'm sure that you'll like it and it's a
good reminder to help you know what
should I do next oh we've got Maurice
from Columbia John from Taiwan Valentin
from Argentina as well
ooh smun Saudi Arabia Paulo in Brazil
hello def all from Spain excellence
nazar in the Ukraine we are an
international group today and if you
can't watch the live video and you'd
like to watch the replay or you'd like
to join another live lesson they are
always on Tuesday at 9 a.m. Eastern Time
Eastern time is New York Standard Time
so right now it is 9 a.m. for me maybe
for Edgar in Brazil it's a little bit
closer to 12 o'clock maybe Hawaiian
Vietnam it's the evening for you I think
and in saint-petersburg maybe it's the
afternoon for you so I'm trying to find
a time that's good for everyone are you
ready to talk about phrasal verbs well
first of all let's look back on 2016
this is the first phrasal verb that I
want to share with
you today but let's use it in a complete
sentence let's think about some positive
things that happened
maybe it's positive things that happened
in English like I learned a lot of
phrasal verbs this year or I got to talk
with a native speaker this year let's
look back on 2016 I'm gonna write this
here on my clipboard and now it'll be
your turn to use this so let's say
looking back on 2016 hmm was a great
thing that happened and you're the
second part the second part of your
sentence this part here it can be pretty
different from mine this is just a
sample you might say looking back on
2016 if we want to have an ING here
finding finding Vanessa's live lessons
was a great thing that happened
looking back on 2016 mmm going hiking
every month was a great thing that
happened to me what was something that
was great or wonderful exciting that
happened to you
Oh too young says when I look back on
2016 I have a lot of unforgettable
things that happened all that's
excellent unforgettable things perfect I
think each year it seems to pass by
pretty quickly but
in reality there are a lot of things
that happen each year so just to let you
know the phrasal verb is here look back
on look back on so we could use this we
could use this exactly like chu-young
says when I look back on 2016 or we
could say looking back on 2016 and this
means you're not looking back with your
eyes we can't at least yet not in
science we can't look back into the past
with our eyes but mentally you can think
about you can reflect you can remember
2016 so you are mentally looking back
and this really means like reflecting
reflecting looking back on the past ah
Alfre says looking back on 2016 bicycle
riding was a great thing that happened
oh you and bicycle riding excellent
activities are always great memories so
Douglas says looking back on 2016
finding the fearless fluency Club was
the best thing that happened to me
wonderful while you've got 1 2 3 4 5
smiley faces must be pretty happy for
you I'm so glad if you also would like
to join our fearless fluency Club there
is a link in the description of this
video you can join me and Douglas in
this wonderful community Oh Charles says
looking back on 2016 I have many things
to say but suddenly I can't say anything
it is hard to reflect and look back
because there are a lot of things that
happen each year so it might be a little
overwhelming
Hector says looking back on 2016 I
improved my conversation skills
looking back on 2016 I improved my
conversation skills or we could say
looking back on 2016 improving my
conversation skills was a great thing
that happened excellent that's great
news
so if you have any tips how did you
improve your conversation skills let us
know I'm sure other people are also
curious Yuri says looking back on 2016
finding your channel Vanessa was a great
thing that happened Oh wonderful
that is beautiful news I'm trying to
make the best material for you so I'm
glad to know that you enjoy it Erie
Betty says looking back on 2016 speaking
English confidently was a great thing
that happened oh we've got a lot of
ideas about English improving
conversation skills joining the course
finding your channel beautiful michael
says looking back on 2016 learning
Android programming was a very
productive thing that I did Oh
learning programming yes so this is
getting ready from you for your future
Oh Erin says looking back on 2016
finding the great teacher vanessa was a
wonderful thing that happened excellent
Oh nom shot did something physical
physically healthy looking back on 2016
joining a gym joining a gym was a great
thing that happened so as you notice
here we use this ing here ing as the
subject because sometimes we talked
about this last month in the fearless
fluency Club but sometimes words that
look like a verb such as running
running usually we say I like running
it's a verb but in this situation it's
the subject of the sentence so we put it
at the beginning running was it becomes
the noun it becomes the subject of the
sentence English is pretty cool like
that huh we can use ing for nouns as
well so we have looking back running it
was
thank you all for using the sentence
structure so that we can really repeat
it Oh files are his hi I'm from Brazil
hello hello I'm glad you're here
Marcos is looking back on 2016 learning
was great for me I have been studying
English for the last 6 months
great Marco's keep it up I'm glad you're
here Oh Harold said looking back on 2016
I was so shy to speak English speaking
English I hope that for you in 2017
you'll be able to feel a little less shy
a little more confident it's a step by
step process it doesn't happen in one
day
don't worry Frost I'm glad you're here
excellent Oh
Raleigh says looking back on 2016 I uh I
improved my English skills with you and
this is another great way we could use
the second part of this sentence I'll
write it here so here's the first part
looking back on 2016 I improved this is
just an example from Raleigh I improved
my English skills so here we're using
we're not using ing again we're just
using a completely different verb in the
past tense I improved you've got lots of
choices in fact it's quite flexible but
I just wanted to show you some other
ways we could say it Oh honda says
looking back on 2016 I met the best
teacher Wow
oh hello from Spain from Beijing great
we've got other friends joining us
through from Vietnam mm-hmm Wow oh you
guys are so nice Martin Yan OH has a
wonderful complement for our community
looking back on 2016 I've been noticing
that there's no better teacher than you
Wow
well I promise that I don't come here
just to get compliments from you but I
appreciate it and this is good
motivation to continue to keep it up to
wake up and make these live lessons for
you greetings Carlos from Peru glad
you're here Oh Allie says looking back
on 2016 I tried different jobs hmm so
maybe you're trying different jobs that
are good for you or trying to see what's
a good fit Emmanuel says looking back on
2016 doing a Reiki course was a great
thing that happened oh so are you
interested in practicing Reiki are you
gonna have a studio or help other people
with it or was it just for yourself so
that you could improve or learn a new
skill Oh Christian says I improved my
English with your videos wonderful
wonderful Alex welcome from San Paolo
glad you're here
thank you so much for all of your
wonderful sentences about this Tina says
looking back on 2016 I went to the u.s.
to study English awesome
what a great opportunity that is perfect
perfect for you so I wanted to quickly
share one more phrasal verb that we can
talk about it's in the title of today's
today's live lesson does anyone know
which phrasal verb I used in the title
today hmm it's two words this phrasal
verb is three
looking back on or look back on but I
use another phrasal verb uh in our title
here o Navjot says go over yes yes go
over go over is the phrasal verb and
does anyone know what does go over me if
I said I'm going over the river
this is physically going over the river
I'm walking probably on a bridge over
the river that's one meaning I am going
over the river but if we're gonna
mentally think about this allie has the
great answer here he just analyzed yes
now judge says examine beautiful this is
the group this is the idea that I meant
for this let's analyse let's examine
2016 hmm so as we examine 2016 as we go
over 2016 we can think about the future
as well because the next year is coming
pretty soon so it's a tradition to think
about what am I gonna do in this new
year but it's also valuable to go over
things that happened in the past year
maybe some great things happen that you
wanted to continue like a lot of you
said you have improved your English or
you started exercising or you found a
new job some good things happened in the
past year so it's important to go over
the past it's just as important to go
over the past as it is important to
think about the future and plan for the
future we can learn from good things
learn from bad things
and hopefully improve for 2017 so this
is the sentence that I'd like to share
now John has it right here it says we
went over I'm using this in the past
tense here hi John Jack welcome I'm glad
you're here we went over some memories
from 2016 so we can use this we went
over some memories we reflected on some
memories we thought about some memories
so this is something that we have
already done we already went over 2016
the good things that happened in 2016 we
went over some memories from 2016 so
today I would like to have a sentence
that we all say together using this
phrasal verb and maybe we can connect
our first phrasal verb as well I want to
help you say it out loud because we can
work those muscles and it's really
valuable to hear your own voice using
English so let's say one sentence all
together if you're in Poland if you're
in Brazil if you're in Montreal if
you're in Indonesia wherever you are
let's say this all around the world let
me think of a good sentence here using
both of these hmm all right let's just
use them in the same sentence the
sentence is something that I recommend
for you last week I did this with my
husband
I took my notebook and I wrote down some
thoughts from the last year so I already
this and I recommend it for you so let's
say this sentence all together I will go
over and look back on 2016 I will go
over and look back on 2016 this means
maybe I will just take a walk in my
neighborhood and think about this past
year what were some good things what
were some bad things
what can I improve for the next year I
will go over and look back on 2016 I
will go over and look back on 2016 we
have started to do this together today
we've talked about your travels your
English things that you've done but it's
important to do this just yourself even
if it's only five minutes as you're
eating breakfast look back on go over
2016 Thank You Allie for writing the
sentence yes I will go over and look
back on 2016 I will go over and look
back on 2016 it's important mentally and
it's important for improving in the
future because this is the third to last
lesson before the end of the year we
have second-to-last next week we'll be
talking about Christmas because I will
be at my husband's parents house my
in-laws house so we will be there and I
can tell you about some of our
traditions I'll ask you about some of
your ideas and then the next lesson will
be the new year so we won't look back on
2016 we will look forward to 2017 so
this is our chance this is our final
chance of the year to go over and look
back on to
thousand 16 now that you said it out
loud I hope that for you you will you
will do it you won't just say it but
you'll do it even just a couple minutes
being able to think about what did I do
what didn't I do what are some
beneficial things that happened it's
kind of surprising if you feel like
you're a negative person maybe you feel
like at the beginning I can't think of
any really positive things that happened
but the more you think there are some
things or if you're positive it's good
also to think about some negative things
that happen because you don't want to
repeat those for the next year so let's
go over and look back on 2016 after this
lesson takes some time maybe you could
even write a little list in English
about the good things that happened the
things that you learned it's a great
chance to go over and look back on it o
12 ich has a great idea I will go over
and look back on your videos so if you
learned something this year go over it
look back on this try to remember those
ideas so I hope for you today this
lesson was useful you had a chance to
repeat these phrasal verbs they might
not be new phrasal verbs for you but we
use them a lot so I hope that today our
repetition from your great sentences was
useful I hope that they will stick in
your memory that's useful help them to
stay in your head so that you can use
them in the future if someone asks what
are you doing you could say oh I'm I'm
looking back on 2016 I'm going over 2016
and they'll say oh wow oh you speak
English that's a phrasal verb you got it
so I hope that this will be something
that you can use in the future as well
and prepare you for the next year so
thank you everyone for joining
me feel free to download my free
end-of-the-year gift this top three
guide the link is in the description
below you can print it out keep it by
your computer keep it in your kitchen
keep it in your refrigerator keep it
wherever you want so that you can
remember these top three tips in the
guide thank you everyone thank you John
Jack Thank You Michelin Thank You
Douglas answers and Erin thanks for
joining me glad you're here have a
beautiful week stay warm if you're in a
cold place pretty cold here but not too
bad actually
thank you everyone have a wonderful day
I'll see you the next time on Tuesday at
9 a.m. Eastern Time est New York
Standard Time see you later everyone bye