hi i'm vanessa from speak english with
vanessa calm today you're gonna learn 33
phrasal verbs let's get started in
today's video i'm gonna pronounce these
phrasal verbs one at a time and then
you're gonna see a short clip from a
scene describing this word so i hope
that this little scene will help you to
get a better idea for what the phrasal
verb means and also it will be something
fun or funny that's going to stick in
your mind so that when you're trying to
think of the meaning of a phrasal verb
you'll remember oh yeah i remember that
scene in Vanessa's video hopefully it
will help you to remember them further
so are you ready to get started with
these 33 phrasal verbs let's get started
to add up to add up at the end of the
month I have to add up all my purchases
I have to add them up it's a lot to
bring up to bring up he brings up sports
in every conversation and she doesn't
know what to say he always brings it up
to blow up to blow up she's gonna blow
up when she realizes that her friend
lied to her she's gonna blow up to end
up to end up I wonder how the story will
end up will the characters fall in love
will they be killed I wonder how it will
end up - back up - back up don't forget
to back up your computer so that you
don't lose all your hard work don't
forget to back it up to show up to show
up
why did Dan show up at my door oh he
lives here to keep up with to keep up
with sometimes it's hard to keep up with
the mail bills and messages how can I
keep up with it I don't know to get
along with to get along with we get
along with each other because we both
like games we get along with each other
especially when I win the game that's
the best to agree with to agree with I
don't agree with this article in fact I
don't agree with it at all
to deal with to deal with when you have
two cats you have to deal with a lot of
cat fur you have to deal with it - hang
out - hang out my cats like to hang out
with each other they are best friends
they love hanging out to check in to
check out we have to check in at the
hotel after 3 p.m. and check out at 11
a.m. to fill out to fill out he is
filling out a job application do you
think he'll get the job as a
professional model he's filling it out
right now we'll see to figure out to
figure out I can't figure out why my
tree died so quickly maybe I gave it too
much water to find out to find out
Vanessa found out that Dan was really a
woman she found it out oh my goodness
to cut down on to cut down on he's
trying to cut down on sweets especially
chocolate chip cookies mmm to count on
to count done you can always count on me
to offer you tea when you visit my house
I have a lot of tea
to try on to try on he didn't try on the
shoes when he bought them oh no they
don't fit it's just too bad to keep on
to keep on maybe if I keep on drinking
coffee all night I can finish my report
just keep on drinking to break into to
break into late last night
dan secretly broke into my hidden stash
of chocolate oh no who broke into my
chocolate it's a disaster to get into to
get into even though Dan is an adult he
got into Pokemon last week he plays
non-stop and won't stop looking at it
he's really into it to bump into to run
into last week I bumped into my college
friend on the sidewalk I can't believe I
ran into him here to apply for to apply
for I decided not to apply for a visa
because it's too expensive I didn't
apply for it to look for to look for
I looked for my cat's toys and I found
them
under the piano I'm glad I looked for
them there to drop out of to drop out of
she told him that she decided to drop
out of the program because it was too
hard she dropped out of it
to make fun of to make fun of Dan made
fun of Vanessa's new style he laughed at
her a lot but she didn't like being made
fun of she felt really sad to break down
to break down a good teacher will break
down a complicated topic so that it's
more understandable he's breaking it
down for his student and she understands
it to give in to give in even though I
was on a diet I gave in when he offered
me a cookie it was too hard to resist to
call back to call back
I called him one hour ago why didn't he
call me back yet what's he doing to come
across to come across I came across a
fascinating fact about Steve Jobs in his
biography he said that doing drugs was
one of his top three most important
experiences in life to go through to go
through Dan is going through a hard time
because he doesn't have any more coffee
will he survive to get over to get over
it was hard for me to get over the death
of my oldest cat he was 18 years old and
I loved him a lot
to look forward to to look forward to
after a long busy day he looks forward
to playing the piano and relaxing his
mind
it's so nice thanks so much for learning
these phrasal verbs with me where any of
them new for you if they were new let me
know in the comments below and write
your own sentence practicing them as
much as possible thanks so much I'll see
you the next time bye the next step is
to download my free ebook 5 steps to
becoming a confident English speaker
this will help you know what is the next
step in your English journey to help you
really master English and speak fluently
thanks so much and I'll see you later
bye