hi i'm vanessa from speak english with
vanessa calm do you know any business
idioms or phrasal verbs let's talk about
them today you're gonna learn three
business phrasal verbs and three
business idioms but as you might know a
lot of the videos on my channel are
about conversational English
so when I wanted to make a video about
business English I thought hmmm who are
some experts who can help me with
professional English expressions ah ha
ha I have a great solution for you today
I'm joined with Layla and Sabra from
love English the love English YouTube
channel they are University English
teachers so every day they help students
with professional polite English whether
that is passing an important English
exam so that you can get a promotion so
that you can get a better job so that
you can get a visa to go to another
country they are experts at this kind of
professional polite English make sure
that after you watch this video you
check out the link in the description to
the lesson that we did on their channel
about the top English interview
questions and answers this is a fun
entertaining and useful lesson that we
did together it's really great to work
with other English teachers and I hope
that it will be to your benefit hello
everybody
we love English I'm Sabra and I'm Labor
thank you so much Vanessa for having us
on your channel and asking us to help
you out with explaining some of these
business expressions and idioms so we
are British if you can't tell our
accents are British and we've got a flag
just to help you recognize where we're
from and we are real teachers we teach
at a British University College we help
students go to university and improve
their language thank you so much Vanessa
and let's get on with the expressions
the first phrasal verb that we're gonna
talk about is to go over something and
the first idiom is to cut corners Leyla
and Sabra how would you use these in
professional business situations to go
over something to go over something so
let's start with a phrasal verb to go
over to something a very common phrase
verb isn't it so yes it is definitely
yeah and when we go over something we
review often a document or a plan or
even a business proposal so it means to
review and look at in detail to make
sure there's no problems hmm so if you
want somebody to check something at work
you might say can you go over this for
me I'm not sure about these numbers
could you go over the figures perfect
example yes figures to cut corners to
cut corners an idiom that kind of means
the opposite is to cut corners so to cut
corners means to reduce the amount of
time or money spent on doing something
and often it ends up that you don't do
such a good job because you cut corners
exactly so for example if you cut
corners when you're a student learning
English you might get someone else to
help you write your essays yep you go
the quick way but it might not
necessarily mean that you do such a good
job or that you learn as much how would
we use it in business laila in business
you might try and cut corners when it
comes to a project that you are
investing in so you might want to save
some money and maybe not have as many
members of staff that you need which
means that the job really isn't as good
as it should be so generally it's a bit
of a negative thing guys to cut corners
I hope you guys aren't doing that thanks
so much for going over these important
expressions you certainly didn't cut any
corners
the next expressions that we're gonna
talk about are to come up and better
late than never
Layla and Sabra how would you use these
to come up to come up okay
another phrasal verb that you will
probably hear in the office is to come
up something comes up and this just
simply means that another situation
arises to come up means to rise up a
situation arises and you need to delay
what you are doing so you may have
planned to have a meeting but something
might come up you might get an important
business phone call that you have to
take and you can't go to the meeting
yeah so sorry this opportunity has come
up I can't
I can't miss it things like that yeah
sometimes people will leave a meeting
early because I'll say I'm really sorry
but actually something more important
has come up
I have to leave I'm so sorry things like
that so yes it is very very common in
the workplace and it comes up to make
happens unexpectedly really better late
than never
better late than never right this one
guys actually it's a great expression if
I often say it but I tend to be a bit of
a late person I'm not the best with time
management
lalla knows so I will often say better
late than never know I'll say it when
you turn so it means it's better to
arrive and to never come to never arrive
so yes I think it's very easy to
understand that one better late than
never
it's not just talking about arriving
though that's a great example but it is
meaning things like waiting for a
telephone call it might mean you're
waiting for somebody to come back with
your answer about a project yes there's
something coming in then yeah I'm saying
yes exactly thanks for that great
explanation the next time that something
comes up and you're late you can say
well better late than never
the next two expressions that we're
gonna talk about art to wrap up and call
it a day lay let and savor what do these
mean to wrap up something to wrap up
something another phrasal verb that
actually I would say we may be used a
little bit less here in the UK but
definitely I've heard the American to
wrap things up and basically it means to
bring things to a close to finish so if
we're in a meeting you might say right
let's wrap things up guys that's it we
don't have any more time now let's wrap
it up you might also be working on a
project with somebody and you might say
okay let's do this this and this and
then wrap things up it's also used very
often in the filmmaking industry they
say and that's a wrap when it's finished
yes so not so much in business but
definitely used a lot in Hollywood to
call it a day to call it a day okay so
an idiom for this is let's call
add a let's call it a day means that's
it now let's call it a days and the day
has finished so the working day is over
let's call it the end of the day for
example very common week we say this two
weeks together actually after we've been
filming for love English we're going off
let's call it a day we've done enough
now let's call it a day so it just means
that's it the day is finished let's go
home alright guys so we are gonna call
it a day now and thank you and Vanessa
for watching this lesson and joining us
on this great collaboration thank you so
much for having us again Vanessa and
hello to all your audience it's great to
get to know you guys a little bit thank
you so much for having us
and good luck in all your business
meetings don't cut any corners and make
sure you go over things very carefully
alright let's wrap up this lesson it's
time to call it a day let me know in the
comments below this lesson where any of
these phrasal verbs or idioms new to you
do you ever cut corners when did
something come up what time are you
ready to call it a day at your job thank
you so much for joining me in this
special video with Layla and Sabra from
love English make sure that you check
out the other video that we did together
on their channel about the top interview
questions and how to answer them and how
not to answer them you can click on the
link in the description or up here
thanks so much for joining me and I'll
see you again next Friday bye
the next step is to download my free
ebook five steps to becoming a confident
English speaker you'll learn what you
need to do to speak confidently and
fluently don't forget to subscribe to my
youtube channel for more free lessons
thanks so much
bye