hello hello welcome to today's live
English lesson here on the speak English
with Vanessa
YouTube channel I'm so glad that you're
interested in improving your English and
participating because this is a live
lesson if you're watching live please
interact write comments answer my
questions if you're watching the replay
no problem you can also interact write
comments write notes try your best to
use this information and today's special
phrasal verb lesson because the goal is
to remember it that's what you want to
do you don't want to forget this after
the lesson finishes if you're new
welcome we have live English lessons
here every Tuesday and Thursday at 9
a.m. est est is New York timezone so
9:00 a.m. EST it's the morning for me
and it's kind of a cloudy morning I
think it's gonna be rainy today but it's
spring that's pretty normal if you would
like to join future live lessons all you
need to do is subscribe to my youtube
channel and you'll get a notification
when we have a live lesson and if you'd
like to continue receiving free material
free English lessons from me I send two
free email lessons every month every
week I mean two free email lessons every
week and you can get those free email
lessons if you download the ebook five
steps to becoming a confident English
speaker this ebook has helped thousands
of English learners become confident
feel like they're on the right path and
know what is the right path it's my goal
to help you as much as possible
including today so if you would like to
get that free ebook there's a link in
the description or up here are you ready
to talk about phrasal verbs today we've
got a lot of friends joining us live
Jose Anatole welcome yeah
and card Oh Joe ow glad you're here mag
no thanks for joining me live I want to
ask you first of all do you feel like
phrasal verbs are comfortable for you or
are they challenging for you I've
created a lot of free lessons about
phrasal verbs there's also a lot of
phrasal verbs included in my courses and
extra materials but I want to know for
you how do you feel about phrasal verbs
I want to make sure that I'm sharing
with you the right information because
today we're going to be talking about
two similar phrasal verbs that have a
slight difference and I don't want you
to feel confused I want you to use them
confidently and correctly Rubin says
they're a challenge Carter says I like
phrasal verbs great so I hope for you
even if they're a challenge Herbert says
they're a challenge well Estela even
though they're challenging for you I
hope that after today you will know two
more phrasal verbs and be able to use
them smoothly and correctly today we're
going to talk about work on and work at
but before we start talking about how to
use this phrasal verb I want to show you
what we're not going to talk about
because there are a couple different
ways to use work on or work at in a
sentence but they're not as phrasal
verbs so let me show you really quick I
wrote some sample sentences in advance
so I don't waste your time but we are
not going to be talking about a sentence
like this I work at the bank this is not
a phrasal verb here at the bank this
sticks together and work is the verb
this is not a phrasal verb work at does
not stay together so we're not going to
talk about where do you work I work
at the bank I work at a school I work at
an office we're not going to be talking
about this and we're not going to be
talking about where you work I work on a
boat I'm a sailor it's not really true
for me or is it I work on a boat this is
the same we're just talking about where
you work this is not a phrasal verb and
these two sentences are correct of
course you can use at and on in this way
but we're not going to be talking about
them like that we're going to take it to
the next level we're going to talk about
how to use them as a phrasal verb so I'm
going to give you a sample sentence and
I want to see if you can use this
yourself before I give a quick
explanation I want to say that recently
I'm working on improving my exercise
habits I'm working on improving my
exercise habits whoo what do you think
that this means I'm working on improving
my exercise habits hmm does this mean
that I'm actually on physically on my
exercise habits yes not so much I'm
working on improving my exercise habits
we have yes a lot of people gave great
explanations to spend time producing or
improving something yes so when you're
working on something it means that
you're it's a process
you're probably improving something I'm
working on improving my exercise habits
I'm working on improving my English
party great sentence Hamza says I'm
working on improving my English grammar
I'm working on improving my grammar
mistakes beautiful what about working at
what if I said I'm working at improving
my exercise skills is this the same
sentence I am working at improving my
exercise skills it's the same sentence
except I used act instead of on let me
show you this quick page here I have two
sample sentences I'm working on I'm
working at I'm gonna underline our
important phrasal verb today working on
working at and what do you see
afterwards it's the same thing it's the
same sentence except we just changed on
an act I'm working at being more
confident when I speak English I'm
working at being more confident when I
speak English these two words have an
important similarity you can use I'm
working on being more confident I'm
working at being more confident the only
time we can use both of these is if we
use an ING verb afterwards we need an
ING verb so if you remember my sentence
from a moment ago I said I'm working on
improving my exercise habits I'm working
on improving in I'm working at improving
my exercise habits in this situation
there's absolutely no difference there
are similarities between these two so
really you've got two choices choose one
that feels comfortable to you and make
sure that you use I ng after both of
these I know a lot of you have been
writing beautiful beautiful sentences
here Diego says I'm working on in
proving my listening skills great I'm
working at being more professional in my
work I'm working at speaking English
fluently I'm working on being a good
speaker lovely yes you've got it that we
need ing verb after this and when I was
thinking about the difference between
working on and working at I asked my
husband because it's it's good if I
think about it but I want to make sure
that I'm giving you the correct material
and I said tell me what's something that
you're working on and he said a sentence
I'll tell you in just a moment and then
I asked him what is something that you
were working at and he told me another
sentence and it proved my theory because
there is a difference between the Senate
structure working on we can use ing
working at we can use ing but there is a
difference let me show you the next page
there is a difference here do you see do
you see any difference between these two
sentences I'm working on my English
skills I'm working on improving my
English skills you might notice well of
course we've got our lovely phrasal verb
and here we could use
[Music]
ing this is a similar sentence to what
we talked about before I'm working on
improving my English though I'm working
at improving my English skills great
same sentence because we have ing here
beautiful I'm working at improving I'm
working on improving but what about this
first sentence hmm do you see an ING
verb I'm working on my English skills
you could say I'm working on improving
my English skills but there's not an ING
verb here huh well this is the
difference with on we can use over a
noun directly afterwards or we can use I
in an ING verb so we already talked
about I'm working on improving that's
great
I'm working at improving but in this
sentence we can't really say I'm working
at my English skills we have to use on
if we're going to use a noun directly
afterwards so let's practice this
concept because I want to make sure that
you can remember it and I'm going to
tell you a couple of the sentences that
my husband said when I asked him this
question so that you can use this as
well I asked him Dan
Dan's his name Dan tell me something
that you are working on and you also can
be thinking about this what's something
that you're working on and he said I'm
working on my business oh that was his
first sentence so he used this
automatically know ING verb I'm working
on my business right now he's working a
lot on his business he has a job kind of
temporary job and he's also working on
his business in his free time so he's
quite busy
he said I'm working on my business and I
said tell me something that you're
working at who and he said
I'm working
going to bed earlier he used an ING verb
directly after at I'm working at going
to bed earlier that was his first
instinct and I think that that says a
lot because I think about it a lot I can
think about different situations
different circumstances but when you
talk with a native speaker maybe you
have a native speaker friend or you have
a partner or you're gonna travel
somewhere you want to know really what
they're gonna say instinctively what are
they really going to use so that's why I
like to ask him questions to figure out
what will you experience when you talk
with a native speaker so he used I'm
working at improving my English skills
and I'm working on my English skills he
used this but you can also use like we
talked about you can also use ing for
both of them no problem we've got a lot
of great sentences so let's talk about
those sample sentences that you wrote
and I'll help to give some feedback
Victor says I'm working on math to go to
university aha so you need to improve
your math skills I'm working on math to
go to university I'm working on
improving my math skills both are great
Aisha says I'm working on my graduation
product great our graduation project
Federica says I'm working on working out
every day
yes get nice and strong you have to work
on your relationship great sentence work
on your relationship or we could say you
have to work at improving your
relationship or you have to work at
keeping up your relationship using two
phrasal verbs here I'm working at being
an independent person beautiful sentence
Khan I'm working at setting up my own
business I'm working on my muscles a lot
of people here are working out
great I'm working on learning more for
college greats Marlena says I'm working
on being here with you every Thursday
I'm working at watching your lessons
more regularly I think you guys have got
this definitely that we can use ing for
either one but working on is useful for
a noun
I'm working on speaking English fluently
I'm working on English great it seems
like all around the world you all have
different projects different goals
different ideas but we have one thing in
common that one thing it's why you're
here
English we have English in common and
that's something really beautiful about
learning English learning a foreign
language you can connect with people who
have different goals and different ideas
but you're all connected because you can
communicate together maybe you're not
working on your graduation project
you're not working on getting a
girlfriend like was it said maybe you're
not working on get being more patient
with your kids like Estella but you've
got one thing in common you're
interested in learning English so when
you meet someone new you have this that
you can you can connect over I'm working
at being a better English speaker I'm
working on my English skills and this is
what I want to say all together before
we go today
a lovely sentence to use our phrasal
verbs I'm working at I'm working on
something are you ready I'm gonna say
this and it's slowly a couple times and
I want you to say it also with me
it is exercise your speaking muscles
Lulu are you ready we're gonna say I'm
working on speaking English every day
are you are you working on speaking
English everyday if you would like you
can write the sentence in the chat box
write it in the comments write it on
your arm so that you don't forget write
it on the wall maybe I'm working on
speaking English every day ooh if you're
working on speaking English every day
but you don't have a speaking partner
you don't have sort British friends or
you're not living in Australia how can
you do that there's a lot of options you
can read out loud you can answer
questions out loud you can talk to your
cat you can try to use English as much
as possible you can imitate when a
native speakers talking in a podcast in
this video you can repeat after me you
can say I'm working on speaking English
every day let's say it slowly practice
some pronunciation imitate my mouth and
then we'll say it fast are you ready I'm
working on speaking English every day
I'm working on
speaking English every day can you say
it really fast how fast can you say it
I'm working on speaking English every
day I'm working on speaking English
every day I'm working on speaking
English every day
yes I'm working on speaking English
every day I hope that you could say this
out loud and I hope it's true for you I
hope that you are working on
speaking English every day thanks for
practicing this phrasal verb with me
you're awesome and I'll see you again in
the next live lesson feel free to
subscribe so that you can get a
notification when we have a live lesson
and of course you can download my free
ebook 5 steps to becoming a confident
English speaker because I want to help
you work on speaking English confidently
it's my goal to help you you can learn a
lot of vocabulary and grammar but
if you want to speak you need to feel
confident in your own skills keep it up
I'll see you again the next time have a
beautiful day thanks so much for
learning with me bye