sometimes a friend will do something
exciting and you'll want to be able to
ask them how it went in this video we're
going to look at five different ways
that you can ask someone how something
went in English the first and simplest
way to ask somebody in English how
things have gone is to say how did it go
and the faster version would be how did
it go
imagine you have a friend who just
started a new job and they've just
finished their first day of work you
could ask them how did it go or how'd it
go
and they could respond with it went very
well or it didn't go so well the second
way that you could ask someone how
something went is to say how did that go
or the faster version how'd that go
imagine someone has told you that they
just used a new recipe to cook a chicken
you could say hey Dave
how did that go and they could respond
with it went very well the chicken was
delicious
or it didn't go well I burnt the chicken
a third way to ask someone how something
went is to ask the question how was that
or how was it maybe you have a friend
that just told you that they went scuba
diving a way to ask them how it went
would be to say how was it or how was
that they could be used interchangeably
you could say how was it Dave and they
could respond it was amazing I saw so
many fish or they might say it didn't go
very well I'm afraid of the water
a fourth way to ask someone how
something went is to ask the question
how did things turn out imagine a friend
has borrowed money from you to start a
business when you see them you can say
how did things turn out and they could
respond by saying things are going very
well here is your money back or they
might say
things aren't going so great I won't be
able to pay you back for several weeks a
fifth and final way to ask someone how
something went is to ask the question
how did you make out and the faster
version would be how did you make out or
how did you make out how did you make
out how did you make out or how Jamaica
imagine you have a friend who recently
took a driving test you could say to
them hey how did you make out and they
could respond by saying it went super
good I passed or maybe they'll say it
didn't go so well
I hit a tree well that was five ways to
ask someone how something went in the
past don't forget to subscribe below if
you enjoyed this lesson to receive new
lessons each week
Bob the Canadian here learn English with
Bob the Canadian I hope you enjoyed this
video have a great day
[Music]
you