hey guys welcome to my channel in this
video I'm gonna give you top 50 English
phrases that you can use in your
everyday life so if you are just about
to embark on your journey to an
english-speaking country you can totally
use this phrases if you have been
learning English for a while and you
want to resume learning this is the best
video to start with so let's go 50
phrases in English in hopefully 10
minutes
phrase number one this is another way to
ask how are you how is it going how's it
going so you meet someone and you time
how is it going
phrase number two when you haven't seen
somebody for a while you tell him a long
time no see
so that means that you haven't seen this
person maybe weeks or months a long time
no see
phrase number three if you want to ask
you what have you been doing you ask
what have you been up to so what was
going on in your life what have you been
up to raise them before if everything is
going well you can just answer
can't complain everything is really cool
can't complain
next phrase somebody tells you something
and you haven't really mentioned it in
the conversation like they guess somehow
that you have a new job and you ask him
how do you know where did you get the
news like how do you know if somebody
tells a cool joke you can tell that's a
good one that's a great joke so the
phrase is that's a good one if you want
to thank somebody you can say it's very
kind of you thank you so much for doing
that that's very kind of you it is very
kind of you if somebody was trying to
help you but couldn't reach the result
you can say thank you anyway it doesn't
matter but thank you anyway thank you
for your effort no thank you anyway and
another phrase that I use in my email
sometimes when I haven't asked for a
person I ask and then I say in the end
thank you in advance which means that I
really hope that you're gonna do it some
thanking you in advance thank you in
advance if somebody made a mistake and
he's really upset about it you can just
say no worries don't worry
no worries which means don't worry about
it it's fine no worries imagine you came
home and there are all of your friends
sitting on your couch and you're like
what's going on in here like what are
you doing here what is going on if you
didn't catch something or it didn't
understand the person you can always ask
did I get you right and then go ahead
and explain where you got did I get you
right if you ask somebody not to be
upset not to cry you can say don't take
it to heart don't take it to heart like
seriously don't be so upset don't take
it to heart another way to ask if you
didn't catch a part of a phrase you can
say I didn't catch the last word I'm
sorry can you repeat it because I didn't
catch the last word if he wants somebody
to repeat the whole phrase again you can
say sorry I wasn't listening because
maybe you were busy maybe you were
talking on the phone and somebody was
talking to you and you're like oh my god
sorry I wasn't listening can you repeat
it I'm sorry I wasn't listening
another phrase that I use all the time
it doesn't matter like don't worry if
you drop your coffee all over me it's
like it doesn't matter I'll be fine I'm
going to laundry anyway it doesn't
matter if you want to wish somebody luck
and I always do that you can say fingers
crossed and you cross the fingers like
that
fingers crossed another phrase that
Americans use is Oh bad that explains it
and the situation is you didn't get
something and then you get an extra
effect and you get it and you're like oh
that that explains it that explains it
another way to tell the person to not be
upset is you can say things happen like
it's okay
things happen do not be upset if you
don't have the name of a person you want
to talk to him you can say sorry to
bother you you know you see somebody's
busy you can always say sorry to bother
you and then you can go ahead and ask
sorry to bother you if you are in the
middle of something in somebody's asking
you something you can say oh you're in
the middle of something and somebody
somebody's asking you to do something
you say I'm sorry I'll be with you in a
minute I'll be with you in
and then you resume doing something and
you say where were we like when did we
stop where were we and you have to
repeat it because what it's the sound
that somebody some people mistake with B
so this is a great way to practice where
were we again if you're in the middle of
a conversation and you didn't get what
the other person was saying you can say
you were saying and with a question mark
which means which prompts the person to
repeat once again you were saying if
somebody got a job of his dreams of
whatever you can say lucky you or
somebody got into the university of
their dreams like lucky you this is a
way of congratulating the person lucky
you or like just emphasizing that he's
lucky lucky you another way to say that
you're really angry is to say I freaked
out like I was so angry I freaked out
this is super angry oh this is like
almost crazy I freaked out another
phrase that native speakers use is good
for you and this could be both positive
and negative when you say I got promoted
and if they say good for you like
congratulations and sometimes if you say
like I'm leaving this place they're like
good for you it would be better without
you and this is a negative meaning so
really listen to the intonation if
something surprises you you can also say
you gotta be kidding me like oh my god I
cannot believe it you gotta be kidding
me to tell somebody to smile and to be
happy you can always say cheer up cheer
up if you want somebody just sound like
crying and complaining about something
that is not happening you can say come
I'm you can do it I come on you can do
it you can pass the TOEFL you can pass
the GMAT you will get it come on you can
do it if somebody is doing really well
you can tell them keep up the good work
keep up the good work
like be as good as you are and keep up
the good work continue being
another phrase is colloquial and this is
what Americans say that's lit which
means that's amazing many Americans said
in California
oh that's lit and you probably heard it
in songs that's lit if somebody is
successful after failures so you can say
there you go I told you you're gonna
make it there you go
if somebody's asking you if you're tired
and you want to say you're not tired at
all you can say not a bit nah I want to
continue I'm not tired
not of it when somebody is asking you
are you sure and you're pretty sure you
can say there is no room for that there
is no room for doubt in America if you
want to SMS somebody or send them a
message you say text to text so I'll
text you means I will send you a message
through whatsapp or a telegram or
messenger of whatever using I'll text
you again to cheer somebody up to tell
them to not be upset you can say it's
not worth it like why are you crying
it's not worth it
you're so much better than the problem
you are crying about it's not worth your
tears it's not worth it I personally
love the phrase you rock which means
you're amazing oh my god you rock you
rock no you've done an amazing job you
rock if somebody's not working really
well and you want them to work harder
you can say you should go an extra mile
which means like work harder you should
go an extra mile another way to say the
very same thing you can say step up your
game like work harder work better step
up your game if somebody's crying and
doesn't want it it sinks you say pull
yourself together
like literally take yourself and pull
yourself together stop working stop
crying pull yourself together
hey calm down yourself together another
phrase that I love you sold me because
sometimes people describe their trip or
somebody they bought and they describe
it is so well and they're like I want to
buy the same thing and I tell them you
sold it you sold me I wouldn't buy this
alright you sold me if you're not
interested in the conversation you're
like sitting you can say
I could not care less this is so boring
I'm not interested I couldn't care less
if somebody's asking you something and
this is a really easy decision for you
like somebody tells you take my 1
million dollars and you say this is a
no-brainer I'll take it this is a
no-brainer means it's a really easy
decision for you if you've done
something wrong and you admit it you can
say I screwed up yes guys I know I'm
sorry I screwed up this is my mistake I
screwed up I screwed it up if you want
somebody to work instead of me you can
say can you cover me like can you work
instead of me while I'm seeing my friend
can you cover me it's time to leave and
guys I'd better be going which means I
should go already it's you know it's
actually 1 9 p.m. right now I'd better
be going another way to say goodbye I
can say take care which means take care
of yourself I'll see you later take care
I don't know what day is it when you're
watching this video but if it's Friday
for example weekend you can say thank
heavens is Friday or think heavens said
Saturday weekend discovery I'm so happy
this was it guys 50 phrases in English
let me know if this was helpful by
liking this video and commenting below
if you know any more cool phrases that
would be great there's a red button over
there somewhere
subscribe to this channel to not miss my
new videos I love you guys thank you so
much for watching this bye
[Music]