hey guys welcome to my channel in this
video I'm gonna give you eight tips on
how to write emails and essays and
letters like an American so if you're
willing to improve your writing please
continue watching this video
[Music]
back to San Francisco that might change
this number one be direct again American
people are very relaxed when I was
dealing a lot with British people I
noticed that their email would be like
that but the whole point can be
minimized to two or three sentences your
goal is to talk about what you want to
talk in two or three sentences in an
email and again be relaxed
relax it doesn't matter if you ask how
are you or are you doing people don't
really do that in emails and I was
surprised with my investor is Fry to me
they say hey marina when I first saw
this I'm like really to use hey in a
formal email but it turns out that yes
Americans are so relaxed they even use
teh informal emails they use a lot of
contractions they use of a lot of idioms
self be prepared to write like an
American and another advice have a
really clear call to action this is
called CTA what are you asking for what
is the purpose of this email make sure
that the person gets it right away when
you are writing in American English make
sure you're using active voice instead
of using passive voice passive voice is
when I say baybridge was built by an
American government this is a phrase I
would use if I'm doing a tour of San
Francisco but if I'm writing an email I
would use active voice the American
government instructed the builders to
build the bay bridge
for example tip number three and this
can relate to your spoken English as
well please please please do not over
explain hey don't explain it just
clarify if you feel that you're asking a
question don't give people answers just
ask that question if you feel that you
cannot explain a phenomena without
coming up with 50 examples then maybe
your description of the phenomena is
wrong so
as concise as you can
[Music]
tip number four when you're writing a
formal email or an essay please refrain
from writing there is of there are for
example there are a lot of students in
San Francisco
basically there are here is just a
filler word because you don't have to
use it students come to study in San
Francisco that's a much better written
sentence refrain from using Paris and
there are serious tip number five some
more words that you should refrain from
using and these words really vary so and
a lot I'll give you a couple of examples
she's really beautiful
instead of she's gorgeous gorgeous what
sounds more American to you where she's
gorgeous try to use words that are
strong in their meaning instead of using
really very so etc next tip is using
strong verb and by strong verbs I mean a
verb that can it comprises a verb and a
noun and I will give you a list below
this video an example is to give
definition is a lot of words but you can
just say to define again you're just
comprising everything in just one word
and this is called a strong verb so if
you want to sound more American and if
you want your written speech to be
really
use this from the burbs if you can say
that somebody was better in competition
you can just say he dominated the
competition instead of saying he was
better or if something became bigger you
can say it expanded by the way guys if
you're writing an essay right now or if
you're raising money in America or if
you if you're trying to get into
American University and doing a lot of
writing I would really recommend fluent
dot Express this is an app that my team
and I develop fluent Express you go
there you upload your text in English
and you get instant correction by native
speakers who would make sure that you
sound as American as you can we're going
to take care of all your grammar and
stylistic mistakes so that native
speakers wouldn't tell the year from a
foreign country
[Music]
tip number seven sometimes I look at my
email and I realize that every single
sentence starts with I I am writing to
ask you for this I wanted to update you
on my pro
I am writing to update you on my
progress I was wondering if you could I
wanted to tell you and this is just III
bow looks so weird so the solution that
I came up with for myself is introducing
bullet points here on my update and I
just go in bullets I don't have to start
every sentence or over and over again
introduce bullet points and make sure
you are double checking your email
double-checking your essay and look for
those smaller things like when you start
every sentence which I
[Music]
another very important aspect is how you
finish your email in America we usually
put kind regards best regards to talk to
you soon
comma marina McGill Co also another cool
tip if you want to impress somebody for
example if you're reaching out to a
university and you're asking for
financially you want to mention
something that would make them
interested in you so for example what
I've done there was an article about me
like making moves in tech in my email
signature I gave a link to that article
and I wrote in regards Marina McGill Co
one of the 16 email powders making moves
in tech you can do the same I always
link to my YouTube channels for example
if you have any articles published that
you published or have been published
about use you can mention them in your
signature
if you're writing an informal email in
America or if you're texting an American
or maybe you follow American vloggers
and Instagram American people use a lot
of contractions in their written English
and now we're gonna learn the most
popular ones i DK I don't know lol
laughing out loud you can write lol with
something's really funny oMG oh my god
this is something is really exciting or
really surprising Oh
BRB be right back when you want somebody
to wait for you for a moment
wi d what are you doing if you want to
make last-minute plans and asking your
friends what is he doing right now and
if he is able to join you for something
LMK let me know bTW
by the way bTW of my name is TV a ma
asked me anything and this is something
when you're like doing a video answer
your questions I can tell you AMA in
comments below and I will answer your
questions in the next video Q&amp;A is not
an acronym but it's common to use n
instead of aunt Q&amp;A question and answers
and this is a part of you know a formal
conference when you can ask a speaker a
question FAQ I know it sounds a little
funny but this is frequently asked
questions the section of the website
where you give answers to the commonly
asked questions TV and to be honest be
honest s MH shaking my head this is
international of I'm not approving that
s mhm BFF best friends forever GF
girlfriend
F boyfriend iMHO I've seen a lot of
those and recently found out the meaning
in my humble opinion this means that in
my opinion you don't have to consider
that so in my humble opinion okay Kimi
iMHO and BD no big deal no problem it's
no big deal
and BD TL DR I've seen a lot of those on
Facebook so for example if you're
writing a really long post and do you
think that a lot of your followers don't
have that much attention you want to
give them like a short description too
long didn't read this is the exact
meaning of this four letters if you're
writing a long text you will give a
couple of sentences at the beginning of
it with a short description and you
would read TL DR IRL in real life why
would you guys actually meet IRL
xoxo kiss hug kiss hugs BYOB this is so
American bring your own beer when you
organize the body you can ask your
friends to bring drinks because you
would not be providing them DIY do it
yourself no DIY do it yourself DM this
is direct message you can DM me on
Instagram direct message be FYI for your
information fYI TVC to be confirmed for
example if you do not know the place
where you're meeting you can write TBC
if the place is TBC the places to be
confirmed
aka also known as Marina McGill Co aka
lingua Marina and the last one pretty
common ASAP people also say ASAP as soon
as possible bye officer and if you're
writing an urgent email to somebody you
can put in the subject this is si ap
it's very urgent
thank you so much for watching this
video up to the very end if you enjoyed
it
write down
your most favorite acronym and please
like this video if it was useful share
it with your friends who are also
studying American English and don't
forget to subscribe to this channel I
will see you in the next videos and
follow me on Instagram lingua marina see
you soon bye
[Music]