It feels like you two are hosting the show.
Yewon, I hear your filmed radio show is amazing.
And there's much to see.
You sing and dance on your show?
Not too long ago... It was a big hit...
I danced to Sunmi's "Gashina."
I sang songs from "La La Land" too.
Pretend this is your radio show.
Show us your radio personality.
Let's see Yewon the radio host.
Just relax.
I'm not sure about the dance moves.
Just do whatever comes to mind.
This is Kim Yewon of 89.1 MHz KBS Cool FM.
I'll dance now.
I thought it was the traffic report.
(She changes as soon as the music starts)
(We never expected dancing like this)
She can do the moves!
(She draws you in)
(Hyejin did that dance too...)
- She's good, isn't she? / - She is.
(Yewon is a good dancer)
(She'll get more fans today!)
(Ta-da)
It's "Amor Fati."
(Fidgets)
(Freestyle dancing)
Kim Yewon!
(I like this)
Choi Sujong! Choi Sujong!
(He's the king of silly freestyle dancing)
(The king has returned)
(This isn't enough excitement!)
(I'll handle this!)
(It's the king...)
(I'll bring excitement into this world)
I shouldn't do this here...
(I am the true dancing king)
I shouldn't do this...
I shouldn't be doing this!
I really shouldn't!
(A pro at silly dances)
I can't do this!
(Very exciting indeed)
Let's give them both a big hand.
Hyunmoo, I'm sure you were reminded of the end of
last year as you watched the "Gashina" dance.
I was a bit surprised.
She did a great job since she did modern dance.
But I felt like Hyejin did a better job.
Yewon's angry now!
(Boiling up)
(This guy is the worst...)
(Geez!)
I really tried my hardest there.
Yewon, your eyes were like...
"Sheesh."
(He can't help it since he's in love...)
Yewon, I hear there's a part you want to play.
I've never been in a period piece.
They call me the PH.
The parted host.
I tend to part my hair down the middle often.
So a lot of my listeners tell me
to do a historical drama.
I should play her father.
Please love me like a daughter.
What's going on with you two?
It's not like that.