yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
good morning from the Mediterranean this
week we were invited by Aida Cruises a
German cruise line on the brand-new Aida
Perla this is the first time we've ever
been on a cruise ship with the whole
family and it was really really special
to be on such a gorgeous brand-new boat
[Music]
we're gonna race all the way to the end
whoever wins gets ice cream
no cheating you have to wait to see that
thing over there
see ya know hey okay hey are you okay
yeah so going on a cruise ship is a
little bit different than what we're
used to we stopped at a few different
locations each one for a day it just
gives you a tiny little taste of each
little place but it gives you a good
sense of what the city's like and what
you can expect so it kind of tells you
where you want to go back to where you
think you could spend a little more time
all right inner a for this week the boat
started in Majorca it went over to Rome
Italy and then up to Florence and then
over to Barcelona Spain and finished up
in my arms
got it
[Music]
the pain
and
[Music]
Trash Can God
[Applause]
there is an incredible father he works
so hard to teach the kids new things new
skills and this week he worked really
hard with Manila on swimming all right
here's the biggest plan you
[Music]
okay get underwater Tennessee was never
done that before
[Music]
he goes down for a long time tricky
watch Manila let go of the wall Minister
mommy's taking on this over their body
mm-hmm give me the guy's middle
conviction guys but I've stood iron and
Johnson dog and come one vendo what
state it is not that resuscitate biggest
gonna miss me hey girl go here's come
buddy I'm here and take and bathe what
side you wanna go on the baby one the
big killer was a big shake big kid one
you wanna go
[Music]
just I wonder if you don't like the
aubergine again here all day huh hey
babe
okay oh cool okay you're going to go
first and second how about you go after
me like Matthew okay you hold it right
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
good Manila are you didn't you didn't
buddy
you did it high five
[Music]
that was fun you want to do it again
now
okay you think
[Music]
[Applause]
did it I'm green like a dolphin
what are you brave like a cheetah
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm placing elephants absolutely yeah
so thank you I eat a Cruise's we have
such a wonderful time on your brand-new
boat and we'll see you next week
how do you say bye to the boat no how do
you say bye
[Music]