hi everyone my name is sara san and i'm
with talk to canada calm and today we're
gonna be talking about you finn isms
imagine that you had to tell someone
that his brother died what would you say
would you just go up to him and say oh
hey john your brother died no that's not
very nice so in english we have
something called euphemisms and euphony
thumbs are words that we use to soften
the reality of what we're communicating
to a listener or reader so there are a
number of different ways that we use
euphemisms so they're used to avoid
using words that have a negative stigma
attached to them and words like for
example war or sickness or death just
helps soften it out a little bit make it
sound better than what it actually is
another use for you Finn is ins is to
avoid offending others by speaking of
taboo or sacred subjects directly so it
helps again soften out the language and
make it flow a little better and not so
absurdly and the other another use for
you Finn isms is to overinflate the
importance of certain words so for
example instead of saying the boss you
can see the executive in that company in
general we use euphemisms to express
what is socially difficult to express in
direct terms so for example well
actually I have a number a set of
examples for you so we have the first
one here passed away or passed on passed
away or passed on is used instead of
dead or died so for example in my
example about telling someone's brother
that he died you would say your brother
has passed away this just sounds a
little nicer and not so I don't know not
so bad I guess the situation is really
bad so let's try and use words that make
it a little bit better right that's a
little point of use of euphemisms so
passed away instead of died or is that
so my grandma passed away 10 years ago
for example another one correctional
facility correctional facility is
actually used instead of jail so instead
of saying my dad is in jail you would
say oh my dad's in a Correctional
Facility it just makes it sound a little
better I hope none of your father's are
in correctional facilities I'm just
given an example my father is not by the
way I'm just letting you guys know okay
anyhow differently-abled
differently-abled
is used instead of handicapped or
disabled so it's usually refers to
people with a disability it can be a
physical disability or a mental
disability or disorder so we say
differently abled
it just sounds nicer and it you know
handicapped is a very harsh word
a lot of people are offended when when
someone refers to them or their family
members as a handicapped person so it's
not a very nice word to use differently
abled because they're probably maybe you
know maybe they can't walk but they're
really good at basketball so they have
different abilities and then most of the
other people around them next all right
collateral damage we hear that a lot in
the news and what is collateral damage
collateral damage is a euphemism for
accidental deaths so when you hear
collateral damage it means accidentally
a hundred people died just by accident
yeah no worries it was an accident
that's what it means but it sounds
better than seeing there were a hundred
until death because then people will be
like what 100 accidental deaths how is
that an accident how does that happen
right so that's collateral damage
letting someone go letting someone go is
used instead of firing someone so
instead of saying John you're fired you
say John you've been great we're letting
you go
it just sounds nicer even though what
you're doing is probably not very nice
he's not gonna like it but you know
sounds better so there's letting someone
go next one put to sleep put to sleep is
basically used instead of euthanized so
for example sometimes you know you may
have a dog who is very very sick and
probably suffering going through a lot
of suffering and pain probably like you
know really really really sick and and
just can't take it anymore and of course
you wouldn't want your dog to suffer um
so you would euthanize him you would
pull the plug on your dog just to save
him from all the grief of and pain and
suffering so putting someone to sleep or
sorry putting an animal to sleep is
better than saying I euthanize my dog I
put him to sleep next one pregnancy
termination pregnancy termination is
used instead of abortion so if you're
pregnant and maybe you're just not able
to have the child or maybe it's not
healthy for the mother to have the child
maybe she will be very sick in that case
the mother will have an abortion or a
pregnancy termination it just sounds
better than saying I had an abortion
I needed my pregnancy or I had a
pregnancy termination this one is on the
streets or without a roof on one's head
and these two are used for someone who
is
homeless so instead of saying you're
homeless you know or he's homeless you
say he's on the streets or he's without
a roof on his head again it just sounds
a bit nicer than the reality of what the
situation actually is there are many
many many different new phone is immoral
instead of seeing you know my sister is
fat you say my sister is overweight or
my sister's full-figured or big-boned or
chubby it just sounds nicer than saying
fat because fat does have a negative
stigma attached to it same as poor poor
instead of saying you know my brother is
poor you say my brother is you know part
of the working class or you know he's
low-income or whatever it may be
it just sounds better than poor again
because poor has a negative stigma
attached to it and finally the one that
I've already mentioned handicapped it's
really not a nice way of saying somebody
is unable to do something the best way
to say in my opinion my favorite is
differently abled but you can also say
disabled physically challenged or
disadvantaged um all of these different
ways of saying handicapped just sound
better and and nicer I guess so thank
you for watching again and Sarah would
talk to CARICOM I hope you learned
something and I hope you're not gonna go
and you know use any
really really really harsh words with
anyone I hope you you use the euphemisms
that I have introduced to you today
thanks for watching again and tune in to
all my videos