hi everyone it's sarah with talk to
canada comm um and today is actually
going to be a funny day because we're
going to be talking about funny english
words so believe it or not in english
there are funny words just like any
other language and today i think some of
the words you're just going to be like
oh my god these words actually exist in
english like what happened but they're
quite funny and interesting so i've
prepared a list of some of the funniest
words or funny sounding words that i
think will be interesting so we'll start
off with my first word blubber blubber
blubber is it refers to the thick layer
of fat on whales and other marine
animals and sometimes we actually refer
to human body fat as blubber so you know
we'll say you know oh my god i ate so
much look at all this blubber you got
all this blubber on my stomach ah i need
to go work out so we use it sometimes
for human fat but it's a funny sounding
word next word discombobulated
discombobulated means just very confused
and disorganized um so for example you
know I was discombobulated this morning
can you believe I put my car keys in the
fridge oh my god so discombobulated
actually you can say confused but it's a
funny word it exists next one doodle doo
doo doo doo doo doo doo everyone doodles
it just happens
um and doodling is like basically to
draw and formally casually especially
when you're preoccupied with something
else so sometimes in class during the
grammar lesson you probably doodle
happens sometimes with my students um
but you shouldn't doodle because anymore
a lot so stop doodling right now
now stop no I'm just joking because I'm
fine so I know you're not doodling but
anyhow doodle is a funny word next one
flabbergasted flabbergasted is actually
I don't know it's just funny to say
flabbergasted anyway it means astonished
or very surprised um basically we don't
use it very often so for example um an
example of it being used in a sentence
I was so flabbergasted when I heard that
you know mark and jenni got a divorce
what happened oh my goodness
right so flabbergasted means extremely
surprised like whoa did that really
happen flabbergasted such a funny word
festooned festoon means decorated so
really you can say decorated but festoon
does funny to say it sounds funny so you
can say for example the bank at hall was
pissed tuned with red and white flowers
okay it's a funny sounding word but
anyhow you can use it if you'd like
finicky finicky is the next word finicky
is someone describes someone who is very
particular and very specific in what
they want they don't really accept
things that aren't exactly what they
want so for example my son is a finicky
eater he won't eat anything that has any
type of meat he won't eat anything that
has any type of vegetables he will only
eat carrot that's it that's the only
vegetable he'll eat so he's very finicky
very particular about what he likes to
eat
that's finicky or you can just say picky
picky is another good word to say
instead of finicky but you know this is
a funny one next one flummoxed or
befuddled this just means completely
confused
so for example the police were befuddled
when they saw that there was no evidence
at the crime scene just means completely
confused what um but it sounds funny
flummoxed befuddled tongue-twisters
some of them gargoyle I'm sure you guys
know what that means or you've seen a
gargoyles at some point in your life um
or even in Disney movies sometimes
you'll see a gargoyle gargoyle is a
statue of an animal or an imaginary
creature like a dragon it's usually like
built into the outside of a building
um gargoyle just sounds funny gargoyle
huh anyway next one
giggle giggle is to laugh with a
high-pitched voice like a little girl so
like hee hee
anyway I'm not gonna do a high-pitched
laugh because you're gonna be like oh my
ears so giggle it's a funny sounding
word next one gibberish can you guess
what jibberish means gibberish a lot of
babies speak gibberish they're like
blahblahblah a BA daba daba daba daba
daba daba da da da da that's gibberish
it basically means words that make no
sense at all okay gibberish just a funny
sounding word itty bitty itty dee dee
dee pity anybody is an informal way of
saying very small um and we sometimes
use it with well we often use it with
children so like for example look at the
itty bitty of ladybug or look at that
itty bitty car or whatever I actually
hear it in music videos too when they're
talking about that girl's itty bitty
waist sometimes um so itty-bitty next
one ramshackle is a funny sounding word
actually never used it or heard it
before but when I was putting these
words together I was like oh my god
there is a word ramshackle like that
exists sounds funny
basically it means something that's
badly constructed something that is easy
to fall apart okay so for example that
you know that that building um has a
ramshackle construction I'm just making
that up or maybe we cross the river on a
ramshackle bridge that makes sense
ramshackle something that's not very
well constructed so we're probably maybe
we may fall so you don't want to get on
any ramshackle bridge okay next one
shenanigans and I hear that a lot and
sometimes I use it basically it just
means like mischief tricks or
problematic activities so for example
John's shenanigans got him in trouble at
work means his little you know hit the
way that he behaves you know his little
bad tricks and things and maybe he plays
jokes on people got him in a lot of
trouble but it sounds funny shenanigans
shenanigans shenanigans just this is
just a funny word anyway next one skit
at all I love that word sometimes you
hear it on in children's movies or shows
it's just an informal word for leaving
or running away okay so for example um
if if a little boy was you know coming
into my yard and he's like trying to
look inside and maybe steal a ball I
would and I caught him I would say hey
you skedaddle skedaddle get out of here
right um so it's just a funny word just
all of them are really funny they make
me want to say hahahahaha I can't
believe these exist anyhow I hope that
you were laughing during
this video hopefully and that's about it
these are all the words that I put
together there are much more words that
are funny in English but I'm not going
to mention all of them again it's Sara
with talk to Canada comm thank you for
watching and tune in to the rest of my
videos