I prefer to bleh-bleh station with some
people what what does that mean I prefer
to bleh-bleh station with some people
oh you mean you prefer to play play
station with some people what was wrong
with the way I said the first sentence
let's say it again I prefer to bleh-bleh
station with some people it looks like I
pronounced all the peas as bees this is
very typical for many English language
learners hello to all the English
language learners who are watching my
name is Sarah with talk to counter comm
and today I'll be talking about the
difference between the P sound and the B
sound I'm aware that a number of
languages don't have a letter P in their
alphabets or the P sound
for example error because none of the
languages that does not have the P sound
for that reason many English language
learners whose mother tongue is Arabic
have a very hard time pronouncing the
letter P in fact many Arabic students
who are learning esl/efl
often mispronounced P as B first let me
tell you about a similarity between the
pet and the buh sound when you say the
paw and the buh sound both sounds are
produced in the same place in the mouth
usually the tongue remains in the same
position and the lips move in the same
way when you say both letters the
difference between the two sounds is
that one is voiced and the other is not
voiced so what does that mean voice them
unvoiced sounds the consonants in the
English language which are all the
letters except for a I owe you you
already knew that are either voiced or
unvoiced so voiced means the vocal
chords vibrate and unvoiced means the
vocal cords don't vibrate if you put
your fingers on your throat you can feel
the difference between voiced and
unvoiced letters when you say the
can you guess which one is voiced or
unvoiced between p and b ha ah perfect
you're absolutely right it's P so P is
the voice glut is sorry P is the
unvoiced letter and B is the voice
letter just going to make that clear for
all of you guys to see it that's a
little bit messy sorry about that ok so
let's talk about some words that start
with B and P we have over here if you
take a look these are some words that
start with B black BAE bear bin what do
these words mean black black is a color
black that's what I'm wearing
BAE BAE is a long body of water that's
attached to a river usually comes out
like this and then that's the rest of
the river this is a bay bear house bear
is a really big hairy animal and you
don't want to get near a bear
they're pretty dangerous and bin bin is
a big container you can put all sorts of
things in these big containers it's a
little bit like this
hope you can see that and then this is
where you put everything inside
so black bay bear and bin now let's look
at some of the words that start with P
the path sound plak plak is the stuff
that accumulates on your teeth it's
that's why we brush our teeth that's
yucky and sometimes you have to go to
the
dentist and get it cleaned play you all
know what play means so I'm not going to
bother with that one pear
what's a pear at pairs of fruit it's
very yummy it's like an apple looks a
little bit like this I'm not very good
Mart but hopefully it looks like a pear
and pin pin is pointy it's like this I
don't know if you can see that but I'll
draw it for you and usually I use a pin
for my hid job but if you poke yourself
with a pin ouch that hurts so it's a
pointy piece that you can attach to
anything close anything that you want
now let's look at these words and let's
say them together I want you to put your
hand on your throat to see the
difference between the vibration when
you say the different words black plaque
BAE play bear pair pin pin good job so
continue practicing these and you'll do
a really great job my name is sarah with
dr. canada calm thank you for watching
and I hope you continue watching all my
videos