I think that all wars are harmful and
there should be in and to all words
would you agree so how can you tell
someone that you agree or disagree with
what they're saying hi everyone my name
is Sarah and I would talk to CARICOM
today we'll be talking about how to
express agreement or disagreement with
someone else when you agree it means
that you think that the same thing
someone else said is true and when you
disagree that means that you think that
what another person has seated is not
true so let's talk about some things
that you can say when you agree and some
things that you can say when you
disagree all right so first we'll go
with agree because it's more positive I
like agreeing with people the first
thing you can say when you agree with
what someone else has said is I agree
with you 100% that's when you fully
agree like everything that he said is
true or you can say yeah you have a
point there you make a good point that
means that you agree with the point that
he's made another thing you can say is I
couldn't agree with you more you know
what that means that means I agree with
you 100% and I can't agree with you any
more
sometimes when you're talking to your
friend you're not gonna say you have a
point there
you're gonna say oh that's so true
because it's more informal when you're
speaking with your friends sometimes if
you agree with one side but you don't
agree with another side so like let's
say two people are arguing about
something or maybe they're having a
discussion you can take one side by
saying I have to side with dad on this
one so for example if your mom and dad
are so you can always agree with one
person and disagree with another it
might be a friend of yours you can say
it I have
to side with Jane on this one whoever
also when you're talking to your friends
this is another informal way to say I
agree with you Oh tell me about it
like for example your friends may say oh
my god I've had such a long day today
you can say Oh tell me about it like oh
my god I agree with you
another thing that you can say is you're
absolutely right sometimes people say
negative statements so like I'm not
going to that party tonight you can say
me neither
so you're agreeing with the person and
you're probably not going to go either
so that's one thing to say that's
exactly how I feel so sometimes someone
may be talking about you know anything
and they may say something like you know
I think that they shouldn't be doing
this to other people you can say I
that's exactly how I feel
again when you're siding with another
person so let's say there's more than
one person having a discussion I'm
afraid I agree with James this time and
then if you agree a hundred percent you
can also say no doubt about it so these
are all some ways that you can agree
with people some of them are informal
and some of them are formal ways some of
them you'd use with your friends and
others you'd use at work so these are
some ways to disagree with someone and I
don't think so so maybe you're saying
well I'm gonna take the car today and
your mom says I don't think so young man
come here another way that you can
disagree is no way oh my god I always
say this one like if I disagree use
someone no way another formal way to say
that you disagree I'm afraid I did
or I totally disagree but this is very
strong so I totally disagree means I
disagree with you 100%
same with no way no way I disagree with
you 100% and then there's another strong
one
I'd say the exact opposite so again
these ones are really strong when you
feel 100% that you disagree with the
person and then sometimes you disagree
but there are some things that you might
agree with so you can say you know
that's not always true yeah sometimes it
can be true but not always so this is
also disagreeing but it's more weakly
disagreeing another way to express that
you disagree with someone but it's not
very strong you could say no I'm not so
sure about that I don't think you're
right there and then finally not
necessarily so these three ways of
disagreeing are a little weaker and
these the two four and five are really
strong ways to say I disagree so here
are the ways of agreeing and disagreeing
I hope you learned something from me
today thank you for watching again it's
Sarah with talked to Canada calm and
keep watching my videos
you