hello my dear friends welcome to my
channel today I have an ambitious goal
of teaching you 100 American phrases
these phrases are for everybody who's
already intermediate and above in their
English language so if you're interested
to get ready get your exercise books and
ride those phrases down or beat with me
it's gonna be a very intensive class
today a very intensive video
[Music]
phrase number ones stay out of trouble
don't get anything that could lead to
problems stay out of trouble
stay out of trouble another way of
saying that is to say don't do anything
I wouldn't do so when you are in a
situation think what I would do in that
situation and do the same thing don't do
anything I wouldn't do you're pushing
your luck means you're taking too many
risks and you might fail because of that
you're pushing your luck you have your
head in the clouds which means that you
are not seeing the situation in a hole
and you do not see the risks like you're
just walking across the road and not
watching right and left you have your
head in the clouds get your head out of
the clouds and back in the water where
it belong let me know this is when you
had a conversation and you need
additional information you can say let
me know when you get it by the way this
raises our American but of course you
can hear them anywhere in the world in
an english-speaking country but many of
them are very specific to where I am
right now and that's the United States
get back to me means respond to me can
you get back to me on this question
later
get back to me get real means when
somebody's dreaming about something and
you know it's not gonna happen you can
tell him
get real be realistic let's get down to
business
you gather together with your company
and you just discussing discussing
discussing you're like the left start
working let's get down to business
it was like pulling teeth and if it was
a really tough day you can say it was
like pulling teeth it was like pulling
teeth good to know this phrase can be
used in two contexts context number one
it's really important to you you want
the information and you think somebody
who gave it to you it's good to know
it's good to know that Washington DC is
they get all the United States but the
second option of using this phrase is
when somebody is for example moving into
a new apartment and you're
really jealous you can say good and no
which means I wish I didn't know that
when you don't know the answer you can
say who knows when nobody cares about
something you can say who cares like
there is nobody who would care about
this situation who do you think you are
oops
somebody is acting in an impolite way
and thinks he's allowed to do that he
didn't say who do you think you are and
there is the son who do you think you
are you're jars
[Music]
one of my favorite ones jar of hearts
who asked you which means no one asked
you sit down and relax who asked you
who asked you I'd like to pick your
brain this is a phrase that a lot of
ambassadors use when we meet them
they're like I'd like to pick your brain
on your marketing strategy which means I
want to know more about your marketing
strategy keep me posted this is a phrase
that we heard a lot from investors when
we just started fundraising and we
thought that they really interested and
they want to hear back from us in the
reality it means we're not interested
keep us posted is a kind way of saying
that I don't know off the top of my head
this is a phrase that you can use when
you cannot give the answer straight away
and you need to do some research first I
suppose just soon a phrase that means
that you didn't do your background check
or you haven't checked the answer and
gave a wrong one too fast without really
checking keep them on their toes means
don't let them relax make them work hard
I am sorry for the mix-up you can say
this phrase when you are apologizing for
confusing something wait don't tell me
when somebody wants to tell you the news
but you already kind of know what he's
gonna talk about and you want to guess
you can say wait don't tell me wait
don't tell me I'd be happy to help is a
polite way of offering your help
you get what you pay for this is when
you get a cheap good or a cheap piece of
cloth and it's really bad quality you
can say you get what you pay for right
this way
this is a very common phrase somebody
comes to visit you and you have a party
in your living room and you say right
this way please
the party is there I can't keep up means
you have so much work you're tired and
you are falling behind I can't keep up
put yourself in my shoes
imagine my point of view like if you
were me what would you do put yourself
in my shoes put yourself in my shoes I
have too much time on my hands which
means I have too much free time maybe
you could give me some extra
work basically you can use this race
with anything time work to have too much
of something in your hands another way
of saying that I have a lot on my plate
when you're overloaded with desks you
can say I have a lot on my plate give me
a break
stop being so rude still being served
Bridget you can say give me a break
give me a break when somebody is
punishing himself for doing the wrong
thing you can say stop being so hard on
yourself relax you didn't do anything
wrong
when you want to inquire how is
something going you were wondering how
is everything with something how's your
family going how's your work going how's
your hobby going this is a very common
question have you heard the good news
something great happened and you want to
share it have you heard the good news
push back the appointment means postpone
the appointment for example you need to
change the timing you're asking can you
please push back the appointment when
somebody is making a lot of excuses for
not doing the work on time you can say I
don't want to hear that mm-hmm I don't
want to hear your excuses
I want the result I'm losing it I'm
going quick I'm losing it you can hear
this phrase a lot in different songs use
them going crazy there's too much that I
can handle
oh man I'm losing it I've lost my touch
I'm not as good as I used to be I've
lost my touch and I don't know you can
talk about work I've lost my touch
in typing and typing too slow now I
haven't kept in touch with them means
you haven't talked to somebody for a
while stay in touch is a great way to
finish a conversation means you want to
hear back from that person please stay
in touch you look like a deer in
headlights which means you're so scared
you're just standing in you're frozen
because you're scared you look like a
deer in headlights
deer-in-the-headlights look can I take a
message
this is something I hear all the time
when it called my doctor's office and
he's not there the secretary asks can I
take a message for your doctor and
another face they're out of office right
now which means they walked away they're
at lunch or they have a meeting they're
out of office right now or another way
to say that is they're not available at
the moment if you're looking to work as
a secretary in english-speaking
countries make sure you're writing this
raises down they're not available at the
moment
don't push me you're gonna use this
phrase if somebody makes you angry and
angry with stupid comments or whatever
don't push me dude don't push me don't
be so quick to judgment another common
phrase when somebody's judging people
too fast without digging into the facts
you can use this phrase I have a bad
feeling about this
maybe you just had a meeting and you
think they're not gonna take your offer
you can say I have a bad feeling about
this on the other hand when you just
applied for university and you're
thinking they're gonna accept you you
can say I have a good feeling about this
I think they're gonna accept me I can't
imagine this phrase is used when
something is really awesome or something
is above your emotion imagination
because it's huge you're like I can't
imagine our color matching a little
birdie told me means there is a rumor or
is something you've heard maybe
unconfirmed but you can use the space a
little birdie told me you're moving to
Los Angeles for example a little birdie
told me make time for something means
fit it into your schedule I'll make time
for yoga tomorrow let me see how I can
move the things around yesterday I
wasn't a call with a UCLA representative
and asked him to have a meeting on
Monday and he said he's fully booked but
he said let me see how I can move things
around maybe he would have time on the
schedule to meet me on Monday
look out
is another way of saying be careful and
please learn a lot of these phrases
because they can diversify your speech
instead of saying oh that's great oh
that's good only be careful use the
phrases that I'm giving you in this
video
think fast if you're playing a game and
somebody on your team is taking a lot of
time to make a decision and the time is
right god you're like think fast think
fast think fast
loosen up is a way of saying relax
loosen put something on hold this can be
used in two situations first when you
call somebody and somebody puts you on
hold and asks you to wait this is
situation number one can I put you on
hold
second situation is when you have
something and you cannot continue doing
this because you will do it later you
are putting this on hold you can't be
serious
it's another way of saying you're
kidding me you can't be serious
when somebody wants to surpass you in
the street you can say go ahead please
continue walking surpass me it's no big
deal
when somebody pushes you in the street
and starts excusing himself you can say
it's no big deal no worries we'll do is
a short way of confirming you're gonna
do something somebody asked you can you
finish this by tomorrow will do don't
put me on the spot imagine that wife and
husband are having an argument in front
of their guests and later in that
evening the wife tells the husband don't
put me on the spot means don't tell me
off in front of a lot of people watch
where you're going somebody walks in the
street and there's a dog poop and you
don't want them to hit it what were you
going what were you going what can I do
for you is a very common phrase somebody
walks in the office and you're asking
what's the reason for their visit what
can I do for you
it's out of my hands which means you
have no control over the situation it's
out of my hands somebody else is making
decision hands off don't touch it
hands off another way of saying wait or
hole
is hang tight just wait hang tight for a
couple days
hurry up means be quick come on
move faster let's do it hurry up hurry
up keep my head above water means you're
doing just enough to survive this can
also be used when you're talking about
your job I'm keeping my head above water
means you're doing everything but you're
almost failing get out of your comfort
zone
this is something I tell you all the
time get out of your comfort zone talk
to native speakers feel stressed but if
this will help you improve a lot this
means do something uncomfortable for you
I can't get the song out of my head very
common phrase do you have the situation
right when Sun is playing all the time
in your head I can't get that song I
can't put a face to the name when you
don't remember how the person looks like
but you remember his name I can't put a
face to the name I have some money
burning a hole in my pocket
very very situation but this is when you
have money but do you want to spend
you're playing both sides this is a
phrase that is used to describe
situation when somebody's agreeing with
this person and that person and can it
make his own mind you're playing both
sides no no you're playing both sides
we need a talk and this really means we
need to talk and this phrase means we
need to talk about a bad topic maybe
you've failed or maybe you did something
wrong
We Need to Talk you're killing the mood
imagine five friends everyone's having
fun and just one guy is like complaining
feeling not happy and bringing the mood
down in the whole company she's just
kind of killing the mood you're killing
the mood that guy is killing the mood
you went too far
means that you offended somebody and
that was like too much you went too far
I was flattered when somebody gives you
a compliment you can say I'm flattered
thank you so much I feel really good
about it I'm feeling under the weather
that's another way of saying I'm feeling
sick I'm feeling under the weather
you win some you lose some this is an
expression used to our cheers somebody
up after a failure because yeah there
are bad things and they're good things
and there are good things and bad things
as well did you get it so even when you
lose there are good things so the
expression is you win some you lose some
please have a seat for example you came
to getting your American visa or you
have an appointment you have an
interview in the university and you come
and the receptionist tells you please
have a seat please have a seat
which means sit down and wait for your
appointment living beyond your means
means spending too much money spending
more than you can have one of the
phrases that I really like please excuse
us very American when you just want to
leave the room but you don't want to say
oh I have to go and do this this man
you're like please excuse us and you
just go and people know that you had to
go you're all over the place this is a
phrase used to describe a person who's
doing this this and that and that and
can it decide what he really wants to do
he's all over the place I have no idea
this is a stronger expression than I
don't know like where is your bag I have
no idea why are you asking me that
I have no idea when something is wrong
you can say I think there must be some
kind of mistake a very common phrase in
a lot of TV shows everywhere I think
there must be some kind of mistake
I think this is wrong don't play dumb
with me means don't pretend that I don't
know something I have faith in you I
have faith in you my darling I have
faith in you guys you can do it you can
learn all of the phrases you can watch
this video two times three times write
things down repeat with me but you can
do this I have faith in you
these are really common phrases and when
you watch TV shows and movies you will
notice that get your head in the game
please be focused please concentrate on
what's going on get your head in the
game
living the dream means that somebody has
everything like beautiful car beautiful
wise they
patience private jet for example living
the dream I'm living the dream you
pulled a fast one on me you tricked me
I don't know just somebody made a joke
on you and you didn't get it and
somebody laughed at you you pulled a
fast one on me I want nothing to do with
it you don't want to deal with the
situation and you want somebody else to
do that I want nothing to do with it I
don't want anything to do with him okay
I'm watching my hands of this whole
situation is another way of saying they
do you want to do nothing with a
situation it's up to you to subscribe to
this channel but I really encourage you
guys to do that the red button is below
she won't hurt a fly an expression used
to describe a person who won't do
anything bad he won't hurt a fly we're
short on time short on time which means
we don't have a lot of time left yes I
promised a hundred phrases in under 20
minutes to make it a really compact and
really intense class intense video say
yes we're short on time I'm actually
finishing up the video I think I'll pass
is a polite way of saying no I think
I'll pass
I think I'll pass so glad you can make
it this is my last race I'm so glad you
can make it guys I'm so glad you're
still watching this video means you now
know 100 phrases in English that are
commonly used in America I'm very proud
of you please let me know what is your
current level of English because I want
to know if you understand everything
that I'm saying or not I will leave a
link below to a free test please feel
free to take it just 30 questions that
would let you know where are you with
your language and let me know the
results below if you're not yet
subscribed to this channel the red
button is below if you're still watching
this video and if you enjoyed the
content don't forget to like it's very
important for me to hear and see your
reaction and I'll see you in the next
videos let's keep in touch
bye bye