hi everyone with Sarah from toxic Canada
calm today we're going to talk about how
to say hi how are you
so I've put together and I've read
different ways that you can ask someone
how they are doing and some ways also to
reply in case somebody asks you that
question so we'll start off with the
easiest one of course how are you
that is so easy it's the simplest way to
ask someone how they're doing some
typical answers would be you know I'm
fine thanks how about you or not bad and
you or maybe you're not doing very well
you can say I'm not doing very well
I'm sick or whatever it'd be another way
would be how's it going how's it going
great
not so great or could be better could it
be better this is an informal way of
seeing how are you so for example this
how are you you would say to your boss
to your colleagues no problem how's it
going you know you can save your friends
maybe your family no problem but usually
not your boss oh how are you doing
how you doing so this one is slain
that's it's not a good way to ask your
boss how are you doing
no this is when you're out with your
friends and you see a good-looking girl
and you're like hey how are you doing or
maybe it's a boy whatever it be so it's
an informal way of saying you know how
are you some typical answers would be
you know not bad and you or yeah can't
complain yeah whatever
alright for how are things this one is
okay to use with almost anyone you know
how are things or how are things going
you can say same as you
or same as always not-so-great or great
or I can't complain could be better
pretty good many different options about
what to reply um so how are things how
are things in how is life is almost the
same thing sort of thing at least so
this one's like how are things going
like in your life and this is saying how
is your life how's life um how's life is
you can use this with your friends your
family as well so typical answers would
be not bad or not-so-great or pretty
good you know if you're satisfied with
your life which I hope you are next so
number six how have you been this is a
very formal way to ask someone you know
how they have been doing um you can't
say this at work you can also you know
say to your friends how have you been
how have you been doing okay some
typical answers I've been busy or I've
been doing very well thank you or I
haven't been doing very well
unfortunately because bla bla bla bla
bla
um how's your family how's your family
so this is not like how are you it's
more about the people that you love or
the people that love you
um so you can say you know they're fine
what about yours or they're not doing
very well
bla bla bla bla bla it's always nice
when someone asks you
it's nice when someone asks you you know
how are you or how's your family or
how's life to also ask about the other
person so if I say how are you oh I'm
great what about you how are you doing
so it's nice to have that to continue
the conversation you don't want one-word
answers next what's up what's up ok so
what's up you've never used with your
boss because your boss is just gonna
look at you like are you on something
seriously so what's up is a way of
seeing you know what have you been up to
or house
going to your friends family I guess
sisters brothers whatever it's okay
typical answers would be not much or
nothing much or if there is news or if
you know there's something new in your
life you can say Oh lots let me tell you
you know we need to catch up do you know
that guy bla bla bla bla right so
typical answers for what's up what's new
what's new and what's up er almost the
same thing we use the same type of
answers so like not much nothing much
Oh same old same or if there is
something new you can say Oh lots of
news let me tell you you know this and
this happened they got a job here I did
that I did this I went skiing okay so
both of them are very similar we use
very similar answers for them as well
and they're also very much related to
what have you been up to what have you
been up to
um again not much would be a typical
answer maybe just the regular or oh my
god I've been up to
a million trillion billion gazillion
different things that I want to tell you
about so yeah these are ten different
ways to say how are you and many
different ways of replying hope this
video helped thanks again it's Sarah
with toxic Hannah calm tune in to all my
videos
you