hello you know what I saw written by one
of my ESL students one time well let me
show you I saw this the flower is so red
it's beautiful flower the one that you
can smell because that is not the flower
that you can smell that comes from
plants that is a different kind of
flower so my name is Sarah everyone and
I'm with talk to Canada calm today we'll
be talking a little bit about homophone
oh they are so fun and kind using but
don't be scared we'll learn a little bit
about them today and we'll talk about
what home phones are so what are they
anyway homophone sounds weird
homophones are words that have the same
meaning but they're spelled differently
and they usually have a different
meaning there's a long list of them but
I'll go through a few of them with you
we'll start off with these ones bye bye
and bye so they all sound the same bye
bye and bye but they each have different
meanings and they each have a different
spelling by to purchase I want to buy
some apples by expresses an agent in a
passive sentence so for example that
would be the song was written by
Jennifer Lopez and by the last by B ye
farewell my dear nobody really says
Farrell anymore it's more like bye bye
guys alright we'll continue on to flower
here is where my student was having a
little bit of trouble flower and flowers
sound the same different meaning
different spelling flower it's a
powdered green and it's usually used for
cooking among other things so for
example
bread usually has flour in it great
flour that's the other kind of flour is
a part of some plants that usually
blooms and it usually looks really
pretty so the flower looks and smells
amazing hmm all right let's go on to
here and here again they sound the same
different meaning different spelling
here means at this place this one means
at this place or spot so are you coming
here this afternoon here and here means
to listen can you hear me yes I can hear
you all right no and no again same sound
different meaning different spelling be
careful all right no no comes from the
word knowledge and it means to have
knowledge so for example I know how to
make pancakes yummy and know mm-hmm
no expresses a refusal or a negative so
an example of that would be you know mom
can I please go to my friend's party no
you can't all right we'll go on to
explain a few other different ones and
these are all the ones that I'm talking
about today are the ones that I usually
see my students have a little bit of
trouble with meat and meat meat means
animal flesh so for example I don't like
to eat meat I'm a vegetarian thank you
very much that's not true actually I
love meat anyhow and then there is meat
meat is to see someone or to be
introduced so an example with me I will
meet Carol this weekend next one right
right right means correct or it can mean
a direction so for example the answer is
right good job or okay then turn right
on ESL Street next one would be right Oh
sounds the same e ha confusing okay
right to put something down on paper so
for example I like to write poems right
right
be careful you don't write anything on
computers and you're typing on computers
you only write on paper alright next one
is there there and there
sounds very much the same because it is
the same but different meanings
different spelling again there this one
here means belonging to them so an
example of that would be that's their
house right there on the corner okay
there the other there number two it
means at or in that place so for example
please sit over there because you're
being a bad boy and then there is there
there is just the short form for they
are so they're going to the pool okay so
it's just like saying they are going to
the pool and finally this one everybody
has trouble with 2 2 &amp; 2 oh my god so
many twos alright
- 2 is towards something or someone
there are many other meanings for - so
be careful ok for this - there are many
other meanings but generally towards an
example of that in a sentence would be I
went to Carol or Carl and told him about
party okay so I went towards Karl or two
to the other two means also or as well
as so for example I have been to New
York too
that means me as well or me also and the
final meaning of to the third two would
be the number two so for example he has
two cars they have two houses all right
so these are just a few home phones but
there are many many many many many
others
be careful thank you for watching I hope
this lesson helped and tune in to the
rest of my videos Sarah again from talk
to Canada calm see you soon