teacher teacher teacher I eat it all my
food teacher I go to the mall yesterday
what sometimes it's really hard to
convert herbs into the past tense
especially because in English we have
regular verbs and irregular verbs hi
everyone my name is Sarah and I'm with
talk to Canada comm today we are going
to talk about regular verbs and
irregular verbs and how we really
convert them into the past tense
it is sometimes confusing especially for
students who are learning English as a
second or third language so converting
regular verbs is usually a little bit
easier than everything else but we'll go
through them today and you'll see what I
mean
so we'll go through some of the regular
verbs that we always use the rule here
is to add IDI to the end of the verb
that's very important that's basically
all you have to do for irregular verbs
if you want to say that you did
something yesterday or like I you know
maybe I walked outside so teacher
yesterday I walked outside beside my
house walked we just add an e T at the
end so here we have cook so that would
be cooked
cooked can you guess worked
II D it's really really easy to change
whoops worked ok back teacher my teacher
okay what so we have walked all we did
was add Edie same thing would talk I
talked to her about the party talked I
know it doesn't sound like we are
actually seeing talked kid it's not talk
kid sometimes we pronounce Edie asked
like a T like talked ok walked cooked
looked he looked at the girl and winked
winked that's all so uh anyway regular
group and then there's jumped jumped
these are all really easy easy words but
again we have so cooked walked talked
look and jumped all in the past tense
okay so all you really have to do is add
et at the end and then the word is in
past tense you can use it for anything
that you've done in the past so it works
out really great easy not confusing at
all but then what if a word ends with Y
and at irregular verb like study studies
our regular verb what do you think we do
should we put it like this
oh no that's not what we do with words
that end with y we actually have to move
the Y and put ie D instead when we want
to make it into past tense so we would
do something like this deed because we
want the e d at the end so we have to
change the I sorry the Y into nine and
then add II D at the end then we have
studied yesterday I studied for my exam
so if it ends with a y and it's a
regular verb it becomes ie D in most
cases so just keep that in mind this is
really simple you don't need to think
too hard about it practice then we get
to the hard part so don't hate me please
don't hate me because we're gonna talk
about irregular verbs they're not too
hard but there are no rules for
irregular verbs what kind of language is
this but yeah in English we don't have
any rules for irregular verbs we have to
practice practice practice all you have
to do with irregular verbs is practice
because each verb each irregular verb
converts differently when we try and
make it into a past tense verb so as an
example do you think he would say I
thinked about it yesterday I thought
about it okay so it changes entirely
like the spelling and how we say it
everything about it changes so we have
thought oh my god look at the difference
like everything after this is gone and
we added new letters teacher what are
you doing - uh sir
using us but this is the truth you have
to practice all your irregular verbs to
get better right so we have in the past
tense right would be wrote I wrote a
letter to my friend wrote okay so again
this is not a rule okay so be careful if
you see another irregular verb that has
something like ite at the end you don't
automatically convert it to OTE it's not
a rule this just applies to the verb
right because these are irregular verbs
be careful then we have read what do you
think how do you think we change read in
to past tense it becomes in to read but
not read the color that's the color red
okay that's not right but we say it that
way it's actually the same exact
spelling as read so this is read now
presently okay and this is read in the
past so how do you know which one to use
it depends on the context if you're
talking about the past you will say red
and if you're talking about now or the
future you will say read so I will read
a book tomorrow or he is reading that's
not well anyhow that's progressive but
don't worry about that I'm confusing you
okay read now read in the past he read
his book yesterday last night I read
something really interesting okay
spoke the theme we said differently
pronounced differently depends on the
context then we have go and go changes
to an entirely new word
there are no similar letters whatsoever
went not I go to the mall I went to the
mall okay be careful then we have come
and that changes into came okay then we
have eat and eat is interesting we use
all the same letters just in a different
order so we have eight so EA T a te so
that makes it a bit more simple
I hope and then they have speak spoke I
spoke to her about that thing that she
invited us to or whatever so see how
with irregular verbs you don't really
have any rules each word is unique it's
different and all you have to do is read
read read right right right
practice practice practice because
they're a little bit more difficult to
to get a grasp of but regular verbs are
really easy to understand so I don't
want to hear any of you guys making any
mistakes with these ones again it's
Sarah with talk to Canada calm thank you
for watching I hope this lesson helped
and tune in to all my videos
you