smoking is bad for you you shouldn't
smoke Wyatt can you believe that smoking
and telling me not to smoke so what do
you say to something like that English
we have stuff called popular cliches
sometimes things happen and we have
expressions for these things or
sometimes you're trying to express
yourself in a specific way and we have
an expression that has been overused as
it's been used for a very long time so
we call it a cliche so cliche is a
sentence or a phrase that usually
expresses a popular or common thought or
idea that has been overused for my
example about the smoking doing smoke I
bet that's happened to you before so
we're gonna talk about a popular cliche
that you can use when somebody's doing
that to you
we'll go through some of the ones that I
love and sound the ones that I hear the
most and and I hope you use them
sometime
all right the first one to pull an
all-nighter have you ever heard that oh
my god I pulled an all-nighter yesterday
I'm so tired pulling an all-nighter
means studying or working all night so
an example of that would be
I pulled an all-nighter to finish my
project that means that this person did
not sleep yesterday so they might be a
little bit grumpy be nice the second one
that I've heard a lot pearls of wisdom
so pearls of wisdom are wise words or
advice for example every time I feel
stuck I asked for my grandma's pearls of
wisdom this is a common expression
feeling stock means maybe stressed out
or don't know what to do another one
that I always hear and I love using
curiosity killed the cat
this means don't be too
acquisitive it can be dangerous and by
inquisitive i mean don't ask too many
questions
don't investigate into things that you
don't need to know so an example of
using that is to remember curiosity
killed the cat
just forget about it just stop looking
into it sheesh all right the next one
don't do as I do do as I say this is
used when someone points out that you
aren't being hypocritical so in my
example about the smoking don't smoke
you could have said to that person mmm
don't do what I do do as I say
so it's used when someone is being
hypocritical an example of that would be
stop talking back don't do that they do
do as I say like if someone is telling
you hey don't back don't talk back to me
but they're talking back to you you can
say uh you know don't do as I do do as I
say you're being a hypocrite there buddy
so this is one of my favorite ones of
course because I love using those next
one let sleeping dogs lie this means
don't look into or investigate something
that was troublesome in the past and
something that perhaps people are not
interested in anymore so for example I'd
let sleeping dogs lie and not reopen the
investigation so it costs a lot of
trouble before people aren't interested
in it just let it go
number six a cat has nine lives so cat
has nine lives means someone might be
having problems now but there are many
chances to do well or succeed an example
of that would be his career reminds me
that I can't has nine lives this means
that this person has probably struggled
throughout his career and each time he's
fallen he's always stood back up so I
like using this one to to support my
friend
alright and finally the moment of truth
these that a lot in movies I don't know
if you've noticed but a lot of movies
where there's like Court or something
like that the moment of truth is like
the moment in which something important
will be shown or decided so for example
of that for example of that an example
of that it's the moment of truth either
we'll get the contract or we won't so
like I said it can be something related
to being true or something related to
being shown so this is toward more
towards being shown so we'll find out
sort of will will we'll know if we're
gonna get the contract or not the moment
of truth but you hear it a lot in court
like it's the moment of truth what is
the verdict or whatever so those are
some of my favorite cliches that I use
all the time again this is Sarah with
toxic and calm and I hope you keep
watching my videos and use some of my
cliches