hi everyone it's sarah with talk to
canva.com
today we're going to talk about some
common english header names header names
are words with the same spelling but
different pronunciation and different
meanings and today we'll be talking
about a list of header names that I find
are very confusing especially for ESL or
ESL students also we'll start off with
the word closed or closed so just to
make it clear this is the word this is
closed or closed this is how it's
spelled
but what's in blue is how we pronounce
it so I wrote it in blue for you to see
how the two different words are spelled
the same way but we pronounce them
differently and have different meanings
as you can see verb or adjective okay
so that's the only thing be careful this
is not how you spell closed this is how
you pronounce it this is how you spell
it
this is the real word real word fake
words okay alright so close the first
one closed has a very a lot of emphasis
on the s sound close means near not far
for example my house is close to the
mall
whereas close is a verb and it means
shut or the opposite of open so please
close the door when you leave okay
so close next one live or live so here
we have live which is a verb and it's
very much the same as reside like the
meaning so for example I live in the
city or I live in a rural area or
whatever but it's a verb and it's live
whereas this one is live so you say it
like you say why but it
in adjectives and it means it's the same
as you know something happening at that
moment so for example I was interviewed
on live TV or there is live music at the
restaurant it means that there's
somebody at the restaurant who actually
plays the music at that time that you're
sitting and eating it's not like some
stereo system okay so live and love next
alternate or alternate the first one
alternate is a noun and it means a
different option so for example we have
an alternate plan if this one doesn't
work
hahaha okay alternate now next one
alternate alternate is a verb and it
means to switch between two things back
and forth so for example I alternated
between using the red pen and then using
the black pen so that means that I wrote
with the red pen and then I wrote
another line with the black pen and then
went back to the red pen and then back
to the black pen and I just kept
switching between them next word content
or content okay so again both are
spelled this way but this is how we say
them content so there's more emphasis on
the con the first part of the word here
con tent this is a noun and it just
means information or objects that are
held in something else so for example
the police officer check the contents of
my car okay it means he checked what is
inside of my car content on the other
hand there is a lot of emphasis
on the the next part of the word so the
10th part so this one we go through it
really fast cun 10th there's a lot of
emphasis on that and basically it's an
adjective and it just means satisfied or
happy so for example I was content to be
reunited with my husband
simple next one this one is really
confusing so be careful but we'll take
it step by step
desert or desert
so here desert is a noun there's
emphasis on the debt part of the of the
word and then it is pronounced like a
set desert ok and a 10 out and it means
it basically it's a very dry area of
land usually contains sand ok so for
example it's hard to find water in the
desert or there's a lot of desert areas
in the Middle East for example desert
desert is also pronounced with it like I
said the S is pronounced like I said
there's more emphasis on the the next
part of the word so the SIRT part so
desert like that it's a verb and it
means to abandon or leave without coming
back so for example he deserted his
children when they were young now be
careful because desert the way that we
say it there's another word desert which
means to eat something
probably sweet usually after a meal like
ice cream or cake that kind of dessert
is not spelt this way it's spelt with
two S's so don't confuse the two this
one means abandon um the other one means
yummy
stuff after a meal okay so just be
careful next one
dove or dov'è uh the first dove is a
noun and it is a type of bird so for
example white doves are beautiful dove
you may also know a brand of soap
that's called dove and it's referring to
that white bird that you see on the
label probably um it smells really nice
by the way I love their products am um
so that's the first dove meaning the
second one dov'è so it sounds very much
like an O in there okay douve and douve
is a verb it's the past tense past tense
of dive and dive like you know when
you're swimming moving o diving so he
dove into the swimming pool alright next
lead or lead oh goodness
lead lead is a verb and it means to
direct or show the way okay or be the
leader
so can you lead me to the bathroom means
can you direct me can you show me the
way okay
whereas lead lead type of metal um and
it's a noun so for example these coins
are made of lead okay
don't forget the blue section is just
how to pronounce them they are not
actually spelled this way they are
spelled like what's written in black
okay be careful next one minute or my
mute first minute minute
is a noun and it's a period of time
usually 60 seconds well always - 60
seconds a minute is 60 seconds so you
know for example oh I'll be there in a
minute okay minute minut is an adjective
and it means something that's really
really really really small so there were
very mine ute differences between the
two cars it means there was hardly any
difference very small differences okay
next one polish or polish Polish well
the first one will go with Polish polish
is it can be a noun or a verb so for
example can you polish those shoes
please polish it polish your shoes okay
that's how we use it as a verb wear a
Polish as a noun for example the shoe
polish is on the table here Polish is
used as a noun and it's pronounced
polish Polish polish it's pretty cool
okay next one Polish polish arm is an
adjective and basically um it's well you
know Poland it means someone who is from
Poland so for example the Polish lady
spoke to me today it's an adjective and
it just means that that lady is from
Poland
all right next tear or tear let's see
tear is a noun that's a tear when you
know the water that comes out of your
eyes when you are sad or sometimes when
you're happy um so the babies
years were all over the place actually
it doesn't make a lot of sense
um her tears were dripping on the floor
tear is another way to say this word
tear and it just means like rip he was
tearing the papers all over the place he
hated all the papers okay or I I'm going
to tear your shirt apart okay if I'm
really mad I don't want you to wear it
okay so tear is a verb it's to you know
this action pew or like that usually
people do when they're mad or when
they're trying to get rid of some
garbage last one separate or separate so
separate is an adjective
separate is a verb so for example
separate I used two separate rooms for
the interview okay um so it means
different two different okay
so I could have said I use two different
rooms for the interview or I use two
separate rooms for the interview where I
separate fat bar rates that's how you
say it it's a verb and it means to um I
guess divide something okay so two
separate can you please separate the
white clothes from the colored clothes
so that we can do the laundry for
example so those are the most common
header names that some of my students
have trouble with and I hope this lesson
helped you thank you for watching again
it's Sarah would talk to Canada
and tune in to the rest of my videos