hey do you want me to do you some coffee
do me some coffee what do you mean have
you ever had people say do you and me
interchangeably that happens sometimes
because do inmate can be confusing
they're often confused because their
meanings are really similar but they're
used differently my name is Sara and I'm
with talk to Canada calm today we're
gonna talk about the difference between
do and make and how we use do and make
so do we'll start with do because
there's a lot to do with do so do four
activities is a verb do to express daily
activities or jobs notice that all these
activities are jobs produce no physical
object because do means to take action
or complete a job or a task here so
we'll talk about a few of them do
homework do housework do the ironing do
the dishes do a job do the groceries so
these are some I guess some activities
or jobs that we use do with because you
know when you put it in a sentence
I'm going to do my homework I'm going to
do the groceries means I'm going to get
the groceries it's more tourist activity
now sometimes you can also be used for
general ideas so we use the verb do when
speaking about things in general in
other words when we do not exactly name
an activity so this form is often used
with words like something nothing
everything
anything so some examples of those are
I'm not doing anything at the time he
does everything for his wife oh she's
lucky I want someone to do everything
for me anyway those are so we had do
four activities don't get confused do
for the grocer do for the groceries I'll
do the groceries do for general ideas
and then we have some important
expressions that we use with do these
are standard collocations of verb plus
noun combinations that are used in
English so for example to do ones best
means to work really hard and put a lot
of effort into what you're doing to do
good you know he did good means you did
a good job to do harm on to someone
means you are being very mean to someone
else and trying to hurt them to do a
favor that means to you know do a
service for somebody without taking
anything in return that's a favor we do
a lot of fevers for our friends to do
business you know hello was nice doing
business with you mister blah blah blah
to do up your jacket actually needs to
zip up your jacket so same meeting or a
banana well done well done guys you guys
got do perfectly you're getting all the
answers correct I'm over done when you
work too hard on something and it's over
done so for example if I put one cue of
makeup on before getting on camera then
my makeup is over done
I might look like a clown but I don't
and they don't have one heel of course
that's why anyhow and then there's
underdone underdone is when you don't
put I guess a lot of effort into
something so your paper can be underdone
if you're writing a paper and it's three
sentences so that's not a good sign
that's underdone
um so activities for general ideas and
then these are important expressions
they don't they may not make a whole
bunch of sense sometimes but we do use
them so keep them in mind
all right now to make so we use make
four to express an activity that creates
something that you can touch make means
to create to produce to bake bill
construct cook manufacture right so
usually when you use make it's to
actually make something that's tangible
so to make food okay so that means
you're going to cook food to make a cup
of coffee or tea so usually when your
friend comes we'll freezy do you want a
cup of coffee or tea I'll make you
something to make a mess okay to make
room for something you know can you
please make some room for me I really
need a ride and you're the only one with
a car happens all the time in college
all right so we have also some important
expressions with make there are a number
of standard expressions that take the
verb make in a number of cases the verb
do seems more appropriate but these are
also standard collocations of the verb
and then now in combinations that are
also used in English so an example of
standard or not standard but important
expressions would make to make plans so
usually people make plans in the
and that's just to you know have
something I guess scheduled to do with
your friends or family or whoever to
make an exception okay so maybe you go
to class late and your teacher says you
Jake usually I send my students to the
office when they're late but I'll make
an exception this time I'll let you sit
into my class I'm going to send you down
to the office
all right so making an exception
make an appointment hello Doctor okay
making a decision so that's when you
have to think really hard make a
decision decide on something make up
your mind
Oh make up your mind okay so make up
your mind is you know maybe you are
choosing between two different things
you don't know if you should go to the
cinema or you want to go and have some
sushi with your friends so your friend
might say come on man make up your mind
you're killing us let's go like hurry up
and make a decision to make money
everyone likes to make money so I bet
you know what that means to make a
choice so you know I've made my choice I
want to move to Italy whatever and to
make a phone call or a telephone call so
I bet you know what that means cuz
everyone has a phone now making a phone
call is very popular so these are some
ways that we use do and make they may be
confusing because their meanings are
very similar but keep in mind does that
make is more for creating things you
know or baking
constructing and do is use more with
activities I hope this lesson was useful
for you thank you for watching again
it's sarah would talk to canada calm and
tuned into all my videos