if someone were to stop you in the
street and ask how old are you or are
you in a relationship would you sir even
if you wouldn't mind answering these
questions do you feel comfortable doing
so hello my name is sarah and i'm with a
talk to canada calm today we'll be
talking about the things that you should
or shouldn't talk about when meeting
someone for the first time in north
america so first we'll take a quick look
at the things that you can ask about you
know no problem you can ask about the
person's day you know something like how
was your day that's fine that's very you
know friendly and normal you can also
ask about vacations what countries have
you visited or where would you like to
go for your next vacation that's usually
okay as well you can also talk about
work you know you can say something like
where do you work or what are your
responsibilities at work that's usually
not an issue most people are very
receptive to questions like these um you
can also talk about hobbies you know
what do you like to do in your spare
time are you interested in anything in
particular at this time that's usually
okay as well you can also talk about
goals something like you know where do
you see yourself in 10 years what about
in five years what about in 20 years
usually people don't mind answering
questions like these you can also talk
about and this is my favorite one
because I love to eat and everybody
knows that I love to eat what's your
favorite food or have you tried Japanese
Italian arabic food usually when someone
asks me that or if I'm meeting someone
for the first time we will always talk
about food because I love hearing things
about food and talking about the
different types and it's usually really
fun and I love trying new things so it
works out great for me now what not to
talk about or what not to ask
about when you're meeting someone for
the first time you should never ever
ever ever ever talk about age you should
never ask how old are you or when were
you born most people will not answer
that question they'll say you know none
of your business you may have to run
after asking that question usually if if
I'm asked that question you know i don't
care i just say I'm 20 huh you know 20
very young which I'm not by the way I
think I've been 20 for the past five
years but all right so age don't ask
about um persons residents where do you
live what's your address don't ask
someone that that's scary if somebody
asks me that I would say hmm maybe I
should call 911 okay that's a very scary
good question most people don't want to
answer that especially not the first
meeting all right next one relationship
status are you married do you have a
boyfriend do you have a girlfriend have
you had boyfriends or girlfriends in the
past that's not very appropriate to ask
someone the first day that you meet them
maybe later on if you know them a bit
better but the first time you meet
someone you should really not ask
questions about relationships because it
just makes the person feel awkward and
uncomfortable you should never ask about
salary you know how much do you make um
how much do your parents make what's
your salary that's usually none of
anybody's business except for the person
who's getting the salary so don't ask
someone how much they make most people
will not answer that question I know a
lot of my friends I've known my friends
for years some of them and we still
don't talk about salary it's it's
something that's very personal and it's
none of anyone else's business okay the
next one family so usually I mean it's
okay to ask someone you know how many
still
wings do you have that's an okay
question is very friendly or do you come
from a big family or do you come from a
small family those questions are usually
fine but asking someone something like
are there problems in your family what
kind of issues have you faced with your
family seek know the those questions you
shouldn't ask okay are you not a
psychologist or a psychiatrist if you're
meeting someone for the first time don't
ask them this question they may run away
and this one is very personal and most
people will not answer how much do you
weigh this question is is extremely
personal most people will not tell you
or they may ignore you or you may have
to run away because they may say excuse
me what did you just ask me is that any
of your business why do you want to know
how much I weighed like geez anyway I'm
just joking but it's a question that you
shouldn't ask so good questions to ask
not so good questions to ask these rules
are not really rules but what I just
talked about in this video applies
mostly in North America in some other
countries you may be able to ask
question like questions like these you
know no problem but in North America
it's not a good idea to ask these
questions the first time you meet
someone I hope this video helped you so
again it's sarah with talk to canada
calm and thanks for watching I'll see
you guys soon