how does a tree work what is needed to
help the tree grow and how do the
different parts of a tree work together
to keep it alive
is this an English lesson absolutely
let me explain here's a tree or imagine
a tree now let's break the tree down
into parts there are roots and there's a
big trunk in the middle and branches and
twigs coming out of the branches leaves
and maybe apples growing on the tree
what does a tree need to grow and stay
alive a tree needs water it needs
sunlight and it needs carbon dioxide so
that it can grow and stay alive just
like in English if we want to learn
English we need to read we need to
practice writing and we need to practice
speaking now the different and separate
parts of a tree are the same thing as a
different and separate and separate
parts of speech for a tree to look the
way it does we need to put a lot of its
parts together to make sentences and
paragraphs we need to put different
types of words together so hello to all
my friends studying English my name is
Sarah with talk to Canada comm and today
I want to talk to you about the English
parts of speech what does that mean
parts of speech
let me tell you pets or speech are
different types of words that make up
our sentences and help us express our
feelings ideas thoughts and other types
of information there are eight different
parts of speech in English and they're
called nouns adjectives pronouns verbs
adverbs prepositions conjunctions and
interjections that's a long list so I'm
gonna tell you a little bit more about
each of these different parts we'll
start with a noun and now it is a word
that names a person place or thing an
example of that is school school is a
noun
I'll give you a sentence you tell me
where the noun is the boy goes to school
every day where do you think the noun is
boy
and school very good all right next in
line we have a pronoun a pronoun is very
similar to a noun a pronoun is a word
that replaces a noun
some examples of that are he she in it
she so I'll give you a sentence he likes
it better when it is cooked where do you
think the pronouns are P and it very
good next we're going to talk about an
adjective and an adjective is also very
closely related to the noun an adjective
is a word that gives more information
about a noun or a pronoun so adjectives
include colors sizes and shapes an
example of that is little so I'll give
you a sentence and you tell me where the
adjective is the little girl went into
the yellow bus hmm what do you think the
answer is little and yellow both these
words tell you more information about a
noun very good next I'll talk to you a
little bit about a verb a verb is a word
that is used to show an action or a
state of being so eat is a verb run is a
verb talk is a verb I'll give you an
example of it in a sentence
they walk to school when it's sunny
where do you think the verb is perfect
let's walk let's pretend you got that
right all right
adverb adverb is a word that modifies a
verb an adjective and it can actually
also modify another adverb and it can
show the extent of something so an
adverb does a lot of things an example
of an adverb is happily quickly
sometimes often never so I'll give you a
sentence
Emily often eats her vegetables happily
what do you think the adverb is Emily
often eats her vegetables happily there
are too often and happily very good
next we'll talk about an interjection an
interjection is a word that expresses a
feeling so an example of that is Oh
somebody's in trouble or maybe yeah
that's disgusting when you feel
disgusted or Wow when you're surprised
that's an introduction I use a lot of
interjections it's my favorite part of
speech next we'll talk a little bit
about a preposition a preposition is a
word that shows the relationship between
a noun or a pronoun and another word so
an example of proposition is in or on or
between I'll give you a sentence the
cookie is in the jar where do you think
the proposition is yeah you guessed it
right
in very good and the last one we're
going to talk about is a conjunction a
conjunction is a word that connects
words or groups of words together so
that an example of that is but and and
or those are words that connect other
words together I'll give you a sentence
I like reading and I like writing but I
don't like math where do you think the
conjunction is I like reading and I like
writing but I don't like math so we have
and and but very good so those are all
the parts of speech in English I hope
you learned something today my name is
Sarah would talk to canada.com and I
hope you continue watching all of my
videos thank you very much
you