hi everyone it's Sarah would talk to
Canada calm today's lesson is about
spelling I hate spelling oh it's one of
my worst things I hate spelling out Heat
spelling I hate spelling some words are
just so confusing so I decided to give
you some examples of the words that I
hate because they always make it
difficult for my awesome awesome
students so we're gonna go through a
list of all the words how they are
spelled and how we actually say them how
they're pronounced
we'll start with ache Oh teacher I have
a headache ache is actually spelled like
well it's about to eat like that but we
say it like ache
next one answer I have to answer my
phone answer answer makes it easier II
what about Wednesday this is one of my
worst ones a lot of my students say
teacher teacher on wetness day I'm going
skiing I'm like on wetness day what's
wetness day Wednesday so we pronounce
Wednesday like that then there's bridge
not bread the gym bridge like that
that's how we actually say it even
though it's spelled this way to confuse
us I hate spelling then we have February
not February February
so this one is spoke well it said Feb
you air II Castle so I live in a big
castle I'm a king cat soul catch
yeah catch the ball catch not catch
climb like climbing up the ladder climb
we have a silent
so that one sometimes difficult to catch
then we have debut debut not debug debut
like that day beYOU Depot like Home
Depot to store Depot d po ocean I love
going to the ocean and just playing with
the water or whatever you want to do
ocean like Oh shun ocean often so some
people like to say often I often like to
do this and do that and it's not
necessarily wrong so you can say often
if you'd like
most people say often I often go to
class on time every day so this one is
like usually people
p-pull so we have a silent Oh
ruff-ruff he's really rough chaos chaos
chaos so here we're actually not
spelling BCH together as Chuck Royce
phone we're seeing it as cup K and
that's when everything is like not in
order or not organized oh my god it was
chaos at school today all the kids were
running around everywhere then we have
dum
have you ever seen the movie Dumb and
Dumber oh my gosh it's one of my
favorite movies dumb like stupid dumb
not dumb dumb so we have a silent to be
be careful next we have enough enough
stop it so that's like e nuts ugh here
is at the end of
and it is said like a it's not the
same for all words not all words that
end with GH are gonna be sad like spa
but in this case it is then we have
thought and we have a silent G and H
sound so just thought like and journey
journey was like you know I'm going on a
journey to Sarah Lanka I want to
discover all the beautiful places in
Sarah wanker jerk me who who went to the
store yesterday who bought that house
who came to class late who so we have a
silent W so when we have W and then H
usually we only pronounce the age
sometimes we only pronounce the W like
in what or where then we're only
pronouncing the W so be careful knee
knee so that's a part of your body on
your belongs here leg and we have a
silent K mmm then we have so it's
not it's not show showed not should you
should go to class every day why aren't
you going
you should watch all my videos why
aren't you watching don't stop don't
stop I can see you no I'm joking then
they have straight like a straight line
straight oh and again we have a GH that
are silent here there in the middle of
word so they're silent straight and
finally sure not sir sure we say it like
this
sure do you want to go to the party
tonight sure why not
yeah I'll go
so these are some of the words that I
absolutely hate because all of my
students sometimes have trouble with
them so be careful when you're spelling
and be careful when speaking you want to
say them correctly
I hope you learned something from this
video thank you for watching again and
Sarah would talk to Canada calm and keep
watching my videos