my father's brother son likes to go
shopping what that's so hard to
understand oh my god I'm so confused
hi everyone my name is Sarah and I'm
going to talk to Canada comm today we'll
be talking about your family members and
their relation to you each person in
your family has a different name and the
different relationship to you
and every single person has an immediate
family member or immediate family
members and extended family members so
today we'll be talking a little bit
about both your immediate family members
and your extended family members we'll
start off here so immediate family
members are your siblings it's what our
siblings brothers and sisters parents
parents your mother or your father
children so that's your son or daughter
and spouse what's a spouse spouse is
wife or husband
so that's your immediate family members
and then you have an extended family and
your extended family includes many more
members of the family so those members
include your grandparents so that's your
mother's mother or your father's mother
or your father's father or your mother's
father there we go
that's confusing and then you have your
great-grandparents and that's the mother
or the father of your grandparents oh so
confused then you have uncles and aunts
and uncles and aunts are your father's
brothers and sisters or your mother's
brothers and sisters cousins are the
sons or daughters of your uncles and
aunts and nephews and nieces are your
brothers or sisters sons or daughters
okay
nephews your brother son or your sister
son nieces your sister's daughter or
your brother's daughter
I'm so confused Oh No
okay so I know that and a lot of places
around the world there's a lot of focus
on the extended family it's very
important that that you keep in touch
and keep connections between your
extended family so today instead of
seeing my brothers fathers or my fathers
brothers sons son what likes to go
shopping or went to the mall we're gonna
talk about the actual names of these
people and your family we'll start off
with you so let's pretend this is you
and you are a male a man so this is you
and then you have your immediate family
you have your wife you have your
children
so that's son or daughter and then your
mother or father and your sister
oh sorry brother oops and your sister
okay so that's your immediate family if
this was you and you are a man okay of
course if you were a women then that
would be husband let's make this simple
all right so you have you your wife son
or daughter
that's your immediate family mother
father brother sisters that's great
that's really easy most people know the
names of these things or these people
then it gets a little more complicated
you and your father
great your father has a brother
your father's brother's name is uncle in
English your father also has a sister
your father's sister's name is aunt so
instead of saying my father's sister is
really nice you can see my aunt is
really nice we use the same two names
for your mother's brother and your
mother's sister we both we call them
both uncles and aunts for both mother's
side and father's side now let's pretend
that your aunt has children so instead
of seeing my aunt's children or my
mother's sister's children you can say
my cousins so your uncle's children you
can call them cousins and your aunt's
children you can call them cousins make
things a lot easier so cousin is used
for female or male so you can use it for
a girl cousin or a boy cousin works out
okay so now we're done from this side
then you have of course let's go up okay
so you have your father and your mother
and your uncle and your aunt and then
you have your father's mother and that's
your grandmother and you have your
father's father and that's your grand
father and of course you have your
mother's mother and we call her my
grandmother and your mother's father my
grandfather total grandparents if you're
talking about more than one you can say
I'm going to my grandparents house if
you're going to their house or I saw my
grandparents yesterday but if you want
to be specific grandmother grandfather
and we say the same thing for the
mother's side or the father's side okay
so then let's go down a little bit here
is you don't forget back to you okay
don't forget okay because it's really
important that you know who you are so
you and your wife now your wife has
parents too she has a mother and father
too we can't forget about them because
then she's gonna be mad at you
so your wife's father is your
father-in-law okay so she can say oh I'm
going to my father's house today but you
have to say I'm going to my
father-in-law's
today dude I'm just kidding okay so your
wife's father is your father-in-law and
your wife's mother is your mother-in-law
okay so those are your wife's parents
your wife also has a brother your wife's
brother brother-in-law your wife's
sister sister-in-law okay so so your
wife most of her immediate family
you're gonna they're gonna be like part
of your family of course
her father is just like your father
except you add in-law same thing with
everyone else
mother-in-law brother-in-law
sister-in-law
that's for your wife's family now let's
go to your siblings what does that mean
again oh yeah brothers and sisters okay
so you have a brother and your brother
is married so what do you call your
brother's wife do you say oh my
brother's wife is so nice no you say
sister-in-law my brother my
sister-in-law live together
okay so sister-in-law is your brother's
wife it's the same thing as your wife's
sister okay so it can be a little bit
confusing sometimes when you say
sister-in-law these people will say um
is that your brother's wife or your
wife's sister which one do you mean okay
so brother and then your wife's brother
your brother's wife your brother's wife
sister-in-law and then you have a sister
of course so you have one brother and
you have one sister woohoo your sister's
husband brother-in-law
okay so sister brother-in-law and of
course your sister has children she has
one boy and one girl
so do you say my sister's children and
you say nephew for a boy and nice for a
girl
so my niece
means my sister's daughter or my
brother's daughter and my nephew means
my sister's son or my brother's son okay
all right awesome so that's you we're
coming back to you again you have
children as well you have a boy and
that's your son that's really easy and
you have a girl that's your daughter
okay so son and daughter and then one
day after 30 years your son got married
woohoo and he had children he had a girl
and he had a boy his girl would you call
her my son's daughter and you have to
call her my granddaughter because you
are her grandpa now grandfather and for
your son's son you call him your
grandson
so granddaughter if your child has a
girl and grandson if your child has a
boy so I know it's complicated but it's
really useful to know these terms if
you're gonna talk about your extended
family again my name is Sarah and I'm
with talk to canada.com tune in to the
rest of my videos thanks for watching
and I hope you learned something today