I like to eat apple in the morning
what's wrong that sentence
Oh sounds weird right I like to eat
Apple in the morning hi everyone my name
is Sarah and I am with talk to Canada
comm today we'll be talking about
indefinite articles in English and a
definite articles in English so what is
an indefinite article indefinite
articles include a and N and they refer
to singular count nouns why do we call
them indefinite articles well because
they don't refer to anything specific
it's more like any why do we call it why
do we call them count nouns like why do
they only refer to count nouns what our
account nouns anyway count nouns are
nouns that you can count like cars
papers anything that's a noun that you
can count and now that you can't count
would be something like water or air
these are nouns that are non count nouns
so you have for example I'll give you a
few examples of why we can't use an N in
front of water can you give me a water
how does that sound
does that sound right can you give me a
water and can you give me some water
that would be the right way to say it
because you can't really count water
here's one water to water three water
most liquids
you can't count so that's why we have to
say some water now we're going to talk a
little bit more about the deaf story
indefinite articles and sorry we're
going to talk more about definite
article which is that it's the only
definite article we have let me give you
a few examples she ate an apple an apple
and here is an indefinite articles it
means any
ate an apple which Apple in the Apple
who cares she ate an apple that's the
point she ate the apple what's the
difference here the makes the Apple
specific so when I say she ate the apple
that means that both the speaker and the
listener know which Apple is being
talked about that's why that is a
definite article that is used for plural
nouns or when you're referring to a
specific noun so we say that in front of
plural nouns and a specific noun it can
be singular but if it's specific like
the Apple here both of them are right
now I want to go back to what I said
earlier earlier we talked we sat in the
beginning of the video we said I like to
eat a Apple in the morning does that
sound right and this is wrong because
you have two of us in front of each
other a Apple okay
in English we don't really have that
much the right way to say it would be an
apple I like to eat an apple
usually with when you have an us sound
at the beginning of a word we should use
an in front of the word and when you
have any other consonant sound in front
of a word we should use aa in front of a
word so a vowel sound would be the sound
of a e i o u when there's a like that so
it can be uh or uh or if those are fowl
sounds consonant sounds are like puffs
or cat or duck or love or money so let's
look at a few examples
orange orange oh so we would say an
orange what about big orange you would
say ah big orange
why didn't we say an big orange
well because the next letter here starts
with a but sound and the letter here
starts with an O sound so we say an
orange ah big orange ah house house
starts with a half sound that's why we
say ah in front of it
ah small house small starts with a sound
so we say ah again
what about armchair n armchair because
armchair starts with a sound so we have
to use an in front of it so be careful
it's not about the first letter it's
about the sound at the beginning of the
word so there are some words that can be
a little bit confusing I'll give you a
few examples to help you out
so let's look here at umbrella
what does umbrella start with well it
starts with a u I know that you can see
that but the sound it makes is a
umbrella so do you think we should say
ah umbrella or n umbrella which one
sounds better an umbrella would be right
so n umbrella because you can't have a
beside each other it just sounds weird
and awkward and really difficult now if
you look here we have another word that
starts with the letter U University does
it sound like the beginning of umbrella
at all umbrella University it so what do
we say a university or an University the
right answer would be a university
because here the U is making like a a
why sound like
University with a why ah
it's making it sorry the you and
umbrella is making the up sound that's
why we say an umbrella ah University
it's about the first sound not the
letter be careful all right
we'll look at another quick example our
starts with H do you think we say an
hour or a hour let's see our a our what
do you think I think you're probably
right
an hour an hour because here the first
letter H is actually silent we don't
even say the hub sound we start with the
oh right away so n our because it's
about the sound if you look under here
we have horse here we can hear the H
sound very clearly a horse so the right
way to put it is a horse because there's
no sound in front or at the beginning of
horse alright so I hope that these
helped you I hope they didn't confuse
you and those are the English articles I
hope this video helped tune in for some
of my other videos thank you and again
I'm Sarah from talk to Canada calm see
you soon
you