hey guys welcome to my channel today
we're going to talk about a mistake in
English language that I still make that
you make like every English language
learner makes it a lot because it's an
easy mistake to make and this is when we
use the word very too many times when we
talk so if you're interested how to get
rid of this mistake please continue
watching this video
[Music]
very itself is a very weak word because
it doesn't add any extra sense very
tired very beautiful very nice it's just
magnifies the adjective that you're
using but it doesn't add anything extra
and it's just taking out your space very
very very bad bad and when you're
writing an essay for your university for
example you're normally limited to like
500 words and if you use very in every
single sentence then you're taking a lot
of space out of your essay and it
doesn't make your speech to look too
professional because again you're using
very simple vocabulary so this video is
gonna help you get rid of the word very
very before we start just compare at
these two sentences I am wearing a lot
of layers today because it's very cold
outside I am wearing a little lace
turday because it's freezing outside you
see how different two sentences are who
you think by the way when you want to
describe when you're wearing on a cold
day Americans and British people would
normally say I'm wearing a lot of layers
meaning that you're wearing a t-shirt
then a sweater there may be another
sweater and then a coat under this car
and there were four layers of petticoats
so you're wearing a lot of layers and
just you notice that emotional colour
that my sentence gets when I'm using
freezing instead of very cold and I'm
gonna give you some examples for other
phrases that you use the most used
phrase in every single ESL student
speech is a very good this is a very
good class this is a very good dress
this is a very good city now how can we
replace it instead of saying very good
you can say it's splendid it's planning
it's great it's great it's terrific it's
terrific
you could also say it's lit the party
was lip-to-lip and this is a spoken
English word so don't use it in essays
but in America it's very widely used
especially among young people your
grades are excellent excellent
this movie is brilliant this is absolute
brilliant this is a wonderful job
wonderful job on Russia brach
you see how many emotions I'm adding
when every place very with a stronger
adjective another example here in
America especially in San Francisco
people love dogs and I think the city
has more dogs than children and whenever
I walk outside I made a cute dog and all
of the dogs are really well trained so
they would approach you and jump on you
and lick you and I would always say your
dog is very cute and I'm tired of this
phrase myself because this is like a
really limited vocabulary and there are
so many words that I can use instead for
instance this is also like for me guys
right now because I really want to get
rid of this very cute phrase I can say
your dog is adorable adorable yes I can
also use the word admirable admirable
and I can also say your dog is lovely
lovely instead of saying very cute all
the time the only situation when I allow
myself to say very is when I'm training
to sounds but and what sometimes I speak
too fast I just stop concentrating on
the way I'm pronouncing sounds and it is
really important for me because I still
have this accent for my native language
so after taking our intensive course in
American pronunciation I told myself
marina
you're gonna concentrate on these two
sounds by the way if you want to take
the course the link will be below if
this is the best course in American
accent I've ever taken and it's really
helpful and you can see my progress hey
so I get it very weak he's very rich
right I'm training these two sounds very
wise I have a very wide circle very warm
it's um it's very warm in here try them
like pause this video right now and try
saying them really fast very weak very
white very warm and just train your
mouth to do the right sounds to produce
the results and this is what the chorus
is about we talk about different sounds
and how to pronounce them like where to
put your tongue and how to open your
mouth something that I also use very
often when I'm in Russia very cold as
I've already mentioned we can substitute
with freezing freezing
we can say it's chilly outside it's
chilly we can say it's frosty frosty and
we can also say for example Russia is as
cold as ice
meaning that pressure is really really
cold when you're retired
instead of saying very tired you can say
Salah stead I'm exhausted exhausted you
can say sleepy sleepy you can say
distressed distress right and if you
want to say that something is very clean
you can say spotless spotless you see
how my speech is improving when I'm
replacing the word Barry and how it adds
more details you actually use less words
but you express more thoughts with just
one word if you're stuck right now and
if you're like oh but how do I say very
beautiful I forgot this word that marina
mentioned I forgot the synonym there is
another tip for you you can still use
the word beautiful but you can replace
very with other words like extremely
extremely beautiful you're looking
extremely beautiful highly highly
competitive highly competitive and
awfully awfully cold
Jesse Cote super which is also like very
spoken super friendly super nice super
cute super cute terribly terribly nice
this can be both negative and positive
terribly nice terribly hot terribly nice
guy and usually and usually smart and
usually beautiful unusually hot mm-hmm
so there are many ways you can diversify
your speech and my task to you your
homework is to write down a comment
below with very plus something and
replace this with just one word this is
a great task for you guys because when
you are learning something new it's not
enough to just listen to it it's also
very important to do something with your
hands so your brain remembers what's the
right way I hope this video was useful
for you guys if you want to train your
American accent just like I did the link
will be below please join the course
it's it will be like one of the best
courses you've taken and this is the
course that my friend and I created
together pure now yes subscribe to this
channel hits
red button here right here the red one
and if you enjoyed this content like
this video I'm looking forward to
getting your comments guys and I'm
looking forward to seeing you in our
intensive class thank you so much and
see you very soon bye bye