hey I'm Kannada language and in this
video I'm going to give you five reasons
why you should learn Russian if you want
to travel in Eastern Europe so that's in
Russia Moldova Bellas and Ukraine in
particular so coming to Eastern Europe
and assuming that the local people don't
speak English would be a really big
mistake
now education first have done a ranking
of the countries around the world and
the proficiency in English what they say
is that this region Eastern Europe is
actually greeted in the fourth most out
of five categories so it's got a very
low level of proficiency in English to
give you a comparison that would be the
same as going to China or to Latin
America according to their grading
system while Central Europe would get
actually a high proficiency so the
second out of the five grade their
agencies are really big difference
between these two regions central in
Eastern Europe in general you can use
Russian as a lingua franca of the region
everywhere except probably fear so much
which is Western Ukraine because here
they tend to speak Ukrainian not so much
Russian in general although the center
of review which is the main city you can
die you can get by regression in general
a lot of people will replied to in
Ukrainian so you kind of need to be able
to read to understand that even if you
don't speak Ukrainian and even if the
only living training just to come here
to live is it's a beautiful city so it's
well worth the investment of your of
your time at the least able to
understand it really one of my favorite
cities in Eastern Europe is here in
review so what are the advantages to you
of having gone to learn to say Russian
now I did a video before with Benny
Lewis of more than three months but we
spoke about the english-speaking pact
which is when if you rely in English you
tend to be more vulnerable to paying
higher prices if you try to pay for
taxis here and you get one on the street
then you have to negotiate the price so
if you speak in English they're going to
think it's Christmas buy them later
they're going to demand you know maybe
50% maybe double the price maybe three
or four times the price then they would
to a local person now the best way to
get a price here they here in Ukraine
actually to call a taxi
they're always cheaper than haggling on
the street but they're you're going to
have to be able to speak up readings to
Russian to be able further technically
because it's the middle progression
that's really only problem I choose to
have that one when I first came here an
identity question I could not order
attacking it was so frustrating you know
you can of course rely on taxi apps if
ever improve things little bit so you
have of course uber that is kind of now
international reports them you can use
that up but it actually tends to be a
bit expensive in any case you were which
is unusual because most countries
actually cheaper option but here for
example you can it's a good even without
the you know the surge charging is still
about 20 to 30 percent more expensive so
the second big advantage you'll get by
speaking Russian as opposed to English
is in terms of just communication in
general right it goes further than just
your basic communication in terms of as
a taxi driver you know but people are
restaurants actually important for
building real relationships in the
region because if you can't speak
Russian then you're really going to now
another people that of course you can
communicate with in general make friends
with or just you know hang out with
while you while you're in the region and
if you don't speak Russian it's really
hard to understand say the conversations
that are going on around you right
because if you don't speak the local
language and especially not Russian in
Eastern Europe then you know you're
going to miss so much without Russian
it's ten times harder I know that
because I actually came on the first
trip to the region without speaking
really any Russian and it was so hard
and it was so frustrating
so the third big advantage to having
learned Russian and probably instant
Europe is the ability to find out what's
going on locally because a lot of that
hits they for restaurants are events
it's going to be written in Russian or
we're here in Western you can so we're
in l'viv so I can be written in
Ukrainian was so you could just about be
able to figure it out normally if you
are if you also can speak Russian that's
a big advantage I give an example
their love of guides local guides or
Facebook pages where people discuss
what's going on and Finn's
like I was in Kiev just the weekend and
because I was able to read Russian I was
able to know that there was a local
electronic new tea party going on and I
could go in join me because there
actually nothing in English so you're
not going to get the best local tips
because local people write about those
in their own languages and that makes it
harder if you rely in English that's
another big advantage is actually being
able to get at local information and
find the best places and read all the
comments that they leave and everything
as you can decide if you want to go to
something so the fourth big advantage is
making your traveling a lot less
stressful so if you can speak and
understand and it just simplifies your
life man I remember the first time when
I came after you seen Europe and I
didn't speak question and it was so
frustrating so much extra pressure to
communicate with people because I
couldn't read anything I couldn't really
get the basic I started in a restaurant
out in Russian or Ukrainian if you're
hearing a disease so that really makes a
huge difference in terms of another
relax and enjoy your traveling get so
much more out of it is not a hermit
eight of stress and panic that you're
being exposed to a language you can't
understand so the fifth reason that I'm
going to give for learning Russian this
week is of boiling scams that's a little
bit connected being higher prices but
it's more explicit because obviously if
you don't understand what's going on you
don't speak Russian and you're gonna
clean as a bigger target because scam
artists look for people or vulnerable
don't really understand the environment
that they find themselves in like for
example a very common thing that happens
to a lot of guys who come here
especially because the women are very
beautiful of course in Eastern Europe
Russians Ukrainians Moldova is
Belarusian people are Baltics everywhere
in the general region women are really
beautiful so a lot of guys say from the
United States North America and Europe
Western Europe they come here hoping to
of course make beautiful girls and that
leaves them very vulnerable they don't
speak Russian
I've never had a bad experience at all
but of course I speak the language and I
hear so many
times that you know they mean some girl
meetings on a dating app for dealing
website they go to a restaurant they
understand what's going on when things
are being ordered all of a sudden the
bill comes and while instead of being
something like reasonable like twenty or
thirty euros for the meal it turns out
it's like 300 and they have some big
burly bouncer telling them that they got
to pay up of course the whole thing is a
scam the goes in honesty both without
restaurant simply to rip them off but I
saw this happened to a to a Portuguese
guy who was travelling here and he got
scammed away in the other part of the
problem for him was I couldn't read the
bill properly he fell under a lot of
pressure just to pay because they had
some champagne and seafood platter but
it was like maybe 10 times the real
prices shoulda come definitely if you
don't speak Russian you're vulnerable
you might be seen as naive and someone
that discovers is going to target so
that's another very good reason to speak
Russian and definitely understand the
environment very well I've also seen to
happen that a friend's house bottles of
champagne and say a restaurant in a
nightclub
and then the waiter came back and spoke
in Russian and said basically yeah this
is the Bhavna or they said oh the folks
out there this one okay and accepted of
course the price of all was multiple of
the original ball that they wanted so
instead of paying say something like
thirty dollars or thirty euros they
ended up paying you know 200 300 so I've
seen to have Microsoft know 450 as
someone not understanding what was going
to bite you get out one right and the
Russians definitely going to be a
creator since Allah if you enjoyed the
video please give it up big thumbs up
and yeah write me about your experiences
of course in Eastern Europe are you fond
of whether you've heard of scum when you
found it to be the price level that you
negotiate was better and definitely in
any case Russian it is a really great
language I really enjoyed learning it
and using it and also you painting them
here in the beautiful city of
in western Ukraine and I also encourage
you to give that a go if it's useful
really final visits here so it's goodbye
from this video dope about China which
goodbye in Ukrainian and this with any
which is goodbye in Russian language