hi everyone my name is Bridget Barbara
and I am learning Russian and as someone
who's learning Russian I can tell you
that there are so many complexities to
the Russian language in this video I'm
going to discuss five of the most
difficult things about learning Russian
let's get started
cases the Russian language has six cases
and each case denotes the function of a
word so for example in English we say I
saw him he saw me it's his basketball so
we know whether something's the subject
the object possessive in Russian there
are six of these cases and it's
exhausting
there's nominative accusative genitive
instrumental prepositional and dative
and because of these cases word order in
Russian sentences can change and the
meaning stays the same because you have
these cases preserving the functions of
each word
so every time you look at a Russian
sentence it's like a mathematical
equation you have to figure out looking
at the tail ends of each word to figure
out what the subject is acting on which
objects and in what context imperfective
versus perfective verbs in Russian every
verb you use implies whether the action
is incomplete or continuous or if it's
complete whether it's imperfective or
perfective so oftentimes verbs come in
pairs
there's Advocaat vs. advocates to answer
there is chi tights vs. Russia tights
which is to read so in English we might
say yesterday I read a book but in
Russian the listener is going to know
whether yesterday you read a few pages
you read a little bit or whether you
finished the book all that sounds
convenience you're providing so much
more information but now you realize you
have to analyze every single action to
figure out whether it's something
incomplete or continuous or if it's a
completed action it's hard verbs of
motion this may be one of the most
difficult ones for non-native speakers
it's definitely one of the most
difficult ones for me in Russian you
cannot simply say to go I'm going to the
mall I'm going to the store they went to
Germany last summer in Russian you need
to specify everything did you go and
come back did you go and stay there did
you go by foot or by transportation is
it one direction or is it
multi-directional is it a singular or a
repetitive action all of this
information is built into the word you
choose prefixes as complicated as
Russian is already now we have countless
prefixes that get added onto words to
inform their meaning so think of all of
the verbs of motion we have to choose
from and now we have prefixes that get
added on to imply things like is it
going towards away from through into out
of etc etc etc pronunciation Russian is
fairly straightforward when it comes to
pronunciation as long as you know where
the emphasis goes you can usually
pronounce a Russian word as it's spelled
which is not the same for English so we
did luck out there however there are
different Russian sounds that are quite
difficult for non-native speakers to
make for me for example the number one
sound is and it shows up everywhere my
there's also the Miyake snack which does
not have a sound on its own but it
modifies other sounds so for example a
word like brought brother with a
Mackie's knock at the end it would be
but I to take some totally different
words but I but those are just five of
the difficulties that come with studying
Russian but those complexities are part
of what makes learning Russian so
rewarding I always say that studying
Russian makes you smarter because it
forces your brain to think about what
you're saying in completely new ways
it's part of the reason that I've spent
so much of my time studying this
language and I made a whole youtube
channel all about my progress
Russian is such a beautiful language and
once
get the hang of it once you get all
these ruled down it's actually a lot of
fun to speak it's like you're doing a
dance every time you talk thank you guys
so much for watching I hope you enjoyed
the video and see you next time