KYDS Subs!
The dads are watching! My Daughters' Men Season 4!
If my daughter wants it...
I'll pluck a star out of the sky for you...
The four dads who feel that way are here today.
- Time flies, right?
- Yes, it does.
We started out excited, and today is our last episode.
I'm sad. I wish we could start again.
I feel like I'm finally getting how entertainment shows work.
You're supposed to know more about your daughter not entertainment shows.
I'm going to need more time for that.
Joo-yeon wrapped up things without the cameras.
- They wrapped it up.
- They decided to take it slow.
I wonder how thing will end for the three daughters.
- I'm excited to find out.
- Let's take a look at the first text.
Today is our last day for texts too.
We got a text from the daughter and her man.
This is so sad!
Who said this?
What is it?
Please express sadness well.
I'm totally in character right now.
Ma'am, you can go first.
In our next lives...
Please...
Please stop.
You're ruining it!
Ready, go.
In our next lives, let's...
Meet on good terms..
Did Yo-Han get his enlistment notice?
I didn't think about that.
But I'm sure they won't talk about next lives.
Yo-Han stopped his song like this.
Maybe it went like this,
"Is it okay even though I have to leave you?"
"I think it will be hard for us in this life. Is that okay?"
Would he write lyrics like that though and perform it in front of Seok-hee?
Let's see who it is.
You're good looking.
Are they parting ways?
- They are?
- No way!
They're parting already?
You're good at rock climbing.
We said Soo-bin looked happy then.
Oh yeah, they went bungee jumping.
What?
He just jumped down.
This is crazy.
- I'm so scared.
- How do we do that?
It's as high as a 15 floor building.
- 50 meters.
- Wow, it's 50 meters high?
I think they said next lives because they're jumping off.
Oh, when they're jumping?
I've done that before, but it was 8 meters high.
But it got even higher.
50 meters is...
You're a strong kid Soo-bin.
That's nothing for you.
No...
I'm speechless.
Bungee jumping contract...
- You didn't drink, right?
- No.
- I'm sober.
- You're sober.
You have to fill that out and...
You have to check your health.
You don't have a heart condition after looking at me?
Did you hear that? "You don't have a
heart condition after looking at me?"
You don't have a heart condition after looking at me?
- I'm kidding.
- You're very shameless.
It helps to get rid of your nerves.
It's fun.
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm dying.
- Like dying?
- I can't talk.
Really?
- What do I do...
- Good.
- It's okay.
- I don't think Soo-bin can do it.
She hasn't tried it?
Never.
What if she cries?
Wow, they're going up so high!
We're jumping from here?
Oh no!
It's different from seeing it on the ground.
We're going up higher?
Do you have a fear of heights?
I don't know! Yeah!
They're holding hands.
You start relying on each other
in scary situations.
I don't think Soo-bin will be able to do it.
- I don't think she can.
- She's shaking for real.
Let's go.
We're jumping off from here?
- You can't jump off right now!
- Hee-chul!
It looks scary even from here.
Look at that!
Look at the ground.
We're going to jump off here.
In real life...
I'm getting sick too.
For couples, the guy as to carry the girl.
Will you be jumping off individually or as a couple?
- As a couple.
- Okay.
They're doing it together?
Couple bungee jumping?
You have to stick your face close to his.
If you don't, you guys can bump into each other.
Yeah, their heads will bump into each other.
- This is upsetting me.
- Why?
They can just hug each other and jump off.
But the guy has to carry a girl in that situation.
I've never seen you like this before.
They should just hold hands.
They should just hug each other.
If you hug like this, your heads will bump together as you fall.
It's for safety.
I wish I were younger so I can try it.
That was out of nowhere.
What a plot twist.
You guys stand here.
It's making me nervous.
What if Joo-min lets go of her because he gets tired?
That means he doesn't care about her.
But I think he'll protect her until the end.
We're really jumping off?
We really need to jump off.
Please lift her up.
In our next lives...
Oh, this is it.
This is where it's from.
In our next lives...
let's please...
meet on good terms.
You just need to hug him tightly.
Try lifting her up now.
Good.
One, two, three...
The girl has to stick tightly to him so they don't get hurt.
She can't see, so she just needs to close her eyes.
She just needs to trust him.
What is she going to do?
Whether Joo-min lets go or not is very important.
Joo-min is very brave.
If they step wrong, they'll jump off without the hassle.
Isn't Joo-min awesome?
Are we really doing it?
What's wrong?
Is there anything you want to say to her?
I want to die right now.
Ahn Soo-bin is a goat!
What does that mean?
It means greatest of all time.
I'm getting scared too.
I can't believe he said that in that situation.
If the girl said she was scared, I'd be like,
"I'm scared too!
"Please stop moving!"
You can't lie up there.
You speak the truth.
- That's right.
- I think Joo-min likes Soo-bin a lot.
Ahn Soo-bin is the prettiest girl in the world!
Here we go.
He's going to count down!
Will they be able to jump on their first try.
- It will be hard if they don't.
-  I think Joo-min will do it.
Let's see.
Wow! That's crazy!
- He's grabbing her with his legs.
- They became like this.
That's crazy.
Are you okay?
We can do it.
It's okay. Hang in there.
Good job.
That was really awesome!
That was amazing.
Sir, when they came
down, Joo-min comforted
Soo-bin and didn't let
go of her until the end.
- He's a real man.
- Didn't you see a new side of him?
Joo-min is amazing, but Soo-bin is amazing too.
For real.
We feel like we're the ones who jumped.
You know the chills you get when you're falling down?
Yeah.
- They're already doing that?
- Of course.
He needs to comfort her.
Give me your hand.
She became pale.
Your knees give away.
- Do you like bungee jumping?
- I'll never do it.
Hold on.
What are you doing in the middle of filming?
I'm the one who's doing it now because you're not telling me to do it anymore.
He's used to it now.
What am I going to do?
She's too...
She can't calm down because she was so scared.
It's still lingering.
And I bet she feels a sense of accomplishment for doing it.
Look at how his thumbs are moving.
His thumbs keep moving.
Mom, I went bungee jumping.
You'd do this only once in your life time.
Mom...
You crossed one off your bucket list.
- It was on my bucket list.
- Me too.
I think it's worthwhile to do it once.
Isn't it okay?
It was meaningful.
It's a new experience.
When he lifted her up and jumped off,
his eyes said, "I've got to protect this girl."
Every guy would feel that way when he's with someone he likes.
He said she's the prettiest
girl in the world.
- He's happy.
- Yes, he's very proud.
Where is that? A ship?
- They go only to nice places.
- They're going to keep talking about it.
- Yeah, it's very memorable.
- Seriously.
We went after rock climbing...
The atmosphere is really nice here.
The night lights are really pretty.
Yeah, it's nice.
The night lights are pretty,
and the girl sitting in front of me is pretty too.
Joo-min thinks she's really pretty.
That's what makes girls happy.
When the guy does that.
It's hot.
Wow, that sound!
That looks really good.
Eat.
Is it good?
Of course it's good when he's taking care of her like that.
It must be really good.
It's good, right?
I think this is the best barbeque I've ever had.
- Am I grilling it well?
- You're the best.
That's good.
What can't you do?
What can't I do?
Not treating you right.
How can he say stuff like that?
Say ah.
He's feeding her!
They look like a couple all of a sudden.
After bungee jumping, you get real close.
- Are you done?
- Yeah.
Should we play a truth game?
This sounds fun.
I think that's the scariest game in the world.
- I'm curious all of a sudden.
- You better prepare yourself.
Really?
My question can come back to me.
And my question can go to you too.
- Okay.
- A drinking game?
You have to think about it carefully..
You go first, okay?
Okay.
Oh, you write down 5 questions,
they get mixed, and one pops up randomly.
- And you ask that question.
- There are apps for everything.
Shake it like this.
Her wrist snaps!
Her wrists are very...
First kiss.
When was your first kiss?
You asked a strong question.
I'm very curious about this one.
He should say, "Right now."
Like what Soo-geun said.
Ask me when my first kiss was.
- When was your first kiss?
- Right now.
Isn't that really romantic?
You think it's romantic?
I like that. You can end it well.
I didn't have it until I was in my twenties.
For real.
Twenties?
He should've said he hasn't had it yet.
He doesn't get the game.
Then when in your twenties?
When I was 20...
I don't want to go into details.
When was your first kiss?
My dad will throw a fit.
He already has many times.
What if she says middle school?
No. Probably when she turned 20...
I can't really remember...
- Can I change the question?
- Okay.
When was your last kiss?
Yeah, the last kiss is more important than the first kiss.
We're curious too.
This is fun. Ask about the details.
The world shouldn't know.
Soo-bin has never introduced you to someone she likes?
She didn't have a boyfriend before she turned 20.
But she said that she did.
And she said she couldn't drink soju but she did this.
I think she's evolved a lot recently.
- Evolved?
- She's evolved through the show.
Let's see the clip.
I got a question you wrote.
Are you interested in me?
That was a very direct question.
I wanted to ask you that.
I am interested in you.
You are?
Like how?
Yes, he wants her to be more specific.
- "As a guy."
- I've never said this before.
What is it?
That I'm interested in someone.
Why are we swallowing too?
I'm not interested in you as just friends.
It's more...
His lips are drying up.
It means I think of you as a man.
To be honest, I kept thinking about you even when I was in Da Nang.
Really?
You're the first girl that I kept calling and texting like that.
Taking time to work on self growth is very important to me.
But even when I'm working out I keep looking at my phone.
Really?
- That's touching.
- I want to check if you've texted or not.
He's saying all the things Soo-bin will like.
It means he really likes her.
He likes her.
Why would I text and call a girl I'm not interested in?
You're romantic.
Thank you.
I think they're connecting.
This is something I want to ask you.
This is actually my last question for you.
- Really?
- What is it?
Don't say it. I'm scared.
- I'm scared too.
- What is it?
I don't think I can listen to it.
After the show...
I knew he'd say that.
Doesn't it sound like "Be my girlfriend?"
Do you want to meet me a few more times and become my girlfriend?
That was direct!
That was cool.
- He's handsome.
- I like him more the more I look at him.
Do you want to meet me a few more times and become my girlfriend?
You're really pretty.
You're pretty today too.
Ahn Soo-bin, you're the prettiest girl in the world!
First, you're very handsome and nice.
You're too perfect.
This is for real.
It's like a movie.
This is really how the young people date these days.
It looks like Soo-bin has fallen for him.
- Really?
- Yeah.
90% of her fell for him when they jumped off.
What do you think she said?
I think she said...
"What about you?"
Ask the question back?
Let's see what Soo-bin said.
Yeah, I'll meet you more times...
and become your girlfriend if I like you.
This is nice.
She beat around the bush because of the cameras.
After the show ends, I'm going to keep seeing you.
I'm going to keep calling you.
Really?
I want to get to know Ahn Soo-bin more.
I'd fall for him too.
You want to try it too?
So when are we going to see each other next?
- Next?
- Yeah.
- Want to meet tomorrow?
- Tomorrow!
Okay, sounds good.
- This is great!
- This feels good.
Would you give your approval if they continue to date each other?
- Joo-min has a good sense.
- Right?
And he's motivated for his work.
He looks dependable.
I'd like them to have a beautiful relationship.
We're rooting for her.
This is...
- You have to act like you're drunk.
- Is she drunk?
Oh, that's what she looks drunk.
We drank a lot, huh?
Wow!
You're amazing!
- It really looks like you drank.
- It looks very real.
- Who is it?
- This sounds like Woo-ju.
- But Woo-ju doesn't drink.
- She doesn't.
Seok-hee wouldn't say that.
They went on a trip to Jejudo.
Maybe she drank a lot there.
But their first night ended.
They should be coming home on the second day.
Did they go for 3 days?
- Oh yeah.
- Isn't that more of a honeymoon?
Or Woo-ju could've drank because she likes Ki-ho.
Yeah, because of that...
There's no way she'd drink.
My gosh, every time we talk about Woo-ju...
- I hope they show her drinking a lot!
- Let's see Woo-ju's clip.
- It's Woo-ju.
- It's Woo-ju!
- I told you.
- Wait.
- Woo-ju always wear this kind of stuff.
- Yeah.
It's Woo-ju!
They all don't know much about their daughters.
Where is that place?
Hi.
You're here.
They're meeting up.
This is your favorite, iced Americano.
- What's this?
- Macarons.
- How did you know I like macarons?
- Really? I got a lot.
Bringing food on the date means she likes him, right?
I told her to never visit anywhere empty handed.
She's like me. She likes sweet stuff.
We haven't seen each other in days.
I thought about you a lot.
You look prettier today.
No. Stop it.
- You're good with your words.
- It's necessary.
That's not good. That doesn't work in your favor.
Is that so?
- I wanted to work with you.
- Really? What is this?
I want to build chairs today.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
Let's put on aprons first.
- What is all this?
- I prepared everything.
It would be nice for a newlywed to build stuff together for their new home.
And a crib.
That would be very nice.
This is kind of romantic.
- How do I put it on?
- From above.
You're good.
- Got it.
- It looks good on you.
- Really?
- It looks really good on you.
The two look really good together.
We can make two chairs with this?
Yes, it's possible.
Will this be able to withstand our weights?
It's more than enough. Wood is
a lot sturdier than you'd think.
It's sturdy.
You're strong.
It's study.
I'll give you an email. Send me your resume.
It looks like they've gotten a lot closer.
Before we use the machines...
This makes a lot of dust.
So there's a vacuum machine we
turn on first. It eats up the dust.
So we'll turn this on first.
It's a little loud. Don't get scared.
If you look here at the bottom, there is...
What did you say?
- That's how...
- What did you say?
There's a switch down here.
You get to whisper to each other.
It's a machine that brings people close.
That's why they're there.
You have to push it slowly.
- You need to watch out for your hand!
- That's scary!
Isn't it fun?
I want to try cutting it.
I'll help you.
Watch. You have to push it hard
because it bends when it's getting cut.
So you have to place your hand here, not there.
No, you're going to get hurt.
Push from here.
Here? Okay.
Here.
Lightly holding hands like that...
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- That's cool and amazing.
- Seriously.
Is he trying to show off his charm by taking her to his workplace?
Yes, totally.
It will be memorable to gift her with a chair.
- Even more so if you made it yourself.
- Yes.
Woo-ju looks very happy right now.
- I think she's interested in him.
- Right?
We got all the materials ready.
Shall we put them together?
Have you taught anyone like this before?
It's my first time making something for a girl one on one like this.
Good job.
That's the right answer.
- Thank you.
- It doesn't seem like you believe me.
I believe you.
Imagine he said, "Yeah, I made it for a girl I loved before."
"For 6 hours."
"Yes, for 6 hours. And we kissed too."
Then it would be total chaos.
How scary!
Shoot it like this, and it won't move.
I see.
He just said it won't move.
He did.
Why didn't it come out?
It's coming out!
I guess it didn't come out earlier.
It's good now.
Can I try shooting it?
I just shoot it like it's a gun, right?
Yes, shoot it like a gun...
- Hold it tight.
- I'll hold it.
Everyone, be careful with that.
You can get hurt.
That's scary!
It looks like a worm.
It looks like she's putting on sauce.
Stop making me laugh.
You laugh at everything at that phase.
- It wasn't funny, right?
- It wasn't.
That's why comedians are having a hard time right now because people laugh easily.
They laugh at anything.
This is how it becomes a chair.
- Wow.
- It's simple, right?
This is nice.
I get to make something like this thanks to you.
I'll give it to you as a gift.
Okay.
He's a good singer.
- Seok-hee is blushing!
- Her face is red!
Give her a kiss dang it.
Yo-Han, you're an idiot.
- Ki-ho reserved this place.
- What is it?
They must be grabbing drinks here!
I told you there was a place I wanted to visit.
Isn't it nice sitting like that?
This is a very unique place.
It's really unique.
They put on a play, and we can drink.
There's something like that?
You usually can't drink while watching a play.
Yeah, will it be okay?
This is really cool.
I wanted to have a serious conversation over drinks.
But we can do that any time.
I thought we could just have fun tonight.
Is Woo-ju finally going to drink?
Thank you.
- The glasses are really cute.
- Yeah.
Should we make it?
Champagnes are okay, but stronger ones--
That's 25% abv.
It will be hard to drink it in one shot.
- It's that thing!
- I'm good at making those.
I mean...
It's good but you get very drunk.
- Shall we do cheers?
- Okay.
Thank you.
My goodness, look at her go.
It's good.
That's how you end up.
It means that he's tried it a lot before.
How could he drink like that when he hasn't tried it before?
I think she's drinking because she feels comfortable, not because she likes him.
Isn't that a good thing?
I don't think she's totally comfortable.
The fact that she drank means...
She likes him.
And she doesn't look like she has thorns in her heart at all.
You're like a poet.
How was furniture making?
Was it okay?
It was fun.
Next time, let's make a jewelry box or a small drawer like you mentioned.
You can make patterns too.
- I guess they're starting.
- Welcome everyone!
Is it anyone's special day today?
Okay.
I...
I went on a blind date for the first time in my life.
His words are very...
Every day with Woo-ju is special for Ki-ho.
- It's a play!
- They're really putting on a play?
I almost died.
What's wrong?
Bbi-bbi, are you okay?
Yeah.
She's really into it.
Have you guys kissed?
Be quiet!
A letter? It's been returned.
Hold on.
I thought there was another one.
It's here somewhere...
What the heck?
Take it. I think it's a love letter.
Someone wrote a love letter?
As an event?
For real?
They hold events for them too?
Ki-ho wrote it?
Did you guys enjoy the show?
Yes! It was very fun!
That was fun.
- Hello.
- Did you guys enjoy the show?
- Yes, it was very good.
- You guys got the love letter.
- Yes.
I gave it to her earlier.
Oh, it really must be from him.
- Ki-ho really wrote it.
- It's a special event for her.
That's cute.
It's better than writing something out cringy.
I hope you guys meet 200 times more.
We decided to come back next month.
Really?
We look forward to it!
You should sing. You have a really nice voice.
- He's a good singer.
- He is?
I'll sing just a little bit.
- He's a really good singer.
- He sings like a musical actor.
You're really good.
How cute.
The two are so cute.
So I saw you for the first time a couple of days ago.
To be honest, you looked a little cold.
A little cold.
I expressed my feelings here and there.
I was really scared that it would come back as a rejection.
I'm not cold.
I feel that now.
I've had that misunderstanding so many times before.
You can't really do anything,
because everyone has an image.
I was very worried at first.
But I think I'm less worried after today.
I was really nervous today too.
We did a lot during the time we spent together.
- This was the first time in my life.
- Yeah, the folk village...
and wearing hanbok for the first time.
Doing things like that
together made you become
special to me although it
hasn't been that long.
We drank a lot, right?
I'm not saying this because I drank a lot.
You're not saying that because you're drunk, right?
It's not like that.
I jokingly said this after the play.
That we'd come back in a month.
Yeah.
I'm a man from Gyeongsangdo.
So it's hard for me to express myself.
Ki-ho looks so pure.
It only looks cool in movies.
But telling your honest feelings drunk isn't that good.
I think the opposite.
You can't meet the person in the eyes if you like them a lot or talk.
So I think he used alcohol to say his honest feelings.
But the other person can think,
"He's so drunk."
Then it's worse than saying it sober.
Do you like guys telling you that they like you when they're sober?
That's the best.
It sounds most sincere when they're sober.
If he said it drunk, then he needs to reaffirm it the next day.
- Reaffirm it?
- Yes.
Think about it. You shouldn't say it like that after drinking.
You should act like you're really drunk.
We're seeing Soo-geun's acting for the first time on this show!
It's the best.
You have to say it before you pass out.
That's how you should say it.
Like it's just slipping out of your mouth.
So it lingers?
I didn't have the courage to say it.
But I really like you.
It looks a little sad.
What do you think about Soo-geun's method?
You feel bad for him so it's a little cute.
It works.
The best thing is getting drunk together.
To be honest, the drinks are helping.
So I think I can say it.
I like you.
What a man.
I'm so happy this season because the daughters aren't getting hurt.
And the guys don't drag things out.
I like you.
I want us to come back here together in a month.
What do you think?
There was nothing to dislike about him so far.
Right, there isn't.
During the play, he said they'd come back next month.
I want to watch the next clip.
Please play it right now!
We'll find out more on the special episode.
Let's take a look at the next text.
Seok-hee and Yo-Han are the only ones left.
Right.
Seok-hee said something like that?
Yo-Han must've messed up big time.
Her texts aren't usually this long.
Make the sunset...
Isn't that Choi Min-soo?
- It was close.
- That was Choi Min-soo.
Make the sunset fall asleep and build
a bridge with the golden spirit...
Since Seok-hee has a husky voice.
Maybe Seok-hee is a good writer like her parents?
- They must be lyrics.
- Yeah!
- From his song.
- The song!
Lyrics from that song!
Maybe she writes some at the end!
It felt like Shin Sung-woo's "Seoshi."
I tried to leave before the sun fell.
You guys ruined the mood!
Let's take a look! Maybe it's a song in return.
Please turn the volume up!
Is it okay...
Come on...
- I told you not to laugh.
- I didn't!
- Don't laugh.
- It's just my face.
I want you to listen to it carefully, okay?
Is it okay...
Even though I'm like this...
Even though my love is like this...
Can I still approach you?
You know...
That my heart...
Is growing more and more...
Do you feel it too?
The times that I longed to spend with you...
As they pass, I like you more and more...
Can you see...
My love?
I didn't know it would grow this big...
Yes, I...
You're the one...
I love...
Seok-hee is blushing!
I think she's going to cry!
- Let's release this single!
- That was awesome.
We just need to fix it a tiny bit.
Seo-beom is really happy right now too.
Yeah, he teared up.
Everyone here is happy.
Yo-Han makes people happy.
I'm not expecting much.
Just tell me how you felt.
The overall feeling?
If I look at the overall picture,
- it's good.
- It's good?
- Really?
- Yeah.
She's beaming with happiness.
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
It was good.
Why aren't you looking?
You have a short thumb.
I have a short thumb.
That was surprising.
I'm glad you thought it was good.
I'll let you listen to it once I finish it.
What do you think?
We might not know much about music.
He expressed his feelings
for the first time
through his lyrics and ended
it with "I love you."
Why do I feel like he said that to me?
He doesn't sound like an amateur.
I've never seen Seok-hee make that expression before.
Seriously.
She turned red and didn't know what to do with herself.
I don't know much about music
but I could tell how much Yo-Han cares for Seok-hee.
Everything looks good.
Should we get hairtail?
Let's get one of these two.
Grilled or stew?
- Stew.
- Stew?
Are you hungry or not?
Of course I'm hungry!
She's always hungry.
That shouldn't be a question.
A small should be enough for two, right?
He just messed up.
Medium?
Medium.
Excuse me, could we get medium sized seafood hairtail stew?
- Jejudo is all about...
- You have to get it.
- You have to get hairtail.
- I'm hungry.
Yo-Han is sensitive.
It's an open view.
The ocean is really pretty.
- She didn't yawn, right?
- She did.
- She yawned.
- She did?
That's a lot.
What is that?
It's moving.
Everything in that rectangle is food?
- It has everything.
- It looks really good.
I only saw stuff like that on social media.
Even if I want that for dinner,
I'd have to go to Jejudo.
It's screaming, "I'm Jejudo!"
We should cut it.
It's splashing.
- My hand is going to cramp.
- Already?
Why does he always get cramps?
Yo-Han always cramps up after doing little things.
When he was singing, I was worried he
would cramp up from playing the piano.
The vibe was going well.
This requires utmost focus.
You get the most cramps out of all the people I know.
That looks really good!
Should we eat it?
That looks so good.
It's the best!
I just imagined what the sauce would taste like.
- With the ocean view...
- It's so good.
Did Yo-Han just pick up a spoon?
Isn't that his first time?
I've never seen him use a spoon before.
It must be that good.
- Don't drop it.
- I won't.
That looks good.
How come I can't get it like that?
It's better to eat it like this.
- It's really good.
- It must be super good.
It must be amazing. Seok-hee is eating with both of her hands.
- It can't not be good.
- For real. It's so good.
It's really good.
Cart racing?
I want to go visit Jejudo.
It's huge.
This is it.
I've never been on one before.
Yo-Han tried everything for the first time with Seok-hee.
- It will be the most memorable.
- Yeah.
The lady can sit there.
And you can sit here.
- 31?
- Yes.
Good.
Look at how Yo-Han folds his legs because they're so long.
Wow, Seok-hee...
What if Yo-Han cramps up again?
It's already going fast!
My goodness...
It's because he doesn't have a license.
He doesn't have a sense of driving.
He said it's already going fast.
Seok-hee looks relaxed.
Seok-hee is even drifting.
Seok-hee is the best driver.
All helmets look like they were made for Seok-hee.
He's going slow because he's scared.
- He has a lot of fears.
- Yes, he does.
I don't think this is it.
What happened to Yo-Han?
Did he step on the wrong pedal?
Please help me!
This is...
Yo-Han needs a lot of help.
Yo-Han shouldn't be taking care of Seok-hee.
Seok-hee is really good!
How are you so good?
Stop.
- You guys are going to race.
- Really?
Will he even be a match for her?
- Let's just bet on drinks.
- Okay.
It's like a rabbit racing with a turtle.
I don't think he'll be a match.
Yo-Han may show his true self.
I'm more interested in when he'll cramp up.
Seok-hee is going easy on him.
- Shouldn't it be reversed?
- Yeah.
That's even sadder.
She gave him handicap.
Why are you so fast?
She's lying.
You're going too fast!
Yo-Han slow down!
How cute.
What the...
Yo-Han, you--
I can't let you win even if I want to.
- The staff is there again.
- He needs a lot of help.
He turned the handle too much because he was scared.
I've given up.
I don't think driving suits me.
- He's just too scared, right?
- Yes.
He's not experienced in driving.
I made Seok-hee get class 1 license.
- She knows how to drive a stick.
- She's good.
And I was the one who taught her,
so she's very good.
It's raining again.
- It's because it's raining in my heart.
- Why is it raining in your heart?
It keeps on raining.
They look like they're golfing.
- Oh that thing!
- Don't you go inside it?
It floats on water too.
It's very bouncy.
Oh you face each other!
- It's the longest course in Asia.
- Let's play a game.
Choose one that you can do.
This thing spins.
We'll pick an artist and take turns singing their songs.
Who's going to pick the artist?
You pick.
Hong Seo-beom.
That's harsh. I only know 2 songs.
Why is it harsh? My dad is watching.
You're harsh.
I only know 2 songs.
Which two?
"Rip Kim" and "It's a Fireball."
Which one are you going to sing first?
Isn't it like that?
You've go to sing it at least past 3 seconds.
I only listened to the highlight because I like it so much.
Your turn.
Her dad is loving it!
Look at how happy he is.
How cute.
I told you I don't know them.
Why don't you know my dad's songs?
He sings really well.
I know he does but...
- She's showing off about her dad.
- There's "The Prayer Of The Poor Lovers."
I've heard of it.
It was the number one song for over 10 weeks.
I'm not 100% sure since my dad is the one who told me.
He tells you those kind of things?
It was called the "Streetboard Chart."
- Out on the streets.
- Yes.
It was the number one song for 16 weeks.
That's amazing.
How does it go?
Sing it for me.
- Make the sunset fall asleep...
- That was it.
- That's what it was.
- I think I know it.
And build a bridge with the golden spirit...
You're good.
Can you sing the original since it's our last episode?
- Yeah!
- On the piano.
Yo-Han, are you seeing this?
Let's listen to it.
That was awesome.
That was really awesome.
So awesome.
I think you singing it now sounds even
more awesome than it did back then.
Which artist should we pick?
Should we pick IU since you like her?
Okay.
I'm good with IU's songs too.
What are we betting on?
- We're in Jejudo, right?
- Yes.
What is it filled with?
There are a lot of mountains here.
You said the ocean was pretty.
I'll give you a chance to go in there.
Why do you think I'm going to go in?
Won't it be too cold for you?
The loser has to go in?
He said, "You're going to catch a cold."
When he's the one who's going in.
Go inside.
He's entering it weirdly too.
- He could just crawl in.
- It's very comfortable.
Hold on...
They're going in it together?
They face each other and roll.
One, two, three!
You can't lift me!
I'll do it.
I'm stuck because of your foot!
- You stepped on me!
- Seok-hee is stepping on Yo-han's foot!
He sounded like he got ran over by a car.
Look at Yo-Han.
This is so funny.
It's like a sitcom.
I'll go first.
Should I start?
No, we need to go down.
Is this going to be open?
How long does it take to get down?
Less than 5 minutes.
That's a really long course!
They're going!
It's already making me dizzy!
What? I couldn't hear you!
This doesn't stop.
My feet are slipping out!
She looks like a piece of paper.
Her feet slipped out.
They must have healthy cochlea because they're young.
I'd throw up.
They still sang during it.
It smells like grass.
This is scary.
This is thrilling. It's fun.
Hold on, I think I'm stuck.
Where did she get stuck?
Of course.
Seok-hee and Yo-Han always make us laugh with their moves.
Hold on. You get up first.
You're squishing me.
You get up first.
He's squished.
Why is this so funny?
What is that? "The Ring?"
He's the ghost.
You're always hurt after everything.
- I won.
- Can you take this off?
Everything Seok-hee does requires a helmet.
She looks like Jeon In-Kwon.
It was fun.
- Who do you think won?
- I did.
I won! Replay the clip!
Replay the clip.
Let's just both go in.
Should we?
Seok-hee is charismatic and proactive.
I said I'd go in there with you
although you're the one who lost.
I didn't lose.
- Let's say I lost. I'll go in.
- Okay.
Then I'll just watch.
Yo-Han fell for it.
- You're really smart.
- I know, right?
I hear that a lot.
Let's go in together.
Why are you whining?
He's going into the ocean?
Is he really going to go in?
Soo-geun, you're an expert on going into the ocean.
What do you think about Yo-Han going into the ocean?
It's easy to go in, but Yo-Han doesn't have fat on his body.
It will get absorbed straight to his bones.
So he'll feel the cold fast.
And the chilly wind.
It's an issue when they come out of the water.
And he might cramp up if it's too cold.
- Is he really going in?
- No way.
You can't go in at a place like that.
- The winter wind...
- Of course not.
The wind is cold but...
He should've dressed more warmly.
Seok-hee, give me your hand.
Hold it right.
She doesn't cover her hand with her sleeves anymore.
You're right. She's not covering it anymore.
They're cute.
They look like they're on their honeymoon.
I want them to be together for a long time.
Let's sit here for a while.
Two days have gone by already.
Time flies by so fast.
- They were there for 2 days?
- Yes.
Oh yeah, they slept over.
How was it?
I'm tired but...
it was fun.
You said it's your first time here.
How was it?
I really didn't know it would be like this.
Like what?
Since it's part of our country,
I thought it would be nothing special.
Now I get why people come here.
- What's wrong?
- Where is she going?
What is it?
Seok-hee did?
- A gift.
- Really?
- Is it a blanket?
- No.
- It's a gift.
- What?
Seok-hee got Yo-Han a gift?
- Really?
- What is it?
I guess it's a gift.
- Is it a dolphin?
- Yeah.
It was at the dolphin place.
- Dalkong and....
- Nakwon?
Yes, Nakwon.
(They experienced dolphin training session the day before)
(She got the stuffed animal from there for Yo-Han)
When did you get it? You had the time to do it?
Yesterday. I changed earlier than you.
So that's when you got it.
Thank you.
- I think it was a surprise gift.
- Yeah.
I'm touched.
- Isn't it cute?
- I love this...
Yeah, it's cute.
Why is my heart beating fast?
It's so good how it turned out.
I really like them together.
Why did you make the clip look like it's the last?
That's when they did the temple stay.
What? She's hugging him?
Oh, a hug?
How cute!
Yo-Han looks so happy.
Seok-hee looks happy.
Let's go.
- He must be feeling mixed emotions.
- He's about to cry.
- This will make you cry.
- Seok-hee is all grown up.
- I'm crying too.
- Me too.
- What's going on?
- I'm about to cry because he's crying.
I like that they're tears of joy.
- Seok-hee is all grown up.
- Yes.
- I'm crying.
- We didn't expect this.
I know Seok-hee is his daughter,
but we also saw her grow up.
What are you feeling?
I'm happy.
We're very happy too.
It was a precious clip that warmed up our hearts.
You saying "I'm happy" makes us even happier.
Why don't you send a video message to
Seok-hee and Yo-Han for the first time?
For the first time ever!
Then just send one to Yo-Han.
Thank you Yo-Han for treating Seok-hee well
and for accepting her even when she's rude.
Your song was good.
He's so lovely.
Thank you, and I hope you guys continue
your relationship loving each other.
Thank you.
Shall we wrap it up--
What is that?
- What is that?
- "Thought it was over?"
They went for 3 days?
He got angry right away.
Hold on! You should've told us!
He must be keeping his promise to go into the ocean!
Let's go in together.
Just take off your clothes.
Oh my goodness!
It's too cold.
He really went in?
Touch it with your hand.
Oh no!
It sounds like seagulls are flying by.
- She sounds like a dolphin.
- What are you going to do?
I didn't know it would go all the way up here.
How is he going to go in?
I'm really going to do it.
Just run to it!
He fell down!
He tried to be cool but he fell down!
- Yo-Han! Another one is coming!
- No!
Until the very end!
That was the best sitcom.
This is really a sitcom.
This is so funny.
Swim a little bit since you went in already.
Thank you guys!
That was so nice.
Anyway, it feels like we watched a drama of their growth.
Yes.
I wish the best for you guys.
We're rooting for you.
We're rooting for you!
- You guys are so cute.
- Be happy!
I hope they continue to cherish each other always.
We prepared special gifts for the dads.
A surprise gift.
We gathered the daughters' honest thoughts
and put them in a video message.
- Let's take a look.
- Let's look at it together.
I'm very thankful that you went on your
first entertainment show for your daughter.
I feel Ike we made a lot of memories by being on this show together.
And how chill you were when it came to my dating life...
Saying "It doesn't matter"
or "I can't help it" made
me feel like you trust me
so it made me very happy.
Don't look for mom all the time,
and look for me too.
Lastly, you know you're my ideal type forever, right/
I love you dad!
How cute.
You said I only look for your mom.
But you guys are going to live longer than your mom.
Don't worry about that. I love your
mom, your sister and you all the same.
I'm very happy because this was a good experience.
When I saw you crying when I was in Mokpo,
I cried a lot on my own too.
You drank a lot and came home and said
that you were really sorry
for making me stay home
and not letting me build
memories when I was little.
When you said that and hugged me...
To be honest, it was hard for me to understand
you and I didn't like you before that.
But that moment made up for everything.
I think that we've gotten closer through this.
And I'll be more bright and cute towards you
like how I am on dates.
I learned that I should approach you more.
Dad, I love you.
I love you.
That was nice.
- The daughters are all...
- They're all thinking of their dads.
I'm sure all parents love their children the same way.
I'm not an exception.
That's why I made a lot
of suggestions so that
I can keep you safe and
well while growing up.
I'm very thankful that you realize I did it because I love you.
Soo-bin, thank you for being born.
Through filming for the past few months,
I think I've been gifted with new experiences and memories.
It was hard because I'm very shy.
But I think I've matured through the show.
I'll try to be a nicer and better daughter this new year.
And I'll do my best to make you happy.
Thank you for raising me.
I love you.
What I'd like from you is...
Life is a very hard thing.
Of course it won't be hard if you could do whatever you want.
But being respected and revered by others isn't easy.
I hope you'll always try your best and study hard.
Hi dad.
Hi.
I know I gained a lot through this show,
but I'm sure you know
about the stress that
I've gained as well even
if I don't tell you.
I'll try my best to not make you worry
so please wait and see.
Thank you so much for always supporting
me and believing in me.
Dad, I love you.
Seok-hee, I know it was hard for you to tell me that you love me
but I love you more than you could express it.
And congratulations on meeting a nice boyfriend through the show.
But I'd like you to ease up on eating a bit.
Please continue to be healthy like right now.
I love you.
We laughed and cried a lot on this season
thanks to the 4 dads and their daughters.
We were very happy.
We say this is the end,
but it's not over until it's really over.
That's all of our hope.
This is the end for us, but the
daughters will be on next week.
The behind the scenes stories from the daughters
and best scenes will all be shown.
Don't miss out!
Don't forget to tune in next week!
This is it for My Daughters' Men Season 4!
Good bye!
Thank you!
We're here with the 4 daughters
from My Daughters' Men Season 4.
I asked them to set me up too.
I called too.
I said I should've been on this season instead.
You really did.
There's a back story.
I hate that.
Wow.
It's really not.
I really liked it because...
Girls are supposed to...